<name>Capital H Group, LLC Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Capital-H-Group-LLC-Reviews-E101506.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2009-09-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Going through tough times but great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – This is a firm with great people, flexibility, opportunities to take on new challenges. I've learned a lot here and have gotten to work with amazing clients.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The economy has been hard on the firm, leading to instability.  Can be a little cliquey.  It is not very diverse.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It will take strong leadership to pull through difficult times.  Please do your best to communicate a vision and plan to get through this together.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Managing Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Innovative beginner for a great consulting alternative”

</title><pros>Pros – Good organization vision; great initial CEO; wonderful holy talented people</pros>
<cons>Cons – COO was untrustworthy; did not practice thoroughly what was preached and thus did not follow through on measuring and managing consistently against vision and strategies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Consistency; trust; integrity</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-09-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Recruiting Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Capital H Group - Nice team but lacks direction”

</title><pros>Pros – collaborative team environmentfair compensationbenefits are above average compared to competitorsnice office spacenice little perks like really good coffee provided</pros>
<cons>Cons – lack of businessvery little brand recognitionlack of directiontoo much duplication of effortslack of support staffmajor changes not communicated timely</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – clarify service offeringsenhance brand visibility with the industryprovide more support for recruiting consultants so they are able to spend time recruiting</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-05-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good place to grow if you know what you want.”

</title><pros>Pros – Capital H Group is full of smart, dedicated people doing work that they care about. They practice what they preach in terms of work-life balance and organizational development. Considerable time and resources go into employees' education and training. It's not always perfect, but it's front of mind, and they try to get it right. The principals and managers have a lot interesting experience and background for younger consultants to learn from.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Many projects are tactical rather than strategic in nature. The point of looking at organizations with a human capital lens is that your people ARE your strategy. Getting clients to understand this often isn't easy, and HR is viewed as a back-office, non-strategic function. As a result, a lot of the work that Capital H Group gets feels like an afterthought.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the fire in the belly for human capital work. Pare away anything that doesn't have that fire.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – Team based environmentGreat work life balanceOpportunities for professional growthManagers care for their employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – Smaller company in the process of growing</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increase the communication between all offices and layers of employees within the organization</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Missing Link”

</title><pros>Pros – Talented EmployeesCompelling Message to Clients - Big Firm Experience with Small Firm FeesAbility to grow at your own pace and develop new lines of businessCEO vision</pros>
<cons>Cons – The "Small Firm Fees" became the same as Big FirmsConfusion as to "who should we be"Lack of direct feedback to those not living the valuesFinance lack of understanding of professional service fee structures</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A decent place to work in consulting”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart people with strong consulting backgrounds</pros>
<cons>Cons – Highly politicalMuch in-fightingProjects doled out based on whether principals like you</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Deal with challenging issues head on</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to watch a business crash”

</title><pros>Pros – Employment, though talent is largely underutilizedBase compensation is at marketBenefits are comparable with other companies of the same size</pros>
<cons>Cons – Incompetent managementSales not aligned with strategy, which is ironic for a management consulting firmExtremely poor handling of acquisitionsIT and security are laughable</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get a new management team to replace the incompetence that pervades the current team. Hire an IT director who is competent and a COO knows how to run operations</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>