<name>Z Corp Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Z-Corp-Reviews-E11112.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-01-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Regional Sales (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Z Corp is a privately held company with a lot of great people.”

</title><pros>Pros – The only 3D color rapid prototyping printer on the market.ProductPeopleManagementPay</pros>
<cons>Cons – VP of SalesNo new materialsNot a bright outlook</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Sell the company why you can.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“As a private company...”

</title><pros>Pros – There were some very talented people where one could learn a lot from.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unrealistic product management objectives and senior management could not make key decisions early in a product development cycle for "go" and especially "no-go". Could not retain talented employees that made a difference in a robust product. Human resource as a department was inadequate.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you were there early enough you really had a chance to help shape the company.”

</title><pros>Pros – If you have good stuff to say they listen, though they may not act simply because its too hard.  Its the coolest product around, unless you're into robots.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The operations team does not like change.  Its had several opportunities to take feedback and do great things over the last 2 years but has not.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great products, good environment, teamwork</pros>
<cons>Cons – Tough market, limited investment, conservative</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>