<name>J Craig Venter Institute Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/J-Craig-Venter-Institute-Reviews-E111330.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-02-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good but could have been better”

</title><pros>Pros – Lot of Interaction with good minds, extremely helpful colleagues, good boss (in my case)</pros>
<cons>Cons – lot of dependency on government funded grants, frequent layoffs</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – you need to provide some stability and assurance to employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Lab Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Relaxed work place, good internship experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Very relaxed work place, and the people in each department bond pretty well. Diverse group of people too. There were lot's of informative talks and a handful of fun events. Modern atmosphere. Casual dress-code.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Seems a bit slow-paced and boring. Never really interacted with people outside my department. There doesn't seem to be any upper management. Lot's of layoffs going around, which brought upon a depressing atmosphere.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to gain research experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great research environment, and, when I was there most of the people were friendly and helpful.  If you work on a project that's funded or is a a pet project of the CEO, then there are a lot of opportunities to be exposed to cutting edge science and research.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is almost no mentoring support.  If you are not lucky enough to have a supervisor/manager that's knowledgeable, capable, and interested in your development, you'll be miserable and you will be treated as though you're an anonymous worker on an assembly line.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Can do a better jobs with mentoring and rewarding good managers.   Also, it would be great if the institute were run like real research lab or academic institution instead of a corporate center or manufacturing floor.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Bioinformatics Analyst II (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work here when you are close to retirement and are NOT looking for career growth”

</title><pros>Pros – Environment is too relaxed, but that is because of the complacent attitude of people here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No growth, bad pays, terrible complacency. It feels dead working here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If NOT wasting tax-payer dollars means consolidating this branch with the one in California, please do so. This place is a joke already.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sinking Ship”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people who care about each other. Good work/life balance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company is struggling and soon will be moving to California. They are not telling Rockville employees that the entire operation is moving and will all be laid off at the last moment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Their is no management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This organization is a case study in how not to run an organization.”

</title><pros>Pros – If you have an interesting idea within research or need a job where you can learn and leave, its a good place to go.  Good step to somewhere sane.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management and leadership is incompetent and noncommunicative.  There is no trust within the organization and no communication.  Senior leadership does not listen nor care what others within the organization think or how the job gets done.  There is alot of favoritism to those that work on projects that favor the for profit company that the leadership participates in.  This organization is just a shell for the for profit research company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would ve bery surprised if this organization exists in 10 years.  Listen to employees, consider planning, think innovatively, seek suggestions of others in non-profit environment and tell the emperor that he is standing there naked.  He might actually appreciate knowing that rather than having everyone just follow along.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very relaxed working environment. Low presure”

</title><pros>Pros – Low presure, good benefit, treat emloyee very well</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company reorganization, change, layoff. Overhead is too high</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to cut more overhead</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work a couple years ago, but now everyone is leaving due to downsizing.”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly employees and a beautiful campus</pros>
<cons>Cons – HR is pathetic - they don't listen to employees.  One sided, hard nosed and not professional.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Bioinformatics Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible Place to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – Very Few - People come in to work because they "have" a job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Absolutely no growth - people are fleeing the organisation - speaks for itself.Never had a performance appraisal done for years - my manager just never did one.In this place, "personal"relationships work best for growth - one of the most unprofessional places to work at. Skills and knowledge have very little place - sucks.I regret not having left sooner, after seeing how different and better almost any other place is to work at.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No point to it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good stepping stone”

</title><pros>Pros – -good hours-flexible schedule-good work life balance and excellent benefits-intellectually stimulating environment where good ideas are developed and shared</pros>
<cons>Cons – --Pay is low compared to other places-recent layoffs have made the environment feel unstable and forced some to abandon the ship</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – --Start talking straight  with your employees- stop the ambiguity.  Realize what is valuable- to the employees and to the company itself.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate IV (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Once was a great company but that time has passed.”

</title><pros>Pros – It tends to be a very relaxed environment at the lower levels in the company. The faculty members are typically very good at protecting their employees from the bureaucratic nonsense that occurs in the upper management. Benefits were very good with reasonable personal costs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Human Resources has very little knowledge of what goes on in a science organization and how scientists tend to work. Employee morale has tanked in recent years with institute takeover and reorganization. A lack of institute-wide direction is also very obvious.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There is a very obvious, but denied, sense of favoritism throughout the company by the senior management. While that will never go away from this company, it borders on how blatant and ridiculous it is.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Summer Lab Research Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great working environment”

</title><pros>Pros – The relaxed atmosphere is what makes it fun to work in the labs here. We were expected to get our work and assignments done on time and with a very high quality standard, but how we did it was left up to the employees at some level. I worked on a genome sequencing assembly line, but there was a lot of troubleshooting a maintenance that made the work interesting from day to day. The fact that we are working on such new and cutting edge projects also made the work more interesting.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I was working a 6am to 4pm schedule which was not fun for me.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would say that the senior management is doing a great job, much better than other employers that i have been with.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A July without lay-offs?”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of good people.  Well, except most have left/been let go now.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No communication.  No future plan.  No leadership.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No point, it's too late now.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Positives outweighed by recent layoffs”

</title><pros>Pros – -Mostly good people-Flexible hours-Interesting projects</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Inept senior management-Lack of communication-Layoffs-Long term viability of Rockville campus in question with construction of new California facility</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be open and upfront with the employees, show them respect and better communicate where the Institute is headed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good resume builder but only for the short term”

</title><pros>Pros – Laid back atmosphereCasual dressGood place to learn techiquesDecent benefits but declining</pros>
<cons>Cons – Favoritism at its worstSenior Management lacks focus and directionGood old boys/girls clubAdvancement usually occurs by who one knows and not by ones ability or achievement</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There's a true seperation between senior management and the worker bee.  There's incredible lack of trust which generates in poor attitudes and work performance.  Your HR department is completely out of its depth and understanding of your employees.  It all comes down to leadership which this company completely lacks.  It's like the wizard of oz-all show and no substance.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“leadership is horrible”

</title><pros>Pros – benefits schemes are good but not great</pros>
<cons>Cons – very complacent org, very weak leadership</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Company, Poorly Managed”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits; better than the most in this area.Flexible, Laid back work environment, Nice coworkers</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unfair recognition , no bonus, stagnant careersWorst crisis Management by company managementone man  show</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please think through before take an action.   Make an effort to find out what's going at the ground level.  Don't just listen blindly to the managers but also listen to employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-10-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lack of communication really hurts this company”

</title><pros>Pros – The atmosphere in the company is friendly and the environment is incredibly laid back. Supplied benefits and perks are a definite plus. There is also a definite sense of camaraderie among the employees left.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There seems to be a serious lack of communication between the higher ups and the rest of the company. More than once I've seen the perils of this problem, yet they haven't done anything (noticeable) to improve it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would recommend learning what is going on in lower levels of the company. Give everyone an equal opportunity- not just your favorites.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>