<name>The Gladstone Institutes Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/The-Gladstone-Institutes-Reviews-E111503.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>IT Administrator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work , cutting edge scientific research”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible working hours, good benefits, good pay, great work/life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow to implement changes and adopt best practices</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Ensure employees provide input into job description and tasks</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Fellow (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good for short term stay”

</title><pros>Pros – good pay, good facilities, nice campus</pros>
<cons>Cons – Politics are a big factor.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great mission and friendly people”

</title><pros>Pros – Great scientific research, friendly people, lots of diversity, easy transportation with even a shuttle to BART, smart scientists, social.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay isn't great for the lower people but the executives and directors are highly paid. Rewards, career development and promotions don't really happen. Some managers take care of the people who complain or don't perform more than the people who are working hard.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on the infrastructure of the organization including HR services. Value the administration as much as you value the science not just in words, but with career development, raises, promotions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate I (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great science opportunities”

</title><pros>Pros – There are multiple avenues to learn at the Gladstone Institutes -- research-in-progress seminars, weekly seminars, lectures, distinguished lectures, lab meetings, etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – PIs, senior investigators, etc. can improve their management skills. They should motivate employees with positive reinforcement rather than by intimidation. This obviously varies from manager to manager.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It is important to update employees on their performance regularly, always emphasizing positive things. Please do not only meet with employees to discuss improvement--this is a motivation-killer and a poor way to manage employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Fellow (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Great vision, culture and people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing to say about it</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Fellow (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent Postdoctoral Training”

</title><pros>Pros – The level of science is truly exceptional. The environment is very collaborative. Open floor plan for each institute which makes it easy to get to know everyone working there, and to collaborate with anyone that can help you.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The institute takes themselves a bit too serious. They believe that everyone works there is excellent, and that they are the best place to work ever. At the end of the day it really depends on your PI and the lab that one works in how your work experience is going to be. Like everywhere, there are good labs and bad labs.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Great Place to Work”

</title><pros>Pros – Academic research environment with institution-wide support and insulation from university system issues. Meaningful research focus. Impressive and caring leadership. Amazing people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is lower than industry, as you might expect, but better than universities. Can't think of anything else really.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Fellow (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pretty much your average overworked postdoc scenario for slightly more money than NIH”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits, location, institutional support, resources.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work-life balance, salary, company culture, opportunity for advancement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate III (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You're nothing if you're neither a post-doc or a graduate student (of course PIs are excluded...)”

</title><pros>Pros – great place for a fresh graduate to gain some lab experience</pros>
<cons>Cons – no career advancement; no career development support; benefits are limited; not to mention pay is pathetic!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – treat your employees like they are valuable; don't just say it, do it like you mean it!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of smart people here, important work being done</pros>
<cons>Cons – few career advancement options for staff who are not academic employees. not clear what the next step is for staff since only postdocs and graduate students have a clear career path</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Personable staff and overall mission driven organization”

</title><pros>Pros – Good working relationships with other departments</pros>
<cons>Cons – Short sighted middle management was common</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More transparency less secrecy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A place to be proud of!”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting work and great people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Administration not valued commensurately with scientists</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>