<name>Danieli Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Danieli-Reviews-E11232.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-02-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – List of Holidays in fiscal year.List of projects handled.Good work atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – For some projects the colleagues doesn't co-ordinate properly.Then again its a part of work life.Less woman employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-02</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“"you are just a BADGE NUMBER and a COST CENTER" nothing else. ARBEIT MACH FREI. WORK WORK WORK. a LAGER!”

</title><pros>Pros – A) you will never get bored and you will challanges with big projects and latest technologyB)  you can travel the world and visit a lot of new placesC) your career and position will not be defined the 1st day and then fixed forever (german style), if you are and EXCELLENCE, you will find all the doors opened for a shiny career (that could be METEORIC)</pros>
<cons>Cons – A) this means that you will be continuously under tremendous pressure, and you will have to bring your blackberry also on WC, under shower and in bed with you.B) travel the world in their site, doesn't means to go in tropical resorts... you will travel always on weekends, in economy class also for intercontinental flights, and of course NO TRAVEL ALLOWANCEC) high rates of BACKBONE LESS YESMAN in strategic managment positions BACKBONE LESS YESSSSS MAN, with reaaly high and huge salary, while your salary will be REALLY LOW, and you will need to work at least 10/11 hours per day and half day on saturday- in this company doesn't exist a PRIVATE life: they dont hire you, THEY OWN YOU.- all the communications will be filtered and read by backboneless yesssssmen that report directly to HR dept, also your private life will be under control</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – dear mr. GPB:stop to hire and trust on dozens of yesmen, that never never never report to you the truth.they only want to be good in your eyes, and save their asses.remember that what made great your company, was not the yes men, but was YOU and the thousand of "furlans cjadrears" habit to "work work work" till die.redistribute the salaries on low levels and cut all the sh*t level 1, 0 and 00.people will stop to escape with the HDD full of drawings and engineering.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Automation Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good worldwide experience”

</title><pros>Pros – job is dynamic,travel around world- you can see places what will never visit (non touristic),latest technology,experience builder- you can learn a lot, and use it for your personal qualities</pros>
<cons>Cons – always fight for better salary, big dead line pressure, working time 10-12 hours is like "normal", people burn out.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take care of people, do not use them like things</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Health & Safety Officer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“HSE department - Growing opportunity in Danieli”

</title><pros>Pros – Good salary, opportunity to work abroad, MNC</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of support to the employee, low motivation</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to improve overall HSE standards</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Structural Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place for start the career”

</title><pros>Pros – Large multicurtural international company. Allows to see how international cooperation works. Projects in different places of the world.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Human resources policy does not exist.  High rate of staff turnover. Company values are not determinated. Company culture is not a strong</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More attantion to the people and quality of the weork</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Just better than ok, get lot of support from coemplyees.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good initial package, better on site options</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unstable due to site jobs, family some times missed</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Can be much more structured</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-25</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Job satisfaction, helpful & friendly atmosphere, career growth, seniors are good & very professional. Everybody knows their job & are equally responsible.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Need to spend some more time to know it. To be very fair, there may be cons but we must avoid them as much as possible and do our own job sincerely.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Piping Senior Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Gaining a lot of experience with international Co.”

</title><pros>Pros – Gain Experience, Build a new Career, Have a good relationships</pros>
<cons>Cons – Time consuming, No stability in family life</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up with good and new projects</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Buyer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“brilliant”

</title><pros>Pros – one of the bigggest MNC in the world</pros>
<cons>Cons – miscommunication between employees in the management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good job, but a lot of things I want to change”

</title><pros>Pros – Good grows opportunity in the international multicultural company</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much non-payed overtime work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 1. changing the motivation system can help to improve performance and satisfaction of employees2. More attention to corporate culture and team building processes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Danieli”

</title><pros>Pros – Very big leader firm, doing business all over the world.You can gain a lot of experience in brief time, that you can easily spend in future jobs.It's quite easy to be hired; you do not need to be an excellence.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is not much meritocracy. As a consequence, employees are generally badly motivated because not properly rewarded if they do well their job. Moreover, there is often  a surprisingly disorganization and lack of necessary informations from bosses.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You should apply more meritocracy and reserve much more consideration to the employees.Training of employees should be much more improved.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Danieli & C. - pro and cons of a company from Friuli”

</title><pros>Pros – One of the top construction companies in Italy, first class world player in Steelmaking plant business. Very good organisation.You can see the world and be involved in huge projects</pros>
<cons>Cons – "Furlan" company. very strong reginal link (good if you are from Friuli). career progress possibility only up to a certain level. good large family business, but still a family business in terms of management.strong centralisation of power.Taylorism applied to engineering and construction: it's amazing how good it works for the company, a bit less exiting for employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – a more widespread managerial culture (particularly within the subsidiaries) and more transparency in goals and strategies would be usefull to polarize employees efforts.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>