<name>e-Dialog Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/e-Dialog-Reviews-E11214.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience in email marketing”

</title><pros>Pros – Work with global client-side brands. Fast-paced. Great exposure to challenges brands face. Just about everyone gets their hands dirty.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Will do anything to please clients, at any cost to employees. Demand never goes away. Overworked and overstressed employees creates very high turnover.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The perks are really bad. Terrible. Invest in finding actual cool ways to make your employees feel valued. Bring your dog to work day is less than meaningless.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A mere shadow of the company it used to be”

</title><pros>Pros – The company is full of smart and hardworking people.  Most are willing to go above and beyond to get the job done.  The atmosphere and dress code are casual, and it's okay to work from home if you need to.  Twenty-five cent snacks are also nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This used to be a great place to work.  The clients list was quite impressive.  The employees were fun-loving.   Successes were celebrated, and employees truly felt like they were direct contributors.  Training and development was a major focus, and growth within the company felt like it was always a possibility.  Everyone was always overworked, and we all knew that needed to change, but with such a high morale, it was still a good place to work.  I would have easily given it a 4-5 star rating.That all changed in early 2011, after the company officially became a part of GSI.  Layoffs ensued, the company lost its stride, and the e-Dialog culture disappeared.  The already overworked staff became more overworked, and trust in upper management disappeared as people began to worry about their jobs.Middle management has tried to bring up morale trying to make people feel informed, but with on-going changes in processes, structure and leadership, it's clear that middle management is in the dark and upper management has no idea what to do next.  An environment that was once very team-oriented has now become one where it's every man for himself, with constant tension and finger-pointing.  Clients are leaving, and the employees that aren't getting laid off are leaving on their own, one by one.  It's a sinking ship.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – eBay is known to be a good place to work, so one can only hope that now, as e-Dialog and GSI become more enveloped into eBay, things will turn around quickly.In the meantime, the folks at the top need to do a better job of keeping everyone else truly informed, and make sure that employees feel more valued and less like they could lose their job at any moment.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Campaign Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No No initiative”

</title><pros>Pros – - Friendly co-workers- Casual dress code- Flexible telecommuting availability- Breakfast, snack and soda benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Management turnover every 3-6 months; different talking head presenting company outlook every other meeting- Middle management isn't kept in the loop- Company as a whole lacks initiative- Hiring process is handled out-of-office; managers high up need to get reqs approved despite roles clearly not being filled- Morale on company is low. Layoffs occurring with little-to-no explanation</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Find some direction, find a consistent voice, bring the subcompanies (TrueAction, MBS, Fetchback, etc.) together under one voice only once each company has the staff and knowledge to stand alone. Also, fix your hiring process.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Contract Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“By far the worst place I've worked at.”

</title><pros>Pros – I worked along with some great people who I became good friends with. Though most are highly skilled, it's very common to end up doing something different than what you were hired for.  In the end, you could end up feeling very frustrated as you spin your wheels working on something you could care less about while using very outdated technology  (Perl, ColdFusion, etc…)</pros>
<cons>Cons – The place is a total dead-end.  The same frustration of going nowhere and working on aimless tasks seems to be shared among most employees.  As far as the engineering department, it seems like it's straight out of a book that could be titled "Worst Software Practices".  There isn't time to do things right, but there's plenty of time to be fixing bugs and rewriting code.It's definitely not a place where you could grow as a software engineer as there is absolutely no concern for code craftsmanship.Within my last two weeks there, I saw about 5 other people leaving as well, which is a big red flag that there's something definitely wrong with the place.  In addition to employees, I saw them losing several big clients.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get some direction on where to take the company and how to be more innovative.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Campaign Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Storming”

</title><pros>Pros – Casual Dress Code, Bagel Wednesday</pros>
<cons>Cons – Employees being overloaded with work, constant system instability, slow career growth</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire additional resources to support clients and invest in your platform ASAP</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A lot of change yet going nowhere”

</title><pros>Pros – Youthful company with friendly, smart and passionate individuals.Provide workers with quality equipment to do their jobs; laptops, software, iPhones, etc..Nice office space.Top clients.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not what is used to be.Employee moral is really low due to so much change at the top and layoffs; went through 3 presidents in 6 month period.Dated technology and platform issues cause many headaches and an overload of work.Initiatives start but are never finished, leaving some people doing one thing while others are doing another.Rather disorganized.High employee turnover.Work/life balance non-existent.Office location stinks.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – First, stick around for longer than a few months and develop a well thought out road map out of this mess.  Second, institute the road map from start to finish and ensure complete buy in.  Third, continue to invest in upgrading the platform.  Fourth, relieve employee workload.  Fifth, provide stability and proof that things are getting better.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Great, smart, friendly employees.  had a boss who made working late enjoyable... bought dinner and beers....learned a lot in this fast paced environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company was bought out by eBay so my position was cut short.. . not much to say about the team I worked with or company..great location</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good but bad”

</title><pros>Pros – Company is doing an ok job</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company needs to improve a lot</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“New Management Team, Exciting Changes”

</title><pros>Pros – Great vibe.  excellent people.  Big changes announced recently to employees. Great new GM/ COO and great CTO with the right vision for new broader organization.  People are coming back!  John Healy has moved on to another company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very fast pace.  You have to be able to keep up.  Must be able to deal with customers.  Salaried competitive, not market leading</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep on heading in the direction you have set.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E-Dialog was great but now has a revolving door of top management and is drifting aimlessly.”

</title><pros>Pros – The employees still care.  They are passionate about what they do and want to change the company for the better.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Clients are leaving and management seems clueless about how to change things.  The employees still care but that won't last if management doesn't get it's act together</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen.  THe people who have been here know what they are doing.  Start acting like a start-up that scraps for every client.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Incompetent managers with bad attitudes”

</title><pros>Pros – cheap snacks.  That is it.  Cheap snacks.  This web site is telling me that I need to put at least 5 words.  There was nothing positive about this company that gets rid of talent and promotes buffoons.  Cheap snacks.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible place to work.  Directors and managers are unqualified and promote other unqualified employees that are willing to kiss up to them.  It says it all when universally the only positive thing people can say about this place is that it has cheap snacks.  I've heard that as one or two of the few competent people have left or been forced out, the directors have once again promoted a few individuals that they know are willing to kiss up.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Fire yourselves and put people in that are qualified to manage.  I wouldn't let anyone at that company that has anyone actually reporting to them manage a Kentucky Fried Chicken.  That is actually very derogatory to KFC, however, if you replaced anyone with the title of "manager" or "director" with someone from KFC, the KFC employee would do a better job.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very high expectations of engineering”

</title><pros>Pros – The people at e-Dialog are good to work with.  I looked forward to getting there almost every day from day one.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The standard of performance in software engineering became, "no delays and no bugs".  There was nothing in their software development process to help achieve that.  While "no delays and no bugs" is certainly something to strive for, making it a performance requirement is unrealistic.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Principal Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Trying to make it better with incomplete success”

</title><pros>Pros – Talking the right talk about agile.  Good use of Linux.  Smart colleagues.  Free coffee.  Cheap candy.  Periodic free food.  Easy parking.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Colleagues competing with respect to how long they work and how early in the morning they come in.  Demands to work during vacation, week-ends.  Demands to reschedule vacation.  People being shown the door with no sensible explanation.  A culture of fire fighting instead of pro-active problem prevention.  Trying to get things done sooner by decree.  Lack of admin access on Windows PCs gets in the way.  Unwillingness to address short staffing that damages progress of multiple teams.  Volatile requirements.  Unevenly applied rules.    Work space so noisy everyone uses earphones or ear plugs.  Benefits do not start one's first day of employment and they don't say so in the offer.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You cannot travel from Boston to Los Angeles in 3 seconds by decreeing that it be so.  You cannot get work done in a certain time by decree, even if it is work that you do not understand.  Technical debt and cut corners are killing your success.  Give people the time to do things correctly.  Work costs less in the long run when done right from the beginning.Read the book, Peopleware, about how noise damages productivity.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“In flux”

</title><pros>Pros – Probably some opportunity to make your own career path if you're clear about what you want to do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Technology is aging and need major overhaul.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Communicate on a regular basis.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company, great culture, definetly improving”

</title><pros>Pros – Despite many changes over the past year, e-Dialog has maintained its core values and culture. The people who work here have a lot of energy and passion about what they do.  I think now with a solid management team in place, headed up by Simone Barratt who is an eD veteran, the company is really headed in a good direction. Another benefit is being owned by eBay, which provides financial stability and lots of opportunities for career exploration and growth.  Not to mention awsome benefits and it looks pretty good on a resume.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working through changes in management last year was difficult at times, lack of communication from the top, etc., but I suppose that is typical when acquisitions take place (eD's parent company GSI was acquired by eBay 7/2011).  Still trying to figure out how everything will work with eBay, but i'm sure that will come in time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue the flow of communication from the top down and across companies (GSI & eBay).  Communication has improved dramatically over the last 4 months as a result of new management and more integration.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>7</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hasn't gotten any better”

</title><pros>Pros – Not very many but here are the ones I could think of- Free popcorn- Cheap candy and soda- Simone is good (but she was appointed far too late)</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Dated tools and no one left who knows how to manage them.  This is a ticking time bomb.- Massive turnover rate                   Employees are still being fired left and right with very little explanation.                   People continue to walk out the door - 2 to 4 people every week.- No opportunity                   Ebay is slowly dissolving the company.  As they continue their consolidation efforts they pick apart department after department.- No clear vision for the road ahead                    Management has cut off almost all communication with the rest of the company.  They keep a shroud of secrecy around their plans going forward.  Rumors spreading like wildfire that there is no plan.- Lines between departments are clouded                    There is no longer any clear separation of duties.  People pass work around because nobody knows who is responsible for what anymore.                    Department heads ignore the dysfunction.  They are all in cruise control.- Extremely long hours with no reward                    There is an expectation that everyone will pick up the slack of the employees that keep leaving.  But no reward for working 50 - 60 hours each week, not even a thank you.                     Level of effort and quality of work are no longer used to measure worth, now it's all about who you know.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop asking kiss up employees and new hires to write good reviews.  Just admit that you have no plan and are waiting for Ebay to move the entire platform to their systems and shut down e-Dialog for good.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“e-dialog wants puts its client's first”

</title><pros>Pros – - Very well known brand- Some of the smartest people in the space- Services centric with an enabling technology- Now part of eBay who is already investing more than previous management ever did in both people and technology- New leadership team with all the right capabilities</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Need to get the next generation of talent on board to complement current talent- Some of the leaders might be driving their part of the car looking in the rear view mirror</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to hire world class people and let them do their job.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>8</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Was a great place work - now EVERYTHING has changed for the worse”

</title><pros>Pros – Some of the PeopleThe ClientsThe building/office</pros>
<cons>Cons – Almost all the good people I worked with have left the companyNow lots of clients are leaving or are in the process of leavingSenior Management either has no clue or doesn't care if company exists in a couple yearsParent company (GSI) has also had a lot of turnover and does not treat e-Dialog well - why did they buy us in the first place?The technology is old and is not really supported - there is one product that I use everyday and it is critical to getting my client's campaigns out and there is no one that knows the code or can support it if anything goes wrong.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Major changes began about a year ago when when President, CTO, CMO, and CFO were all let go.  Then there was a layoff of all the people that made the company magical.  Then people were let go silently on a weekly basis.  Then lots of people started leaving on their own and still are.If you have a plan please communicate it.  If you only want us to service GSI clients and become a production arm of eBay then let us know.  This is a service company -so the most important asset is the people and you don't seem to care when they leave - and then get replaced with inexperienced people who don't understand our industry.  And nothing personal but the President of e-Dialog is just as inexperienced as the new people coming in.Some of us are working very, very hard because we value our client relationships.  If it wasn't for my client, I would have left a while ago.  I am looking to leave but only when I find the right job and when I do leave I sure upper management will not care but I know my client will.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>6</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sad to see it disappear”

</title><pros>Pros – I work with a great team, and we have a good management staff.Casual environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Attrition! It's been heart-breaking to see the people who built this place all leaving, either on their own or otherwise.Work-life balance is not good for people in some departments.Promotions seem to be given as political thank you's rather than on merit.  "Managers" with very poor approval ratings get lofty titles.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I won't bother saying "bring back the old days" because it won't happen, and with so many new people here, it'd be impossible anyway.  But there was a reason GSI picked us up for so much money a few years ago, and it was our culture that made us that company.  It's baffling to those of us who survived the blood baths that e-D is being changed so much, and that so many GOOD, caring people have been allowed to leave.  You want to help your bottom line? Listen to the people who tell you their managers are no good, get rid of those managers, promote the right people. Happy people make happy clients make happy shareholders.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“On the ropes.”

</title><pros>Pros – cheap sodafree popcornfree food at least once or twice a week-(decent sandwiches, cookies, etc.)most of your co-workers are friendly</pros>
<cons>Cons – Staggering turnover rate.  Droves of people leave each week, only to be replaced by new recruits the following week.  Not sure how long they can keep up this model and stay afloat.  Company has resorted to "job fairs".  Ancient technology...You won't be on the cutting edge of anything. Drab, uninspiring, boring products with no zip and no appeal.  Complete disconnect between various groups in the organization.  No career path, no appreciation for work well done. Certain favorites get away with utter incompetence.  There is no accountability where its really needed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Not sure if there is anything that can be done at this point.  It may be too late.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-29</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>6</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good company gone mediocre”

</title><pros>Pros – Awesome and intelligent co-workersEmployees who care about and focus on client needs25 cent snacksCasual dressLavish summer outings/Holiday parties (those days are gone, though)The company is undoing the demoralizing disaster of the job title homogenization</pros>
<cons>Cons – Old technology (but there's a plan to fix this not yet well communicated)Uncommunicative/uninspiring managementContinuing loss of talented, long tenured employees; disquieting drain of domain knowledgeNearly entirely new management with little knowledge/appreciation/understanding of those employees with high domain knowledgeIf not for the meeting with John Healey  all confidence would've been lost.  Bring back John Rizzi or have John Healey come back more often.  We need a leader of their caliber.  It's not too late to turn it around.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Your people are your best assets; understand and treat them better and stop the churn.  Get a leader who can motivate.  Communicate more.   An interesting question:  "Why was e-Dialog so highly rated in 2008-2009 with what was then considered outdated technology?"  One possible answer:  Awesome people.  Do something to retain them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Incompetent Management Team”

</title><pros>Pros – casual dress codeholiday party, paid for by company (probably non-existent now)</pros>
<cons>Cons – new management (GSI/E-Bay) is:-incompetent-lacks vision-communicates poorly/not at all</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Ask yourselves 'Why was e-Dialog successful before we got here?' and  'Why is it a sinking ship now?'</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>7</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Was a great place to work.  Terrible now.”

</title><pros>Pros – Basically none, other than the 25 cent vending machine.Any other pros that existed before left with the old management team.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Before, and for a time after the GSI purchase, this was one of the best companies you could work for.Great people to work with, great parties, and the management team had a clear vision and knew the market well.The current C-level team is completely incompetent and does not understand the technology.  They fired some of the best talent in the industry and let many more walk out the door.  Because they didn't understand the culture at all, the plan to "shake up the organization" backfired and people in the "wrong" department started leaving.  So they resorted to a job fair.  However it's clear that they still haven't learned that you reap what you sow and continue driving us down this path to destruction.This company is now very depressing to work for.  The hours are long, pay increases have ceased, no one is motivated, there is no communication from management whatsoever, and CYA is standard operating procedure.  The outlook is dim at best.  As soon as GSI started getting heavily involved in preparation for the ebay purchase, the machine started breaking down.  No one is left who knows how or cares enough to fix it.I don't think we will be able to get back on the bike and finish the race this time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Fire yourselves and get people who understand that the model laid out in 'What's holding you back?' is not sustainable.  Especially in a company that operated successfully for ten years by taking care of its employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“New management = Venom”

</title><pros>Pros – Used to Be:EnergeticInnovativeValued employeesTransparentOpen communicationPassionate Executive team (original exec team)These qualities have dissolved</pros>
<cons>Cons – Clueless Management TeamDishonest Management TeamCYA - Never wrongPolitical arenaPoor communicationLack of leadershipDated technologyUnhappy workforce</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – This advice is not only for management, but also individuals who may be interested in working at e-Dialog. Honestly, I don't know where to begin. e-Dialog was such a great place; a place where recognition echoed through the halls and everyone worked together to achieve a common goal: to be the best in the industry. Now its all about money, not people - about making yourself look good, and your co-workers bad - to be perfect and never at fault - to work countless hours, while upper management stroll in at 11am and depart at 4pm, and you are stuck working through the night. But the funny part is, if they focused on the people, the money would flow even more (just like the older days). I left on my own accord because I was: under valued, under appreciated and most of all disrespected. There is no way, no dollar amount or no apology that will ever have me work there again.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't work here”

</title><pros>Pros – Colleagues, $0.25 Vending Machines, Culture, Dress Code, Clients.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours, average work week was 55-60 hours. Wrong people in management, they were promoting people before the company was purchased the first time into management positions. These people were not competent, nor experienced enough to actually manage careers and career growth.New leadership team was brought in at end of 2010 from parent company and has ruined e-Dialog. These people had layoffs which affected about 1/3 of the workforce in March 2011, they then demoted all the employees who were left. The employees who remained left for better jobs. The company had so much attrition that e-Dialog had to have a job fair to make up for the job losses. What a joke.The new leadership team has ruined this company. Clients are not happy, the workforce is not happy. The current leadership team is not the best fit for this company or the industry; it is a prime example of the wrong people at the table trying to lead a company that they knew nothing about.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Retire</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Database Programmer Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“At one time, was great... but stumbled and has failed to regain its step.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great peopleInteresting clientsRelaxed dress codeFlexible hoursDecently amusing events</pros>
<cons>Cons – CYA attitudeLack of communication form upper managementTaking advantage of those willing to work hard without them being properly recognized or compensated</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Dont pretend to be good at communicating. In the last 6 months we have been downright lied to. Your employees are not stupid. Please dont treat them like they are. Dont fool yourselves in thinking that holding an abundant amount of stupid events/parties or having a 'popcorn machine' is going to make people happy. All its doing is allowing you to mask the fact that people used to be legitimately happy to work here, and now the majority of people are miserable.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Campaign Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You'll learn a lot, work a lot, play a lot... and work a lot.”

</title><pros>Pros – People - young, smart, funny, hard-workingCulture - FUNBeer - As long as it's after 4 and you're not too rowdy. Never need a reason to celebrate.Events - eDogalog (tailgating), Wine tastings, popcorn machine in-houseFun</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hoursLittle ability to prevent issues keeping you from logging offCYA cultureNo test environment for live production environment</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – COMMUNICATION. Be way more transparent. Be real.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>6</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work hard and get little acknowledgement to the people that actually do the work that makes the company money.”

</title><pros>Pros – -Laid back atmosphere-Dress code is very lax, people wear jeans flips flops and some people have mohawks.-Subsidized vending machines, interesting events sometimes planned.-Contests to win Red Sox tickets</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Company lacks an ability to implement corporate roadmap-Mandatory hours are 9-6-Little opportunity for workplace enjoyment-Atmosphere is pretty much "Work very hard"-The business operations/account side of the company enjoys an easy ride, while the production/technical/client services is always overlooked-Very little opportunity for advancement within the department</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The executive team has recently left the company, from the CEO John Rizzi down through each VP, with the exception of two. Things are uncertain due to the eBay/GSI sale, of which e-Dialog is going to become part of eBay. Management is currently out of sync with how disenchanted their employees are - borderline mutiny. My advice would be to address this issue by NOT insulting your employees during company meetings.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of potential but management not strong enough to facilitate positive change”

</title><pros>Pros – The peopleThe cultureLocationHoliday events401k match</pros>
<cons>Cons – Weak managmentsiloed  thinkingLow expectations of management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve communication with employees. Provide management training, get managers working together and communicating common goals. Implement a program for 360 reviews, maybe even skipping a level to allow more feedback to senior managers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Production Department Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company culture brought down by incompetent management”

</title><pros>Pros – -Casual work atmosphere - breaking out beers on Friday afternoon-Supportive low-level management. Some of the team managers are great.-Profit-sharing (sometimes)-Great, young workforce</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours (9-6 standard, many people eat at their desks; frequent latenights are rarely noticed and even more rarely compensated)Some departments are apparently not serious about retention - a lot of very excellent people have been lost due to understaffing.Questionable promotions. The policy seems to be to hire from outside, even when internal candidates are qualified, pre-trained, and eager to advance.Some managerial incompetence goes a long way.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Skilled and dedicated employees are a great asset; you should take a look at why turnover is so high in some departments.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Campaign Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“easy going”

</title><pros>Pros – people are nice and environment is easy-going</pros>
<cons>Cons – lack of recognition or no rewards system</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – try better to keep good people</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company but growing a little too fast”

</title><pros>Pros – -$.25 snacks in the vending machines-Casual dress code-Relatively young workforce-Upward mobility-Very social office-Located near a good pizza place</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Company is growing very quickly and sometimes incompetent people become managers-Recently purchased by a publicly traded company (GSI Commerce) so the old e-Dialog culture may be on the wane-If you get saddled with a demanding account, you may have to work loooooong hours</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Find a better way to reward/compensate those who work on difficult or demanding accounts so that they don't feel isolated and other employees don't feel that there is an in group out group dynamic</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-25</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall, a good place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great atmosphere-people enjoy being here. Very team oriented. Management recognizes stress and tries to provide fun breaks. Good opportunity to advance, change roles, and move between offices internationally.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Standard hours are 9am to 6pm, which is a long day.Review process is arduous.Raises not based purely on performance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get a 401K match.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“--”

</title><pros>Pros – Often good opportunities for promotion due to speed of growth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some growing pains as company expands at such a rapid rate</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Recognize competition from outside of the standard channels</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awful place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – You get to learn a lot by being thrown in the deep end and the hugely long working hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – Where do I start? Long working hours, no support, bullying at times, no career progression, no organization or good structure.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take care of employees and their well being. No one at e-Dialog feels like staying there long term as the company doesn't care about the employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Client Service (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great clients, evolving buisness moving to multichannel, part of ebay, exciting times ahead”

</title><pros>Pros – - Work with some great clients- central London location- opportunities to develop- chance to have responsibility- part of eBay- great team- smart people- evolving from an ESP to multichannel, working with attribution (ClearSaleing), retargeting (FetchBack).</pros>
<cons>Cons – - play hard but also work hard- demanding clients, you have to be prepared to roll you sleeves up and get stuck in</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to ensure that opportunities to work with other products are made available to all existing employees as well as new, so everyone gets the chance to develop. Better communication around new product features and product roadmap across all channels. More marketing about the work we do for our clients.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-31</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Team (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The blind leading the blind.”

</title><pros>Pros – - Casual attire- Liberal attitude, flat hierachy- Modern centrally located offices on Tottenham Court Road- Free chocolate and beer on Fridays- World class clients- Great summer and Christmas parties- No one knows what they're doing so you can get away with murder</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Senior management consists of inexperienced, under qualified long time e-Dialogers- Departments and long serving staff are constantly shuffled with a number of inflated or mickey mouse roles- Depending on what project you get put on your work hours can be ridiculous - think 12 hour days plus weekends without even a thank you let alone time in lieu.- Highly experienced staff quickly leave as senior management are unable to allow them to work efficiently or deliver on career progression promises- As a cost cutting measure inexperienced staff were recruited creating a knowledge void and increased mistakes which have to be dealt with by those who are experienced- Bullying issues are not addressed</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Grab the bull by the horns and realise the ship is sinking.  You had an opportunity to listen to your staff and make subtle changes before the rot set in but that opportunity has now passed. New blood is required and quickly, unfortunately this means cutting the wheat from the chaff is the only option - are you brave enough to do what you know you need to before eBay force you to?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-02</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Do not work for this company”

</title><pros>Pros – -Some people are nice-chocolate given for free on friday</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Very boring repetitive work- Company tools arent invested in and are old and failing constantly-Blame culture-Senior management only looking after themselves-No career planning-Very high turnover of staff</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Care about the people that work at your company and not lining your pockets</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“4 CEOs in 2 years”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice office and building. Cheap snacks.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 4 CEOs in 2 years says it all. This was a good company made bad in early 2011.The only constant is turnover. Good employees leave and the bad remain. As turnover increased, so did backbiting and blaming. Throw other employees overboard before you get tossed yourself.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Just shutter it already.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's OK”

</title><pros>Pros – If you've worked here after a while and aren't involved in a crazy client it's a great place to work. I've never been micro-managed. Also you'll never have to work more then 40+ hrs as long as everything is working. It's a very chill place to work at here and most of the people are interesting to talk to.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Technology is way old. Things barely work. No one to learn anything from. If you want to learn the how to do cutting edge marketing or technology this isn't the best place. Find another job or work here and Google what other companies are doing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get some smart people here to solve your big problems.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Campaign Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“DO NOT APPLY FOR A ROLE!!”

</title><pros>Pros – You will have health insurance, Life assurance and pay for eye appointments.</pros>
<cons>Cons – rubbish management, work like a robot, cant move from your desk, have to stay back until early hours of the morning. Staff sleep and shower here as if it is their home. There's a mouse running around and nobody cares. Workload wise - you are given no clear instruction or any information on your workload. You have to really adapt your persona to be ruthless in this role and demand further information to do your work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – recognize talent. put your foot down with clients. there should be a no late night policy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Producer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Was fun at one time, now tho...”

</title><pros>Pros – Great clients, incredible list of Fortune 500s</pros>
<cons>Cons – Legacy software, management didn't communicate well</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't hire bad CEOs</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It used to be great, then it was acquired--twice.”

</title><pros>Pros – Work-from-home flexibilityCasual dressCentral location for NH and MA employeesStrong teamwork mentalityLots of young energy among the staff</pros>
<cons>Cons – e-Dialog was acquired by GSI Commerce in 2008, and then GSI Commerce was acquired by eBay in 2011, right after I started working at e-Dialog. As so many acquisitions go, there was no attention paid to change management, and as a result, a mass exodus ensued (not fun to watch a month after starting a new job). e-D is now a mere satellite to eBay, and we are treated as if we don't exist (at least I hope eBay doesn't communicate this poorly with its own headquarters employees). I'd like to think it will get better with time--a change management consultant has been hired and has solicited feedback from employees (it was refreshing to finally have our concerns heard). Unfortunately, upper management will have to approve any plans the consultant devises, and I honestly don't trust them to make decisions in their employees' best interest. However, this is my job, and I will do it the very best I can until I can find an employer that's a better fit for me.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Connect with your employees through diligent communication, and stop adding more upper management jobs when we need more people in the trenches to actually get work done.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Positive Reviews!? Wonder if it's senior management. This company fell down and is struggling to get back up.”

</title><pros>Pros – Some of the employees are great peopleCentral locationGood benefits - bupa, pension and eBay acquisition means more like more holiday, dentalfree nespresso coffeeGreat clientsCasual dressSummer/christmas party</pros>
<cons>Cons – Senior management seem to keep changing their minds. Firstly they re-orged the company structure, people said it wouldn't work, and now some changes are being made and some stuff is going back to the way it was. A lot of time and energy was put into the changes so it's annoying that they feel they can keep making changes just to see if they work.Long hours and heavy workload - especially with all the people leaving those remaining are expected to pick up the slackLack of support from some managers if somethings going wrong at the end of the day or after 530The training you receive isn't great particularly with the new structure, new employees are coming in and being put onto large accounts. They make mistakes which their buddy has to be careful to pick up on so we don't have errors putting added pressure on existing employees.Salary is poor compared to other places and you're not paid what you're worth.Not much opportunity to progress. The new structure has made positions that are quite specific so if you want a traditional account management/client services role, this isn't it.Lots of people constantly leaving meaning we lose great people and great knowledge.Lack of recognition for doing a good job or consistently doing a good jobManagement seem to be quite secretive about their plans moving forwardReview feedback can be unfair almost as if they feel they have to give you some negative feedback even if you're doing well. There's no harm in giving someone areas to develop but you don't need to put them down in doing so.Management can be clandestine about future opportunities for your career to get you to stay but these then never come to fruition.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I've spoken to several employees who are looking for other jobs - and they're only the ones who would tell me about it. Some of them are also really good for the company and will be a big loss. It's indicative of the current structure and management. My advice:Don't keep making changes to the structure - get a professional to look at the positions you have to ensure you have the right mix of positions, seniority and places for people to enter and progress.Stop trying to amalgamate all roles into one.Pay your employees what they're worth. Don't wait until they are handing in their notice to offer them more.Reward and value the people who work hard and do a good job regularly</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great for a long time, but decline started when original execs were dumped, & is long way from glory days.”

</title><pros>Pros – great people, committed to clients and each othercasual atmosphere/dressgreat clients, growing industrycheap snacks, lots of free food</pros>
<cons>Cons – Currently eating competitors' dustLack of direction on who we are and who we want to be, and how we are going to get there.Lots of talk about talks with eBay, but very little filters down to rank and file. We are told to keep waiting for this fabulous plan they are planning. This has been the same story for almost a year.Having Simone back is great, but hard to see concrete changes that have been made as a result.Attrition was stemmed for a while, but has picked up again, which should tell you something right there.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hurry up already!What are we doing with our product?What is our messaging and positioning?eBay acquisition doesn't really seem to benefit e-Dialog yet.There is still a lack of engagement day to day, which is why people are leaving. Get Simone in Burlington permanently. She needs to be more visible.You need to tell people how much you value their hard work. Reinstate the core value awards.Need to get back to knowledge sharing. Reinstate the PS meetings.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Enjoyable workplace and a company back on the rise”

</title><pros>Pros – CultureThe peopleNew ManagementKnowledge SharingClient liste-Dialog is truly a great place to work regardless of past hardships. There has been a significant change in the atomosphere since the management changes and I for one can see a turn fo the better.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 2011 was a tough year for manyClient expectations at timesChanges will continue to happen and bumps in the road, but pros currently outweigh the cons.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I believe managment has gotten quite a bit better. It is obvious the company will still endure changes as it comes back from slumps in 2011, but it seems it is on the right path. Continue to reward your employees for hard work and dedication.Many employees are starting to see the light again.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I truly enjoy working at e-Dialog and I am looking forward to the new opportunities to come!”

</title><pros>Pros – e-Dialog is a team oriented company that truly works to satisfy client needs.  Because there is such a need to work with large clients and satisfy their needs, the company attracts very dedicated and intelligent people.  It is truly refreshing to be surrounded each day with such a great group of co-workers. There is a lot to learn about the industry and e-Dialog's clients and the working envronment is conducive in learning and growing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Commitment of at least 9 hours per day</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unsettled”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people and leadership. Opportunities for skills training and development</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of clarity in job roles since the recent restructure which mean sometimes things are easily complicated.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Potential if they can work out their issues!”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits are good, people are very nice and competent.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Heavy turnover! bleeding 3 -4 people/weekNo one seems to be able to make a decision, a lot of talk but no action.Poor communication, you find out everything through the "grapevine"Don't care about the people who have been there a long time building the organization</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get your act together and keep the good, loyal smart workers, don't let them all leave</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This company is in a death spiral”

</title><pros>Pros – - Some of the employees remaining are good people- 25 cent vending machines</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Turnover. There is a steady stream of people running for the exits. Entire departments no longer exist.- Long hours- Political connections are the path to power here. Competence is not rewarded, it's all who you know.- CYA is the operative word of this organization. Trust no one.- Software and tools are dated and, because all the long term employees are now gone, no one has any idea how they work.Company began unraveling when the long time and much admired CEO left in late 2010. That was when e-Dialog was one of the best employers in the Boston area. CEO was replaced by someone who had no idea what he was doing.New CEO immediately started layoffs. Massive layoffs lead to a surge in profits and crushing workload for remaining employees. Crushing workload and lack of appreciation and trust drives out experienced workers who take all their knowledge with them. New trainees can't keep pace with new work. More employees leave and more work is left to pile on those who remain. Death spiral results. New CEO fired after 8 months but damage looks irrevocable.This company could serve as a textbook case of how to destroy an organization. Don't work here. If you do work here, get out.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Sticking around at e-Dialog is like being one of the people manning the pumps on the Titanic. Get a a lifeboat before they are all gone.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Development Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Simone Barratt will settle the organisation and propel it forward”

</title><pros>Pros – Commitment to excellence - including the best clients, the best programmes, and the best staff.  Simone's promotion to President is a big plus.  Simone is an 'A player', and will (re)accelerate e-Dialog's success.e-Dialog genuinely cares about it's staff</pros>
<cons>Cons – None really - it's a hardworking environment, so if you're looking for a Mon-Fri 9-5, then you'd better look elsewhere - but if you enjoy success and are a motivated person, you'll shine at e-D!  The promotions/rewards are there if you want them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Producer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hogwarts Express to Doomsday”

</title><pros>Pros – A brilliant opportunity for interns & college grads to learn production & programme management in all areas of the email business.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Believe you me, within 3-6 months- you will be promoted and leading a lethargic, prima donna team of near retirement age mates with "computer" experience from Slate Rock and Gravel or wide-eyed, legal-to-drink newbies learning to use Outlook. If you read between the lines, you'll notice that the gene pool is thin so step up or get out.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Company Culture is about what matters most -- PEOPLE. People are happiest and most productive with careers that tap their natural aptitude. HR needs to stop spinning the wheel of fortune and focus hours on building employee career development plans; including goal-setting , strengths-building, and real opportunities for advancement. If you want to build a high standard, start with a Company Mission and found it on the respect for real talent, career growth, pay for performance, and a high quality of life. Also note that there remain talented people on staff, please acknowledge them. Shout outs that "fall on sleepy eyes" do not motivate teams or create a competitive culture. People need to regain a sense of work place pride. Having a pulse should not qualify candidacy into any open position. Equally, do not promote out of desperation, it will infuriate the remaining few loyalists. Managers need to morph into Mentors and own their responsibility to have 1--1 meetings.  Don't forget that small tokens like "great job" or asking "how are you doing?", speak volumes....</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“was good but underwent awful restructure”

</title><pros>Pros – Good technology: the infrastructure is great; some applications not so great.Fun people: quite young overallCasual dress code</pros>
<cons>Cons – Recent restructure moved people from jobs they did well to jobs they have no interest in or have no skills for. A lot of great people have left and inexperienced people have been promoted to fill the vacant positions.3 month notice period introduced recently.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you reduce benefits and change someone's job to something they're not interested in working on, they may not want to stay.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>8</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Started out great but everything changed...”

</title><pros>Pros – A couple of years ago, the pros were:InnovativeEmpoweringChance to work with top-tier corporationsLots of opportunities (didnt like your role? You could move to a different one)Good communicationSolid leadership teamAppreciative (long hours but very appreciative upper mngmt)Somewhat fun (young atmosphere)Decent trainingVery collaborativeAll of these pros disappeared within the last year or two, since the purchase by GSI and subsequently eBay</pros>
<cons>Cons – Current Cons:Zero communicationZero appreciationHorrible, untrustworthy, politically motivated C-level teamLonger hours (always long, but now longer)Poor technology/no investment, thus unhappy clientsNo support - management or otherwiseCYA mentality instead of collaborativeIn short, GSI fired or forced out all of the excellent mid and top level managers (along with the non-managers who also worked extremely hard), promoting those who instead were politically motivated but not at all qualified.This company - in a period of just a few months - went from one of the best companies I'd ever worked for and was proud to be a part of, to one of the absolute worst.I would absolutely not recommend working here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Theres a reason this company was consistently rated at the top of the heap - and it certainly wasnt the technology. Without the dedication of the previous staff and the previously omnipresent passion, this company would be nonexistent. This fact is something GSI missed completely and will, eventually, suffer for, through lost clients, profits and reputation.In short, this company is a blood sucking corpse of what it used to be. I have no words of advice. And even if I did, wouldn't share them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Database Programmer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“From open-door to closed-door communications”

</title><pros>Pros – Fellow employees are/were top-notchCompetitive pay scalePotential upside with eBay acquisition</pros>
<cons>Cons – No LeadershipNo Communication from Sr. ManagementUnaddressed Attrition</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Communicate strategy to address employee/client retentionPublish Business PlansRe-Structure, again</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>6</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Used to be an excellent company.  Not anymore.”

</title><pros>Pros – Most co-workers are great.They have a flexible schedule$.25 vending machines</pros>
<cons>Cons – New executive team.Poor salaries.Almost no recognition for quality work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop treating new employees better than current employees who helped build the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people! Horrible communication between management”

</title><pros>Pros – - Flexible hours- Great people- Great clients- Fun events</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Little to no growth opportunity- Lack of communication between management- GSI changes</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please communicate better between employees and management! Provide better growth opportunity for HARD WORKERS....</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You will learn alot to build your career”

</title><pros>Pros – Work with world class clientsGood exposure to digital marketing</pros>
<cons>Cons – Organization too flat; limited career advancement</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“From Good to Uncertain”

</title><pros>Pros – - friendly, helpful people- fun events- great brands- nice office- good commute</pros>
<cons>Cons – - uncertainty / fear- lack of trust in leadership- crumbling benefits- titles have no recognition of experience- uninspiring leadership change</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The best way to lead is to inspire and show by example. Show you care about the people and their talents. We aren't moved by crude tenacity or regurgitated quips.  "A good leader inspires people to have confidence in the leader, a great leader inspires people to have confidence in themselves."</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Initially, very collaborative and energizing but became very different place as Corporate became more involved.”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart, hard working folks.  Great clients.  Employees want to do good work and maintain fun, informal culture.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Over last year, pressure from corporate to grow became overwhelming.  Nearly entire long-term senior team has been transitioned out of organization.  Significant investment is required in platform to continue to satisfy and maintain clients.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make significant investment in platform.  Fix employee morale.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“So much potential for greatness, struggling to reach the next level”

</title><pros>Pros – - opportunities to grow and advance if you're competent, inspired and are given the bandwidth and resources to make it happen- solid training programs, and support for external education, in both technical and management skill sets- a lot of great people to work with- a lot of world-class clients to work with-  parent company making interesting moves, but better communication required to ease concerns and build excitement- interesting field of work, with great potential for a lot of exciting times ahead</pros>
<cons>Cons – - unfortunate lack of vision, progress towards maintaining competitive edge is questioned by many- poor management of lower level resources to ensure proper load distribution of either heavy work periods or loss of staff- inefficiencies abound and lack of investment in tools and services to improve efficiency and quality due to lack of focus on long-term returns on such investments- changes in corporate structure, lack of investment for stated initiatives and vision leave many questions and concerns unaddressed, and lower-level staff unconvinced of a promising future- some senior management are obviously a poor fit for their department (or possibly not supported by their Execs), but no one has made the tough decision to replace them (or support them) with someone who can address long-standing issues and implement improvements- slowed growth or staff stability issues leave many feeling like they need to leave for the next opportunity</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make the management changes or structural changes needed to address long-standing quality and efficiency issues, will require investment in tools and new processes, but will greatly improve staff moral, client satisfaction and retention.Invest for the future that's already upon us, convince us and our clients that we're in it to win it. Let's forge a vision and pursue it with passion.Parent company is doing a lot of interesting things, but causing concern, somewhat unnecessarily in lower-level staff - could be addressed with better communication (again, back to vision).</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It has been a great ride”

</title><pros>Pros – The CultureThe PeopleThe WorkThe Office</pros>
<cons>Cons – Looks like there may be a lot of changes - not sure why or what they will be</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Communicate what is going on - the real reason people are leaving - and the plan for the future</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“depends on what you are looking for”

</title><pros>Pros – people are young, energeticteamwork environmenttop marketer in its fieldgrowing fastcompany activities</pros>
<cons>Cons – severe CYA environmentlong hours - average 10-12 a dayno OT compensationincompetent management team (depending on dept.)little to no recognition for constant above-and-beyond workconstant employee turn-around</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – appreciate your workers. give bonuses where you can, especially for those working long hours. recognize the problem with the department(s) that have constant turnaround. get rid of incompetence.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>