<name>G-III Apparel Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/G-III-Apparel-Reviews-E1126.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-03-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very good, stable company”

</title><pros>Pros – Very good, stable company to work for. Many brands and departments in one location if you are interested in working for a very large company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited advancement given how the company is structured. No management training.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Too many silos, where one department doesn't know what the other is doing and how decisions affect others.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stable, but not exciting in terms of product”

</title><pros>Pros – Stable, good hours for the fashion industry.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not very clear management structure.  Run very "family business" style, even though the company has grown quite large</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More standard performance review practices, allow employees to explore and work towards advancement.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A learning experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great relationship with coworkers. Learned a lot about all aspects of garment manufacturing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not fairly compensated. Under staffed in a lot of areas</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take note in the people who true work hard for the company interest free because they truly love what they do. And reward them accordingly. A lot of employees feelNeglected.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Food Safety Hygiene Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“i'm really appreciating the seasoned marketing and branding executive & G-III is a leading manufacturer and distributor”

</title><pros>Pros – G-III’s business outlook or future economic performance, anticipated revenues, expenses or other financial items; product introductions and plans is completely amazing and takes the best care of its employes .</pros>
<cons>Cons – No one is perfect and  it is this imperfection which develops the organization and G-lll's  is really showing  its talent and  crosses its barriers .</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – work with honestly and keep in mind G-lll is our bread and butter .</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A company which offers the freedom and platform to manage your own business”

</title><pros>Pros – The company is flexible, giving key employees who are ambitious the freedom and scope to go out and get things done, with very little red tape. G-III operates like a small business, although there are public group with over $1 billion in annual sales.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of structure and policy often leads to confusion about who is responsible when things do not go as well as planned.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>