<name>REAL D Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/REAL-D-Reviews-E114134.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-10-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Materials Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A demanding job but i was motivated to do my best,”

</title><pros>Pros – An exciting place to work; the Operations and Engineering teams are top notch; fun stuff working with 3D technology!  Good pay, good benefits; upper management wants RealD to be a top 100 best companies to work for in the US.   Very lofty goal indeed but the could make it happen.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Each employee needs to take control of their work/life balance, cuz the company wont do that for you.  I made that mistake.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more forthcoming with your plans with layoffs.  It will help those impacted to be better prepared if/when that event DOES take place.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun startup, cool technology, good for people who dont need a lot of handholding”

</title><pros>Pros – opportunities to work on many different and exciting projects</pros>
<cons>Cons – management not focused on employee concerns</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – reald still not a household name and it should be</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unfocused, insufficient resources to execute”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay OK to goodBenefits goodInteresting business spanning entertainment and technologyFast pace</pros>
<cons>Cons – Vicious politicsInformation hoardingTop down executive team approach disconnected from most of companyUnclear roles, responsibilities and decision-makingLack of focus means everything is high priority and company wants to do everythingInsufficient resources to execute well on non-prioritized tasks and projects</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – FocusClarifyEmpower and reward good leadership</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>