<name>K Line Europe Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/K-Line-Europe-Reviews-E114249.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Information Systems Deputy Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The best company I've worked for!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – The best easygoing managers, extremely friendly atmosphere, family like.</pros>
<cons>Cons – a little bit boring Japanesse corporate culture</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marine Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its like a family and takes care of every employee”

</title><pros>Pros – Its really too good to work in K Line, because the company work like a family and understand the situation of every employee and never force anyone for any thing. In one line i want to state that if the employer thinks that you are their own then definitely every employee will also think same. this is the reason that yhis company is a leading company in this world.</pros>
<cons>Cons – as per my point of view their is nothing to say about any downside of this company. Because exactly their is not a single downside of this company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Just one thing to say you guyz are rocking. This is a company in from which other companies can learn how to run a company smoothly and manage people even onboard and even offshore.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-22</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good job”

</title><pros>Pros – working in a highly competitive work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – pleased to make technical reports in more detailed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Very good management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best in Merchant Shipping”

</title><pros>Pros – 1.Excellent environment.2.Good support.3.Good salary.4.Fast promotions.5.Better evaluation of my work than other places.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Chance of getting into this company and starting job from a 3rd world country like mine is pretty difficult.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It would be greatly beneficial if the management give emphasis to get their officers from my country directly through interviews rather than maintaining a agent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Master Officer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“K Line LNG UK”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work/leave ratioGood salaryGood personal relations</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very limited filed of opporunities to move onshoreSmall company in LNG business</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Company management has to improve in many fielddDecision making and support to offsore personell has to improveBetter HR selection is MUST</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>