<name>ITESM Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/ITESM-Reviews-E116703.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Professor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fair conditions: teach, teach, teach”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a very different experience depending the campus you work at, some are excellent, others a living hell. I was lucky to work with great people. Working conditions are good, salary is always negotiable despite what some say.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As with all private universities in Mexico, they are going to ask you to teach a ridiculous number of hours per week, plus admin work. No room for much else.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – One word: relax the hyper-centralized policies: let good campi self-manage. Stop the micro management of every single process.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Program Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ITESM”

</title><pros>Pros – The best private University in Mexico, innovative, the profile that students achieve while studying here is the most liked in Latinamercia by employers according to QS ratings.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Favoritism, not everybody has the same promotion opportunities, while some people may have the best chances to get more degrees and diplomas, others are deined trhat opportunity without a plausible or specific reason but if they like you or not.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Equity for everyone, beacuse if by any chance you are the "favorite" of your boss, great you get everything you want to imrpove, develop and be seen, if they just like you or on the contrary, you are different that he/ she you will not get any opprotunity.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good to work as a student”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a good job for a former student, but it is not good to make a career in it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is not quite good at it could be in other institutions.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Researcher (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great job.”

</title><pros>Pros – Very youthful workplace to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Fixed salary rates with low flexibility.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Beware of your credentials before accepting a job.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great location to work if you are a student and you need to gain some working experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – Location.Great place to make working connections.You can get a lot of experience if you are a student.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary was just very low.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You should pay more to employees so you can maintain a quality in the company's personnel.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>English Teacher (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Invest in their people's education, not in their salaries.”

</title><pros>Pros – Teaching environment is wonderfulColleagues are mostly nice</pros>
<cons>Cons – Contracts for 6 months are not ethical</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop thinking of education as a business. You're not running a company, or at least that's what you said. When teachers are in trouble, learn to help them. Contracts for at least a year.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Investigation Assistant”

</title><pros>Pros – You can get a scholarship for your Masterm, High level education.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The salaries are not that good</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Very nice place to get better opportunities</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Professor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very Good”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work environment and growth opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low salaries no bonuses no medical expenses</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Director of Marketing, Communications and Student Services (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent place to work and develop managerial skills”

</title><pros>Pros – Great engagement from the board and directors to develop community and univeristy environment. Huge opportunities for personal and professional growth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is located in a small city.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Profesionista De Apoyo (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Paid Masters degree, full use of the installations, free courses. very punctual payment. good career options.</pros>
<cons>Cons – bureaucratic  and sometimes tending on the monotonous</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Few Pros vs Cons ITESM”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy place for worknice work enviroment</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are not great oportunities for get a better job inside the company and also the profesional development is null</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Todo vacations and hour flexibility but low pay”

</title><pros>Pros – It has lot of paid vacations and in the area I was working there was a lot of flexibility as long as you fulfilled your work objectives.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the pay was low and with little growth opportunity</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hard but academically it costs”

</title><pros>Pros – - good benefits, they are the ones CONACYT gives you plus some extra income and gratuities- really good professors- great installations - access o library, secure building, classrooms with all the material needed, cafeteria.- challenging- a lot of  extracurricular classes you can take</pros>
<cons>Cons – - the benefits change among different research groups- not always are the working hours respected ( some times more, others less)- there is not an opportunity for giving classes or having a mid time job.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It is a little to soon to give some feedback, maybe just that it is annoying that EGADE students can't enter automatically to de main campus of ITESM .</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Director De Digital (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Misleading job opportunity”

</title><pros>Pros – Away from the city and little traffic</pros>
<cons>Cons – awful working environment, poor management and minimal support on new projects</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Think of your people as the ones that are building your company</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – The chance to study your Master's Degree at no cost</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow growth, outside people don't appreciate that you work at ITESM</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Scholarships (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work, but very elitist”

</title><pros>Pros – Can be as much as an hour late in some days, have a lot of water cooler time and you have a general idea about salary ranges. Good benefits if you are full time with contract. Food in premises is great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not very well paid, some decisions made by management are taken very quickly and leave little time for preparation. Social science graduates and non-sport people are usually rejected.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Let ideas flow upwards, a lot of people would give you innovative ideas if there were a more rewarding culture. Instead we just learn how to beat the system and make the minimum work we can.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Professor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I work on an ITESM Campus but not at Monterrey”

</title><pros>Pros – The best benefit for employees at ITESM is the scholarships you get for your family members</pros>
<cons>Cons – Female have less opportunities than male (as everywhere)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give same opportunities to females as given to males</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>English Teacher (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Business school that works you to the bone with decent to so-so pay.”

</title><pros>Pros – Dynamic and innovative in some areas.</pros>
<cons>Cons – High stress, seeks to demand all the work it can out of you, more machine like than human.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make the place more human, pay teachers better, give more time off.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-08-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ITESM”

</title><pros>Pros – ITESM is a great place to work because of the ambience and growth opportunities that are offered. The school will always support employees when it comes to obtaining new qualifications such as master degrees and PhDs.Salary is good and enough to live well within Mexican standards</pros>
<cons>Cons – People in Mexico tend to think that only rich people study and work at ITESM. This is obviously not true since the school has a very large program that provides scholarships for students with high academic performance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Leadership at ITESM is good. I believe that some decisions should be made in teams and everybody's opinion should be heard.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>