<name>G-Tech Professional Staffing Inc. Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/G-Tech-Professional-Staffing-Inc-Reviews-E117387.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2008-07-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“G-Tech is providing a service with minimal effort and interaction.”

</title><pros>Pros – G-Tech is very concerned about making salary payments. If they do not receive my time entries to process payment they make every effort to obtain it from me and my authorizer.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I have not had a salary review sinsce starting work for G-Tech in December 2005.Some of the forms G-Tech requires are not user friendly and require too much time to complete.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – G-Tech is a technical staffing company and I feel they do not pay particular attention to individuals situations. Be more flexible, understand and accept the clients requirements.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Employee/Administrative/Clerical (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“G Tech Professional Staffing is Very Limited in Ability to Move Up the Ladder”

</title><pros>Pros – The staff is VERY friendly and accomodating.  They are able to answer all questions you may have.  Flexible with scheduling and use of vacation hours.  They visited from Michigan to talk to the G tech contractors in our building and genuinely was appreciative of our hard work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited communication and need to fill out timecard every week.  Not allowed to take out vacation pay in advance in cases of emergencies.  Missed pay due to change of policy.  Gtech no longer calls employees if they do not receive the timesheet, whether or not you fax the timesheet.  The benefits are bad.  Health insurance is bad and not many facilities are actually covered and even those that are listed on the website are obsolete with wrong information.  Copay for 1 visit was 50 bucks!  Can't get the perks of being a direct hire at a company and they take a cut of your actual pay.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I feel as though staffing should not have changed the timesheet policy....it was more convenient and reassuring to know that staff would call or make attention to timesheets that were not received.  Sometimes the failure of the fax machine or missed faxes could be attributable to this.  It is definitely a hassle to have to fax a timesheet all the time.  A time log-in through the phone system might be a better idea.  More ability to move in different available positions in nearby areas might be a plus for change of pace in work environment.  Better heatlh insurance alternatives would also be a great idea.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“G=Average”

</title><pros>Pros – There are a lot of good sincere people.There are lots of job opportunities for technical staff.Its a growing company.Respects people.Good leftovers (food).</pros>
<cons>Cons – Churn & burn.Wages are low.Commissons are low.Lots of paperwork.Conservative.Nylons required.No H1s.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Simplify!Pay better; could/should be a leader to get experts.Offer more development training.Better tools to do job.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>