<name>Element K Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Element-K-Reviews-E11961.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Element K was the best work-family I've ever known.”

</title><pros>Pros – The people that I worked with at Element K are incredibly fun, honest, hardworking geniuses. People were creative, working together to offer the best in class online training options to corporate clients. I learned more from the people at Element K that I could have learned in 20 years of collage. The corporate and personal values were unparalleled.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Element K was located in Rochester, NY where the is never enough good weather. In good times, employees were hired at high wages, and longer term employees that were hired at lower salaries often were not compensated equally to new hires.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to listen to the employees who make things happen. Value those that work hard and support them in their efforts to do things well for long term goals. Identify those who always try to find the easy way out and limit their influence/power.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A casual and relaxing place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – No dress code and casual atmosphere.  Great people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Production likely suffered from the laid back culture</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't sell the company....never mind</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Instructional Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart, hardworking, loyal employeesFlexibilityGreat friendshipsGood tools and processes</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low salaryChanging managementGrowth/advancement was slow</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fantastic Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Work/Life BalanceDynamic CompanyMany of Different Types of Projects</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can be some long hours (working weekends, etc.)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You guys were great.  Keep your heads up.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>District Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company, great culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Freedom, ability to learn, competitive salaries</pros>
<cons>Cons – Small company, needs product investment</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Instructional Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A nice place to work, but watch your head on the ceiling...”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent benefits, time-off policies, chance to work with wonderful, caring, and bright people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No career advancement, no internal training (although emphasis is put on personal growth during performance appraisals - so just do it on your own time and your own dime). There is only so far the company will let you grow. Once you are there, they would rather hire from outside the company and keep your talents in the dead end job.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Develop from within...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engagement Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A positive place to grow and many fabulous people to work with.”

</title><pros>Pros – You can grow into different fields with the company, the evinornement is very laid back, and the people in this company make it worth coming in every day.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay is not that great and there are many long hours. Its hard to change things that haven't worked in years because management is set in their ways.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Used to be great”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Coworkers, Product, Legacy and Technology</pros>
<cons>Cons – Layoffs, Benefit and Current HR</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Content Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people working on some world class e-learning”

</title><pros>Pros – Really smart people working here.   Definitely some of the best instructional design and e-learning that I've seen in the industry.    Great use of media - video, graphics, 3D, and instructional games.    Cool new outputs.   Company seems to have won a number of new customers and working on some great new projects.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes there are long hours.  Some irrational customer demands will drive you crazy.   Some managers place unrealistic timelines on projects.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you aren't part of the 'in crowd" you should start looking for a new job.”

</title><pros>Pros – When I started at Element K, it had a wonderful, family-like atmosphere. I loved going to work every day and really thought it was the best job I had ever had. The team I worked with was extremely supportive, and they organization had many traditions that contributed to the wonderful feeling.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management has no idea what it takes to make the product they sell, and they figure as long as it has Element K's name on it, it's good enough. There is no connection with the end users of the product.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay attention to your customers, and listen to the people that actually make your product.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you want your career to die, Element K is for you.”

</title><pros>Pros – The benefits are not bad, but getting worse.The people are generally nice to work with.It is a casual, yet professional atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you want your career to die, Element K is for you.You can expect more work, for less pay, year after year.If parent company NIIT has their way, your job may be transitioned over to India. (Though lots of people are in disbelief.)No opportunities for career advancement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more truthful about the situation.  Do not tell everyone things are ok, when things are not ok.  Adjust your expectations to match the size of the work force instead of fostering failure after failure.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Worked In CDS (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Laid back place but not for advancement”

</title><pros>Pros – Laid backDecent peopleAble to balance personal and work lifeConvenient to shopping areas and many of eateriesCausal</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low payManagers played to favoritesNo real set career path for most positions within the company.No real accountability for errors</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please follow some local successful companies in the Rochester area and observe how they treat ALL of their employees.Update technology and training oppt's.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Instructional Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Relaxed environment, but little incentive and iffy management”

</title><pros>Pros – Relaxed dress code - shorts in the summer.Flexible hours - management is very understanding about family and health time off and making up time on another day.Intelligent, friendly people and very little politics.They pay a large percentage of health insurance premiums and offer a very nice plan.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Little incentive provided in any way - no bonuses, only token recognition at poorly attended staff meetings, few regular raises.Poor middle and upper management. Many inexperienced managers and many managers working outside of their specialty.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make more of an effort to appropriately qualify accounts while maintaining reasonable customer expectations. A US based workforce can not compete with overseas based companies on price, you need to compete on quality and service. When you over-promise and under-deliver, while managers who are working beyond their training and expertise are simultaneously not listening to the workers 'in the trenches', you end up with poor customer retention, non-existent margins, and a downward spiral for a business.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Network Administrator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A day at the beach meets Dilbert”

</title><pros>Pros – There are some really great people that work at EK. They have some of the most intelligent engineers as well as some very creative people. They have a few really great people in middle to upper management. The pay is decent and the benefits are fairly decent. EK has a lot of upside potential.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some departments have terrible managers. Don't even bother trying to negotiate compensation package. Old technology, overworked staff in certain departments.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – What is our vision? How are our actions aligned with our vision, mission, and goals?</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-02-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engagement Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Beware of layoffs!”

</title><pros>Pros – Depending on your position, they allow a lot of freedom, such as working from home.  they don't watch you over your shoulder all day as long as you're getting your work done.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They just laid off 30% of the workforce.  A lot of work gets sent to India. Inconsistent cash flow into the organization.  Definitely a company getting punded by the economy.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus more on quality and get back to basics.  Stop worrying so much about landing the big contract and put more energy into the small businesses that cannot afford a training dept of their own.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Instructional Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A company that was once great, and still has a lot of potential despite some retention challenges.”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible schedules, relaxed environment & dress code, appreciation for family and work/life balance. The people that work at Element K are friendly, very smart, and demonstrate a great deal of respect for diversity. There was (at least was when I worked there) a corporate shut down every 4th of July week, which gave everyone a chance to relax over the summer. There are internal systems in place for employees to network with each other, form discussion groups, and connect beyond work related tasks.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited career paths, heavy focus on overseas outsourcing, much more attention paid to offshore workers career needs rather than a balanced approach for total company. Depending on the department you work in, you could make a better than average salary or a lower than average salary. No 401k matching (was taken away when I was there, along with gym memberships and incentive plans, but some or all may be back now. Unsure.)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Recognize and reward accomplishments consistently, across all departments.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Element K moves into a new phase and has the opportunity to become a huge player in this space.”

</title><pros>Pros – Element K has extremaly flexible solutions to offer.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Finding their voice in a quickly changing environment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Align the teams, have consistent message and focus!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Developer II (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Element K is a fun place to gain some experience out of school, but no place to have a serious career.”

</title><pros>Pros – Fellow employess are good people, which makes for a fun work environment. Hours are pretty flexible, too.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor pay, and the technologies we use are years behind what's current in the industry. Your career will die here. Also, we lose money on a lot of the deals we agree to with clients (and many are way too smalltime). We'll actually lose big money just to add a client to our portfolio. Also, everything we do is rushed, with no planning.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Enable us to get up to date with the tools we use, pay us the going rate.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A dream company”

</title><pros>Pros – You will feel at home</pros>
<cons>Cons – Doesn't have a good cafeteria</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work in”

</title><pros>Pros – element k is very well processed company which gives the best quality of output to the customers</pros>
<cons>Cons – I didn't see any downside working with ek because if the work is completed on deliverable time, then no cons</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>A&M Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very good company to work with and a great atomoshpere”

</title><pros>Pros – Work EnvironmentEncouraging to celeberate all regional festivalsIntegrityTeam WorkEmployess Satisfaction</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of opporutniesLack of creativityfew senior management people</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work life balancePoised for growthGreat peopleGreat culture</pros>
<cons>Cons – Toomany Silos within the company</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Instructional Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great brand lost in the crowd in India”

</title><pros>Pros – Learning opportunitiesCasual and friendly atmosphereTalented peopleA lot of respect for your work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Absymmal pay (bad than a start -up KPO)Outdated tools and infrastructure</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK for Starter Job”

</title><pros>Pros – Good for 1st or 2nd job but not long term</pros>
<cons>Cons – People at headquarters can be difficult to get along with; too much work for one person to manage; no room for advancement; clients are jerks; weak benefits package</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK Company - promotions by popularity not skills or achievement”

</title><pros>Pros – Casual work environment, nice colleagues, good work home life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – promotions not based on achievementscompany is not well know or respectedembarrassing to work for a company that is Indian owned</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Promote from within based on achievements</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great co-workers/Pay Rate not so much”

</title><pros>Pros – Great co workers/mid leval mangementVery laid back place to work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company is always being soldOld Technogly</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop Selling the company</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Was a great place before they went to war with Skillsoft”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of virtual workers, so working from home was often an option.  Very smart, hard-working people.  Pretty decent all-hands meetings in terms of creativity.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Strategy changed from "help the client" to "get Skillsoft".  Gaining market share is important to any business, but wouldn't it be better over the long term if you did that by making your customers happy?</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There are long-term consequences to short-term behaviors.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-08-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor management”

</title><pros>Pros – Absolutely no reasons except that it is an establihed organization with some reputation in the market.... .... ... ... but the worst place on earth to work at</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very poor management, no concern for another person's life or time, no punctuality, lot of politics within the organization, worst place to work at</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire good HR who really have some experience and who can treat people like people and value others' time and life</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>