<name>John H. Stroger Jr. Hospital Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/John-H-Stroger-Jr-Hospital-Reviews-E120831.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I've great some great experience at the hospital with patients also staff whom have express appreicate for a job well”

</title><pros>Pros – Some of the best reason to be employee at stroger hospital is the benefits are good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some of downsides to working at stroger is that at election time mangement changes when someone new is elected into office.Which means there a turn off in most positions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – My advice to mangement would be  that when things are changing , get ideas from the staff that works in the areas of change . also to put everything in writing .</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Staff Registered Nurse (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Crazy work environment, but always something to do, never boring.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good attention to detail by management; great general learning environment.  Good benefits, friendly staff, and overall fun group of people who do what they can with little resources and a hectic environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not a lot of negatives here.  I guess traffic and parking are hard, and also, in the winter, it's a little harder to get around.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Nursing Assistant/Medical Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It  was excellent i gain all my working experience or most of it from working in their ambulatory clinics and hospitals”

</title><pros>Pros – I like working with diverse community and meeting people of different cultures</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is no cons excellent place to work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Licensed Practical Nurse (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Man!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great experience ...you learn and see a lot</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management sucks keep employees morale low</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Fire everyone and start over</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Endoscopy (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's like any other day job in the medical field”

</title><pros>Pros – After 25+ years of service at John Stroger, base pay doesn't get any higher than 89k. Over time is the only way to make more. But we get great benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Typical employee groups- lazy, hard-working, weird, funny. Nothing out of the ordinary</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Higher less lazy people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“frustrating...but rewarding”

</title><pros>Pros – This is an environment which really cares about the patients (clients).  This is also a place with great camaraderie</pros>
<cons>Cons – The infrastructure is neglected....the facility was brand new in 2002, and now appears 50 years old inside.Employee morale has dropped significantly with a slew of layoffs in the last few years.Advancement is nearly impossible without "connections"...merit is</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work conditions need to improveIntroduce MERIT promotions</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Physician (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tough work, but rewarding”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting patient mix, working with the underserved</pros>
<cons>Cons – Administration moves slowly, resources areImited</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Intern”

</title><pros>Pros – Good pay and benefits for employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – Employees need to be more respectful towards patients</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok”

</title><pros>Pros – Working for them is ok.  Management is ok.  Coworkers are fun.  Work life balance is not so bad.  Overall experience is good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hmmm enjoying it so far.  Work can be physically tiring at times.  Need to improve cleanliness though and probably hire more staff</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I think the management needs to review the way things are being managed in the hospital especially on cleanliness and efficiency.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>