<name>Moses H. Cone Memorial Hospital Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Moses-H-Cone-Memorial-Hospital-Reviews-E121381.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Admission Services Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Generous raises, great people to work for, recognizes accomplishments, easy to move up in the ladder...</pros>
<cons>Cons – Fast paced environment, managers put up with employees who should be fired</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Environmental Services (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of changes”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice people to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Policies changed often, leading to lots of room for error due to the confusion.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more consistent and support workers when they implement new changes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>RNII (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Registered Nurse ICU”

</title><pros>Pros – System is growing quickly which provides opportunities. Nice profit sharing program (2% - 5% of annual salary) on top of the 403B match.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Below average pay, dated equipment, punitive environment, below average compensation for area, drama, Drama, and DRAMA.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Realize that management is rarely as effective or as needed as they think they are. Quit spending small fortunes on hiring a never ending stream of new executive and then rehire all the RNs, CNAs & other essential staff your "efficiency company" (a contradiction in terms) decided you (read as your neglected patients and exhausted staff) could do without.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>