<name>William W. Backus Hospital Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/William-W-Backus-Hospital-Reviews-E121648.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>MIS (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“small hospital, now part of a bigger system”

</title><pros>Pros – good pay, average benefits, small town hospital getting bigger</pros>
<cons>Cons – Now part of HHC; lots of changes coming...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Certified Pharmacy Technician (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Shift differential, 403b retirement, flexible hours.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Off campus parking. Need to take shuttle in on first shift only</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work  yet need to stay away from negative "clicks"”

</title><pros>Pros – Strong goals and vision.  Trying to be cutting edge.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some old school negative clicks still exist</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tensions are high, patient care is excellent.”

</title><pros>Pros – Not sure on this one. ..maybe a paycheck, but even that isn't a definite.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I have often seen people let go and jobs eliminated, even when they have been there for years. New upper management is in place and they are building up the hospital ie, remodeling the E.R and various areas of the hospital, however, no additional employees being added. In fact, people are being let go and benefits and "perks" are being eliminated. Employees are so disappointed with current environment they are perusing a union.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Some of the perks that have been taken away need to be replaced. I don't think leadership realizes the extent of the low morale within the hospital. There is alot of frustration.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Now its just a job”

</title><pros>Pros – Will still have a few good people left to work WITH. Its a Paycheck. Its a Paycheck.........At least I have some control over my 403b</pros>
<cons>Cons – Taking away our benefits, reducing pay by removing holidays and setting up the holiday pay so you have to be a circus juggler to get it. Firing people left and right. Swipe police monitoring breaks. (god help if you forget something in your car) working as a nurse with 7 and 8 pts. Charge nurses with 7 pts. Running short-staffed all the time. A lot of  the good people are running for the door. At the  rate the rats are deserting.....the ships going down fast!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 1. Don't treat us like we are stupid. We recognize that the blog and town meettings were a ploy to gain our trust before you stabbed us. We see how you stir the "pot of doom" to make us believe that the healthcare bill will be the death of healthcare when in fact a large part of the completely non-paying pts will now at least have some insurance. Please realize that without us this hospital dies. I have NEVER liked unions but I do not see any choice in this matter. You made it "us against them", now you get to sit back and deal with the looming and probably inevitable union arriving..</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review of the organization”

</title><pros>Pros – This organization focuses on patients and can be an amazing place to work. The benefits are phenominal. 4 weeks vacation 2 weeks sick time, great medical and dental coverage compared to other employees and pretty competetive pay.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The lack of career advancement and promotion potential is disappointing. The lack of a involvement in the career development of staff.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – My advice would be to offer career tracks where people could develop and advance within the organization instead of having to go elsewhere.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Where has the family atmosphere gone?”

</title><pros>Pros – Convenient to travel to...Good pay....Fair benefits...My manager is the fairest and the best. Good hours,,,,Sharing of the holidays fair and adequate...</pros>
<cons>Cons – Since our new management has taken over patient care in my opinion has suffered tremendously. Mandatory cancellation of RN's has taken a toll on the staff, Morale is down terribly, You no longer can count on your hours being at 24 or 32. At any given time you will get the phone call that you are being canceled. Cafeteria food has deteriorated. Prices in our cafeteria are no ridiculous for poor quality of food and the hours are not conducive to staff members. They have cut our shift differential and our accural of paid time off. There is absolutely no recognition for longevity. Supervisors and upper management all received bonuses whereas the working staff received dramatic cuts in their pay..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your staff...We are trying to tell you something....Have the Board of Directors talk to the staff without Mr. Whitehead or karen Long being there...Talk to the staff that has shown their dedication and longevity...And answer the question honestly  Why did 50 RN's apply to Lawrence??</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>