<name>Leonard J. Chabert Medical Center (LSU) Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Leonard-J-Chabert-Medical-Center-LSU-Reviews-E121751.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-02</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cried every morning before work, then every afternoon after work.”

</title><pros>Pros – The brownies in the snack shop were great. There were a couple of people who were nice, but not many.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The people at Chabert were petty and ridiculous. The low pay evidently mostly attracts a certain kind of person that is typically low class, and prone to drama and stirring up trouble. It was difficult to just go to work and do my job because of the people. Chabert sucked to work at!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try listening to your first line supervisors, especially when their subordinates are the ones bullying them daily.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Registered Nurse (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good nurses should look elsewhere.”

</title><pros>Pros – Patients are great, residents interesting to work with. Relatively clean facility.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Administration and nurse managers make it impossible to do the right thing. Standard of care is often not followed throughout this facility. Very little communication between those 'above' and staff. Understaffed and often dangerous to patients and employees, in my opinion and experience. Staff physicians often not present as called for. Pay raises have been frozen for years. Threats of lay offs every fiscal year. Not family friendly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Needs total overhaul. Also some type of professional watchdog on the premises. Those in management be sent for further education on leadership roles, following OSHA guidelines, labor laws, etc. Needs much more nursing staff to adequately care for patients. Better communication with staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>