<name>NYU Langone Medical Center Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/NYU-Langone-Medical-Center-Reviews-E121521.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice location, ok research, ok training, nice people, overall good life experience but people tend not to stay. often academicians stay for 5 or so years and leave for a better position. unable to keep top talents</pros>
<cons>Cons – poor pay relative to cost of living and limited space. difficult to make comparisons to places with vast amounts of space but could do better with what is available</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the best people thorough better incentives</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Research Associate”

</title><pros>Pros – Great organization to work for. Facilities are state of the art and research departments are all centrally located in midtown manhattan (East). Really good benefits and work/life balance is just right. Great first job for anyone looking to start their career.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Research teams are very independent. That means that every PI runs their team in a different way and collaboration with other teams is limited and completely dependent on PI. That also means that your growth potential is also limited by the needs of team you work for.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – My specific team lacks someone that coaches and mentors RAs....we're all young and trying to learn the trade and go to grad school...but guidance is not helpful because advice is very general...there also needs to be more interest in the part of the PIs tom ensure the RAs are on track to accomplishing their goals...not just the PIs. Despite this, I think this is a good place for someone just starting out.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Research Fellow (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“POst”

</title><pros>Pros – Great infrastructure, great location, excellent research, and excellent medical services. Wonderful staff/employees at every level. Postdoctoral research program is one of the best in the country.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Reimbursements for expenses always take a very long time to come through for employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“NYU Medical Center Review”

</title><pros>Pros – developed great relationships with the staff</pros>
<cons>Cons – Was never hired for full time position</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Intern”

</title><pros>Pros – Reimbursed travel expense. Clear description of what is expected.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not paid. No immediate employment opportunities.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No”

</title><pros>Pros – Great name to add to your resume</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hard to move-up and very slow moving. Departments are very siloed. The environment can become stifling and it's hard to "move up". Not a conducive workplace for young professionals.after a few weeks, I became someone assistant and was asked to do tasks that were menial and just ridiculous at times. Some directors become micromanages because they feel like they have something to prove. It has been the worst experience for me.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Terrible culture for young professionals”

</title><pros>Pros – If you're looking to go back to school, working at NYU is great because they'll subsidize your education.</pros>
<cons>Cons – My experience working at NYU Medical was a true disappointment. I ended up working as an administrative assistant, even though that is not the job I was hired for. The culture is also so stifling and no one seemed to enjoy coming to work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make room for fun, hire more creative people, and be realistic with what you're looking for in the job search.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Administrative Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Benefits/Name recognition”

</title><pros>Pros – Normally work with great colleagues. Exceptional health benefits which is as to be expected.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most divisions offer little room to grow. You either have to leave or change departments. Work can be monotonous and not really intellectually stimulating. Pay is low for the industry.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take management classes</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The.Worst.Professional.Experience.Ever.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Reputation; Pleasant "Day-One" training staff.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of training and guidance for employees new to the Organization; Micromanagement; Some managers have tremendous egos, and go on extreme power trips.  As a Systems Analyst, I'm forced to wait until I attend Epic training in order to do anything beyond view data in the system, yet I'm constantly given assignments that I don't have access to complete....Yes, I typed that correctly: I'm given an assignment, which is more likely than not absolutely critical to someone (Yes, give a highly important project to the newest guy on the team...makes sense to me....), and then I have to nearly beg one of my colleagues to "help" me with it (read: do it for me since, as I said, I don't have the proper access)Mangers hide behind my title in order to avoid having to train and mentor me (I've heard on more than one occasion : "You're an Analyst, we shouldn't have to tell you A or B", when A or B is something that I'd only know having worked at the organization before, which I haven't!).When I voiced this frustration to my manager, his exact words were : "Yeah, it sucks not being able to do what you're hired to do. Sorry".Not to mention the blatant racism and favoritism....and the "we'll throw everything at you and see what sticks" (again, my manager's exact words) paradigm......And not to mention the vulgar email that was sent by a member of our group (supposedly jokingly, and accidentally) to our entire distribution list, and there not being an ounce of repercussion for the guy who sent it....Long story short: Worst. Professional.Experience.Ever.  I refuse to believe that after 10 years in my field, I've suddenly become incompetent........</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't hire from the outside if you're not willing to train.A department that restructures and re-hires yearly isn't indicative of a functioning department.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“NGO which is good for work visa sponsor”

</title><pros>Pros – NGO which is good for work visa sponsor</pros>
<cons>Cons – low salary hard to live in New York City</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worthwhile for 2 Types of Employees Only”

</title><pros>Pros – This is a small autonomous psychosocial research group within the much larger NYU Medical School (which, in turn, is a component of NYU Langone Medical Center). The larger institutions only affect this group in terms of policy (e.g., # of vacation days) and benefits (e.g., health insurance), all of which are good (except no maternity leave). Working within the research group per se can be valuable for either young people (such as those just out of college or 1-2 years post-college) who are looking to get some real world experience related to psychology, sociology or public health, or for individuals with advanced degrees (Ph.Ds, M.Ds, etc.) who want to establish themselves in academia, e.g., eventually becoming a Co-Principal Investigator on an NIH grant. In addition, group members are generally supportive of and helpful towards one and other.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you don't fall into one of the above-named categories (i.e., just starting your career or holding an advanced degree), beware! There's a tacit 2- or 3- tiered system and, if you don't fall into the upper categories, you'll be grossly undervalued, mistreated, and underpaid regardless of your productivity. There's very, very restricted room for growth (again, unless you have a Ph.D., M.D., etc.) so at most one should spend 2-3 years here and then take your experience and move on! Also, the pay is not good compared to many private sector jobs, and all of government-sponsored research has been hard hit by the sequestration, resulting in slashed budgets and a drastic reduction of scientific grant awards. Finally, the boss is a hardcore workaholic and tends to impose unreasonable deadlines.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value your employees and listen to what they have to say.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to be involved in research”

</title><pros>Pros – Typical entry level research job. Overall, great experience. I enjoyed working with my colleagues. Benefits were good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No growth. Management jobs were rare.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people, flat IT organization, but weak organization structure and leadership”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart people, great knowledge.  Unique environment, highly visible and challenging.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of investment in their people - many contractors working hard, while employees not being challenged to do a better job.  Resources are thin and some key people are under a lot of pressure.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – IT structure lacks maturity and leadership - employees are disjointed and need a cohesive direction and strong leader to give them focus.  Leaders need to create a large team that works together - many strong ideas prevent achieving the greater goal.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Fellow (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor management, little chance of advancement for academics and downright dangerous environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Good PhD and postdoctoral associations</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor management: No communication, bloated and highly dysfunctional administration that is invisible in actual day-to-day management. Utter waste of ressources on prestige projects at the expense of hard-working employees.Little change of advancement for academics: Entry at postdoctoral level means no further advancement. No effort to let anyone onto tenure ladder as higher positions are exclusively filled by outside recruitement.Dangerous environment: Much ado about compliance with OSHA, patient privacy but actual working environment is old, dangerous and even grave problems such as black mould infestations are simply ignored.The complete dysfunction of the entire organization was plain during Superstorm Sandy and in the weeks and months that followed.I was happy to leave.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would suggest replacing the entire management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>EPIC Credentialed Trainer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Good Epic Credentialing Opportunity”

</title><pros>Pros – The healthcare professional trainees at NYU Langone were polite and attentive as a rule, and the pay was excellent.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Problems with a lack of communication, a lack of oversight, and unapologetic nepotism on Epic team.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More oversight of Epic teams is needed to curb unprofessional behaviors that interfere with learning and training. Competition between trainers was allowed to devolve into discriminatory bullying and obstruction of classes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“no opportunity to get funded”

</title><pros>Pros – good name recognition. good location.</pros>
<cons>Cons – professor has no funding. equipment and research are kinda old</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – na</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Environmental Health & Safety Specialist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall, NYULMC is a good place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – The organization does a good job of providing perks for their employees. While there aren't any bonuses, they provide discounts for health clubs, wellness programs, commuter shuttle and other benefits to staff. They also are big on work life balance which is a plus.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The structure/culture within the department needs work. The "buddy" system they have is not set up correctly and needs to be redone. This system along with the "unwritten" rules are very ingrained in the office culture and can be difficult for new staff to adapt to. Management is very hands off and inaccessible to new staff. Manager and some co-workers were rude and unprofessional.The hardest parts of the job for me was trying to fit in with the office culture, working under a manipulative co-worker and keeping up with the large workload.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I think management should take the time to interact with new staff. Provide feedback in a productive and kind manner directly. Discuss the office culture with new staff to avoid any misunderstandings.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Researchers are top, administration is not.”

</title><pros>Pros – The researchers are incredible and what they are doing is phenonimal. Being around them and forming relationships with them is invalueable.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The administration (department administrators, sponsored programs office, finance) is filled with incompetent people who play favorites and look out for each other. Of course there are a few great exceptions without whom the researchers would probably lose their minds, but overall this is no way to best manage research administration.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop being selfish. Treat your best faculty and staff well.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Scheduler/Dispatcher for Language Access Service”

</title><pros>Pros – Great environment, encouraging team. Plenty of opportunity for personal growth and experience in a well known, fast growing hospital.</pros>
<cons>Cons – None that I can think of.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Okay place to work. Limited opportunities”

</title><pros>Pros – Competent colleagues. Good work life balance. Good benefits and competitive pay. Decent offices. Not a bad place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bureaucracy, politics. Management and senior management don't appear to be that competent. Only way to move up appears to be a lot of brown nosing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire managers that actually know what they are doing instead of people that can BS their way past you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great”

</title><pros>Pros – Great company to work for . everyone is kind.</pros>
<cons>Cons – amazing place to work .love it</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – keep it up :)</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Assistant Professor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“overall good experience”

</title><pros>Pros – good benefit, pleasant work environment, high quality of science</pros>
<cons>Cons – limited career opportunities for non tenure track scientist</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – increase the option of staying as scientist in the non tenure track</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Research Fellow (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to advance career in science”

</title><pros>Pros – Great research facilities, collaboration opportunities, lots of career resoures and social activities for postdocs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – PI controls everything, the whole experience might be very different depending on the lab, talk to lab members before joining a lab.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Doing great work especially after Sandy</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Healthcare IT (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bad IT department experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Advanced systems. Lots of new things to learn. Large and well known organization.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management encourages snitching. Really ill atmosphere in the team. Everyone tries to set each other up. Management denied vacation, asked to work unpaid overtime extensive hours, lied on the evaluation review, discriminated. Union employees are slacking putting additional workload on non-union employees.  Pay is way lower than anywhere else in the industry. Working space is really small in a molded basement. Employee rotation is very high so there is always someone new and in training while the rest of the team is carrying workload.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Technician (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Friendly environment to work at but lack of advancment”

</title><pros>Pros – Provide good vacations, good insurance and most people are friendly and helpful. A lot of great researchers and doctors.</pros>
<cons>Cons – poor departmental administration/ management. Less flexibility.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management should try to understand the needs of researchers and to help them instead of creating more problems.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>FGP Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Depends on which department you are in...”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent benefits, rewards employees working there for many years</pros>
<cons>Cons – Feels more like a corporation than a hospital, sometimes feels like numbers are more important than human beings, but it depends on the department as I have many friends who are happy with their positions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – My time at NYU Langone made me realize that the medical center was largely reactive rather than proactive, solving known problems only when a formal complaint is lodged.  Solving the problem as they are made aware of would enable smoother operations.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Environmental Health and Safety Specialist, I (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great environment, flexible employer”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible, trust employees to manage themselves, educational opportunities plentiful</pros>
<cons>Cons – Below average salary, poor communication between departments</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Research Scientist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Neutral experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent working relationships with people that care to make a difference.Support staff efforts to meet needs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not enough specific knowledge on administrative issues.Turn around time is fairly dismal.Flip-flopping leaders.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Too many cooks in the kitchen.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Would not recommend working here - horrible experience with management/HR”

</title><pros>Pros – The hospital is well known.</pros>
<cons>Cons – HR and management do not have anything organized and together. From day one there were mistakes with my offer, which took forever to come through - it took so long, my manage thought I was setting a start date and I had to let her know that I hadn't even gotten the paperwork from HR yet despite being told I had an offer. Then when I got the paperwork it was wrong. I was also very underpaid compared to similar institutions/positions, and was told there was no room for adjustment. Then for the whole year I was there I was never given a phone, computer, or desk - and I was in a position where I was supposed to see patients in a private space. When I left they cancelled my prescription coverage the month before I left and didn't tell me - noone in HR gave me any information about the leaving process at all.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>EPIC Credentialed Trainer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A worthwhile experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – The work location is very accessible by mass transportation.The ability to be very flexible.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No answer provided relating to this.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to communicate with the employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Radiology IT Support (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hospital IT”

</title><pros>Pros – The hospital offers great pay and benefits to new employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company culture is "dog eat dog". The members of the group are self serving and unwilling to share knowledge. They are rude and snide with each other and with the hospital staff. It is a thankless, in hospitable environment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You will get out of your staff what you give to your staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Office Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Learning experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice people, opportunity to learn and grow professionally</pros>
<cons>Cons – The upper management doesn't seem to care about the people doing all the work, I never see them.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Director, Development (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This is  a solid institution on a rapid upward swing in both performance and reputation.”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart, motivated people, high level of integrity; institution moving upward rapidly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can be constrained by bureaucracy and divisional turf wars led by highly competent people with enormous egos.  Needs extra effort and creativity to break through at times, but not impossible.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue focusing on retaining top talent.  Invest in good people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Better opportunity and excellent work environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Compensation range is good and good Mantegna system.</pros>
<cons>Cons – its not an e verified employer, so need sponsorship for international applicant.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Epic Clinical Systems Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overworked Clinical Systems Analyst”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits - I like that NYU gave employees 8 % for their retirement account in addition to the employee contributionGood people who work at the medical center</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too many politicsDifferent departments in IT have different rulesTop heavyCommunication is lackingSenior managemnt moves people up without the necessary skills or experienceHad 4 managers/directors in 2 yearsPeople on my team were downright meanNo upward mobility in careerNo work life balance - I worked 80 hours in 1 week and my boss did not even bother to give me a day off</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't promote people who do not have management skills to be a managerI feel in IT, people who truly deserved to be promoted were passed on by other inexperienced people.  I have been at NYU for 6 years and I saw it going downhill.  Isn't a place suppose to improve over time?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fantastic work environment, great healthcare benefits”

</title><pros>Pros – As far as academic institutions go, this is an extremely functional one. Yes, there are arcane things, but all in all the community was great, the teams were interactive, and the opportunities for cross-education and exposure were good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – like other academic institutes things are not always efficient.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cold Corporate Soulless Culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Doctors.  Maybe working at the School is a better, more professional environment?</pros>
<cons>Cons – Please talk with former employees about NYUMC.  You'll hear the same statements about how the employees are treated by management  -- yelled at publicly, coworkers suddenly terminated -- how the NYUMC culture is not one of team building and collaboration.  Working there is a grim experience.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – When they were closed by the hurricane, maybe it would have been best to remain closed and just keep the school open?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Research Fellow (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall a positive environment”

</title><pros>Pros – In general, many colleagues are very nice to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Payroll and benefit personnel can sometimes be frustrating to deal with;Post-doc salary can be higher</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Some of the payroll and benefit staffs could perhaps treat post-doctoral fellows in a more courteous manner</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>HPLC Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Summer intern, learned a lot.”

</title><pros>Pros – Lab work, Fun learning environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Monotony of work inside a small lab.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Would be a great place if not for politics”

</title><pros>Pros – Great PIs, good health benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – Politics where high management (dean, vice-dean, directors) promote themselves and those known to them; no respect for employees; no promotion expectation for the little guy.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire better management not those who believe they are better than everybody else. Hire management who know what they are doing, who respect their peers, who respect the PIs and employees under them.  Respect the people who work hard for the better of the institution!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Organization Crushed By Incompetent Middle Managers”

</title><pros>Pros – Mission-driven, patient care focus, exceptional medical staff who are at the top of their field.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Secretive and incompetent middle management, little-to-no growth opportunities, unnecessary politicking at all levels, zero mentorship, witch-hunting environment, constant mountains out of molehills hinders progress of projects, development of staff, and overall effectiveness.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get a clue. Talk to your staff!!!  Mentor junior staff instead of seeing them as a threat.  Eliminate the internal silos so that you increase transparency. Treat people as you would want to be treated.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Administrative Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Could use some improvements...”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits- starts with 4 week vacation, great dental and health care options. They do give recognition to employees monthly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Have been there for 6 years with no raise or chance to be promoted (until recently.. but it is so bureaucratic that it will take months to approve this!). Not organized- so when I try to better the department I work in- or get this promotion- there are too many barriers for anything to move quickly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve the hospital for patients- the Hospital for Joint Diseases needs to go under renovations now! Also the departments have to beg to make small improvements- there needs to be more clarity on communications throughout the entire Center.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Web Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall a good place to work, needs to focus on creating the same cross departmental policies for fairness”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay in line with average, if you self advocate for a higher salary when you interview for the job they will consider it. I did and was successful.Good health benefits, as you'd expect working for a medical center.Automatic 3.5% yearly raises (provided you aren't written up, etc)  6% company match to your 401k or 403b after 6 month probationary period. Employee must contribute 3% to get the match, which isn't very much to ask.HR is very good about providing protections so people cant be fired off-hand, just because a boss dosen't like the way you look, etc.Get to work with very intelligent people who are mostly niceYou can get full tuition reimbursement for classes related to your position at the med center, if the classes are unrelated, i believe its 80% reimbursement.  You do pay taxes on the classes though as the IRS treats it as a gift.You get to have the name recognition of having NYU School of Medicine/NYU Medical Center on your resume</pros>
<cons>Cons – Each Department Chair basically sets the tone and culture of each department, as well as some rules, for example whether telecommuting is allowed or not, dress code, etc.  So the day to day work environment could be very different from employee to employee. For new employees this can make it hard to gauge what you might be getting into. I happen to work for someone who is ok, sometimes (not all) he can be a little manic and formal which tends to make employees anxious, and he enforces a no jeans/shorts/bare arms dress code.  This isn't unreasonable, but I am envious of a friend of mine who does the same job I do in a different dept, who is allowed to dress more comfortably and casually.  Particularly as in our position we dont really interface with the public very much, such as patients or donors.If you leave the institution before 3 years, you are not able to keep what NYU has contributed to your 401k/403b.The other con is the location.  You either pay ALOT in rent to live nearby, or you are forced to commute in and out of lower manhattan.  You do get a pretax commuter benefit but it only covers about half the cost.This is a very busy place with tons always going on and to keep track of, and if you are not a doctor, its likely you will find yourself consistently assigned with additional work thats not in your job description.Other than a one year review after hire, in my dept (again see my note about Chair setting culture) employees aren't given a review unless they ask for it. I suppose this is a good thing if you are a slacker, but for others it denies us an opportunity to talk about various (non-urgent) issues we might have, without having to start an awkward conversation.In speaking with certain people, I have learned that some employees in my dept have gotten 6 month bonuses and others have not, just because the people who received it asked for it. Even though the employees in question were the same quality and did the same quality work. This is unfair.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It would be great if the medical center enforced a center wide policy of allowing telecommuting one day a week for employees (there could be criteria so people would have to become eligible for this, but I think it would be a great way to reward faithful, good employees) and not leave things like that and dress code up to individual depts.If people are consistently assigned a task outside of their job description, and it becomes part of their job, give them a raise beyond the 3.5%The issue of who should receive bonuses should definitly be a set cross-departmental policy. If someone didn't earn it thats fine, but if you are going to offer it at all, it should be a clear set policy with eligibility criteria, not some phantom "does it, or does it not exist" thing thats whispered about. If I receive no complaints about my work, it makes me feel like crap when my friend/coworker, excited about receiving her bonus, asks me if I got mine (that i didn't even know existed) when I didn't get it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent place to learn, work and live healthy.”

</title><pros>Pros – Best education and medical care in NYC. On par benefits which gives full satisfaction as a full time employee. Convenient place to all public transportation in NYC.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much reliant on vendors. Management needs to think outside of box and take responsibility and fix broken system. Improve employee morale.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing great work. Think independently and understand industry trends.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome place to work. Very professional, lots of perks”

</title><pros>Pros – Very professional staff. on the unit in which I worked. There was never the telltale type gossip and backbiting that you witness in other Hospitals. It was NOT A hostile work environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 8 hr shifts. Difficult in a city with many challenges related to commuting.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Scientist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Highly bureaucratic”

</title><pros>Pros – Health and retirement benefits are excellent</pros>
<cons>Cons – Highly bureaucratic and unprofessional atmosphere.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more professional</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>EPIC Credentialed Trainer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Mismanagement of resources and lack of staff appreciation”

</title><pros>Pros – -Working for a world famous institution</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Schedule was constantly changing-Hardwork was not appreciated-Major communication problems</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – -Communicate better with staff</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Researcher”

</title><pros>Pros – Good facilities in general. I like it</pros>
<cons>Cons – Overall pretty good. Sometimes the tasks are not that clear.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more organized with student interns</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Frustrating”

</title><pros>Pros – The coworkers were great and the location was nice</pros>
<cons>Cons – The work, the supervisors/management, the lack of training (System, Industry, and basic job duties)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay attention to your employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Intern”

</title><pros>Pros – -Free lunches from pharmaceutical companies from time to time-Very flexible working hours-Low stress job-Friendly Environment-Competitive Pay</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is not a lot of challenges to the job. It can get repetitive and boring. Also lack of direct communication can be a hassle.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Physical Therapist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tiring, it hurts my hands, but It's worth it, and easy.”

</title><pros>Pros – The people there are nice. Although I rarely see them.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's noisy there. nothing else....</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do whatever you want.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Fellow (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good learning experience as an intern but no advancement to paid position”

</title><pros>Pros – Great experience learning how to use tools and technologies and helping the doctors and staff treat patients and do research. The hospital supports volunteers with cafeteria discounts and sometimes branded merch (a white lab coat with my name!) which was very helpful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – My position was unpaid as an intern and I didn't have a paid offer or much room for advancement. Even free NYU tuition, which is an amazing perk of actually working there, wasn't available to me as an intern.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Department Administrator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Mixed Bag”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent benefits. Tremendous growth. New state of the art space.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Leadership disconnected from employees. No real career path.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Too big for its own good”

</title><pros>Pros – Salary is ok. Paid tuition remission for graduate school.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Worked insane hours with little thanks. Many workers have a "that's not my job" policy. Departments don't work together. Everyone is miserable and can't wait to get out.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employee satisfaction leads to retention. You keep losing the good ones!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Research Fellow (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“pleasant and fruitful”

</title><pros>Pros – friendly and open academic atmosphere. sponsors H1B.</pros>
<cons>Cons – performance of different labs varies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Child Psychiatry Fellow (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“NYU Langone/Bellevue Hospital Center is a great place to train for psychiatry.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great supervision.  Knowledgeable attendings that are well known for their work and research.  Very well respected as well as approachable.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can be demanding, with heavy call schedule and high patient loads.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – n/a</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“NOT THE PLACE TO BE IN IT UNLESS YOU WANT TO RETIRE”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent PayHealth BenefitsflexibilityVacation daysthe people</pros>
<cons>Cons – No career pathPromotion is based on who you know, not what you knowArrogant and clueless leadershipAge discrimination: Unless you are a senior, don't expect to be promoted to manager or anything above.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Making NYU a world class institution starts with employees. Stop hiring executives when the work ratio between employees is so disproportional.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>EPIC Credentialed Trainer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Contract Employees are Human Beings Too!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – NYULMC is definitely trying to position their institution to give NYPresbyterian a run for the #1 hospital spot in NY.  Their endeavor to bring EPIC online in December 2012 for all its clinical departments is ambitious and worth giving acknowledgement.NYULMC has great discounts which Contract/Temp employee can use, although they are not able to access the standard benefits of medical/dental/tuition etc...</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unfortunately, the EPIC / IT department leaves much to be desired in treating contract/temp employees as human beings.  First, being contract means you do not have benefits.  It does not mean you are not protected under Federal laws & State regulations for EEO/AA.  If a F/T employee receives accommodations for disabilities, age, ESL, and religion -- SO DO YOUR contract/temp employees.The EPIC Dept. is not structured to credential and train employees who are protected by regulations, its is simply: If you cannot learn our curriculum as it is written, then you are fired.  It is disgusting to have a CT training manual which states "how respectful you should treat adult learners" but a curriculum to credential trainers that does not reflect this or a live training course/manual that does not accommodate these protected groups.There is anything worse than a person/group which documents all of their "MISSION & VALUES" in a 60+ page packet and then systematically violates each page over a 10 week period.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Dear Dr. Grossman, until you remove these BAD APPLES passing as PT's and their senior leaders, who systemically violate the protected rights of individuals -- your will fail in December...and worse yet, be sued for discrimination.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not the best medical center to work at”

</title><pros>Pros – NYU boasts some of the best facilities in New York. It has a lot of assets and locations around the city. The food at the medical center is decent.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is no sense of community, there are barely any perks for employees, and the system of logging hours makes it feel like being in a jail - (thumb prints, really?!). Overall, enjoyed working in the lab because my PI was great, but the medical center itself was not a good place to be.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Realize that your employees are people and give them some perks. NYULMC acts like more of a business than any other health care center I have ever seen.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Program Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Comme ci , comme ca”

</title><pros>Pros – varied environment, access to expert in basic sciences and clinical sciences in varied area.Great benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of support and integration with  general administration. HR not useful.Direct supervisor incompetent and hostile.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Psychologist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“NYU Psychologist”

</title><pros>Pros – Stimulating and professional work environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Cons of working in a large institution -  bureaucratic challanges</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Data Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great benefits, pay subpar”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits, health insurance, etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management can be disorganized. Employees are 50/50 either really nice or really gossipy/catty. Salary is lower than competing jobs for same skills</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work on organization, employee satisfaction, speed with which tasks get completed (especially MCIT)</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great hospital--becoming more business-like every day. Great leadership and excellent benefits.”

</title><pros>Pros – Visionary dean/CEO has led tremendous expansion, undergoing transformation to world-class fully integrated academic medical center.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Could use more transparency on reporting relationships. Lack of org-charts is very frustrating. Some of the red tape and processes are very backward but overall middle-of-the-road for a legacy hospital and improving every day.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Set up an innovation office that is multidisciplinary to explore new business areas, new research fields, new partnerships. You'll be surprised what your lowest level managers and middle managers could assist with, in achieving greater opportunity generation.  Technology transfer and licencing along with the NYU main campus around novel therapies and drugs could also prove itself as a new revenue stream.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great medical institution, lousy place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits, great location, great place to stay if you are close to your retirement</pros>
<cons>Cons – No career path, no professional development, no mentoring, blatant favoritism, opaque inefficient management, at least in support departments. Sometimes unethical practices take place.You will come here with the same set of skills as you will leave with, without acquiring any new knowledge, which, by the time when you want to leave will be completely obsolete. In other words, complete professional/intellectual stagnation.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – CFO and Senior Management are aware of the problems, and are working to fix them, but the inertia is humongous, it will take a good decade to bring the institution out of its current amorphous state, the institution can go belly up well before it happens</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Training Fellow (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Blah and more blah is all I really have to say.”

</title><pros>Pros – They have frequent happy hours, which is relatively nice when the rest of time time you are worked to the bone and beating yourself up for the sake of science.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's in midtown and impossible to commute to.  One alternative is to actually live in the building that you work in (or across the street).  But then, there is a good chance that you will have years of your life shaved off in work hours.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice place to work, but seems to have communication issues in administrative departments.”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice environment. Good benefits. Overall enjoyable and pleasant place to work. Mostly I work in the research building, which is beautiful. People are friendlier here than I have seen previously.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Administrative services are a pain to deal with, including HR, finance services, and IT. Dealing with these types of departments usually results in a headache and dissatisfaction.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is a great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – They offer great benefits for their employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – The salary is not great</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Collaborative and Professional”

</title><pros>Pros – Most of the people here are smart and know what the situation is.  They sincerely try to do the right thing and work to help each other</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are some management hurdles that need to be addressed to make it a truly world class organization.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working for NYU Radiology has become difficult  these past few years due to the new Managerial Staff.”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits, some co-workers, and the networking opportunities within the medical field are some good reasons to work at NYULMC.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unless you're a doctor, nurse, medical staff, or head position within a dept. you pretty much mean nothing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – This review is solely based on my experience in my department, not NYULMC as a whole.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not enough structure to manage performance or build career path”

</title><pros>Pros – Can be very good place to start a career in healthcare as there are opportunities to transfer across different areas often. For the right person who is capable, I have seen people who were able to climb the ladder.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are too many people who are not willing to work together to achieve results, and lack of structure, support, or direction from management at times. There is also rampant favortism.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management is not interested enough in the success of their employees or in promoting based on merit.  They need to work on fostering collegiality among the community.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good teamwork”

</title><pros>Pros – Good opportunities for education and advancement</pros>
<cons>Cons – Building is kind of old and dark, compared to some area hospitals. Could use a facelift.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great hospital but they need to do more to recognize and value their staff.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to learnAmazing colleaguesA great hospital that really focuses on patient care</pros>
<cons>Cons – Employees treated as dispensablemicro managementlittle communication from senior managementsenior team is invisible to most staffno path for professional developmentculture of criticismlow morale is rampant</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Recognize that an organization is comprised of the people who work there and invest in staff and staff development.  Be consistent in your messaging and walk the talk.  Foster a culture of respect.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't get your hopes up for fair promotions even if you deserve them, but the benefits are ahh-mazing.”

</title><pros>Pros – 5 weeks vacation; mostly 9-5; tution remission; part of huge team (~80 people) which can be inspiring as there are many people to learn from; raising money for really impressive medical programs, institutes, and physicians that make huge impact.</pros>
<cons>Cons – VP has control/trust issues that prevent her from entrusting her senior team to make decisions and in turn, trust those on their individual teams. This creates an environment where people feel second guessed and unable to own their work fully which makes people miserable.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start trusting those who you hire -- if you don't trust them, don't hire them. And if they trust those they manage, then trust them on it. Say hello when you see your employees in the hallway. Nothing has to be so serious -- we raise money for brain surgery, not perform it. if you inspired those around you in small ways, everyone would feel more motivated and less reprimanded...and then work way harder consequently.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible, very stressful dealing with a manager that has more say so than the doctor”

</title><pros>Pros – Great administrative staff, great patients</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hippocratic Oath is not practiced here. If you practice good ethics, this is not the place for you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Maybe if you respected your staff members, they would respect you in return.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Development Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor leadership support and inconsistent promotion practices”

</title><pros>Pros – Tuition remission and other benefits are substantial and varied to meet the needs of all employees. Facilities improvements throughout the medical center are impressive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Leadership support is lacking in many aspects, clear vision and direction is not provided.  Feedback and performance reviews are ineffective.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Middle and upper management would benefit from training on how to support their staff appropriately and communicate effectively.  Clear promotion paths should be outlined and communicated.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's a Job”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits and vacation time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – To climb the ladder, you must know people.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Recognize when you have a beyond and above employee.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall a nice place to work with lots of opportunities for movement.”

</title><pros>Pros – benefits, location, 403B match, lots of seminars and interesting lectures</pros>
<cons>Cons – bureaucratic, health test requirements, slow to change way things are done, opaque leadership style, staff infrastructure is not as fully developed as it could be which leads to people doing the work of multiple jobs</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give HR more flexibility in allowing for raises/promotions within departments/positions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Program Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unfortunate lack of promotion structure.”

</title><pros>Pros – Large urban hospital center located in New York City.Interesting patient exposure.Currently expanding the local food options.Unlimited sick days</pros>
<cons>Cons – Complete lack of promotion and/or bonus structure.Large divide between clinical and support staff.Lack of clarity regarding job description.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Incorporate an incentivized bonus structure, do away with Enterprise Connect, do away with excess accounts payable paperwork.Utiliz p-card system for business trips.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-22</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Graduate Student (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is a wonderful place to learn, work and live.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great housing options, helpful staff</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some research advisors expect you to work 24-7.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more outreach events</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“so far so good”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a non profit orgnization so I don't have to worry about the economic impact of the recession. Also it's a well respected company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay scale might not as good as the Wall Street companies.  Bonus is not much or none at all.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The internal process is too difficult sometimes.  Some departments are not doing a good job and seem never try to improve.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible”

</title><pros>Pros – The Name of the insitiution will look good in your resume</pros>
<cons>Cons – Steals vacation time away from youDecreased their benefitsMake it hard for you to advanceToo much office politicsLow competitive pay</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – In order to transfer to another dept, you are requred to give in your performance evaluation. I had a good review in my performance evaluation, however my boss won't give me a copy. So how can i advance or transfer? Your system needs to change.You need to find a way to filter out your management. Specifically upper management. you treat the place like a corporation. You need to care about people and employee. Pay better too.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Information Technology (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's Getting There”

</title><pros>Pros – great work life balancegreat benefits packagegreat work varietyJust implementing policies like ITIL so you can help shape things</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low competitive salaryLack of job definition or advancement pathsHighly babied user populationCan be very political at times</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No advice to management. It seems like they are on the correct path to making it a world class institution</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tremendous Improvements Made, More Expected to Follow”

</title><pros>Pros – The Dean and CEO Bob Grossman is making enormous changes, most of them very good. Some of the old guard is resistant to change, which can account for much fo the grumbling. Grossman is ever-present, very positive, a talented physician, and an extraordinary fundraiser. He has spent the last three-plus years clearing out dead wood and attracting new talent. This is a very exciting place to work. How many Medical Centers have recieved four $100 million+ gifts from donors in such a short time span: none.</pros>
<cons>Cons – My con is more of a personal one.  If I worked for a different senior manager, I would be having a much better experience. My manager rewards mediocrity and is fearful of anyone who has as much if not more intelligence and experience than she. Enough about that. The big con for me is the cost of health care for those who pick the out-of-network plan. Unless you have a catastrophic event, you will pay for most of any out-of-network care.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The HR department staff has some very poor communicators. Example: I was told, "You can change your benefits options in October."  I tried to change my benefit options on the website, and could not. I go to HR.  Same person says, "I told you you could change your options in October, but I did not tell you what day; you should have checked back with me on the day."  Priceless, really, as the person never specified it would be on specific day. She told me I was "wrong."   Not the first time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“NYU is a great foot in the door”

</title><pros>Pros – They offer competitive salaries, flexible workshifts, and opportunities for advancement</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes the workload is overwhelming especially if you are the individual in that position for the entire department. Sometimes you are asked to do things that is not in your job description.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – In my opinion, the advice would be to have some stability. There's a lot of middle management positions where the individuals are not there longer than 2 yrs cap.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Attending Physician (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stay Away”

</title><pros>Pros – reputation of the institution is good</pros>
<cons>Cons – very poor communication. no feedback. poor delineation of responsibilities and poor command structure</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Clear hierarchies and  command structures should be defined. Decrease the bureucracy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“HR needs an intervention”

</title><pros>Pros – No internal equity, Employee Relations doesn't appropriately handle internal issues that arise within HR</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor management, probably because there was no one to perform management functions</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – look at your leadership and the satisfaction of their employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Experience for a Future in Neuroscience”

</title><pros>Pros – Everybody works together as a team, from the principal investigator to the lab assistants; in fact, everybody often goes out together on Fridays to cement those relationships.  People generally respect and support each other, working hard to make sure that research has been completed with due diligence.  I feel that primarily, effective communication is the best feature of working here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A volunteer's pay (0), but that's to be expected.  There's some drama in the office, though that can be entertaining so long as you're not involved.  People work extremely long hours to complete projects, but this is of course academia.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make sure that the lowest people on the totem pole, namely the lab assistants, get coddled a little bit more, especially at the beginning of their employment; adjusting to a rigorous research schedule can be difficult.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bureaucratic Institution”

</title><pros>Pros – The benefits package is great.5 weeks of vacation is extremely tempting.Nice family oriented group.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too bureaucratic...takes 10X longer to get things done because of all the red tape you must pass through before decisions are made.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Micro-management has a counter effect on employees...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bad employee treatment”

</title><pros>Pros – Salary and benefits are good for experts</pros>
<cons>Cons – Senior management in IT division recognizes people even under performer who had stayed for long years then meritorious candidates who joined recently. Hiring and firing happens very frequently. I would suggest people to think thousand times before making a career move to NYUMC IT division.Independent thinking, best practices and recognition are not welcome. You have to think alike or keep quite.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No use. Since senior management had to be entirely changed in IT division and new leadership team required at various levels</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-10-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“NYU housing is horrible! For the price I could get something else in New York”

</title><pros>Pros – SeminarsGood access to in network doctorsBasic research and clinical research collaborations</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too big for it's own goodNot enough housing for staffLack of food choices around Murray HillFar from Subway</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop testing the fire alarm</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-11-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Management (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It could be great for you at NYU Langone Medical Center!”

</title><pros>Pros – There are a variety of fields and career paths persons can follow.  Jobs are not limited to health care or research. If one chooses to change careers they need not apply outside the company. The company offers employees a career track to advance their careers. Senior management keeps the community well informed of the ongoings of the organization and employees seem to have a passion about the company</pros>
<cons>Cons – The health coverage and tuition reimbursement are not comparable to other reputable organizations in the area. Employees pay pay too much out of pocket expenses for their health coverage and tuition reimbursement is limited to secondary degree programs at NYU only.  Management is still a very top-down approach with males dominating the senior level positions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Better recognition programs and incentives for employees are necessary to retain employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“the analogy is : you get what you pay for”

</title><pros>Pros – tuition benefits for the employee and the employee's kidshealth insurance and dental insurance is not badaccess to the hospital facilities if you are on a PPO or even HMOjob stability - won't get affected by the financial crisis .. i hope.</pros>
<cons>Cons – average pay is lowernot sure if this is applicable to all departments; but growth is extremely slowpay hikes are very smallthe benefits department is extremely ignorant.a lot of information that needs to be forwarded by the HR and benefits department to all the employees is not done in a correct manner and/or on a regular basis.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – employees don't ask the world out of you. Please pay some basic attention to employee needs.every once in a while (read atleast once in a quarter ) ... senior management should have the decency to communicate directly with lower level employees...i sometimes walk by the head of my department and feel like she has never even noticed me... and we aren't a big group.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great technology.... counterproductive work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – First, it's a great research hospital with lots of collaborations with industry which help to bring cutting edge technology to the center. Industry research scientist are also placed at the center and are supposed to be willing to help you complete your research. There is supposed to be a symbiotic relationship... the medical researchers help the industry representatives with feed back about the product to make the technology better and techniques developed on industry technology can be controlled be industry so they remain cutting edge. The medical center benefits b/c they are supposed to receive the newest upgrades and new products first. Industry representatives are also supposed to help researchers achieve their research goals. Instead of the medical researchers wasting their time fighting the technology to get what they want to achieve, they are supposed to be able to easily implement their ideas. If this symbiosis worked the way it should in theory it would be a great environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No one wants to help each other. They just run their experiments and if they overcome a problem that might help someone else they keep it to themselves. Researchers often hide data and information from each other. The workplace shouldn't be a place to hang out but people should atleast get along professionally rather than trying to stab each other in the back. Senior researchers that have been at the institution for a while don't look to improve the career of grad students and post docs. Instead they look at them as work horses that must work themselves to death for the benefit of the senior researchers with nothing in return.This makes for an extremely hostile environment where research is hampered by egos and sometimes corruption. Industry reps are trying to produce products while attempting to help researchers. They are under stress and avoid helping researchers as much as possible. Senior researchers get the most attention b/c they have industry connections that can get representatives fired. I have never worked in a place where people waste them time with back handed comments as much as this place.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Encourage more collaboration and reward employees when they do collaborate successfully. Foster poc and grad students since they are ones pushing the work forward. Nourish them... senior researcher didn't come out of the womb in that position.. they were fostered by someone along the line who helped them achieve the position they are in today.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice environment but not really a community”

</title><pros>Pros – I'm a native New Yorker so I enjoy the fast-pace work environment.  You greet many people throughout the day but by the next day, you forget who they are.  The building is beautiful.  You get along fine with your employees.  Speaking to your supervisor, depending on who they are, can get intimidating.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too many upper levels of management.  If you want something to be fixed, you have to go through various departments and people.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Could be a little more organized.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Could be worse”

</title><pros>Pros – NYULMC is an interesting place to work - but definitely not meant for everyone.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too many things in the political environment prevent the job from being done correctly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on the needs of the client/patient instead of the egos of other employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Down but not out!”

</title><pros>Pros – Like all jobs, you get out what you put in. NYU Langone Medical Center has an array of job functions to choose from. Sometimes within the same department. You can be at NYU for 20 years and have different jobs within different departments.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unfortunately there are some departments where you can advancement is limited.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experiences as a graduate student”

</title><pros>Pros – They care about their students and make sure that you have access to all of the resources you need</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some professors lack interpersonal skills</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Postdoct friendly”

</title><pros>Pros – large infrastructure, a lot of offerings, core facilities</pros>
<cons>Cons – salaries discrepancies between labs (2 adject labs - 4 year postdoc in one lab get 56K and in the other 44K per year); uneven mentoring</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more control over salaries in the lab, mentoring/coaching training for old school PIs</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent Overall”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent benefits and educational opportunities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary is not competitive with other hospitals.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great”

</title><pros>Pros – Has been a great place to work in.  Good mix of union and non union positions.  overall great place to work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hard to find doctors who take 1199 insurance even for employees.  Not much areas for employee breaks.  Overall good out weighs bad</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – you should take employee feedback a little more serious.  Many people seem to be unhappy.  Christmas parties could be better too.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“respectful”

</title><pros>Pros – prestige of working at a world reknown medical center. Management is respectful and  provides ample time to balance work and personal life.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I don't have any down side except that my current salary for a professional with 20 hears of experience is very low</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listening to staff, and learning from their conversation. become more knowledgeable of their obstacles at work and help out the employee in achiving their goals</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Information Technology (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Too many changes”

</title><pros>Pros – BenefitsSalaryPeople are nice to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – I transferred from 1 IT department to another. My department is so huge that communication lacks. Not sure how people get promoted since I have never experienced one in the many years I was here. I work hard and its often unnoticed. Getting time off is difficult even if your supervisor approves it.  There are many employees in my department who have been at NYU for 25+ years with under perfoming work. In my previous IT department, these employees were praised for the years of service rather than their work. Newer employees were often overlooked.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Talk to your employees - make some changes - make your employees happy</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor Excuse for an IT Department”

</title><pros>Pros – NYU lacks the knowledge to implement a class A network</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor Upper and Mid Managment,  Little to No Knowledge of ITNo Vision, No Goals, Poor Planning, Poor Implementation and No Follow UpEmployees are not respected by Manangement</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get rid of the I am God Idea and get educated and respect your staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Institution has room for improvement”

</title><pros>Pros – RN salary is competitive with other institutions</pros>
<cons>Cons – Room for career growth depends  who you know</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employees should be treated equally and opportunities should be made available to all qualified employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Clinical Research Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great brand name but unfortunately the cons outweigh the pros here”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits; close to transportation; electronic IRB submissions and streamlined research process especially in comparison to other academic institutions</pros>
<cons>Cons – Politics and brown nosing are extremely prevalent to the point where rubbing elbows is more important than the actual work being provided; Lack of guidance; PIs can over ambitious and take on too many projects leading to coordinator burn out, Most PIs and/or research managers will not provide adequate training for entry level research coordinators-again leading to burn out, frustration and error; underpaid in comparison to other institutions; unethical behavior is prevalent</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start trusting those who you hire -- if you don't trust them, don't hire them.Provide more incentives for career growth. It would help retain competent employees and prevent the revolving door effect</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“pretty good, good environment. people are friendly. integrated patient, education, and healthcare.”

</title><pros>Pros – lot of opportunity. world name recognition.</pros>
<cons>Cons – lower than normal salary. not enough events for employers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – need to pay more</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Workload can become exhausting.  Good place for learning.”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of opportunities to get involved in interesting and rewarding work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots of off-hours work, many weekends.  Little flexibility.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Lack of communication from the top down.  Should better get to know the employees/groups your group is associated with.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I feel like my work is valued and that the organization strives to be excellent.”

</title><pros>Pros – Supportive atmosphere, challenging work, high standards of professionalism.Very good opportunities to advance and to develop new skills while working here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Typical bureaucratic stuff, "no" is almost always the first response to any new idea, slow to implement changes, rigid promotion and raise structure.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's a good place to start your career.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great scientific environment within the center and including the surrounding institutes in Manhattan.Fantastic Postdoctoral Program (organizes career workshops, social and networking events).And just like in real estate: Location, location, location!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary is less than at other institutes in the city.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting & disappointing as the job simply turned out not to be a fit for me.”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent benefits. Dedicated community. Innovation. Commitment to change. Quality of staff, medical and administrative.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Overwhelming rate of change and cost of living in New York.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent  brand name, horrible management  (however it all depends on your department)”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits.Easy work hours.Excellent resources.Wonderfully situated location to take a nice walk or sit in a park during breaks.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of communication between management and subordinates.Really bad/unethical office politics within senior management that spills over to subordinates.Mediocre growth opportunity.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep with the times. Business/management practices that worked 10-15  years are no longer feasible. Management should think outside the box in terms of health trends, new reforms and recruiting/retention of talented personel.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience - mediocre benefits”

</title><pros>Pros – A great place to network, gain experience and to meet great experts in your field.  You can work for different projects if you are working in the research sector.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The benefts are not the best, medical options are ok. The salary is not that competative. The maternity leave is laughable.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Its would be great to allow employees to attend work for free. Also, it would be great for you pay  maternity leave, using vacation and sick time if you have any left is not a good offer.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Program Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ok”

</title><pros>Pros – There is pretty decent health coverage</pros>
<cons>Cons – No oppoortunity for promotion or advancement</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create a bonus structure, allow opportunity for raises</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Rewarding”

</title><pros>Pros – Close-knit community and great supervisors who not only teach you but also care about your progress as well as overall improvement</pros>
<cons>Cons – Location and the facility itself aren't that great- it is in the middle of the woods and the lab is very old.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Technician (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good starting position in research.”

</title><pros>Pros – - Very intelligent people all around.- HR is very helpful and informative.- Well funded hospital (apparent once you go inside)- Most labs are very well equipped.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Really depends on the P.I. you're working under. (I ended up working for a complete jerk, and my short-lived experience there was thus quite miserable.)-Dependent also on PI, the amount of training you receive. (I received very little and was expected to do things that I clearly expressed I had never done)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat your employees with respect. Also, training them adequately would be nice. The general training for ALL hospital employees was pretty thorough, why not in the individual labs?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“about job”

</title><pros>Pros – good position with good experience and basic benefits. they have a good retirement plan that you can join into.</pros>
<cons>Cons – academic medical center community can be a challenging environment</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – NA</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting and Professional Place to Work”

</title><pros>Pros – Professional Growth, Friendly People, Good Salary</pros>
<cons>Cons – Political, Hard to Change Job Titles</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More Communication</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Staff Nurse (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Promotion should be by knowledge and experience and not by who you know.”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a state of the art facility. Most managers are competent in their jobs. Teamwork is visible on the units.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I feel that because it is a private institution. Some of the patients have an aloof attitude and making it more chalenging to serve them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – For some management and staff members, teamwork should be encouraged and set by example. Work should be appreciated as a person. Work out indifferences with team members instead of going to the union first.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review as a Research Assistant”

</title><pros>Pros – People are nice and friendly to work withPositive feedback on workGreat resources available at your disposalGood with vacation days, sick days etc.Great health insurance and benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – I did not enjoy havign to go through the hospital entrance to get to the labs, seeing so many sick patients every morning on my way to work was a real downer.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The actual administration deparment was not very well organized. Anything that should have taken a day took more like a month. This didn't really affect me on a daily basis since I did not have to deal with them too much, but when I did it was a bit of a hassle.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Research”

</title><pros>Pros – Great NameSkilled PhysiciansGood reputation to outsiders</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low salaryPoor opportunities for advancement</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide additional funds to renovate older research buildings</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“developer job”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy, work life balanced, vaccation is good</pros>
<cons>Cons – You can't go to up</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire more technical people</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy work enviorment, everyone is friendly</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bad location, not close to public transportation</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Training Fellow (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“NYU: Good place for science, but no respect for postdocs”

</title><pros>Pros – The ability to collaborate and advance your scientific career is fantastic here, because there are world class researchers everywhere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – NYU consistently takes postdocs for granted. The housing office is abysmal, despite the fact that this is a very rich university that could afford to treat postdocs well and help them out with housing. Other New York area research institutions do a much better job of this. The Rockefeller is one example.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Offer postdocs the ability to list NYU as a guarantor when they are applying for apartments. This would really help.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Intern”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible schedule, laid back atmosphere for workers, not too much red tape and bureaucratic bs. The people I worked with were great to spend time with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Did not feel that I would be able to move up in the company no matter how long I worked there</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Empower your employees more, challenge them and they will respond with more vigor.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>