<name>K-LOVE Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/K-LOVE-Reviews-E122595.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2008-07-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Continuity & Traffic Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“EMF is a place of hope and encouragement”

</title><pros>Pros – To bring faith, hope and encouragement to 3 Million listeners. The year I had applied they had received and deterred over 1800 calls for suicide, received 82,000 requests for prayer and had 5 pastors on full time staff. This radio station is unlike any you've ever heard or seen.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Money flows upward meaning it appears that upper management get alot more money and the lower jobs that actually touch the listeners get paid ALOT less. Some of the middle management are incredibly talented people but they are really poor at handling people. They need to scan and train some of their managers with better people skills.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Even out the financial playing field and make sure your middle management is competent managing people and not just "talented" enough for broadcasting. Other than that EMF Broadcasting is a FABULOUS place to work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Disappointing”

</title><pros>Pros – The mission at the heart of this ministry is good. Overall, a very passionate core of people doing great work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Advancement is very limited. Despite internal emphasis on developing skills of people within the organization they don't excel at this.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Wake up! You talk about the importance training people to become more skilled, valuable employee but rarely follow through with training opportunities. Especially in some middle management staff, who are un-trained and under-supported. I think you frequently drop the ball in how you handle this. Many poorly managed staff changes that point to harsh HR tactics and policies, and insensitive leadership.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>