<name>K-Swiss Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/K-Swiss-Reviews-E1268.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2011-06-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great learning experience”

</title><pros>Pros – K-Swiss offers a great learning experience even when starting out.  Good chance to grow personally.  Very friendly employees and atmosphere</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poorly run with very little communication between management and lower employees.  Hard to speak up and have your voice heard.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Graphic Designer 15yrs Here (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An amazing rise followed by the disappoint truth that Management lost sight of it's true vision for success.”

</title><pros>Pros – The opportunity to work on design in every area of the business including, advertising, product photography art direction, packaging, branding and more.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No raises for 8 yrs in a row. No advancement. No growth.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Design your way out of the problem. Get someone with a true business background but not from the footwear industry.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Footwear Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Pros and Cons of working at the company called K-Swiss.”

</title><pros>Pros – Laid back atmosphere and friendly co-workers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Forced to "clock-in", very little opportunity to move up the corporate ladder, no travel.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Clear and open communication across all categories to have a unified vision of who and what K-Swiss is.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>