<name>J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/J-Sargeant-Reynolds-Community-College-Reviews-E128328.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Division Support (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“On the fence”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Hours, No Weekends, Great health benefilts</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay not equal to private sector</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hold employees accountable</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great aspirations”

</title><pros>Pros – The higher up administrators are excellent. There really is a great attitude of helping people succeed with their dreams, which is the point of any institute of higher learning. Some newer hires have really made some great improvements, and it'll be good to see more of that as time goes on.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The different departments are really separated, and communication seems to be a problem. After a middle-management level, something breaks down. People who are just there to get a paycheck are rampant, and it's frustrating when you see so many small things that could be improved.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It's okay to set reasonable expectations and then if people don't meet them, it's okay to have some sort of repercussions for that. It's okay to fire people who are truly ineffectual.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Disappointing”

</title><pros>Pros – State benefits, centrally located, tuition plan, employee recognition system, ability to observe students advance their station in life through accessible higher education</pros>
<cons>Cons – Politics and competition foster a culture of distrust and skepticism. You need back alley deals in order to get anything done. Certain leaders exploit the system to the detriment of the college.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Promote a more collaborative culture, weed out the culture of divisiveness.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>