<name>Play n Trade Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Play-n-Trade-Reviews-E135990.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-04-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly coworkers, amazing experiences. Play N Trade was one of the best jobs that I ever had - and I miss it!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Play N Trade was new to Canada, there was only two in Ontario. My location had to close due to competition with EB Games</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was okay”

</title><pros>Pros – Getting to help different customers, meeting a ton of new people, coworkers (besides manager/owner) awesome layout, players club, try before you buy. locally owned</pros>
<cons>Cons – Biggest con was the owner.. He would never listen to any advice and always gave us some excuse that was always bs. I was an assistant manager and he always kept me in the dark with everything going on. Plus he would never keep on with any software and we'd have the same stuff for months. I was supposed to be getting bonuses and everything which I never saw a dime out of</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn to listen to the employees instead of thinking you know everything.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very bad experience”

</title><pros>Pros – The only good reason to work at PNT.....................the discounts you get in used games</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everything.........hours, salary, management...etc  :(</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Owner (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great, at the store level.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great and fun enviroment, Nice staff, family oriented. Fun place to work. Good management at store level. Good employee discounts.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Dont get product in time, Corporate needs to step up and help at the store level more. Not enough ational advertising. No benefits</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Corporate, needs to work on advertising nationally and a better way to distribute product to be able to compete with the big box stores.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a bad place to work for minimum wage”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible scheduling.Reasonable hourly pay.Increased seasonal hours.Major holidays off.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Corporate doesn't seem to provide enough support to the franchisee.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The local management needs to keep up the good work!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's OK”

</title><pros>Pros – You get a good opportunity to try out all the latest games which are released. You can also get inventory before its released in bigger stores.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management doesn't do a great job of letting its employees know when they have been appreciated; it would be better to show such appreciation with salary raises, bonuses, etc.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Let your employees know when they are appreciated by allowing them additional merit increases and opportunities for advancement. Customer and management interaction can also be improved.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>