<name>V-Soft Consulting Group Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/V-Soft-Consulting-Group-Reviews-E135999.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Network Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Employment Opportunities”

</title><pros>Pros – Great staff with excellent service, very helpful at all times.Good employment opportunities and excellence in placing jobs for networking field.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The resource managers need to be trained to help them understand the various fields of technology.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The resource managers need to be trained to help them understand the various fields of technology.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-10</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work atmosphereExcellent growth opportunitiesExcellent Benefits package</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company is trying to grow too fast.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep growing the company</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-29</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lack of Respect”

</title><pros>Pros – good location; good medical benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management out of touch...too much drama in officeOnce a month paydaysmicromanaging of employeeslow paybarely any PTO vacation or otherwiseunequal treatment of employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Slow down, get involved without micromanaging</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Growing Company with increased opportunities. Enjoyed being on board for more than 2 years now.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great team to work with. Improved benefits than when I started 2 years ago. Lots of training opportunities to keep skills sharp in highly demanding industry.</pros>
<cons>Cons – like to see increased training opportunities in latest skills.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep growing and continue to take care of employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>ERP Trainer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“VSoft Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Long contracts with big companies. Good salaries, good location, very good for helping people who need visa sponsorship. Small organization.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inexperienced HR, management. No follow-up on issues, no reviews, confusing benefits packages (verbally told one thing, and then told another in writing).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Better benefits, better follow-up, less confusing/misleading benefit information. Treat non-visa employees the same as the visa employees (with better benefits). Better recruiting process - make sure people are qualified before putting them on a client site.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Full of Opportunity for Career Growth!”

</title><pros>Pros – Growing companyGreat ManagementHeading in good directionLots of opportunity to grow careerLearn a lot while on the jobTeam atmosphere is fun</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not enough PTO in benefit package</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Review PTO policy and compare to other like companies to be more competitiveContinue to hire the best people to augment the team</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I had a lot of opportunity at V-Soft, but they don't treat their employees very well.”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a great place to get your foot in the door.  There is opportunity to advance, and you get to work with some great people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They don't treat their employees well.  Poor senior management.  Everything is looked at as a negative even if something positive has happened.  There is a very poor culture and atmosphere.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Set reasonable, achievable goals.  Remember that previous employees also represent your company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great door, but overall poor leadership”

</title><pros>Pros – I loved working on the team I did. The people on my direct team were some of the most knowledgable in the company and they helped me learn and grow. They were also a great support system for me while I was still getting my feet wet.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Leadership doesnt communicate or seem to have reasoning behind anything they do. The executives seem to make the environment into "us versus our employees." They put on a nice face, but really its all about the short term. There seems to be little to know long-term stability</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Your employees are smart and bring a lot to the table. You seem to focus your attentions on the employees who do the least and poorest work, so rather focus on employees who bring a lot to the table and can help grow the company overall.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“SAp Analyst for PM module”

</title><pros>Pros – Good experience and exposure, nice people to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad benifits and pay, travel required 10%</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Its good , keep going.encouraging place to work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“After three months of training and certifications, they have not been able to place me on any client project”

</title><pros>Pros – The training they provided was very good and I was easily able to obtain my industry certifications.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The people in charge of placement do not bother to understand and match your skills and experience with the available positions</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Programmer/Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent mid-size IT consultancy”

</title><pros>Pros – They have a few direct clients in the Louisville, KY area. If you are a smart and quick worker, you can get a good percentage of the hourly rate.</pros>
<cons>Cons – When you travel back to India, its very easy to get your visa or even your extension denied. You will have to manage your technical and professional progress yourself, this is more of a body shipping business, they don't know what you are doing at the Client's office.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Build teams and market solutions to the Client, rather than body shipping one consultant to one Client. Provide bench pay to all employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Better then others”

</title><pros>Pros – Good compensation. Free access to trainings on latest technologies for all the employees throughout the year. Good Human Resources department.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unfortunately not everyone gets treated so well. Depending on how much business you bring on board you are treated accordingly.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I worked there for one reason (to find a better job)”

</title><pros>Pros – If you need a job and dont have some technical skills this company is good bet to get you trained and placed. but they are not doing you a favor .  they are investing and wont let you go till they get their money back. they used to good pace to work for few years then they got greedy and reduce pay scales and started  hiring family members . which nearly kills any hope of advancement. also there are no pay raises. To tell you the truth they are meat shop. they also dont treat their clients well. their services personeel who try to get you projects would change your profession to get you making some money</pros>
<cons>Cons – Moving for client projects. ?bench time</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat employees as human being and not as commodities</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly associatesGood LocationManagement is ok</pros>
<cons>Cons – With, the, no, red, yellow</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Please beware of this company”

</title><pros>Pros – They can exploit you in all possible ways.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bunch of uneducated and illiterate people..uncouth and nasty..</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“One of the best in the IT consulting”

</title><pros>Pros – good pay, good benefits, good management</pros>
<cons>Cons – none at all, everything is good</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ok to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Helps to find the jobs for all levels people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Doesn't respond immediately to phone calls and emails</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to get back as soon as possible</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>