<name>JWT Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/JWT-Reviews-E13666.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Producer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Agency Producer”

</title><pros>Pros – Great, busy environment! Loved the company and my co-workers. Great mentorship.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Great mentors but disorganized management. At times overworked.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sort of a has-been agency trying to make relevancy in an increasing digital world”

</title><pros>Pros – The office is beautiful, big name clients, benefits are great, most of the people are nice, and there's a bar.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some upper-levels are has-been's that made it big with traditional media (print/tv), but now struggle to have a foothold in digital. The company struggles with its digital work, smaller agencies do it better and cheaper. Large parts of floors are just filled with rows of empty cubicles, not sure if JWT is low on work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Embrace teaching/mentoring a little more.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Art Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“okay”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people, great benefits, relaxed atmosphere, nice office space and location.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Little or no growth opportunities. Buddy system. No organized performance reviews. Rare or non-existent salary raises.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take better care of your current employees. Complete performance reviews and career goal plans. Improve culture and internal communication within the company. Pay and promotions should be based on skills, and performance and not on friendships and favoritism.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – JWT offers great benefits. including medical, dental and 401K participation.  They are very generous with their paid holidays.  It is a fun and festive atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The compensation could be more competitive.  There is a lack of a yearly review which doesn't give you the opportunity to make a case for an increase.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – A yearly review that would determine even a small increase would show that the hard work appreciated.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great to fair”

</title><pros>Pros – Relatively stable 150 year old agency -- good training for young people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Politics in the higher ranks, inability to change in response to market conditions</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep it simple and focus on what matters.  Insist on alignment -- there is way too much disagreement and discord in the upper ranks of JWT.  It makes for a very negative work environment.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Inspiring atmosphere, unique office environment, still feels like a big traditional agency.”

</title><pros>Pros – The office itself is a big selling point - open layout, colorful and bright architecture. Doesn't feel like a rigid, corporate environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – there's no way to get around traditional agency politics. JWT is still struggling to break the mold of digital advertising.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More raises are deserved.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Executive Creative Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best of the BDA's,”

</title><pros>Pros – Bob Jeffrey Runs the best agency in WPP. His standards are consistently high. Plus, he is a gentleman.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is unfortunately part of WPP, which means that in common with all agencies reporting to a holding company, making the numbers is more important than the work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Open a bar and make all the drinks free. Then, buy yourselves out of WPP and create the best agency on the East Coast.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Operations Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Get a champion and you'll be fine”

</title><pros>Pros – Great office space. Changes often enough that if it's not working for you at a particular moment, wait it out and you mind find the changes to your advantages.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lacks a true north. Seems a bit rudderless and senior mgmt only seems to care about very small issues versus those that make the money. Tend to abandon all existing culture when chasing and bringing in the latest hot shot</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Communicate more with your people about what's going on.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Internship at JWT in Atlanta”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun environment with great people and work/life balance. The work was challenging and there was a clear stimulation to think outside the box and find creative solutions.</pros>
<cons>Cons – My time there wasn't long enough to identify any significant downside.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Finance Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“JWT Good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Tremendous work/life balance at JWT</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes boring work at JWT</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Opening to the world”

</title><pros>Pros – Great international and integrated network</pros>
<cons>Cons – Ownership of the brand is concentrad in few offices</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make people travel in the network</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Office Support (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Place To Start A Career”

</title><pros>Pros – Huge network, A Lot of Opportunity</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very political, must know the "right" people</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – e more equitable</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“JWT - Good if you're 'in'; otherwise, keep quiet, and keep your head low.”

</title><pros>Pros – I liked my department - SMART people. Some GREAT Creative folks.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is more about impressing the client with good looks than real, actionable insights.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Care more about the client and less about your personal looks.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Environment, No Career Growth”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun, young, good location and good SME's to learn from</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper Management wouldn't even care if you died</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – At least act like you care.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Once a strong agency. Great People, Little leadership”

</title><pros>Pros – Some good clients, talented people. Desire to be a good agency. Client has loyalty to agency and wants them to do well. Current COO is talented, wish he could lead more rather than just follow the President.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Once they get a direction they change the course again. Little leadership. Work is suffering because of high turnover. They do not preach or practice any kind of values. Extraordinary amount politics.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in Leaders, not PR people or superstars. Be present in the office and consistent with what you want us to do.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“2013 or 1999?”

</title><pros>Pros – Bars in every office. Good clients, large network, award winning work outside of USA.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Raises are few and fair between. Very little room for growth. Management does not know the talent that they have. Still struggling with digital work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Challenge employees to be great and they will. Managing by fear of "reorganizations" is poor on morale. Increase communication, praise and celebrate accomplishments</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No talent, incredibly political and less than interesting people”

</title><pros>Pros – The office was incredibly well-designed</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper Management is more worried about covering their arses than they are about growing client business, training people and great creative.It takes 4 times longer to get anything done b/c you have to dance around the politics of not smart people before you can actually do something.Its the place for people that can't get into real creative agency's. It's a bunch of people that spend all their time looking at other people's smart work instead of building great work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – While you may wear a suit that does not equate to professionalism. You ignore client issues and blame others, you have no idea what a good idea is, and everything is driven by $.Quit your job- you are failing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun, maybe too much so”

</title><pros>Pros – Great offices, fun people, great M/F ratio (if you're male).  Very global, lots of really exciting creative work.  WPP agencies also tend offer better pay and benefits than other holding company agencies.  Upper management is great and very transparent.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Though you are given quite a bit of responsibility at entry-level, it's difficult to take on greater roles without being extremely persistent and proactive.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Challenge your employees and they will rise to the occasion.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A mess of a place”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people, cool office space, bar in the 2nd floor</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible management, little room for advancement, egos run a muck and if you start off in a junior position you will be treated with little to no respect</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Planning (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great learning experience!”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity to work on iconic brands!Strong strategic focus.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No efforts to involve new employee in the company culture.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – NA</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Print Production Supervisor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“6 years and a Black Pencil and several Lions for my efforts.”

</title><pros>Pros – Really try to push the envelope creatively. Got to work on a tone of different creative executions beyond traditional ads and outdoor.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Account group is lacking in leadership. In the end of my days I felt they were trying to overly push a digital agenda, while the traditional (TV and Print) and non-traditional (Ambient/Experiential) efforts were killing it for the clients that got it. The post Ty/Rose days began a downward spiral.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't cut your nose off to spite your face.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Finance Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great environment to work in. People are friendly and management is very flexible.  Would recommend this company!”

</title><pros>Pros – JWT provides a friendly environment and is pretty flexible when it comes to work-time.  Upper management doesn't babysit their employees; employees can pretty much work independently.  The HR dept. is easy to talk to; the Finance dept. is readily available.  There are lots of company functions to attend (parties, celebrations, mini-concerts, etc); the environment is very social, casual, pretty laid back.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The major downside is the pay isn't very good and the raises are very few and very far in between! Upper management doesn't really consider their employees opinions however, they do ask for them, probably just to be courteous. The workload in each dept. is very different; in some depts. employees can get their work done rather quickly and can surf the net all afternoon and in other depts. the employees are buried working straight from 9am - sometimes 6 or 7pm.  Also, there's very little career advancement opportunities at the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upper management should be MORE INVOLVED in their DEPTS and not just focus on their needs and what they have to get done!  They should not only ask what they can do to help their employees fulfill their job duties but actually provide what is needed to their employees in order for them to get their jobs done.  They also need to realize that life expenses are continuously rising and they should be more proactive in getting their employees raises instead of pocketing thousands of dollars in bonuses for themselves and blaming their managers for not being able to get anyone any money!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>I T (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Colorful and fun, with bar attached!”

</title><pros>Pros – A lot of good company great friendships. Get to be involved in a lot of client facing events. A lot of fun at internal event and holiday parties.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing to crazy you can't handle.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good work life balance, horrible compensation.”

</title><pros>Pros – Time off and work life balance is wonderful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is little room for growth and raises don't exist.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The agency is what you make of it”

</title><pros>Pros – I was given the resources and opportunity to pursue the more interesting projects that came through our production department.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The Creative is stagnant, mostly print based and scared of technology. There are a rare few who get it, but, mostly duds</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get more tech savvy creatives.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Creative Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Could be a great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – The offices are amazing and the great bar is great. They are good at having parties.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The management believes in NO reviews, NO raises and NO advancement. You are lucky to be working there.</cons>
<advice-to-management> – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An Incredibly Enriching Learning Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – The environment at JWT is incredibly high paced, involved, friendly, and intelligent. Everyone that steps through the office doors has an eagerness to work and a love for what they do. There are numerous office events to keep employees connected and JWT encourages learning and growth. Interns don't get coffee... they do real-world work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I had a perfect experience with JWT and don't see any true cons.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Producer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“fun place to work at”

</title><pros>Pros – great atmosphere, great management, fun times</pros>
<cons>Cons – some of the people take some warming up to</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – n/a</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Creative Services (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“JWT”

</title><pros>Pros – Working for one of the largest ad agency in the world looks good on the resume. Great place to catch up on your sleep.</pros>
<cons>Cons – managers are not trained nor interested in managing employees, tasks are repetitive and employees have little to no dedication to their clients success. If JWT should lose the Ford account, this agency will fold so fast as other accounts do not account for greater billing. And, Employees are bored working on this account. It shows in the lackluster, dull and boring Ford ads. Ford is getting over billed for services, as employees are encouraged to pad their billing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn to manage, set</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Planner (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Under construction”

</title><pros>Pros – New leadership has been dynamic and new business has been active.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots of turnover has made the teams feel unsettled.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>PHP Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Doesnt pay contractors on time”

</title><pros>Pros – Dallas office has good people.Variety of work available</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management not focused.Management not involved.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay attention to how your treating contractors.I was contractor for this company in October and November of 2012. My first paycheck was delayed repeatedly by repeated mistakes, and there was no response from the company other than 'nothing we can do' Once the check arrived, it was short, because the paperwork deadlines did not match the pay period information I was given, and was only told this after the fact. I resigned and went elsewhere, however at this time they have not paid me my final pay in violation of texas payday laws.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Planner (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“NY Office: Nice people and decent talent, but don't expect much coziness”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are quite nice and generally good to one another. Not a lot of giant egos and a lot less cut throat than other big ad agencies, but the work is not quite at the same level as a BBDO or an Ogilvy.  The hours are decent and the clients you work on are solid.  Looks great on a resume.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's a huge office so don't expect anyone to look out for your professional development. The New York office is too big and has too many problems to have any sort of mentorship culture. All of that is your own responsibility and you should seek out someone personally to help you learn the ropes and give you advice about managing your career at JWT.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in your people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok, if anonymous.”

</title><pros>Pros – Some nice staff, interesting, challenging work, interesting if anonymous office in great location, freedom to set own hours. Work mostly unsupervised.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Cold environment, definitely not one of the friendliest places I've worked. Meetings set then abandoned without notice.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create a little more conviviality.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun culture but no work/life balance”

</title><pros>Pros – Great, modern office.  Lots of coworkers that like to party and have fun.  Flexible work environment if you have been there for a while and are on the right team.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Overworked, understaffed employees.  No work/life balance, you are expected to respond to work requests night and day.  Limited raises; most employees only receive a raise after several years if at all.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make employees more accountable for their actions; responsible/dedicated employees are constantly picking up others slack.  Reward high performers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Reporting Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Good atmosphere...good people...good clients...no complaints. Best job I ever had.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I don't have anything to report as "Cons".</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Creative Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good creative, bad organization”

</title><pros>Pros – focus on creativity. a few truly inspiring coworkers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – too many meetings. spent half my time explaining what we were doing rather than actually making work. the project could have been organized much much better. team were spread throughout the building- spent hours of my day just trying to get together with producers, account execs who were scattered throughout a building the size of an entire block.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Media Planner (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work environment and awesome team members.  Believe in work/life balance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Change in management and there was more turnover than ever before.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Account Reprsentative”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting people and global clientsWealth of Knowledge in AutomotiveHistory</pros>
<cons>Cons – TravelCorporate card reimbursements for travel</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep mentoring people</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Art Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Big Old School Agency”

</title><pros>Pros – They have an open bar and a nice art on the walls thats about all.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much middle management and not enough smart thinking.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Art Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good and bad”

</title><pros>Pros – global network gives you access to major clients with big budgets. good people. the office has a bar.</pros>
<cons>Cons – meetings, meetings about meetings. long hours. lots of wasted time. no creative leadership</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Accountant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience, wonderful team”

</title><pros>Pros – great team to work with.Management is very considerate when it comes to time off.Great benefits package, profit sharing and lots of days off.Flex timeGorgeous workspace and lots of fun.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary is averageAvg. of three years for a raise.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No complaints.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was good.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people and environment. MAde some good friends when I worked there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Conpensation could have been better.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Supervisor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“High Potential, Good People, Multiple Personalities”

</title><pros>Pros – Resume builder - JWT name and accounts, Smart people and high standards. New management team. New ECD and team hired to address and raise the bar creatively.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Internal chaos, lots of change in process and management constantly - always trying to find the best fix but not finding it. Lots of turnover. Bad communication between departments from the top down. Bad morale. Long hours and few receiving pay increases over the years. Most feel they could be the next to go - as a result top talent moving on. No defined culture or glue that holds everyone together.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hiring and retaining top talent is the first step. Ask and listen to each employee on what they need. Follow and pattern yourself after successful companies on how they treat employees. We are in the business of building brands and defining cultures as a business but it starts at home first. And JWT is just a name without the talent that brings it to life inside.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Producer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“meh.”

</title><pros>Pros – nice buildinggreat IT departmentgenerous holiday calendar</pros>
<cons>Cons – no real room for advancement inside the company</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – offer regular reviews and promote growth and salary increases</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>New Business (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's one of the best platforms to work on in the entire industry”

</title><pros>Pros – JWT isn't for someone who wants to mark time. It's an incredible stage on which those who do their very best will thrive. But it's big business and it's deadly serious about it all. I can't count the number of terrific people I worked with there for over a decade and those who really put their shoulder to the wheel and who had identified and articulated their own goals -- then went after them -- are the ones who excelled the most visibly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It can be incredibly stressful, the hours and demand on time can be extraordinary, but... Again, this isn't some Mom + Pop boutique.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do far more to KEEP your talent since, after all, it's by working at JWT and for your incredible clients that people make their reputations. I just think it's a shame that so many in senior positions come and go. I would try to stem that flow!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Producer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great career builder”

</title><pros>Pros – big, fortune 500 clients, big budget management experience, lots of support teams - almost over staffed sometimes.  You will learn a lot and be asked to do a lot - learn from that.</pros>
<cons>Cons – muddled in the middle. hard to move up or down. Stay & learn while you can - you will work, no doubt  - but promotions and salary increases are a myth.  You need to move on to move up.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – get back  to management reviews and some small salary increases to keep people motivated. Otherwise the turnover in the middle will continue.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Copywriter (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lost in a sea of creatives.”

</title><pros>Pros – There are lots of opportunities, clients and people to workwith. They have a strong rep and long history. if you push, you'll. Find the job you're looking for.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are so many employees that if you don't start with a core team on your side, a niche of your own, it's easy to get lost in the mix.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There are lots of fish in this big pond. There's no beurocracy problem, just an opportunity to cultivate a lot more untapped talent already under your control.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is good, there is a lot of change going on and they are constantly trying new things”

</title><pros>Pros – Scale of the business is amazing with access to great clients at a senior level.  There is a ton of global opportunity and more chances for travel.  The office is super well designed and people are nice.  There is a bar and lots of events.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bureaucracy to get things done is hard and there are too many people on every project.  Best to stay under the radar somethings and just do stuff rather than talking about it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to figure out how we work and publish it to everyone so everyone knows and it doesn't keep changing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cool agency, poor management”

</title><pros>Pros – The office decor is great and they also have a full bar, popcorn machine and a play room that has Nintendo Wii, a pool table, etc. so employees can relax.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management didn't care about my personal growth, long hours I worked, or support I needed to succeed on this account.  I had to ask permission from my supervisor and manager to speak with my Client... I've never been so micromanaged in my life!  And the way certain creative teams spoke to and yelled at the account team was appalling. What was even worse, is that upper management knew about their behavior and did nothing about it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees and you should have the mentality that no one is superior enough to do any job or task.  Provide your employees the guidance and encouragement to do well by providing positive reinforcement and constructive criticism.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Planning Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of smart people and opportunity. Limited vision and leadership.”

</title><pros>Pros – People, stellar planning department, variety of accounts</pros>
<cons>Cons – Leadership is struggling, lack of creative talent, slow, political</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to learn”

</title><pros>Pros – Put on major clients right off the bat. Great training and great inside look at how big-budget advertising happens. Fun to work in the heart of Manhattan and work around some truly talented and inspiring people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Of course crazy hours (like working til 1am), but that's to be expected. In-fighting and politics are hard to avoid.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't be afraid of the new up-and-comers. The better they look, the better you look.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Creative and brand focused, but needs more marketing application”

</title><pros>Pros – Vacation and holidays are great along with workplace flexibility.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Needs to value and reward employees more for performance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you want to retain employess, don't overlook the most valued asset.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“JWT is a great collection of talent. Conservative clients, but high aspirations. T”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people, smart, eager to do a great job for clients</pros>
<cons>Cons – Like the entire industry, I think it is trying to adapt to the realities of today's media world. However some days it feels like it has one foot in the past.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to yourself sometimes.... And then go and listen to your employees and see if it matches</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>IT Worker (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits are very good ecxept for medical co-pay.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No performance appraisals. Employees in same department are treated differently.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be fair</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“fun”

</title><pros>Pros – great office atmosphere, fun people</pros>
<cons>Cons – top heavy, lots of 'hiring buddies'</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“JWT - Step It Up”

</title><pros>Pros – Great location and workspace. Employees are given generous vacation time and the agency hosts frequent networking events. Many new business opportunities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Entry level and account positions are treated as easily replaceable. Salary discrepancies are sometimes apparent between male and female positions. Upper management seems unimpressed by output.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Appreciate your teams and encourage interaction between groups.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Broadcast Producer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Disorganized, process heavy, creative driven workplace with unaccountable employees and management.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good access to global advertising clients, brands, and accounts, opportunities for exposure at entry levels to high profile work. Ample opportunity to learn and a good springboard to working at another company or in another field. Great opportunities for creatives.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Disorganized, process heavy, creative driven workplace with unaccountable employees and management. Current focus is on Digital, yet most revenue is still in print and broadcast. The agency is old fashioned and does not understand the digital space logistically or technically. Agency can't retain it's best employees. No review or promotions for over 3 years.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Some sort of review, promotion, or bonuses would be nice. There is no incentive or accountability for people to work hard or do better work. Senior management spends all day in meetings, oblivious to the day to day issues and realities of running a business.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – JWT is the best agency I have worked for. Great team, and great creative for such traditional clients.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Growing within the company might take some time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would definitely work at JWT.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Place To Work”

</title><pros>Pros – All round great agency to work for- great work and great brands. I would recommend the agency to others interested.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I really don't have any downsides to working at JWT, perhaps the pay scale.  The agency is a really great place.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – NA</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Relaxed Corporate culture”

</title><pros>Pros – The relaxed atmosphere and dress code is a definite plus. Schedule is relatively flexible and management is supportive of work/life balance. Fun, creative atmosphere. Very cool office space. Young and fun workforce.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Career growth can be difficult. The review process seems too subjective and not fully reflective of salary level. Feedback from immediate supervisor is lacking.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve review and promotion process. Too many people leave due to lack of career growth. Some managers would benefit from taking management classes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good culture, good accounts, no promotions”

</title><pros>Pros – The culture fostered here is strong, but there are obstacles for such a huge agency trying to reinvent its mission. A traditional agency, posing as a digital shop, trying hard to provide 360 results. Some very smart and talented people here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some very UNtalented and difficult people work here. Poor client management. Unfair expectations are set. The weasels climb while the hard workers go unrecognized. You won't get promoted or given a raise here, so its best to work really hard on the global clients, get the work in your book and move on</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Install a regular review practice. Work harder at understanding employee goals and helping them grow.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Broadcast Producer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“JWT Chicago - Producer”

</title><pros>Pros – JWT was nice because you have the opportunity to work on some big brands and a decent work/life balance.  All in all, it's not a bad place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some of the downsides of working at JWT are the lack of overall feedback.  We report to New York and direction and promotions are untimely.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The only feedback I would have is to listen more to the people you lead.  Many times I felt disconnected.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Chaotic and disorganized amidst the painful transition from traditional advertising to advertising in a digital age.”

</title><pros>Pros – JWT has some truly great people in the New York office.  The facility itself is also impressive, and the open floorplan is actually quite pleasant and conducive to working as a team.  Location is great too.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours can get very long.  There is disorganization at many levels of management, which is disheartening.  There also seems to be a general lack of prioritization.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The house needs to be straightened up a bit, and some serious focus needs to be applied to existing issues rather than pushing forward on new initiatives all the time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“High responsibility without financial matching”

</title><pros>Pros – JWT gives entry-level employees a lot of responsibility at an early stage in your career, giving you exposure to high-profile clients (allowing junior people not only in meetings, but empowering them to run meetings). The company encourages employees to participate beyond the accounts they are assigned to, anytime I mentioned interest in helping on a new business pitch to learn about a new category/industry, management encouraged the side projects, which gave me more exposure internally and increased my category knowledge.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours at JWT were long and unpredictably so, and unfortunately salaries did not reflect the "banker hours" and leaving at 6pm was even a taboo.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increase transparency around promotion process and salary increases to manage expectations. While there is technically a "review process", in 4 years I had 1 review and it didn't provide any actionable feedback or clear indication about what behaviors would be encouraged/rewarded with a salary increase.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“as cool a culture as you can get for such traditional clients”

</title><pros>Pros – cool people and work environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – very traditional clients that are hard to transformwait and see for new management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – it would be preferable to push our clients harder and not be so afraid to lose business as a result of what we believe is right.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Freelance Digital Copywriter (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Chaotic, Disorganized.”

</title><pros>Pros – Prestigious agency, large, well-known clients.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It could have just been the account that I worked on, but I found it to be a totally disorganized operation in onboarding freelancers and getting them up to speed. Long hours because objectives constantly changed. Not enough desk space so situated in a makeshift area unsuitable for working. Not enough time to ideate. Felt like I was on a hamster wheel.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you want the best work and thinking out of freelancers, spend some time to acclimate them. If you choose to let them sink or swim, they'll most likely sink.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Big agency with some expected shortfalls.”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart and passionate industry people.  Big agency name recognition.  Big clients with big budgets.  Opportunities to work on a variety of accounts.  Global reach.  Great teamwork.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Process heavy.  Conservative clients tend to force conservative creative.  Many layers of upper management.  Elaborate performance review process with no connection to salary.  Little work-life balance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep an eye on how many hours your staff puts in.  Everyone expects to work hard and do what it takes for their clients, but there are limits.  You're unnecessarily risking high turn over with some great people.Connect performance reviews with tangible salary benefits.  Multiple years of exemplary reviews with no salary increases tends to disappoint and diminish motivation to excel.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Copywriter (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Some good, some bad”

</title><pros>Pros – Talented people. I've meet some very bright people and found the working environment to be OK. Vacation/days off package is exceptional. Other benefits are slightly better than average.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Big, corporate agency with a matching culture. The organization is struggling a bit...office closings, senior people leaving. Most of the dust has settled now though.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to the people more. Communication seems to be rather one-sided. Needs to be more of a two-way dialogue between leadership and staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good resume builder...if you can suffer through a year here.”

</title><pros>Pros – The office is pretty cool and there is a lot of opportunity to see other work going on in the agency.  The name is a good place to have on your resume and if you are lucky, you can end up in a good spot.  Creative is fun and the resources within the agency are great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor management.  Totally corporate and top-heavy.  Bad salaries, no work/life balance.  Lower level employees are treated like machines.  Had to work overnight on multiple occations and then literally had to ask to go home and sleep the next day after client meetings.  There's no positive reinforcement and everything is a dramatic emergecny.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get with it - start treating employees like people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Production Artist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Big business restricts quality of work at JWT.”

</title><pros>Pros – Up to date technologies. My computer station has some of the fast Macs out there with large monitors and brand new laser printers. The work environment is open space with new facilities and funky decor.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are NO raises given since I've been here. I've heard people have worked here for 5 years and have not received a raise! People working in the Print Studio get overtime after 10 hours of work in one day. So you have to work over 50 hours in a week (but we work 40 hour weeks) to get any OT.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more organized. It seems like everything comes into the studio a big mess. Nothing is straightened out until the studio receives work, which then reduces the quality of the finished product. Communication is BIG! There needs to be more communication. Things happen without anyone knowing. There is also a lack of respect for what me and my fellow colleagues do.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Th epicenter of the American auto industry, Team Detroit.”

</title><pros>Pros – You work for a huge account that's very directly tied to the American economy. When you produce good work, you feel like it might actually have a huge impact. You have a hand in work that reachers millions of people in prime time. But that doesn't neccesarily mean its exciting work. The company has the ability to do great things, if the were brave enough.</pros>
<cons>Cons – When things don't go as planned, the effects are felt equally strongly.The client is a sinking ship. Things might get a lot worse before they get better. The leaders are old dinosaurs opposed to change.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You can't keep doing the same things you've always done and expect them to work. Take risks. The result can't be much worse than what's already taking place.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-07-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Graphic Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If advertising is your game, this is the place.”

</title><pros>Pros – Working there opened doors of opportunity as far as having a highly rated international ad agency on your resume. I believe their good name for advertising and their reputation, more then mine, got me the initial interviews and a couple of job offers. The design firms i worked with liked the fact that a designer from a big agency came to work for them.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There were a lot of office politics involved. If you negotiate well through office politics you will thrive. As in high school, you deal with the popular kids and the not so popular kids and you realize that life isn't fair all the time. You need to play well within that culture</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I don't really have any to give them, don't think they'd listen.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Account Executive (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dynamic work around the hour”

</title><pros>Pros – Diverse projects and various tasks gives employees good knowledge of different industries. As an Account Executive in the client servicing department, you will be expected to become an expert on all sorts of businesses your clients operate in, whether its personally relevant to you or not. This provides a great opportunity to get introduced to different brands and industries and grows you as a well-rounded and informed individual.You will likely meet interesting clients, make positive business relationships and attend several client events. Being in client servicing is very dynamic, requires a lot of interpersonal skills and is by no means a static desk job.JWT's network is global, giving you access to a massive bank of knowledge which you may use wisely to grow your own potential and skills. If you're lucky, you'll also be able to work with offices from different cities and learn from them.The atmosphere is casual and comfortable. You have direct access to management and different departments. There's a lot of room of building great friendships in the office and sharing many social activities outside the office with your colleagues.My first job was with JWT, and I would definitely recommend it for all graduates or 1st jobbers willing to get a well-rounded experience in marketing. It's exciting but not easy, teaches you patience, working under pressure and dealing with a variety of characters and projects.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Depending on the size of the office in your city, you might find yourself dealing with a large number of clients, which although is a good experience, might be extremely overwhelming and pressuring. Similar to most successful advertising agencies, the working hours are extremely long. If you're looking for a 9-5 job, then JWT (and advertising in general) is definitely not the place to go.Similar to many agency jobs that involve client encounters, you may have to deal with extremely difficult clients with extremely demanding requests and ridiculous deadlines. You might find yourself stuck in the office at 9.pm simply waiting for a phone call from a client to provide you with an approval on an email you've sent hours ago. Tasks may sometimes become frustrating if you're not a patient person.In addition to long hours, work from home on weekends is not far fetched. You might find yourself struggling to maintain a work-life balance at early stages, but that becomes better as you learn to efficiently manage your schedule and deadlines.One long term potential disadvantage with working with several industries is that you may find yourself becoming a generalist; i.e. knowing a little of everything but not a lot in one particular thing. This may be considered an advantage or disadvantage based on your career plans and objectives.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Global Account Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good learnings, but limited career prospects”

</title><pros>Pros – Loved the people, loved the culture, loved the creativity, and loved working on a Global team taking care of 40+ markets.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation was not as competitive; career prospects not clear.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – n/a</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Supervisor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Huge agency, with bureaucratic approach”

</title><pros>Pros – Good learning experience if you are starting out as it probably manages the entire spectrum of brands globally</pros>
<cons>Cons – Its pretty large agency, with several levels , hence slow not exactly nimble.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Encourage proactive approaches.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ups and downs..felt like a drop in the ocean”

</title><pros>Pros – stable, good accounts, great billings</pros>
<cons>Cons – you teand to get lost in too many people, political</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – listen to the employess</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Big ambitions.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great freedom to do creative work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours. Not a lot of connection to other offices.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Learning!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Meet and make tons of contacts</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pays and stressful timings!</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Real place for mad men..”

</title><pros>Pros – - one of the world's largest advertising company.. great reputation for great profile- very well structural organization.. providing great knowledges and experiences- true expert in advertising and marketing communications.. second to none- lots of big-named clients- higher pay</pros>
<cons>Cons – - darn long working hours.. probably on holidays.. so many endless meetings and meetings- can totally ruin your life and relationships- rush works and ad hogs.. real stressful- highly competitive and aggressive environment like usual ad agency..  but some people are really nice, too ('cos you probably spend more time with them than your family.. so, new brothers and sisters)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please consider a holiday compensation</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Summer Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great internship experience in planning div”

</title><pros>Pros – Good team to work withHelpful</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not given enough responsibility at times</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – Work Environment is very good</pros>
<cons>Cons – Growth is limited when starting off</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Account Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“so far its been good”

</title><pros>Pros – it has a very strong support system. great team spirit and to do attitude from everyone around.has great relationships with the client which with strong history.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not  really satisfied with the salary band. Also need to have more training opportunities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to get my grips in the advertising industry”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people, global clients, and vibrant office.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited perks compared to other major players in the industry and still somewhat traditional at its core</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more daring and simplify bureaucratic process</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Digital Art Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“challenging and stressful”

</title><pros>Pros – you will have a great opportunity to work with a team on big campaigns, also it keeps you on the challenging mode all the time. there is a great opportunity for improvements.</pros>
<cons>Cons – two much work, and lack of communication</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – give the joiners an opportunity to improve them selves</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Specialist Planner (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good agency for more balance”

</title><pros>Pros – Ability to build brand, work hard / play hard attitude, good place for career development and moving up, strong talent, working toward through the line integration</pros>
<cons>Cons – Client roster isn't great if you want ethical companies - Army, Shell, Nestle, HSBC...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Prioritise values and CSR more as a means of being future focused. Campaigns that win at Cannes are about shared value and social good</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Comp Artist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great on a resume”

</title><pros>Pros – Creative people were all over, very inspiring.  In addition, JWT is a great name on a resume.  Lots of opportunity to learn and an interesting place to work.  Nice offices.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Constant turnover, seems to always be in transition.  Had the advantage of being an old fashioned ad agency and a digital shop, but now stuck between both worlds.  Has a lot of potential.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep on truckin</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“dont expect much”

</title><pros>Pros – the clients is the strength of JWT</pros>
<cons>Cons – u ll not be a free bird</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Smart people, traditional agency.”

</title><pros>Pros – Very creative teamsBrilliant strategic divisionsOn the ball trendwatching research</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sheep in wolves clothing: tells clients they know digital but fall short in activating a truly social ecosystem. Media channels are not for selling, they're for using as marketing and conversation avenues, IMHO.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stick to what you're good at, and don't extend into unfamiliar areas unless you understand and are willing to put forth the effort and risk tolerance necessary to start something fresh.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good, smart people in all disciplines but poor organizational management”

</title><pros>Pros – A chance to work with smart, dynamic, cross-functional teams.  Working on the right account can give stellar experience creating excellent integrated, creative work</pros>
<cons>Cons – A struggle to get raises for approved for high performing employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Develop standardized success metrics and flexible comp structures that reward high performers and don't reward low-perfomers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Creative Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“excellent network agency, good spirit , it's a pity the human resources are a catastrophy”

</title><pros>Pros – good network agency around the world. Good creative muscle.good culture and values.good intentions.Creative led.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very bad human resources management in the middle east area ..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest more in a proper human resources structure in the middle east.Be clearer when transferring people around the network about their rights. Stay transparent,ethical and just.It's a people agency, so keep it simple and clear.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>CRM Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“NOt a good site to work”

</title><pros>Pros – cool creative aura. good ambiance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – workload, not quite a motivational environment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“JWT is a solid job.”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a very enjoyable work environment with very talented people. Benefits are excellent.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This company doesn't appear to award raises to employees and path of advancement is very limited.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Consider at least annual cost of living wage increases where individuals' performance is satisfactory.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Planning Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“JWT Intern”

</title><pros>Pros – Superb work life, amazing work culture</pros>
<cons>Cons – a little low on pay</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – definitely a worthy experience</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“it has been a great learning”

</title><pros>Pros – Great atmosphere, good people to work with...</pros>
<cons>Cons – benefits should be more better. apart from that no complaints</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-27</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Vice President & Senior Cr Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent people friendly work place”

</title><pros>Pros – Large infrastructure, present across the world handling top most global brands</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too big to make remarkable individual contribution</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Account Executive”

</title><pros>Pros – very stable clients, goog work and life balace, super working environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – entry level salary is not very satisfied</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – no</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fantastic network of talented individuals”

</title><pros>Pros – JWT has an amazingly strong pool of talented individuals. It also has a fantastic network of offices, making tapping talent that much easier. On a side note, it also has some of the nicest people around.</pros>
<cons>Cons – JWT doesn't feel like a creative agency. It very much works like most corporates do. It's a shame only because one of the most endearing bits about being in advertising is not being constrained within a corporate structure.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The management would do well to remember that the people are what keep the wheel spinning..</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Satisfying”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent social life and co-workers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bureaucratic, minimal payscale, revenue targets hamper creativity.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Compensate better.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Some Good Talent, constant revolving door.”

</title><pros>Pros – Above average salary for my position on a large client, but in general salaries are fair. Great working environment, wonderful people overall, the usual client perks. Lately they've been cleaning house which is awesome.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Questionable leadership, some bad big hires, bloated egos. Revolving door of execs for a while there and loss of large clients, one after another. Still a "from the gut" kind of culture and resistance to reliance on data and facts from strategy from some strategists and creatives.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 2012 has been great. We love the house cleaning.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Vice President (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A wonderful place to work and learn!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great colleagues, legacy of delivery and learning, wonderful brands. Afforded me a great experience, working alonside really bright teams and excellent clients.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Maybe just a little bit bureaucratic...some of the people seem to work a little less than others</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep it up - and keep JWT a wonderful place to work in.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Accounts Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pathetic experience with Calcutta branch in India”

</title><pros>Pros – Before I joint I thought there will be a lot to learn at JWT but unfortunately got nothing</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Very unprofessional work culture- The worst salaries ever- Politically induced environment where one person gets a raise while another at a junior level does not</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to retain good talent and get rid of unwanted extra staff</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“small vision”

</title><pros>Pros – clients are vast and varied.</pros>
<cons>Cons – no support from management, myopic view of running a business, no training, no long term focus.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“big.”

</title><pros>Pros – free porridge before 9 am. nice loos. cool terrace. big name clients. nice location. nice offices. nice bar.</pros>
<cons>Cons – too big to make a mark. far too easy to get very lost in the shuffle of junior people. lack of planning mentorship. feels slow.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Account Executive (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great school, but slow career progress”

</title><pros>Pros – JWT was my first real job experience and a wonderful school. Besides the amazing professionals and mentors that I had the honor of working next to for 3 years, the company's up-to-date, rapid and exciting business strategy taught me immensely about brand management, campaign execution, time and budget constraints and working in (pretty large) teams. I was also exposed to a competitive and demanding environment, which also contributed to develop my soft skills, learning the "rules of the game" and fueling my passion for Marketing, Advertising and for consistently wanting to progress in my career".</pros>
<cons>Cons – Despite my appreciated high performance and delivery of results, which were acknowledged by colleagues and supervisors, I was unable to find the opportunities I searched for in ascending positions and advancing in my professional path. The company, as many advertising agencies, is quite inflexible and opportunities for promotions, raises or further training are very rare. There came  a moment when, unfortunately, I could not sustain myself in the same position without any expectation of near-future growth.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Develop new and innovative ways of retaining talent. During my few years at the company, I saw dozens of incredible professionals leaving because of lack of recognition, feedback and career development. This doesn't have to do with salary only. If great ideas can be designed for the very important clients, why not use this inspiration for keeping the very important collaborators as well?</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The university of Advertising”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a fantastic place to learn with an abundance of intellectual resources at it's disposal</pros>
<cons>Cons – A little slow, laid back and creatively not very outwardly ambitious. Too bogged down with itself.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Loosen up the culture and make work a more enjoyable experience overall.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A place where fun is part of the work”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent working environment.Helpful and friendly colleagues.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sub-par pay.Lift doesn't work all the time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Creative Services (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you think you are Creative, it's time you get it out of your head onto a piece of paper....”

</title><pros>Pros – Super Cool environment to work in. Really awesome office. Great brands to work on.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Still stuck with the SoBo attitude of advertising. One can train there only if one's rich.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Account Executive (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great minds, crazy hours, feel-at-home experience!”

</title><pros>Pros – Brilliant talent; Great DTP team; Big accounts and a great brand activation team. Never seems like you're actually working since there is so much else going on in the office. Great opportunity to network with people from the media. Works as a great stepping stone for advancing a career in brand advertising.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Creative execution in print and outdoor. Some of the work coming out of the team is not Cannes material. Most of the other top agencies produce far better work in terms of creativity with their campaigns. There is a tendency to promote in-house which sometimes can be limiting since better outside talent is ignored</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire a new Creative Director from outside the JWT friends circle. Re-vamp the account management team by poaching for talent from other agencies.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Art Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Art Director”

</title><pros>Pros – Multi cultural environment, with many possibilities, always learning, passionate, really creative</pros>
<cons>Cons – can be stressful, social life not always on the first plan, some sacrifices to do (week ends charette)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Planning Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Creatively and strategically, I'm unhappy. But then again, I'm a naturally dissatisfied individual.”

</title><pros>Pros – International team. Some talented individuals. Good people.Good clients.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Traditionally-minded agency. Anchored in old-fashioned communication models.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Wake up and smell the latte. Social media anyone?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Art Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“13-year experience, salary of a 3-year experience employee”

</title><pros>Pros – One of the top advertising companies in Greece</pros>
<cons>Cons – Mostly people with less experience get higher salaries</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat their people equally</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Supervisor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fantastic work environment but late nights and bad money”

</title><pros>Pros – the work environment is great and very secured</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very bureaucratic. Chances of getting a raise are low, if you are not in the right circle. Might get lost in the crowd.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Creative Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Creative Director ( India -  Mumbai)”

</title><pros>Pros – Legend, the size, business , the politics these days</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots can't right now, to many of them</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Change needed to do real work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Account Director”

</title><pros>Pros – great companyworldwide agencygood at team building between departmentsgreat place for career development</pros>
<cons>Cons – long, long hoursno time for family activities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Art Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great clients but lacks a work/life balance.”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting brands to work with. Security in numbers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Up to 3 hours unpaid overtime worked everyday. Such a large company that it hard to get a pay rise etc as it's always 'in the hands' of some one more superior and out of reach. Your just a number. As far as design agencies go, they tend to have a factory feel to them, just churning out the work without much room for creativity. Your expected to give your whole life to the job, not much time for family, friends and life out side of work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value the talent you have more. We will work better if given breathing space and time with our families. Don't treat us like we are just a number as we are not all as replaceable as you might think. Being understaffed will only cost the company more in the long term.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Art Director Trainee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An experience worth a lifetime”

</title><pros>Pros – There are good people there, who help you out!Get to learn lots of stuff.get to be more confident.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing is changing.At my floor work was less.There is lota of dirty politics going on.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please there is no management between the groups of the brands! People are getting in trouble.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company, not very good salary”

</title><pros>Pros – it is a fun place to work at, great people, good work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad salary & no set work timings.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – pay more</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Planner (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing”

</title><pros>Pros – A fun place to work</pros>
<cons>Cons – No  perfectly defined working hours</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Director Media Investments (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A rewarding and learning experience”

</title><pros>Pros – The international network supports dissemination of knowledge. This is essential for skill upgradement. The stress is on creativity as large organiGMations are traditionally blamed for being not so creative - JWT has focused on this area of late. This has been done not at th cost of systems and processes that make working at JWT such a rewarding and learning experience. Method is the best learning to take from JWT.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salaries are not best in sector. The appraisal system leaves a bit to be desired and there is altogether too much systems and process focus at times such that fresh talent and fresh ideas can be sacrificed on th altar of methodology.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice office space”

</title><pros>Pros – JWT has a nicely decorated office with real art, clean bathrooms, and some good employee events.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Heavy, clueless management teams.   It's a revolving door of management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop trying to change by adding more management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Some great people but bureaucratic.”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of great people.  You can make real friends here.  Very social environment.  Fantastic roof terrace overlooking Knightsbridge.  Right next to Hyde Park which is great in the summer.  Bar downstairs.  Lunchtime BBQs when the weather is good.  Brand name carries weight.  Can be a good place to train.  Potentially a good place to network, depending on what department you're in.  Company is making an effort to create more digital and new media initiatives.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation substandard.  Salary increases can be challenging to get.  Many people leave to get paid more.  Management lacks transparency.  Can be political and bureaucratic.  Very much an old-boys club.  Account management department all over the place, hence many projects never go away.  Many people from junior to senior staff get away with very rude and aggressive behavior that would be unacceptable elsewhere.  Takes a long time to get anything done due to the size of the agency.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value employees and treat them with respect.  Pay people appropriately in order to retain some of the terrific talent at JWT.  Work to maintain a more civil environment.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Informative, challenging, exciting, interesting.”

</title><pros>Pros – -Prestigious-Rigorous-Fast paced-Interesting-Encouraging management-Employee participation and feedback appreciated-Opportunities for growth-Supervisor feedback is constructive and pertinent</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes there is a discrepancy in communication between the various levels of management, which leads to time being wasted in simply confirming instructions or feedback.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There should be a more cohesive approach to task management, in that sometimes the bigger picture gets glossed over while getting caught up in trivialties.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Global Account Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work, with opportunity to grow. Great offices in London!”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people and cultureGreat experienceBar and restaurant in the office with great rooftopVery central location in London - Knightsbridge</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary not very competitiveNot much training and development of staffEnglish public school mafia - a lot of egoAgency is very slow process wise - getting things done takes time, but this is the case at most large agencies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Better compensation and development of staff at all levels</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Was exciting in the beginning”

</title><pros>Pros – Young crowd...Fun place to work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Growth opportunity was low and limited</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My family in a foreign city”

</title><pros>Pros – Meeting great people with a very diverse backgroundIndividualism is highly welcomedCoworkers are warm-hearted and became very good friends you can rely on any time</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unstable work environment - turnover too highLack of supervision within Account teamsToo much workload and underpaid for this amount of overtimeUnclear roles and responsibilitiesPerformance reviews are not being given too much attention or importance</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make sure teams are complete, that everyone knows clearly who to report to, and that there is someone to report to and to support on a day to day basis</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Group Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not bad”

</title><pros>Pros – There is good balance with work and life.They gave good benefits.Paid overtime and car service to take you home.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There was a lot of favoritism with managers. You are easily promoted if  you work hard and are "friends" with managers. High turnover rate.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Freelance (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cool place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good environment, professional people, great facility space</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hectic and disorganized, inconsistent depending on job</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more organized</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Blindsided by paranoid management even though clients loved my performance on the accounts I ran.”

</title><pros>Pros – Compensation was good at the time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I had to call London to get my NY people a raise - WPP is truly the Evil Empire financially.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It's OK to be straight, OK Bob Jeffrey?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to cut your teeth”

</title><pros>Pros – This is a great brand, with an impressive client list. The NZ office is small (hasn't hit above 35 staff) and so there are times is feels like a close family rather than just a place you work. There is good opportunity for movement within the international network which is advantageous in advertising. The new management team promises big changes and exciting days ahead.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's small. Which means one bad apple can ruin the whole vibe of the office. It's a fairly traditional agency who are, I believe, genuinely excited about embracing the changing marketing landscape. That excitement is yet to turn into results though. The creative department has been under-staffed, under-resourced and either too experienced or not experienced enough to produce truly forward-thinking, big ideas. Suits are very good but young and inexperienced without real mentors to help guide and shape development. They often feel "thrown in at the deep end" with no safety nets or support from management figures.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you are truly trying to shake the "old stalwart" image of JWT, invest more resource in grooming and nurturing your junior talent. Otherwise you'll continue to be seen as a ivy-league prep-school for advertising execs.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall good experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salaries need to be more competitive</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Creative Group Head (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The best place to start or grow your career”

</title><pros>Pros – In a creative agency, one thing must remain certain: the creative product must always be the end point. JWT Kuala Lumpur is perhaps the most focussed advertising and communications agency in Malaysia in this regards; its unflagging drive towards product excellence is spearheaded by solid creative leadership, while account servicing are generally aligned and enthusiastic in seeing the work through. It has also built an award-winning heritage, being only the second agency in all of Asia to win a Cannes Lion Grand Prix. The place is populated by some of the most highly awarded creatives and account servicing personnel in Malaysia (even Asia), yet the people themselves are friendly, down to earth, helpful--almost family. There is plenty of meritocracy too--with senior members being promoted for solid performance in preference to hiring from the outside. For fresh graduates (or newbies without any experience in advertising), if there's a first agency to learn all the right things from, it will have to be JWT.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Like Crispin Porter + Bogusky, the constant drive for creative excellence affects work-life balance, with teams sometimes overworked and fatigued especially when balancing the finer details between client standards and internal creative expectations.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take care of some basic emotional needs, avoid pitching for lost causes, spread the wealth more evenly and eliminate indoor smoking.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good firm to learn & grow.”

</title><pros>Pros – This is a place where you can really show your strengths if you have any. But definitely not a laid back place. Prepare yourself to work hard to prove yourself. Multinational exposure and network support is powerful. Training & workshops go always to talented hard-working people only. the new CEO & ECD are quiet bold so I think things will change by time for the better of the employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is very hard to get your idea through to the real world. Lots of people criticize your work for no reason and client service support is not that good on all accounts.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Minimize levels of approvals for the creative work and consider retirement plan.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Traditional global advertising agency”

</title><pros>Pros – Great working atmosphere including building (bar, roof terrace)Established global brandMix of large global accounts and local accounts</pros>
<cons>Cons – Large company - process heavyAverage creative outputBelow average digital competenciesUn transparent pay and bonus system - below industry average pay for lower tier roles</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Recruit and train for digital - make this a serious priorityDevote more new business to getting smaller local clients who will be more likely to do creative/ digital workReduce process that preventing us from doing quick and cheap digital work for existing clientsMake pay and renumiration more transparent</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very Creative, Innovative Culture”

</title><pros>Pros – JWT has morphed some of it's agencies into a new model called Team Detroit. I believe this has created an opportunity for synergistic, innovative work in the future.</pros>
<cons>Cons – While digital is clearly the future, there is still the sense that part of the agency remains stuck in the traditional print/broadcast model of the Mad Men era.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would suggest that management continues to focus it's efforts on hiring the best and brightest young minds to stay on pace with the future opportunities.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Accounts Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very corporate type of advertising firm - if you are looking for a creative funhouse do not come here.”

</title><pros>Pros – -Great Brand-Well-known clients and opportunity to switch clients every now and then-Friendly atmosphere without too much politicking-Beer cart on fridays</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Lousy pay and no employee loyalty-long hours but relatively easy work so you are bored easily-not much room for promotion</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – -Raise salaries slightly-Treat employees better, reward loyalty-More opportunities for low-level staff other then mind-numbingly boring and routine work</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“JWT lacks the foresight to be able to help employees grow within the company.”

</title><pros>Pros – -Good hours-Some smart, fun people that are always open to learn new things-Easygoing culture-Casual dress code-Good work/life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Good work is rarely tied directly to bonuses or promotions-Senior leadership is stuck in the past, and not ready to embrace new technologies for their clients-Lack of communication down the ladder</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat your employees as an asset, not a liability.  Encourage those who are exceptional to stay and hone their careers within JWT, rather than go elsewhere where they can earn more in similar roles.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Handler (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“CheethamBellJWT”

</title><pros>Pros – Prestige - one of the most reputable agencies in Manchester with a good range of blue-chip clients.They are very competent at producing quality above the line campaigns.Great design dept.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor internal comms. Directors have lost interest in the business. Poor career advancement opportunities. Creative dept takes no pride in projects unless they are sexy ATL campaigns.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>