<name>Triangle Rent A Car Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Triangle-Rent-A-Car-Reviews-E136521.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its was something to do.”

</title><pros>Pros – Manager was pretty hands off. They pay you. If you like being outside, you might like the job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Conditions were not great. You sit in a garage all day,</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sales associate”

</title><pros>Pros – Comm, Flexible hours, Nice people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everything, Pay, Management, Other employes</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do better with employees thats all</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“its ok”

</title><pros>Pros – you receive slight employee discounts on rentals, you receive monthly commission, a lot of down time, large variety of customers</pros>
<cons>Cons – no raises, employee discount is not truly a discount, recently cut hours down, large variety of customers. accommodations for employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“CSA”

</title><pros>Pros – pretty Good job to work for</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow days during the off season</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Run, don't walk away”

</title><pros>Pros – Most location managers are great to work with. Flexible hours are usually available if you need them.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Employees are viewed as replaceable and turnover is very high. Raises are almost unheard of, promotions do happen, but not very often. Upper management's only concern is the $ they can put in their pockets. The atmosphere at that level is to bully whomever in order to get what they want.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get your head out of the sand. It is no longer 1978. Talk with your employees and listen to what they may have to say, as they have valuable information that you don't hear. Treat them as if you really do care about what they do and you will have that attitude returned to you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Keep looking....”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a job that you can use for resume.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very poor pay, no performance reviews. High employee turnover/revolving door type place.  Much much much more....trust me.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Follow and enforce the rules of the company handbook.  Increase hourly wage scale to keep quality employees from leaving... Upgrade the benefit package.  Take your head out of the sand, this is 2013.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-10</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible scheduling, nice employees, fun work environment, and easy to learn.</pros>
<cons>Cons – None that I can think of.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst Job Ever”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible HoursFriendly work staffInformal work enviroment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low payImpossible to get a promotionless than 10% of employees met sales goalLow employee MoraleOutdated equipment</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increase employee pay</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Rental Agent (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ok pay for too much work”

</title><pros>Pros – team like environmentfreedom to work without someone standing over youplenty of down time during the less busy season to sit around and fantasize about a better life</pros>
<cons>Cons – paycheck is laughable unless you get a huge commission check - which after taxes is a jokesmaller company, so not as popular as bigger rental companies, so not very busy making it harder to make commissionupper management sends out condescending emails that boast how some locations are awesome and and others basically suckforced to upsell costumers till youre blue in the faceno real opportunities to advancecar detailers are paid peanuts so when they quit (which is often) rental agents have to slave away washing cars and handling customers all in the same breathhours of operation are longer and more inconvenient than other rental companies</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – do more to ensure your employees are happy and in return youll have more loyal workers glad to put in the extra effort....free pizza might satisfy a class of 5th graders but working adults? not so much</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun”

</title><pros>Pros – flexible hours, commission plus base pay</pros>
<cons>Cons – long hours, not enough opportunities during the week</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – na</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>