<name>Guggenheim Museum Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Guggenheim-Museum-Reviews-E137747.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great work environment, terrible pay”

</title><pros>Pros – your co-workers are fun and professional</pros>
<cons>Cons – while the benefits are good, the hourly pay for store employees is dismal</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Visitor Services (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work..”

</title><pros>Pros – good working environment/ co workers</pros>
<cons>Cons – low pay, no advancement opportunities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“could be better”

</title><pros>Pros – -Very kind and warm team in the Curatorial Department- For the most part it was actual work, and not a coffee-and-dry-cleaning internship- Provides excellent exposure to other arts and cultural spaces in the city, through the Museum Culture Seminar held every week- A very good and sincere attempt from Guggenheim Internship Department to make the internship enriching for interns- Very open communications- Although they do not have job placements, they keep the interns and ex- interns in the loop whenever there is a job opening at the Museum.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Does not pay- For those who hold some work experience, the internship will not be particularly challenging. Personally I did not find the work intellectually stimulating.- Very little opportunity for working across departments, or learning what other departments are doing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – pick up on the particular abilities and qualifications of interns, and allow them to use that to contribute positively to their work at Guggenheim. What is the point of hiring highly educated and qualified interns if they are only meant to do filing and data entry?</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Solid company to work for, but salaries could be more balanced across the board.”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits packageExcellent health insurance coverage with low employee contribution and additional coverage for domestic partnersSuccessful 403(b) retirement plan options</pros>
<cons>Cons – Competitiveness amongst peersDisparity in salary ranges between various departmentsSome departments seem bloated with employees; others getting by with the bare minimum staff</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great internship experience”

</title><pros>Pros – All of the interns do actual work (i.e., not just fetching coffee)There are a number of departments to choose from when applying so interns are able to specialize"Museum Culture Seminars" every week in which interns are given an inside look at various aspects of the art and museum worldFree admission to the Guggenheim and any museum in the city with your staff ID</pros>
<cons>Cons – The internship is completely unpaid though there is a stipend available to graduate student internsSome of the Museum Culture Seminars can be boring</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I only worked closely with my direct supervisor and department so I cannot speak to the overall management but I was happy with my experience</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“exciting”

</title><pros>Pros – collaborative, team building, can do attitude</pros>
<cons>Cons – lots of work, work around the clock</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more acknowledgment of staff's hard work</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Learning Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great intern program, good feedback from supervisors, opportunities to do more than data entry or filing, nice work environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not much room for growth</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good connections, no pay”

</title><pros>Pros – Made good connections, learned a decent amount, enjoyed free museum entrance</pros>
<cons>Cons – No pay, given work no one else wants, little one-on-one attention</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>