<name>Model N Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Model-N-Reviews-E13771.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Member of Technical Staff (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok Ok”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent place to work, good culture.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Currently in a down hill</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more pro active</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Room for Improvement for Boston Office”

</title><pros>Pros – Work life balance with opportunity to work from home when neccesaryFully stocked Kitchen and weekly catered lunchCompany outings - dinners, cookouts, annual clambakeReimbursement for healthcare opt-out (great bonus if your spouse has coverage)Quiet office - good for heads down working</pros>
<cons>Cons – Quiet office - there is no buzz of creativity in the airMeetings often scheduled on west coast time (during our lunch/dinner)Aggressive release cycles often lead to poor qualityNo visibility into company health - 6 months after celebrating an IPO, 25% of the company was sent to pack up their desks.Inflated company goals ensure bonuses don't have to be paid out.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good work culture, work life balance”

</title><pros>Pros – Committed leadership teamLeadership team is always accessibleWork life balance- flexibility to work from home</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing that I havent experienced in other companies that stands out. Perhaps better processes if I can point one.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review for Model N”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly people and great Friday lunch. Sorry, wish I had more to say.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Middle and upper management are a mess, lazy, do not empower their employees, are not proactive. Allot of meetings, slide decks, promises; then go back to their office and do nothing. Lazy outside sales people at this company. The morale at this company is super low unfortunately. People look and act depressed coming through the front door. I've never seen so many unhappy people in one building. You can feel the heaviness in the building.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upper management needs to be fired. Instead of laying off good people, fire upper management. TRAIN new people coming in, do not throw your own people under the bus to serve your agendas. Show up and lead with integrity. Sale this company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Uncertain Future”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. The best aspect of working for Model N is the coworkers. In general, the people at Model N are friendly and easy to get along with.2. Depending on the needs of the customer, the job is very flexible and allows for working remotely when necessary.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. The biggest downside to Model N is the lack of job security. With Model N's current situation, it is hard to tell what the future will hold for the company. After a recent round of heavy layoffs, the uncertainty among employees can be felt.2. As a consultant for Model N a lot of time is spent battling with the Product Development team. Often times the software does not work as it should and there is unnecessary push back from PD when the focus should be on what makes the costumer happy.3. It often feels that there is not enough support and team members can be stretched thin at times.4. The compensation and benefits leave much to be desired.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good team environment, but really bad higher management. Sales team sucks”

</title><pros>Pros – Good team environmentFriday free lunchHigh tech (development team) department was good, but it's not there in US anymore.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The annual performance review sucks! The raise in no where near market standardsThe higher management really sucks. Due to the fault of Sales team there was huge lay off with no hints about it until the it was done.They use old technologies.They don't have good strategy for new products. They don't have proper direction.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire good sales people and do keep in mind about people's livelihood.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Architect (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Never seen a company goes down hill this fast.”

</title><pros>Pros – - Few smart employees- Zack Rinat, CEO who tries hard</pros>
<cons>Cons – I don't think I can do enough justice on what the company lacks for, because there are so many.- Benefits, one of the worst. You end paying 40-60% more health and other benefits in terms of copayment- No 401k employer contribution- Worst kitchen stocked with all cheap food from Costco.- Friday Lunch, whatever Office manager likes it.Mostly, you end up in eating all the cheap and junk food, pizzas being the worst.- Middle management, if you want to learn politics then learn from them- Product management, you must be kidding.- Old timers, CTO.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get your act fast. This is Silicon Valley.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awful”

</title><pros>Pros – I just put this review here because I read some of reviews here. I worked in Model N. I just have one advice to you, stay away from them as much you can. It has verbally and mentally abusive environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – old fashioned companyno work life balanceno growth path</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Terrible”

</title><pros>Pros – I am writing review here just for one reason, I do not want someone repeat my awful experience with them. I worked there and I can tell you just stay away from them. It has mentally and verbally abusive environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – old fashion companyno work life balanceno growth in careerno leadership</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very stressful and not fun”

</title><pros>Pros – Mostly a great team with 'can do' attitude. Trying to satisfy customers in very hard markets by making up significant shortcomings in the product with services</pros>
<cons>Cons – Opaque decision making process which is not data driven and with no discernible method. People do not count in the services organization. Strange, as people are what this is all about</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get real about the products and pay attention to what your team is telling you</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Huge Dissapointment”

</title><pros>Pros – *Decent Breakfast cereal/Drinks*Independence in completing tasks*Friendly open culture/CEO is very open and approachable</pros>
<cons>Cons – *Layoffs*Huge inflated management layer*No work-life balance-expectation is to work 24/7, travel on any notice, and give up any life outside of work.Upper Management all flaunt beutiful cars*Engineering is abroad-QA is horrible and work needs to be redone*Benefits-No 401K, Pay seems almost below market rate</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Engineering needs help big time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Had some bumps, but still a great place to work,”

</title><pros>Pros – Lot of resources in terms of money, expertise, and support.Good managers and good work-life balance (at least here in the Boston office).Good opportunities for learning and advancing one's career.Recently had some layoffs, making the company more lean and efficient.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A little bit disconnected from HQ office in CA.Incentive structure is a little flat (ie. not much reward for those putting in extra effort).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Find ways to address the "cons" listed above.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Principal Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stay away unless you are ready to put 90 Hour work weeks”

</title><pros>Pros – Base Pay is good comparativelySome remote working potential</pros>
<cons>Cons – Expected to work technically 24/7Have to travel to unexpected client locations.Poor Product DevelopmentNo sustained growth of the company unless another Big Pharma buys their productBonus is not based on factors that employees controlHorrible Work life balance with expectation to work 90% of weekends in a yearThere are a bunch of Uptight, stuck up  individuals in Middle Management who will run this company to the grave. (However they do have fancy titles - Director, Associate Director, Associate Assistant Director, Jr. Associate Director). Except for a few Technical resources, everyone is a Director</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Fix your product and fire the "middle Management' idiots</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Think twice”

</title><pros>Pros – Some good people work at the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management tries hard to improve the company, which is good.  However, they don't seem to understand what the problems are which says a lot about understanding the challenges of the company.  Employees are treated poorly and large portion of bonuses are based on factors that employees can't control.  Company has a core set of values they love to emphasize but they don't follow them or hire people that fit the core values.  Turnover is so high you're constantly re- creating processes or spending huge amount of time training/ teaching.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Broken Engineering Organization”

</title><pros>Pros – Profitable Company.  Will sometimes adopt new tech.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The build system is broken.  The is little QA Automation.  There is absolutely no Modularity.  No attention is paid to best practices.  The Platform team is too small to properly support a company of this size.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more accepting of input.   Senior management tends to adopt a strategy without seeking any input and then refuses to discuss even minor changes.  They are happy to bring in outside consultants to advise the company, but they then either ignore the consultants input or in some cases have even become hostile when the consultant offers an opinion that conflicts with what they have already decided to do.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Enticed by salary, awakened by TERRIBLE corporation from the top down.”

</title><pros>Pros – Enticing starting salary, and that's where it ends.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor leadershipNon-existent managementZERO work life balanceTangible knowledge of no employee value</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't be lured in by the salary, mediocre benefits, and current IPO. This company places no value on it's employees, the end user product is a joke, and the indecency of employee treatment is deplorable.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Member of Technical Staff (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Rotten middle management, everyone on vacation, no accountability, no innovation”

</title><pros>Pros – I'm gathering the below information from my perspective as well as other current and former employees.- There are some good people there. Everybody is very friendly, nice and a few of them are technically ok.- The CEO is strong, Model N is running for the long haul- Good professional service branch- They sell their software and services very well- Leader on the market- Great unexplored potential in terms of innovation and business potential. There is a lot of business knowledge at Model N but nobody seems to be willing to take this knowledge to create a product to revolutionize either Analytics or the pharma industry or both. Yet I believe they can.- There are really smart top executives (some less smart).</pros>
<cons>Cons – - No innovation, old and ridiculous technical stacks (salesforce, qlikview, old, clunky Java framework)- Complete distrust from Product Managers towards developers (justifiably so)- Rotten middle management (see below)- The company grew too fast, making some bad hiring decisions (bad hiring is ok, not firing fast is not).- The software developers' salary are not on par with other companies in the bay area, even if they tell you the opposite. Don't believe them.- It's becoming more and more political within my team. It has always been political between teams. I think this comes from several factors. First, the project is not delivered on time so the management/developers try to cover their ass, second, both developers and managers don't seem to focus on delivering a product to be used by customers so they spend their energy elsewhere.- A lot of incompetent people (especially in QA, developers, middle management).- Prefer to put processes in place instead of making people accountable. It dramatically slows down productivity but justifies the managers' jobs.- Employees and managers alike prefer to go play table tennis instead of finishing their tasks for the sprint (maybe because there is no accountability). Most of them are here from 10am to 4pm (a bit less on friday evening).- My team has 3 managers for about 15 people. I was floored when one of them said he "did not do anything today" during a daily update. The following day he was in meetings and the day after he reviewed commits... Maybe there was a table tennis tournament at this time so this explains that...- All the talent has left the company since the managers were more interested in their politics. Talent is replaced with incompetent people.- It is not a software company anymore but a service company. It may be interesting to work for Model N on the service side, not on the development side.- The CEO is either completely out of touch from what's really happening on the development side or he is fully aware of it which is even more worrying.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Good people want to innovate, love accountability. When people leave a company, they most probably leave their manager even if they don't say it. Maybe the amount of people quitting in the recent months should be a red flag ?To Zack Rinat. Please throw an eye or put a hand in both your 'strategic initiatives'. I think they were great initiatives, wrongly executed. The analytics team needs a real director, leading innovation, not a kid. The other team does not need 3 managers (2 now). Most of this team is on vacation. Hopefully the UX lead and PM pushing the product, but they are the only ones.If a project keeps pushing it's release date, one or several people are not doing their job...The company has great potential, unexploited.I'm not worried about the future of Model N.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not well organized”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice people. Big office any kitchen. A lot of parking. Beautiful area. Strong CEO</pros>
<cons>Cons – No room for creativityToo many managersVery hirarchical</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There is a disconnect between management and employees who do the actual work. They seem to have different agenda. Please define: Where is the company going? Strong CEO.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a bad company to work for.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work life balance and opportunities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing bad to say really.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stressful”

</title><pros>Pros – Still try to figure those out</pros>
<cons>Cons – too many cons for me to list</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – it's not enough to have a list of values you aspire to. employees really should adhere to them</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Frantic pace, can't keep up with growth in customer facing departments, and no focus on employee growth”

</title><pros>Pros – Fast growingHigh demand for productsBecoming de facto industry standardVery high caliber customer facing employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – Recent addition of "IBM mafia" at senior and mid-level management - no real understanding of Model N culture, products or sources of past success.Culture changing from support of risk-taking to "identify and punish those who make mistakes"</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on the IPO has detracted from the company's past successful processes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Mostly non transferrable experience gained.”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy learning curve in the High Tech vertical.Gain good experience using your Java and SQL skills.Some very smart people work there.You have an opportunity to make connections with people leaving and joining other companies.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Despite tough learning curve in the Life Sciences vertical, no effort made to keep valuable employees.Mostly properitery technologies and frameworks - not useful for future employers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Consultant”

</title><pros>Pros – At Model N, you will find yourself a part of a team that offers a variety of perspectives and also encourages you to share your own.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Could improve on building more dynamic culture, employee training</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engagement Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Can get political and can impact your morale when expectations are not communicated”

</title><pros>Pros – Some work from home sometimes but then some people have taken a really bad advantage of that and impacted new comers and put projects in jeoprady</pros>
<cons>Cons – - political- unfair HR practices- can get very isolating- some old timers are very selfish about their knowledge to the new comers and the management is willing to let go bad habits of old timers and punish the new comers a lot .. seriously I am not the kind who uses these negative reviews but they can lure you into a great offer and then go back on their own promises</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create a better mentorship program for your professional services and have a better understanding of performance management</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-01</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Solutions Architect (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing collection of smart folks”

</title><pros>Pros – Work with an amazingly smart group of people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working through 3 timezones can get rough</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Member of Technical Staff (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Software developer at Model N”

</title><pros>Pros – Pretty stable job with good work/life balance. No micro management.Interesting challenges on the business side.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No technical innovation, not an engineer-friendly company, cheap company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Generally good, satisfied with almost everything”

</title><pros>Pros – Conducive work environment, challenging but interesting projects</pros>
<cons>Cons – Disconnected among world-wide offices, need more interactions</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consulting (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“very political and lack of support from old timers”

</title><pros>Pros – dynamic environment but  a niche company</pros>
<cons>Cons – - very old school mentality- over commitment of resources- high pressure without the support for new comers- lack of structure- can get political</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – Leader in it's nicheExposure to fortune 500 companiesFull visibility into the company's financial performanceSharesFantastic staffMust be a team payer</pros>
<cons>Cons – UnderstaffingLong hoursNot enough women in managerial positions</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More females should be incorporated in leading  / management positions</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Mixed Experience, Good Environment for Growth, Low Compensation”

</title><pros>Pros – Model N's work has a clear purpose.  My manager was flexible about my hours and vacation time.  I did not encounter issues with office politics or favoritism.  Model N is more willing than most employers to sponsor foreign workers who need H-1B visas or other sponsorship.  (Perhaps as a result, the workforce is more diverse and international than in the average company, with a particular focus on workers from India, where Model N has an office.)  The Redwood City offices are modern and clean, with good facilities and computers.  The company is profitable.</pros>
<cons>Cons – My salary was lower than I would have received at other tech companies in the area.  Benefits are just the basics, like health insurance (e.g. not like Google, with free meals, the ability to take your dog to work, etc.)  Model N's financials were poorly documented in its early years, resulting in long and difficult audits.  Management has been promising an IPO since at least 2006, but it never comes.  (At one point, they almost had it, then called it off when the economy turned bad.)  There have been large layoffs in the past, correlated with bad economic times (the tech bubble burst, etc.).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I appreciate that you've built a company that provides livelihoods for many people, and also eases the logistical burden of pharma and semiconductor companies in managing their revenue.  You're doing good work.  To take it to the next level, I'd recommend three things.  (1) Try to ensure there are no future layoffs due to the economy by prioritizing employee retention and hiring above other expenses.  (2) If possible, consider offering some inexpensive extra benefits for employees, like the ability to bring dogs to work.  (3) Keep growing.  There are many large companies with complex revenue issues, and you could expand past the pharma and semiconductor industries.  Doing less customization of the software on a per-client basis may make it easier to scale up.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Intellectually strong environment with easy burn out factor.”

</title><pros>Pros – Intelligent employees willing to share informationWeekly company meetings with a lot of information (though sometimes it's overkill)</pros>
<cons>Cons – No career growth or professional development within my organization unless your an engineer. Always expected to do more, even when juggle 3-4 projects.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Serious look into and define career paths and professional growth plans for all levels of the company; it's been on the employee sat. survey for a while now.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“WAS a great place to work, but unmanaged growth has created unneeded layers and bureaucracy”

</title><pros>Pros – Learn cutting edge business and technology with smart people working with industry leaders as clients</pros>
<cons>Cons – Top heavy for the amount of revenues it brings in</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Reduce instability by reducing top heaviness</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Member of Technical Staff (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to work if you're self-motivated, and can deal with clearing up ambiguity on your own.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great opportunities for career advancement, personal growth, and development.  Debate and questioning of the norm are encouraged practices, and politics don't come into play.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working on a complex product oftentimes means that nobody understands the complete picture.  Knowledge is often silo'd and it can be difficult to manage cross-team communications when everyone is busy.  This is not a problem if you're OK with playing detective and tracking down the right people to get your answers, but it can be somewhat of a challenge.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Encourage better cross-team communication and knowledge sharing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Principal Member Technical Staff (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review Headline”

</title><pros>Pros – Work on the core technologies that makes one very stronger on the technology front</pros>
<cons>Cons – Stick to same product with not much great enhancements in some of the areas of the product</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management needs to share the required information to the down level employees making them feel part of the team.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“9-5ers struggling to get to the next level”

</title><pros>Pros – work/life balance is allowedcorporate culture strong in the organizationgood people to work withgood performance is recognizednot a lot of politics among entry level employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – poor vision for the future from management (no realistic, attainable goals in sight)people have no desire to become a great companya lot of 9-5ers stagnant in middle managementreliant on few super talented individualsdisconnect between management desire and realitylots of politics at middle management and upper managementtalented youth leave the company within a few years</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The company needs fresh blood and new ideas to move forward.  The same old people running the same company for 10 years has caused it to stagnate.  CEO and executives need to be more hands-on if the company is to take the next step because middle managers surely will not do it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>SMTS-2 (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A struggling company trying to succeed, but making the wrong moves”

</title><pros>Pros – - Fair pay- Work load manageable- Friendly people- Free Friday lunches- Allows for balanced work and personal life</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Management is not experienced enough.  Planned projects half baked.- A hint of nepotism in it's way of promotion.- Some talented people do not get recognized, as result people are leaving</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on retention and recognition, and not just doing the fluffy stuff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Used to be good, but is getting nowhere”

</title><pros>Pros – Cooperative culture. Flexible work schedule.</pros>
<cons>Cons – After several reorganization, it has become more and more a political place in recent years and the current middle management team is very immature.The domain is narrow and the technology is proprietary thus there is not much career growth potential and future marketability.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to retain the great developers and managers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Web Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wanted Growth at the expense of Employee lives”

</title><pros>Pros – Allowed me to learn and grow in a pre-corporate environment allowing me to experience what the real work force in a big company is like.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management never cared about personal employee needs. Constantly disapproved of work completed but never expressed why or how to make it better. Never clear on what needed to be done. Used up valuable time on minor projects that were later never even used and then complained when bigger projects were not completed on time. Expected the work of 5 people from 1 person.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Instead of treating your employees like slaves, why not ask them why they leave so fast after starting there? There's a reason why people don't stand for way you treat your employees, i highly suggest looking into it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-10-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Member of Technical Staff (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for technical growth”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Lot of technically strong people to work with2. Very well architected application software3. There is always interesting projects to work on during new releases and hence great opportunity to grow technically within the company4. No laidback culture</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Lot of technically strong people but many of them are workholics, so makes you one workholic as well.2. Pay is below market standards unless one bargained pretty well at the time of offer3. Career growth is limited as there are too many people working hard and smart at the same time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to pay attention to people development as well</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Member of Technical Staff (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company and execs serious about success, but don't know how to communicate with employees.”

</title><pros>Pros – The company (and CEO) just won't quit or settle for second best.  The executive team tackles challenges in a very aggressive way.  I had a good relatively experience on the product side, and felt appreciated.  Lots of detailed company information in company meetings.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very serious atmosphere.  Overall sense from management that company comes before family or a personal life.  Senior management very defensive about criticism from employees.  Some employees seem "black listed" and get treated differently than "star" employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work on improving your people skills with employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-11-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Occasionally chaotic start up experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Good opportunities for growth, provided you are part of the right projects.  Colleagues are smart and friendly, and willing to help out.  Casual working environment, flexible with telecommuting, etc.  Management is remarkably candid and open about discussing company matters.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible documentation of product makes it hard to really feel confident that you know what you're doing.  A cavalier company attitude of trial by fire, which can be traumatic to those not used to that kind of environment.  Company's focus is on expanding product functionality instead of quality, which leads to a horribly buggy product.  Some client implementations became a tight rope walk of keeping the current system stable while implementing new features.  People are rewarded for their work depending on how high visibility the project was.  Those put on smaller clients had a tougher time with career advancement.  Working in consulting gives no long term stability, which impacts work life balance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Put some more emphasis on product quality.  Pay more attention to giving mentoring opportunities, and invest in people development.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company not what it used to be. Everyone is trying to leave.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good opportunity for advancement simply because of vacancies left by the number of people leaving. The company is not likely to fail. There is very little competition in the niche market. Their only competitor was on the verge of going under. However, Model N failed to deliver the knock out punch. Now there is chance the competitor may come back. Look to the management for the failed opportunity and simply poor execution. Executives are open about the problems facing the company. The transparency should be applauded. They just went through a round of laid offs to trim out some fat.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very high employee turnover. You are lucky if you get to work with a person for over a year. Management is misguided on the product. Trying to put out too many releases stuffed with too many features. Everyone on the already thin engineering team is rushed. The only possible result is poor quality software. The development process is a complete train wrack. Multiple staggered releases. Everything must be rushed. Management fails to recognize the process is wrong. Company is forced to start an office in Indian because everyone in US is leaving. They use an potential IPO as bait to attract new hires but failed to mention they already had one failed attempt at IPO.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Why is everyone trying to leave this company? Have you done anything to address this issue?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A company with a promise of great future, but inability to value its employees”

</title><pros>Pros – The best reason to work for Model N are the people you work with. It's a dynamic environment. You have the opportuunity to work with many brilliant folks. The company is very ambitious and so far has been successful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are a lot of politics. There is virtually no opprortunity for professional growth and development. Recently the treatment has been poor on both personal and professional levels. There is no opportunity to advance or move to other positions in the company. The compensations is below market level.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Put the people who work for you first.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-07-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Line Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A company with great opportunities in a niche market”

</title><pros>Pros – The company treats employees very well and rewards good performance.  I see a lot of people getting promoted from within and many long time employees who started right out of school are now at director level or above.Model N is also great at balancing work with life.  I see people who are given extra time off when kids are born and others who get a lot of support from the company and their immediate supervisor for things like school.  It's nice to see a small company doing that.I also like the fact that management is transparent and communicative.  Any management decisions are reviewed with the entire companies and employees are given opportunities to provide feedback.  I feel like a part of the decision making process here rather than just an observer.Last but not least, I think Model N is a good financial opportunity.  The company is growing and is a good candidate for either an IPO or an acquisition.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very industry specific.  The company focuses on financial software for pharma and high tech companies, which means employees need a lot of technical information and knowledge.  The learning curve is very steep.  This means that new employees sometimes feel overwhelmed when they join.  There is a lot to learn about the product and the industry.The Model N location is also not ideal.  It's right in the middle of a big office park which makes finding lunch spots difficult.  Although there is a close by Cal Train station, which does make the commute a bit better.Finally, I think it's honest to say that, as a small company, Model N is not as stable as a large organization like Oracle or Google.  If you're looking for safety, a small company is probably not the best place to find that and Model N is no exception.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Look at more verticals.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-07-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Member of Technical Staff (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company, bad development practices”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work/life balance, decent pay (though you might have to fight for it), good benefits/vacation.  Very flexible regarding work schedule.From the perspective of an employee in Product Development: You will get to work on an amazingly large and complex app without being boxed into one tiny role.  While this has its ups and downs, it will teach you things few other companies can.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long development cycles + waterfall model + complex codebase + unplanned support work = prepare to fall behind.  When you do, prepare for more people bugging you for progress reports than actually helping to resolve the issue.  There is little interest in working on anything not immediately and directly sellable to a customer.  They are not "pro-training"; expect to do most learning and skill development on your own time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The business side is important, but pay more attention to what's going on internally in PD and PS.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good engineering processes but need stronger culture/people with self responsibility”

</title><pros>Pros – Its a good place to learn engineering processes if you're just starting out: automated regression tests, large test suites, individual developer development environments, dual monitors, work laptop, formal design specifications required prior to beginning work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Passing the buck from some members of the organization rather than taking responsibility to ensure that their part is done well.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do what is necessary to bring the best into the organization.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager-Product Development (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Product Developement department is more or less driven by Services Dept because of lack of strong Management”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Company to learn and grow fasterVery flexible for employeesVery Transparent organization</pros>
<cons>Cons – PD should have its own agenda, priorities, processes to handle releases. IT should not always be revolving around customer and services as it is a R&D division rather than a billable Team.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>SMTS (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company is on the verge of extinction.”

</title><pros>Pros – The Pros part of this company is that if you are not part of this company you are very lucky. Almost 6 month back company was doing good but IPO has made them beggar.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work life balance ever Worst, you will loss every thing and have to stick with Laptop even on weekend to save your job and even though you will not be sure what will happen to next morning.Management is hiding a lot of information which was not there 6 month back. Senior management are just doing time pass and sucks blood of  employees. No structure in organization like "if you are free do this or do that ". And one more thing they don't have proper skilled people now most of them are moving out. By mistake if you go there, just for an alert mostly you will be interviewed by Entry level even if you are 5+ experienced guy thus you can better understand company situation.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No use as if they would have listen us ,situation would never be like this, But just a message that a company wins only and only with a skilled set of people never by a useless senior management and servile.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great work life balance”

</title><pros>Pros – -Flexible work environment.- Great team</pros>
<cons>Cons – - lack of clarity about career growth.- becoming a hierarchical organisation from being a flat one.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good -> (tending towards) not so good”

</title><pros>Pros – Good initial pay offer but less increments;Nice process in place</pros>
<cons>Cons – Micro management at its best;work load levels are high</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Management abilities of  Model N India”

</title><pros>Pros – Model N India :Model N provides facilities like work from home. Flexible timings.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Model N India :Poor management. If some thing happens in the team Management will not react and Management says handle on your own.Priority given to more Senior resources, What ever Senior resources do Management accepts it whether they do positive or negative tasks. because if a senior leaves the company there is a sevior impact on company.No powers to HR Department . Every thing controlled by Managers.Poor training facilities for the product. There is no repository for the Product documentation. More Dependency.They record one- on- one meetings.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Immediate reaction to be needed from Management when some thing happens in the Organization.More powers to be given to HR Department.Improve the traing facilities and Product documentation.Don't blindly accept what ever senior resources says.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Senior Management, Old fashioned”

</title><pros>Pros – Senior Management appear to care about the well being of everyone in the company.There is great communication from Senior Management.You are working with the company, not for the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The mentality is very old and out dated. If you hated tech companies in the late 80's and early 90's, you will not enjoy it. If you liked how things used to be done, this could be a plus for you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management needs to figure out how to jump from the 90's to the 2010's. (What does this mean?? It means, back in the 90's, Companies said, "no you can't do that". Today, Companies say, "What do you need us to do?")</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company selling complex solutions”

</title><pros>Pros – Good company culture and high caliber people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited internal growth opportunities and career paths</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – CEO needs to provide management team more autonomy and authority.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No worK load, chill environment”

</title><pros>Pros – No work loadWatch CID, Taarak Mehta ka oolta chasmah , movies anytime.Play TT all-timeGood pay for doing nothing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No cafeteria in the office.Only coffee and tea are served.There is only 1 TT table in the office.No cultural diversity.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Development Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Open Culture 2. No Restrictions 3. No Hierarchy 4. Lots of freedom to do anything 5. Very less schedule pressures. 6. Interacting people 7. Highly motivated team.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Processes in-process of stabilization. 2. More control in US office 3. More dependency on Platform.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing opportunity for beginners”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Good management.2. Agile process3. Recognizes hard workers.4. Expanding within the LS industry.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Need to perform better in HT industry.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Higher Management should not treat employees as slaves”

</title><pros>Pros – Support from the immediate leads is very wellFlexible hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – Higher management thinks employees as bunch of slaves in accordance to behavior.There is a realisability of partiality between employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't let 5 yrs or more leave your company they are very valuable.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good friendly place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Work From Home, Flexibility, Friendly Team, Competency, Nature of Work, Recognition, Perks, Guidance, Options available,  Great leadership team, Company policies</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited technological growth available, Kind of work that we tend to do could be more challenging.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please adopt more employee friendly policies.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“balanced work place”

</title><pros>Pros – Lot of benefit package.balanced work environment.flexible timing.transfer of product knowledge from seniors to juniors is good.overall ok.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the location of the company, product not hitting indian market. there will be a saturation of product knowledge at one stage.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bias Management”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible Timings.Frequent Updates from the higher management about the company future plans.If you are coming from some reputated company,you can bargain good on salary.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you are working in PD team, you can enjoy the work environment.For rest of the people, management treats them as labor that works hard but will not get enough.No work life balance for PS team members. No recognition for PS team members.HR team is very bias towards PD.So moral of the story...If you are in PD you are king else Beggers are no choosers!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don’t be so bias.PS gets you the maximum revenue. At least treat them with respect.PS works hard Works round the clock. But gets not even peanuts.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great”

</title><pros>Pros – Provides challenges. Willing to give you increasingly challenging opportunities if you can prove your capabilities. And the Management team is top notch.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Up to you to make the best case for rising up. Initiative is appreciated and can help you here. Without initiative, one might stagnate.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Not much I can give. They do a great job of steering the company for the short and long term.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very Comfortable and Challenging Atmosphere”

</title><pros>Pros – Challenging tasks where we can get a exposure for advancement.Fun at Work. No Hard rules,restrictions or timings.Excellent work and Personal life balance.Flexibility of work.Very cooperative Management and staff.Transparency from High level Management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Little Politics among high level Managers.Poor Company Branding.After certain period with the company there is nothing much to learn for you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Training plan for new joins should be improved alot.Futuristic Human Resource Planing should be improved.Equal importance should be give to all products.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Challenging work, good learning experiences, long hours”

</title><pros>Pros – Growing company that is a leader in it's niche. Very bright people, high energy, strong focus on the customer. Annual meeting in California is nice. Top leaders are very smart people who are easy to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Culture and standard operating model is to work very long hours. Its expected. Hard to have a personal or family life. Learning curve for the product is very steep and not a great process to bring people up to speed efficiently. Makes your first couple of years with the company more painful than it needs to be. Company is ripe for acquisition so long term future is unsure.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve repeatable processes so people can work smarter and not harder</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pretty Decent Employer”

</title><pros>Pros – * Small Company and rapidly growing in the software life sciences space* Lots of Marquee Clients* Decent Work-Life Balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – * Work is downright tedious/monotonous especially in the professional services side. If you are expecting a consulting type gig, it's far and few* BA's now are doing a whole bunch of menial support tasks that should be handled by Tech Support</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Model N work culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice place to work.Good balance between in professional and personal life.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very small company.Bit of political environment in immediate managers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They are excellent and take every care to reach out every employee.They give every importance to the employee's interest.Keep the pat .... going on!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ok place”

</title><pros>Pros – OK place to work nothing great</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management does not care about employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Go with an exit, you will never IPO in this market</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK place to work.  Needs some changes at Sr. Mgmt level”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting and sometimes challenging work.  Talented, nice group of people at the lower levels.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not always fair in review and advancement process.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Time for some changes. There are definitely people who do not fit in the desired culture.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No value for people. You will become a slave!”

</title><pros>Pros – Hard working. Woroholics. Can learn how to survive in a cut throat environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No value for people. No transperancy. Lack of job security. No setting expectations correctly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn to communicate with people clearly and have the courage to call a spade a spade.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>