<name>E-Emphasys Technologies Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/E-Emphasys-Technologies-Reviews-E139819.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2010-05-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“never graduated from startup”

</title><pros>Pros – Salaries are bit above average. Freedom to take initiatives but ideas are hadly accepted. As long as you are on a project life is cool as company does not interfere</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sloppy management, no reviews, no planning, New ideas are heard but never accepted or impmented, managment by crisis philosphy. Few documented process which are implemented cases by case basis</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Come ot of the startup mode, give middle management responsibilities and authority. Back your works and decisions. Implement policies and procedures.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-02</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Professional/Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“e-Emphasys Technology Mumbai - pathetic work culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Indian IT Company , having business in  software implementaion and support.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work culture is like manufacturing industry. Fixed working hrs. If one wish to leave 10 min early for urgent work/problem need to take half day not good especially ladies.Unprofessional policies for employeesIncriment and bonus percentage is very poor as good as nilManagement can tell any one anytime to put down the paperIts a family affair so outside employees are victim of this systemNo value for employee's opinion and feedbackAccept job in this company / option if you dont have any other offer.....</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve policies for employeesRespect employees ( Jr. and Sr. both)Improve product and work culture</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>