<name>Gensler Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Gensler-Reviews-E14045.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Architectural Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Social office environment”

</title><pros>Pros – I enjoyed how friendly and welcoming the office was, the quality of the work, different disciplines represented, and the work hard/play hard culture. Coworkers took time to teach me and took an interest in the quality of my internship.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As an intern, I wasn't assigned any design tasks and wasn't a full member of the design team (though I expected this).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast, furious, but fun.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great culture, creative people and lots of awesome design.  The clients are top notch and so is the work on all levels.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots of overtime, though they do pay for it.  Bonus days celebration money and extra holiday parties should go into employee compensation instead.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be aware of and give breaks to over-exerted staff.  Don't be afraid to set some rules and practice some discipline.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Refreshing culture, great people, no limit to opportunity. Great brand.”

</title><pros>Pros – Innovative, entrepreneurial and collaborative work environment/mindset.Smart people who are leaders in their field and approach design holisticallyGreat firmwide support resources that you don't get in smaller firmsAbility to work on projects you want to work on</pros>
<cons>Cons – One firm approach sometimes difficult to balance with local/entreprenuerial approach</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to drive innovation in not only design but management. Don't get stuck stale in management approach or practices.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Prefer Not Answer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible Company - Bad Management”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice Facilities, happy hour and cool co-workers</pros>
<cons>Cons – Every DEPARTMENT: management micro-manages, they do not like any work you complete, Long hours and pretentious people. Most of the employees are fun people, but there is not a single good person in management at this company. Dress code is very strict and management don't care about how others feel.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You are pretentious, arrogant and you only care about the outside. Not a single one of you are a good person, you should be ashamed of yourselves.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Interior Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hyped, overrated culture and values, highly political & less deserving senior management”

</title><pros>Pros – Free food, Friday beer socials</pros>
<cons>Cons – Underpaid and undervalued staff, frequent 7 day weeks, no overtime, employee development here is a sham</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you don't care for design, and hard working employees have the spine to say it,than hide behind clever marketing tactics. Some of the women executives here run the office like their own personal household, making junior staff run to fetch them lunch even to mend their broken shoes ! It's pitiful !</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working here was great and not so great”

</title><pros>Pros – -beautiful offices-great co-workers-profit sharing/ESOP plan</pros>
<cons>Cons – -management doesn't walk the walk that they talk-say that employees have freedom to think and create but when it happens the idea is either stolen or squashed-management not educated and afraid to have hard conversations with employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – -get out from behind your desk, off your phone and stop txting.  talk with employees.  mentor them.  that's your responsibility as a manager.  care about the culture and the people.  that's what art gensler started.  keep that alive andnot the almighty dollar.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Architectural Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK”

</title><pros>Pros – Resources, Structured Management, and Overhead Benefit</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hierarchy prevent staffs from professional growth</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It all depends”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice office environment, abundant resources, exposure to large scale and signicant projects around the world.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Highly political, favoritism and mismanagement in many offfice locations and their studios (departments).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Promotion should be based on seniority, ability and dedication. It should never be a popularity contest.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Over Managed”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent compension.  Need to set your own roles from day one.  The more you give this company the more they will take from you.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The Atlanta Office is way over managed.  The senior managment team has very little trust in their staff and treats all employees like children.  This in a very depressing place to work.  Very hard to advance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop over managing the staff.  This does not "Empower" anyone.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-31</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Very collaborative, well-respected firm.  Great company culture that encourages entrepreneurship, collegiality and community involvement.  Bonus program and PS/ESOP programs can be very rewarding to those who stay with the firm for a long time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Big company, so sometimes making changes to processes/policies can take time. The Regional structure helps to offset this somewhat given the fact that the regions still have quite a bit of independence and latitude to explore new practices/methodologies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't let the growth of the company turn it into a bureaucracy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing company, some difficult politics”

</title><pros>Pros – Positive, encouraging culture; many education opportunities; professional staff; great benefits. It's a fabulous place for young professionals to learn the business.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Corporate culture isn't suited for everyone, you have to choose between technical and design tracts... And technical staff is not highly valued.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Intern opportunities. They try to create a stimulating environment for interns.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people, good work-life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – Though I got to work on pretty cool projects, most of the work are interior and retail. Though ok for many, not my favorite.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Project Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people, no attitudes (that;s hard to find in the architecture industry).Lots of opportunities to travel.Pay for overtime.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay structure is not good.  They consider your bonuses as part of your salary.Difficult to advance your career</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do away with bonus system.As the largest architecture firm in the world your compensation package should be above (not below) the industry average.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was awesome while it lasted”

</title><pros>Pros – Professional growth, profit sharing...keep working hard everyone...my balance is growing!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Politics, lack of strong upper management in some offices,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't hire staff that is not qualified, just because they are inexpensive or 'cute'.  Senior staff has enough to do without mentoring 1/2 the team.  1 experienced member can handle the work of 3 "newbies".Lead by example, not just propaganda.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Job Captain (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to learn the ropes.”

</title><pros>Pros – Positive community, lots of co-curricular activities to help you meet those outside your studio, great project portfolio to learn from, mentor-driven culture, good pay and bonus program</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hard to get out of your studio, especially if you're not very involved with activities; can get "stuck" with one project manager for multiple projects if they want to keep you, which limits your exposure to other mentoring opportunities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Especially with younger employees, try to focus on maximizing their exposure to different project types, management types and client situations</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Creative and innovative place to work at”

</title><pros>Pros – creative, innovative, modern, fun parties</pros>
<cons>Cons – people here are underpaid, especially on the corporate side</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great corporate internship experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to work especially for those new to the corporate lifestyle. The DC office is pretty "chill" and there's a lot of workshops and things to do outside of work. The pay is decent for an internship. A lot of opportunities to work collaboratively with other disciplines.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Meetings about meetings about meetings. Too many meetings. I just want to do my work.Wasn't a big fan of DC but the corporate lifestyle is something you get used to.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – N/A</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Architectural Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“architecture”

</title><pros>Pros – encouragement, encouragement, encouragement, encouragement, encouragement, encouragement,</pros>
<cons>Cons – low income, similar project, low income, similar project, low income, similar project, low income, similar project,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Myth”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benifits, offices in all major cities. Good for someone who wants to work the system and move around a lot.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Be prepaed to take a salary that is lower than industry standard.Be prepared to devote your whole life to the company. It is kind of a pyramid scheme.  I was high enough in the company before I left that I was on the hiring committee. From the minute a person is hired it is determined if they are "super star " or a "work horse" If you are labeled super star you are introduced to all the right people given the best projects and staff to assist you. If you are labeled a work horse you will hear all the propaganda about opportunities and doing great design but trust me you will never be anything other than a work horse. You will work crazy hours,one project after the next in hopes of getting some small bonus come June. The bonus will never be equivalent to all the hours you will put in.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get back to the original roots and vision of the company. If you stop low balling fees you can give your employees a better work life balance .</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Architectural Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is corporate design for corporate clients. Not a lot design or creativity. Keep it clean lines and of the book spec.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great learning programs and knowledge stuff.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No back bone for Design direction.  Just make client happy.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They need to pay more attention to existing employees, rather then look for new hire</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Architect (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not what it used to be...”

</title><pros>Pros – Great national recognition in the design industry. Meeting lots of different people who come from different work background. Work in different offices and project types (retail, office, campus, etc) if theres an opportunity. Bonus is good when you are there for a long time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I was there a long time and worked in 3 offices, so I can say its not just a one office problem. I would give it 4-5 stars when I joined in 2000 to only 2 stars when I left in 2011 because it was less about  design and more about just drafting and managing. They put in collaborating spaces all offices but don't want you to spend time just sitting talking about project with so tight deadlines. They tell you not to charge overtime because job is out of money but insist on deadlines so production have to work free weekends or into the night, but where are the managers. You don't see the negative because marketing department is always a step ahead with the next great thing. Theres competition between offices, and alot of picking favoirtes. I can say that cause I was a favorite in 2 of the places so not just sour grapes. I saw lots of senior people make huge mistakes and blame juniors. Promotions based on favorites for sure. When you are there you drink the Cool Aid and believe it. I decided to leave to see if other places of same size had less politics, and found several that were better.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Too many layers of senior management that are out of touch with offices. They got so big and mighty that they lost alot of the personal aspects and made false promises. Many have been there 20-30 years and don't know how to change with the time. Young staff are learning the bad habits.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Job Captain (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Job Captain”

</title><pros>Pros – Paid overtime.  Guaranteed performance bonus AND Christmas bonus.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very minimum base pay according to AIA</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increase pay.  Get rid of the Designer/Job captain production roles.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great work is done but at the cost of employees' lives”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart people, financially VERY secure as a company, and they do great work - often. Compensation is good for people who stay a long time - if you're moving around a lot look elsewhere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low base salaries and reliance on bonuses - the famous phrase they use when hiring is "Take a leap of faith"...the rules about promotions are not rules at all and the action of the company breed intense cynicism. Some offices are really, really unhappy - almost terminally so. No overtime in some offices and people work crazy hours. A completely political company - find someone to be your powerful pal. This does not make for an ideal place. Overall, it's actually badly managed in spite of massive profitability.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Follow your own rules; try to find the core of integrity and live it; remember that you need employees who are balanced and content, not driving themselves crazy to be recognized. Profitability is only one indicator of success.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Stimulating experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great mix of young energetic designers and seasoned professionals.  High energy environment. Progressive design culture.  Large resource of experienced people to guide employees at any level.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Recruits right up until the point of starting lay-offs.  It can seem very corporate and impersonal, but the company is mostly merit based.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There should be more performance reviews and feedback, and a free flow of information back & forth from employees to management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Job Captain (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company to start your career”

</title><pros>Pros – Great learning environment and team working environment. The company is highly focus on developing global presence and providing a great platform to connect with offices in different countries.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some offices can be too large and politics in the office can be stressful.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Run away!”

</title><pros>Pros – Strong future. Company continues to grow while others remain static. Job security and benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Does not value their employees, treat them as commodities.  Does not appropriately communicate company  culture. Management is cold and will disparage you if you step off their beaten path! Pay is lower than other companies. Environment is stressful, uptight, and one of blame.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Build a culture of collaboration based on respect and admiration NOT FEAR!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Interior Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's the #1 Company year after year for a Reason...”

</title><pros>Pros – Really supportive colleagues and bossesIncredible opportunities for continuing education in what you're interested in and what Gensler is interested inProjects are extremely diverse, plentiful, and you can develop long term relationships with clientsProject Managers give you the liberty to guide your own path and responsibilityClients are long term and already have built trust relationships with Gensler. Much easier to build more design ideas onto a trusting partnerBonuses (Holiday and mid-year are better than competitors. Overtime really acts as an incentive as the year goes on rather than being paid a higher salary up front and then zero overtime).People are golden at this firm. They hire based on personality and moral/ethics and make sure people play well with eachother.There is a genuine camaraderie that cannot be replaced and cannot be duplicated. If you're lucky to get an interview, give this place a chance and remember the people who typically post on any of these websites are negative.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Like any other A&D firm, the hours are long and the pay is low. We are in this profession for the passion we feel for this field, not more and not less.It is a bigger firm, so if you are the type to get wrapped up in any "office politics" (which by the way  are ANYWHERE you go), you may not find this the right fit. If you are quiet, but feel comfortable speaking up when you're not comfortable, you will be heard and the leaders will do a really good job of placing you where you need to go in the next 2 months.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing what you're doing! The culture is amazing, we have more get togethers and parties then you could imagine, and you're always there when somebody really needs you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stay Away from the Machine”

</title><pros>Pros – Good BenefitsNice office and location</pros>
<cons>Cons – No work /balance lifeNo compassion for Hurricane Sandy victim'sWill make you work through a STORM</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more compassionte, the bottom line is important; but you will end up turning away good employees in the long run.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Executive Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very dynamic work environment with amazing team-building opportunities.”

</title><pros>Pros – office events, amazing catering, constant peer support, excellent ability to improve your skills and participate in award winning projects, leaders of their industry, best benefits with first year bonuses</pros>
<cons>Cons – none, requires independently motivated individuals</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Job well done.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Job Captain (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A well oiled machine that treats you like a machine”

</title><pros>Pros – Plenty of resources and experience that cuts out the mundane parts of the job.  The materials libraries, blocks, presentation templates, and client relations take out a lot of detailing and cold calling that take valuable time.The pay is good, the boomerang program ensures employment. They also pay overtime</pros>
<cons>Cons – Because they pay overtime, they treat you like you have no right to leave.  Project managers NEVER tell the client no and that costs the younger designers almost all free time.  There is a large descrepancy between the big dogs and the worker bees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Tell the client no enough to sustatin a healthy work/life balance for employees.  The reason ALL projects assume ridiculous schedules is because the industry has allowed them to.  Rather than offering quickest delivery, offer a happy healthy and positive process that will end with a better result</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Architect (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“What you make of it”

</title><pros>Pros – Project diversity, lots of opportunity to find groups within firm to pursue interests related to design/profession/workplace culture, compensation package</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can get lost/buried within the sheer size of the firm, tendency to get pigeon-holed (for better or worse) based on initial/early impressions</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Check-in with your employees in a way that doesn't make it seem like you're being forced to do it because it's company policy or because it's the annual performance review. Give employees an opportunity to get out of their 'niche'.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Strategic Planner (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun and creative culture with great people”

</title><pros>Pros – creative, talented staff, surprisingly ego-less for this industry. Collegial and supportive environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – pretty flat organization, which is great for getting responsibility but may limit career advancement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a place that fosters good design.”

</title><pros>Pros – It can be a pro if you thrive in a highly structured corporate environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Thoughtful design is not acknowledged or rewarded at this firm. Helpingpeople advance their careers is not a concern of the company.Working extra hours and not being paid for them are expected by theiremployees, and this is communicated through punishment if the employee fails to do so.They will pay you less than any other firm will and try to make up for itwith small bi-yearly bonuses which are not as large as they promise theywill be when you first sign on.  High profit is the prevailinggoal of this organization.  Unless you are a cut-throat business person who strives in a profit-drivencompetitive environment, don't bother working here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You will be getting paid under market value and expected to work overtimewithout recording your hours in order to complete unrealistic goals in ashort time frame.  Upper management will use the lower level employees as scapegoats, if theydon't make high enough profit margins. Likely, if you are not upper managementthe chances are high that you will eventually be laid off for reasons beyond your control.Daily you will see new faces in the office, as they rotate through peoplequite fast, using them when deemed as profitable and turning them awayas fresh new unassuming employees roll in.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“friendly environment to work, co-workers are nice”

</title><pros>Pros – friendly environment to work, co-workers are nice</pros>
<cons>Cons – not possibly to return hire former intern</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I loved it there.”

</title><pros>Pros – What an awesome firm to work for.  Despite the fact that it is a HUGE office, it really has the atmosphere of a small one.  As an intern I had access to all the resources necessary to really learn as much as I could while I was there.  I really felt like a part of the team.</pros>
<cons>Cons – While it is a great firm to work for, the work they are doing isn't always to most interesting, design-wise.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The internship program is VERY well run, organized and enjoyable.  Gensler is not only a firm but a family.  While it sounds a bit corny it is absolutely true.  Genlser treats its employees with the utmost respect.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Job Captain (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible place for moms with young kids”

</title><pros>Pros – They give you lot of responsibility and dump work on their employees which is good for some one who wants to learn.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I want to warn all ambitious moms (especially with younger children) not to join Gensler. They dump a lot of work and pay peanuts! It is strictly business for them. Top management are not trustworthy.Basically when you compare the stress vs. the pay you get,  it is worthless to go work for this company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please keep your word. In today's world where news travel very fast you cannot tell people one thing on their face and do completely opposite thing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Student Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to learn from senior leaders.”

</title><pros>Pros – Senior Associates are very knowledgeable.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very corporate environment and can be different from studio culture of architecture school.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Job Captain (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Corporate, mediocre design, very complacement and political”

</title><pros>Pros – Employees are a pleasure to work with. Lovely office in SF. Paid overtime (unheard of in architecture profession). Good retirement and medical plans. Opportunities to work abroad.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Office and NW region is controlled by the CFO. Therefore productivity and billable hours are more important than design. Project Managers don't manage projects, more are glorified accountants. Top heavy and difficult to advance. Huge bonuses for the partners, mediocre for the remaining. Salaries are withheld as a bi-annual bonus. Employee reviews are a way to placate staff and not as a tool to professionally develop.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop 'strategically' hiring, grow the company within. Value your staff and not the hire-fire that you have become. Too many financial presentations to how much Gensler earns. This actually irritates the staff to how much money is not trickling down. Stop saying how great you are at design: you need to be innovative rather than looking to the trade periodicals for insipation.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great learning environment”

</title><pros>Pros – To be surrounded by smart and competent people who have a talent for ground-breaking design. An amazing place to observe and learn from the amazing people around you.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is a bit large. It is a bit too organized for my taste. Design and creativity can not be derived by a table of elements... it comes and goes and changes with each person.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – keep it up!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Just a stepping stone to something better....”

</title><pros>Pros – Gensler provides its employees with good benefits and office support.  It is an international firm w/ award winning work and talented employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Depending upon the office you work in you may have limited opportunities.  Each office seems to have its niche and sticks to it.  Management is not really interested in stepping out of their comfort zone and expanding its business portfolio</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management is very personable and I feel easy to converse with professionally.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You will never succeed”

</title><pros>Pros – Latest Technology new computers and laptops.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No groth potential at all.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire skilled people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Architect (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Generally a good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good projects, generally a good work environment, though I left years ago</pros>
<cons>Cons – Deadlines and salaries (true for most design professionals)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager/Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Great perks, good leadership and coaching, good feedback</pros>
<cons>Cons – If I could do it again, I'd start my career at Gensler and stay there for 20 years.  So many people have been there 15, 20, 30 years that it's difficult to make a big impact when there are so many senior people ahead of you in line.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Consider more than years of experience when determining salary and promotions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My experience was good and bad mostly due to my inexperienced manager”

</title><pros>Pros – It has great employee culture. You will feel that you are respected. It is also a very well-known company with strong brand. They promote employees from inside which can be good and bad at the same time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you are not architect or designer, you are 2nd citizen at the company unless you are in the executive position.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Mid Career (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Benefit's & Client's are the Best Part”

</title><pros>Pros – Profit Sharing & revenue base performance bonus a +!Variety of work in other office, NB mainly Workplace, no real creative outlet.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not all Leadership is the same, some are very supporting and available, others sit in their 'glass tower' waiting for the world to revolve around them.  Seek out those you want to learn from and work with = communicate & you'll enjoy your experience.  Sit there and sulk, and you'll only have yourself to blame.Corporate environment - speak up if you want it!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hopefully the change has been beneficial for the OC office.Art who?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Your Mileage May Vary”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice office at Rockefeller Center, exciting projects, variety of people to work with, IT and tech were top notch, training opportunities were plentiful.  Systems and standards to work between offices are well developed and implemented.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is unfortunate that there is little personal interest shown in staff advancement by upper management or in fostering a harmonious team in NY.  Smaller Gensler offices do much better at this. The impersonal approach results in a roller coaster of layoffs and hiring where experienced folks with higher salaries are shown the door in favor of low salaried interns who can't yet function in the real world of architecture. For the new hires it is a baptism by fire and many mistakes are made due to lack of experience and mentor-ship.  Bare minimum benefits, minimum pay, less than average vacation.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Let the next generation take over and cultivate the necessary experience level needed to nurture a staff that covers the whole spectrum of knowledge needed for quality design work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Architect (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“one of the best architecture company”

</title><pros>Pros – creative and reasonable working hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – sometimes too slow down, need more passion</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – too horizontal</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern Architect (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I'd go back”

</title><pros>Pros – nice corporate environment.  nice people.  fair compensation.  there was mostly freindly faces, and you could move around within the company, within reason.</pros>
<cons>Cons – easy to get lost in large corporate environment.  good be a plus if you are slacking.  but a real negative if you are heads down working hard and not tooting your own horn.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – the business model seems to be thriving so I don't think I can offer any real change.  the popularity contest that is advancement is really a part of human nature.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Architect/Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's all old school”

</title><pros>Pros – bonuses.....colleagues are friendly.....office design is favorable to employees. ... its part of "Gensler" firmwide.</pros>
<cons>Cons – archaic work philosophy.....clear hierarchy of management and salary based on degrees and licensure, not on skills and progressive attitudes.  People are a number and not seen for their talent or what they bring to the table.  Long hours and little appreciation for dedication to the company and project.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get to know your employees beyond their resume.  See what skills and talents they bring to the table and appreciate the value they add to Gensler.  Be more progressive in your attitudes and work ethic.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Happy to come to work everyday”

</title><pros>Pros – Gensler pays overtime which is not common for architecture firms. I am respected and treated well by my leadership and management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working at a larger firm is harder to get noticed and get promoted. Someone will always complain about lower salaries/raises/bonuses during this economic climate.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest more in the people that work for Gensler (in the way of industry conferences and events) so that they may feel valued and inspired.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Corporate architecture”

</title><pros>Pros – Bonuses. Gensler's commitment to continued education by providing lunch ceu's, etc. Their help in encouraging and supporting professional licensing. Client does seem to come first.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I will have to agree with some of the above posts in regards to the fact that promotions are often made on the basis of how well one cultivates relationships with the managers rather than on the basis of skills and knowledge.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Review some of the people that have been working there for a while. Just because they've been there for a long time doesn't mean that they should continue to work there. Client does seem to come first and in turn some of the workers are over used and are given very little time for a lot of work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“All was not as it was made out to be...”

</title><pros>Pros – Better resources and equipment, good coffee, the office has a nice house wine</pros>
<cons>Cons – Favortisim, Lack of Respect, No openess to new ideas in design.  The work is not fresh.  An established elite group who do not have much talent.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Open your eyes and your minds in Houston.  Leadership needs to recognize that they put many out on the street with talent and skills while leaving the old guard behind who just don't have a fresh vision.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Job Captain (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“There's a reason it's consistently rated #1.”

</title><pros>Pros – Wonderful culture,  high quality of design and encouragement from management for community involvement. I highly enjoyed my time working there, especially as someone who was very involved in the internal culture.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is definitely a corporate environment, for better or worse. You must work with a variety of people, project types and levels of management to advance and that isn't always an easy task to accomplish.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create more opportunities for younger staff to work in different typologies and with different studios. It seems that once a person is assigned a studio, and subsequently a project type (i.e. retail, commercial, etc.), it is very difficult to gain experience in other areas.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Management (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dallas office is all about "appearance", not value for the client”

</title><pros>Pros – Overall compensation seems to be fair compared to other companies.  The office appearance including the reception and employee area is nice and not forboding at all.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No respect for the hard workers that do accurate work and make the office profitable...there is political pressure to look good, instead.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Remember who brought you to the "dance".  A lot of people are now gone that should still be there.  Treatment of the employee should be just as important as treatment of the client.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Job Captain (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It has a very beautiful interior inside and you can work over there exerting your possibilities and abilitiy.”

</title><pros>Pros – nice working environmentopen and many opportunities for work</pros>
<cons>Cons – hard to transfer between studios</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They have to learn to foresee the future business trend and think about indivisual career pattern in case of catastrophic layoff</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-10</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart, intelligent co-workers and vibrant management. Office environment is beautiful, compensation and benefits are great. The perks are wonderful too. Everyone in the office, no matter their position, is made to feel like a part of the team, such as being invited to brain storming sessions for projects you aren't working on.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours, lots of overtime and a fast-paced work environment that can, at times, be stressful.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Wonderful company and work environment! Keep up the good work!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Architect (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fine place to work if you are at a dead end in your career.”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits. Ability to travel. Able to relate to Dilbert.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Promotion not based on ability, but on relationships (much like the rest of the real world). The 'IBM' of the architecture world- ie. very corporate atmosphere. Much less creative and intellectual than most architecture firms. Gotta love your own cubicle.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The way to grow the business (and sustain it) is to seek out and promote exceptional people. Too little of this happening. Stop preparing for your retirement and start planning for the longevity of THE BRAND- Gensler, that is.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-05-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Be careful of the revolving door....”

</title><pros>Pros – Good compensation package; offices worldwide, and the variety and caliber of projects make for a stimulating work environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company tends to overhire.  And while compensation for overtime is fair, weekend work can quickly become the norm--managers' lack of planning can become your fire drill.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management should insist on weekly studio meetings, where all levels of staff are required to attend.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Interior Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Houston office needs work”

</title><pros>Pros – Gensler has an elaborate company subculture of office events and online communities for those who want to partake of it.  Opportunities to work on projects in distant locations are frequent.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Senior management in the Houston office is male-dominated; a glass ceiling appears to exist for women, gays, and minorities.  Promotions are often made on the basis of how well one cultivates relationships with the managers rather than on the basis of skills and knowledge.                                         Over-hiring in 2005-07 has recently resulted in rounds of layoffs.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Gensler's firmwide leadership would do well to replace a lot of the senior management in the Houston office.  The once-robust economy masked a lot of inept and arrogant managers because there was so much work and money flowing through the office.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type> Project Management (Operations)  (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Though not the CEO he's involved. He's w/ project teams going over designs and leads matters that require board approval”

</title><pros>Pros – Solid company with solid core values.  Not your run of the mill firm, but one that in many ways has stayed true to the "mom & pop" values.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inconsistency in management decisions.  It often results in jealousy among staff members.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Infighting breads weakness.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Architect (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Was happy there, but happier gone.”

</title><pros>Pros – Gensler is a good place to start out in your career. As you stay there, it is easy to get pigeon-holed in the corporate structure. You can start to feel like a cog.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is lower than at other firms because bonuses are considered as part of annual pay. Bonuses are optional, so to the firm's advantage.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Let people grow and try different things. Be more consistent in reviews and evaluations. In the New York office, the culture was pretty cutthroat. Staff needs to feel like the boss has their back.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-02-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Management (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Gensler - A great place to work when the economy is strong.  Look out below when the bottom falls out.”

</title><pros>Pros – Like a family.   Great profit sharing plan and ESOP plan.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They layoff very quickly when the economy gets bad.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Plan for the future.  Put money away for a rainy day so you don't have to lay off people when the economy gets bad.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Job Captain (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Former Gensler employee, with high regard for Gensler”

</title><pros>Pros – one reason people get left behind in their professional careers is there loss of continued education.  Gensler offers many oppurtunities for continued education.  The work enviroment is great.  technology is always cutting age,  new programs a continuily implemented, and atomosphere is very colaberative, you almost feel like a great big family.</pros>
<cons>Cons – At the end of the day business is business...loyalty to the company can seem to go one way.   employees can sometimes be overlooked due to high rate of hiring and number of employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Gensler should offer a better severance package.  Gensler expects great work and loyalty from their employees.  but when laying employees, offering a week severance package is sometimes taken as an insult.  Also senior management should look into their sub managers every once in a while to ensure the mangagers below them are caring out their respocibilities according to the companys mottos.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Mangement/architect (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cult members welcomed”

</title><pros>Pros – Great opportunity for the young. Good opportunities to travel.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Easy to become pigeoned-holed. management tend to see only what it wants to see. Best to be a total yes man it order to succeed.  Remember at Gensler you are just one cog in the big machine.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn to look beyond your own ego and realize that those with ideas that challenge present these ideas to help not to criticize.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-11-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Architectural Job Captain (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great projects to work on, and if you're lucky, great managers and people to work with”

</title><pros>Pros – Great project type variety depending on what practice area one works in. Fantastic place to meet and work alongside people at all levels who are bright, ambitious, intelligent and high caliber. Company gives financial support of exam cost or sof tudy time if one is pursuing accreditation or licensing. Encouragement volunteerism and other community-based extra-curricular activities. And did I say that there are great people working here?</pros>
<cons>Cons – Stuck-in-single-role happens a lot for those in CD production work. Lately, I've witnessed senior office personnel condoning and joining in on publicly deriding employees who are on their way out (resignation, firing). There is no clear mediation system in place when employee needs conflict resolution. Micromanagers and angry-managers (not pervasive but pity those who draws the short straw) subtly abuse lower-tier employees and thus appear to be rewarded for it based on $budget and $revenue. Gensler is a world class architecture firm, and should never ever resemble a sweatshop. However in SF there are studios that believe in: Client needs first, star players and squeaky wheel needs second, nose to the grind people needs third. If I was a client or a star player I would not be having a problem.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need alternate channels of communication (not just with studio/homeroom, not just PDP) to address issues such as conflicts or success mentorship/coaching. A menu of go-to persons in different studios or office/firm entities would help; internal billing for this type of role would encourage more persons to be such advocates. Need to get middle managers to ensure that their role is to empower lower-tier employees to fill their shoes, not be the gatekeeper to the club. This is a quality-assurance business requirement that project managers often forget.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-11-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Architectural Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The g.PDP”

</title><pros>Pros – The ability to work with teams and various levels of expertise and experience is invaluable. You learn more in one day at work than several years at any university. Gensler affords the opportunity to expand your knowledge and to be exposed to various types of projects.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Its a very large firm, so it takes more effort to stand out amongst the rest. If moving ahead at Gensler was based on knowledge, performance, and the potential to grow that would be amazing. More often than not, its who you work with directly that puts in a good word for you in order to move up this corporate ladder...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Mentor the junior/intermediate designers so that they may be able to fill your shoes in 10-15 years. Managemnet is something that needs to be instilled and trained early on, so that it enables the designers to integrate budget and staffing seemlessly into design processes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Each office very independent, but overall much more political than it used to be.”

</title><pros>Pros – Focus on design excellence, and client solutions is very rewarding, and allows for relatively junior staff to be important team members.  Has the most dedicated staff that focuses on client satisfaction.  The name really does draw out he best talent in each of the cities they have an office.  They do provide the best design in most the markets they operate in.</pros>
<cons>Cons – While they pride themselves as being "one firm firm" that lacks inter-office political fighting, this is highly dependent of which office you work in.  Some offices are highly political and others are not.  Promotions are given out less about skill and talent, and more about how extroverted you are.  Not a company to succeed in if you are an introvert, which means most of those that do the heavy lifting and the detail coordination will get left behind.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Control your regional offices, and eliminate problem managers that are overly political.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“not satisfied”

</title><pros>Pros – Good looking company, convenient location, fun entertainment with free food and drinks.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor HR management, no  discipline, luck of trust in employees, poor training, high expectations, poor coordination between teams, HR members are rude and always gossiping behind your back. Personally, I wouldn't recommend working in London office.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve discipline, treat everyone equally and not by language or its background, stop GOSSIPS, it's getting out of control!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Architect (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company generally, but very big and very political”

</title><pros>Pros – Good employee benefits, good salary and bonuses.  Young enthusiastic junior staff energise the office.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very political environment.  Profits take precedence over quality of work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Architect (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“it is fantastic to work for Gensler.”

</title><pros>Pros – good work culture, one-firm-firm, work ethics, entrepreneurial, work is fun, good potential for right candidates, good leadership, firm as family. good for architects.</pros>
<cons>Cons – long working hours, since it is started recently one need to watch on the prospects.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – focus on asian market</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast Paced”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work environment and benefits.  High quality of projects</pros>
<cons>Cons – None that every other design office doesn't have</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good culture, compensation is lacking.”

</title><pros>Pros – They are willing and able to compensate you for your continuimg education and there are plenty of in office opputunities to continue your learning for credits as well. The culture is good and they seem to value people as individuals and there are bi-annual reviews to allow for good dialogue between you and upper managment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay is low and it is said that the bonus makes up for the low compensation. The bonus is on par with the rest of the firms in the industry and it simply brings your overall compensation to market value. This is a great firm with top with prestigious clients and every year they have better earnings, why not share some of the b\value the employees have helped earn.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company to work with”

</title><pros>Pros – International environment, beautiful offices in great locations, friendly coworkers.  They work on a broad range of projects and so there is a diversity of expertise in-house</pros>
<cons>Cons – Depending upon where you begin, it may be a bit difficult to transfer between studios, so be sure to specify your interests from the beginning</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Architect/Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not the place it was”

</title><pros>Pros – Size of the organization and client list allows for great opportunities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Those opportunities are only for the same favored few, the majority never see them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Loose the Frat house mentality</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place for aspiring architects, pretty good for interior designers, not so great for people most other areas.”

</title><pros>Pros – You get a lot of exposure to different kinds of projects, with a focus on large-scale.  Different departments share exciting work or projects weekly, so you get an idea of the scope or work, insights on clients, education on challenges and limitations of field, etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you're not an architect or interior designer, the people who run the place often don't understand your needs - they are architects, and understand architecture.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If upper management could figure out a way to make themselves more accessible, they would get a lot of valuable input from their employees.  This would need to go beyond simply saying that they're accessible.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“senior architectural designer”

</title><pros>Pros – gensler is an international firm, easy to transfer</pros>
<cons>Cons – hard to get overtime pay</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great stepping stone.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to build a global network, and then jump. One of the only truly global design firms.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Phenomenally hierarchical. Promotions process is Kafka-esque. Politics are incredibly delicate and pervasive.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value your people--all of them. Foster a culture of respect across disciplines, professions, roles.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's hard work and fast-paced, but you are surrounded by the most creative + talented people in the industry."”

</title><pros>Pros – Great leaders with a strong vision.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inconsistency in messages at times</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people, good culture and workplace atmosphere</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some tedious projects, very political, high fees</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“White collar corporate architecture firm - a making machine”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of work, helpful coworkers, large-scale projects, and opportunities for employee training. Learned a lot as an intern.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Ridiculously tight time schedules, low pay, and design is often sacrificed for - you guessed it - money. Very typical corporate design trends.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You guys are doing the best you can - but try mentoring the younger folks more!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Scrape away the veneer and you find the rotten core”

</title><pros>Pros – None, unless you count the ability to survive such a bad environment as a pro for your future growth</pros>
<cons>Cons – Terribly political organization that has a rigid caste system with employees at the bottom of the rung.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Instead of issuing sound bites you might try walking the walk versus just talking the talk</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-31</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company If you're just starting out”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of job responsibility, diverse projects to provide you with an opportunity to grow your skills, you're not treated like an intern but instead looked at as being equal, large workforce to provide many opportunities to grow and learn from your peers, great way to learn about different manufacturers in the business as they are always eager to speak with you when you tell them your with Gensler</pros>
<cons>Cons – Easy to get placed in a niche. Sometimes there can be many late nights making it difficult to take advantage of industry events.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to communicate with your employees to discover new areas of interest to allow them to expand and grow as a designer.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great design firm, but fast burn”

</title><pros>Pros – Highly creative and passionate people. Great mix of work and global reach. Lots of opportunity to learn and collaborate.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very intense and sometimes unmanageable deadlines. Not enough structure or adherence to standardized procedures.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Clearly communicate objectives and priorities. Hire enough resources to do work if perfection is the standard.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“World-class company and talented, great colleagues”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with talented, creative people on amazing projects.Feels like a family.People are friendly; those that are hired and turn out not to be usually find a way out, because they can't hack the positive vibe.Very entrepreneurial--if you have a vision of doing something and the ability, Gensler will give you room to try it out.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Design doesn't pay as well as other industries.Has it's share of office politics--but not as much as others in this industry.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't get too corporate. Keep it real.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Place to learn, upper positions based on popularity not skill or work ethic”

</title><pros>Pros – The education and learning opportunities are fantastic, the large network of offices means that there is a lot of knowledge sharing. The majority of the people at Gensler are great to work with and there is a strong sense of family and community among the "workers".</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management is a bit of a popularity contest and it is a bit top-heavy right now. while there is room to grow career wise, because the firm is so big, it is hard to make a difference. If you want to suceed and make it to the higher ranks, dont worry about actual work ethic or performance, you are better off socializing as its not about what you know, its who you know.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay attention to the people who are actualy doing the work, dont pick people to promote and leave the rest behind. there are a lot of amazing people who are getting used & abused, doing the work of many, while there are probably an equal ammount of people not doing much at all but socializing and playing on the internet. You could probably acomplish the same amount of work with 2/3 as many employees. Use the technology you have, and pay attention to what people are really doing on their computers all day and get rid of the extra fat. Also toughen up on the people who blame the programs for their inability to do a good job- those are the ones who dont know what they are doing!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“There are lots of learn opportunities at this company”

</title><pros>Pros – This company has lots of resources and can utilize talents from around the world.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are some politics to be dealt with on higher management level.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Perfect Platform”

</title><pros>Pros – EntrepreneurialismCommitment to clientsRelationship focusAmbitionAbility to adapt and evolveEquity in distribution of rewards</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not always clear what to do (but I like that)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on the culture. It is our gift and our biggest asset.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall Gensler is a good place to work at.”

</title><pros>Pros – Management is pretty understanding in permitting time-off for personal/family matters.Company's financial status is shared among employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not too much room to grow for accounting/finance people.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Open communication can be improved</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Growing experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Many different types of projects.  Rewarded for taking initiative.  Many great people to work with across offices. Benefits and compensation package.  Overall a enjoyable company to work for.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some employees are given preferencial treatment.  Large offices tend to take advantage of small offices.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide guidance on career advancment for all areas of expertise.  Some chosen professions are left out.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Best”

</title><pros>Pros – Great clientsGreat designGreat peopleCollaborative cultureCreative processChallenging workSupportive peersFun and socialIntelligent solutionsDiverse staffCutting edgeRespectful cultureEnthusiastic teamsCommitted to quality</pros>
<cons>Cons – Networking internally and externally is essential for personal growthExpectations of staff are high and cultural fit is as important as talent</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Empower staff to be entrepreneurialInvest in young staff and challenge them to leadInvest more in cutting edge technology</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-31</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sold a bill of goods in the interview process”

</title><pros>Pros – comraderie among peers in a similar age range (Gen Y)creative environmentlocationfun and social activitiesleader in the industry</pros>
<cons>Cons – antiquated model of promotion based on favoritismlack of any true management structure that functions cohesively (offices and partners are pitted against each other)competitive and at time cutthroat environment among peerslack of support for development</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Change the mentality in which you operate - need to function more like a corporation given Gensler's size and less like a partnership.  Younger talent comes into the organization looking for training, development and growth opportunities and is instead given crap work, unrealisitc deadlines, a lack of resources and very, very bad people managers who treat people poorly.  Focus on building your manager training and people practices, change the structre to have one leader (3 does not work) and make the promotions process more tangible and transparent based on actual results vs. favoritism.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Interior Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very nice!”

</title><pros>Pros – very friendly environment to work in</pros>
<cons>Cons – pay not too competitive compared to other companies</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Thank you!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Architect/Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stated goals are not to be believed.  Beware, this is a highly political environ in which 'yes men' are rewarded.”

</title><pros>Pros – If the above is for you - there are Good benefits & interesting projects.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management does not communicate & will not hesitate to sacrifice subordinates if in their interest.  Again, do not believe stated goals.  It is best to keep quiet & not be innovative with this company - it is threatening to mgt.  If one is looking fo a place to be a 'yes man', this could be a good place to be.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to start.”

</title><pros>Pros – It was a great place to meet other designers who have several years experience. The designers were experts at what they do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes as intern you get stuck doing the grunt work. But it wasn't anything that you wouldn't do anywhere else.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Program Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A frustratingly wonderful or wonderfully frustrating place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent salaries for the industry.Very good profit sharing and ESOP plans.Opportunities to work in offices around the world.Opportunities to work with top notch clients.Gensler makes pretty good use of technology to allow you to get your job done more efficiently.A number of senior and mid-level people who work at Gensler are very intelligent and have something to teach you regardless of how much you already think you know.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Gensler is an organization that began life as a design firm and has, over the past few decades made serious steps toward becoming more than just a design firm.  Essentially, I've seen Gensler attempt to move from being a design firm that offers consulting serves to a consulting firm that offers design services, which it appears is what the senior leadership has tried to do.  The problem with this is that the firm tends to fall back on design every time and abandon any efforts to branch out, thereby lurching the organization back and forth every few years.There is definitely an atmosphere of favoritism within the firm.  If your manager likes you, then, as long as you're good at what you do and do quality work, you'll get ahead and do well in your career.  If not, it is extremely difficult to progress or sometimes even survive within the organization.  I've experienced it both ways and have seen it both ways with many others.Also, Gensler has long been, and remains, something of a cult of personality -- be it among the leadership or among some of the more "talented" design staff.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Decide what you want the firm to be and stick with it.  If you want to be the best design firm in the world, you've got it nailed.  But, if you want to be something else, figure it out and go for it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to grow and learn”

</title><pros>Pros – Corporate Giant - Allows maximum amount of resources and wide range of project types.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Because it's such a large company, you must make more of an effort to be visible. Compensation doesn't seem to meet the rates of competitive firms.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employee compensation doesn't seem to meet the rates of competitive firms.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Gensler”

</title><pros>Pros – The culture of the firm is wonderful! On the Architect and Design side there really is tremendous pride in the work that they do that easily spreads to the other departments including Corporate. People are proud to say they work here and most people are friendly, welcoming, and willing to help yuo succeed.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I think there is sometimes a disconnect between the senior management and the lower management in regards to knowing what is actually happening on a day to day basis from the people doing the detailed work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It all depends on the line of work you are in. I feel it is more difficult on the corporate side because people are there to do their one job. There arent multiple people with the same title or job description.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-09-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No. 1 design firm in the world”

</title><pros>Pros – Great culture with amazing talent.Very appreciative about your accomplishmentsRecognized for outstanding performanceEncourages collaboration between officesGreat clients and projects</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working a lot of overtime.Some prinicipals are strict about punctuality but some are more flexible.The way things are sometimes handled is a power trip for some.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Spend less money on upper management retreats and, instead, apply it to the June performance bonus and/or to the December christmas bonus.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-06-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Concerns”

</title><pros>Pros – Amazingly creative place with studio workers very collaborative and cooperative.   Good benefits and challenging work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In Firmwide in particular, a vey deep disrespect and contempt amongst the people for each other.   A fairly high turn over as well.    Communication and direction can often be lacking.  Former employees often still spoken of badly.   Processes can be very cumbersome.   Bullying behavior is rampant.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value your people from the highest level on down.    Commit yourself to a course and stick with it.   Show respect to your loyal and hard workers and listen to their ideas.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>