<name>D.E. Harvey Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/D-E-Harvey-Reviews-E14290.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-06-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Safety (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Safety CultureOwners really care about employeesManagment backs you upGreat CompanyPays for training</pros>
<cons>Cons – Minimal room for advancement in safety dept</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create safety management positions</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Superintendent (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Harvey is a hard working company with many opportunities for young project managers and superintendents”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of work going on in the Houston area right now. They have good opportunities for growth in the company depending upon how hard you work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some office politics. You have to work extremely hard to get promoted and sometimes it may take a while to obtain.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Lots of good leaders and bad leader within the organization. The ones only focused upon their own personal achievement and not the companies tend to be micromanagers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a bad company per se, but not for the faint-hearted.”

</title><pros>Pros – 360-degree view and responsabilities of project management</pros>
<cons>Cons – Good old boys' club, make sure you get the right people in your pocket.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Clear definition of goal, consistency and enforcement of rules would make up for sometimes inherently unequal treatment of employees.A better benefit package would not hurt.Year-end bonus calculations need to be shared.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-07-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Field Office Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“D.E Harvey Field Office Manager. The things they don't always tell you.”

</title><pros>Pros – Fair salary, great benefits, different atmospheres of work.  Your experience will depend on your team so do your research and listen to what you hear.  PPE is not always stylish but with the right set of jeans and a nice blouse you can rock it most days.  Interior Field Office Managers have it easier so unless you like the great outdoors be specific when they hire you what you want.    Bring your admin skills and you have it made, don't shy away from learning to read blueprints and getting your hands dirty.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You move around a lot in my job.  May not always have a/c and it's killer trying to find something to go with a hardhat and steel toe shoes. You don't always get the same perks everyone else does. Play your politics well for this company.  Watch what you say and who heard you say it, gossip makes the world go round and this company is no exception.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work with some shoe companies to let the ladies wear more comfortable shoes.  Be more consistent on what you offer your employees at time of hire.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>