<name>K-Designers Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/K-Designers-Reviews-E142622.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“new to job”

</title><pros>Pros – alot of incentives & motavation</pros>
<cons>Cons – unstable kind of stressful , protocol needs adjusting</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Telemarketer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Terrible respect for employees”

</title><pros>Pros – none at all, terrible lying company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everything imaginable, sick to my stomach thinking of this company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat your employees wih respect and dignity.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Potential to make decent money but they take advantage of customers”

</title><pros>Pros – Good earning potential if you're patient and willing to make the sacrifice.  No background checks, drug-testing, etc.  Pretty easy to get hired.  Decent sales training.  Products seem to be high quality.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Products are overpriced.  They seem to take advantage of consumers who are less-educated.  You are required to work evenings and Saturdays.  Straight commission.  No pay for training - they will pay you a draw against future commissions.  Regional travel at your own expense (gas, hotels, etc).  A lot of bad customer reviews online because of pushy sales tactics.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more selective about who you hire and make an investment in new employees (i.e. - paid training).  Be honest with customers and don't pressure them so much.  Be forthright with new employees about realistic income potential during the first month, year, etc.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great opportunities for advancement, family oriented business, never bounced my paycheck”

</title><pros>Pros – Pros are they are a leader in their industry, opportunities for advancement if your willing to work hard, great leadership, innovative outside the box thinkers,andthey never bounce a paycheck. I have been there for quite some time,and I am pleased with my choice of employers. They have an open door policy for ideas and concerns,and give me the skills to be successful if I want to be. They have great pride in what they do, the remodels we do, caring for customers,and it shows. If your not afraid to work, KDesigners is a great home.-</pros>
<cons>Cons – They took the free coffee out of the break room. :) In all seriousness all companies have their drawbacks, but nothing that would make me hesitate in not reccomending this company. Kdesigners is a good company to work for.-</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please keep up the good work. I enjoy the freedom to be creatiive,and be appreciated for what I do.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-10</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I have never worked for a better company”

</title><pros>Pros – I have spent many years as a manager for Larry and there is not a company I would rather work for.Most of the negative reviews that are posted here are put up by sales people who had no idea of what they were doing or what they were selling.Home improvements are a difficult sell especially in these tough economic times,it isn't as easy as it once was.Product knowledge and a background in construction should be a  requirement for any home improvement sales person,unfortunately many think they are too good for that and continue to sell one headache after another.I have seen the company pay through the nose for many jobs that were over promised and undersold.Larry has done his best to promise 100 percent customer satisfaction before we receive one penny from our customers,show me one other company that does that.I am proud to say that I work for the best remodeling company in the West.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours and hard work,but after all isn't that what makes it satisfying.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Require our sales force to learn basic product knowledge and visit their sales before the job is completed,that way they can learn the ins and outs of construction.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Finance Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Finance Associate - A professional, friendly & great working environment”

</title><pros>Pros – I am very impressed with the attention to customer service and the wilingness of all employees at K-designers to help customers to resolve any issues that may come up.  The finance department is dedicated, helpful and the attention to details is above reproach. It is a joy to work for this company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No problems. I am happy to work here</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Warehouse Operations (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“one very happy employee”

</title><pros>Pros – I am a warehouse employee for KDesigners in sacramento,CA  and i believe this is an extremely professional  Company,with good values,fair practices,that encourage a team atmosphere,and is pleasant and fun to work for.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I do not see any</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – thanks for the opportunity to be a steward of the warehouse .</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>7</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Selling with no morals or ethics.”

</title><pros>Pros – You really can make some great money, you just have to work hard and pay attention.  The commission can be very generous, but they are a lot of factors you need to watch out for and sales are hard to come by.  Management was straight forward about how commission could be messed up, but did not get very detailed.  obviously if you forget to charge the customer for a product but promise it to them, your commission will suffer. The only thing is, there are 10-20 other charges they do not tell you about so you have to pay attention to detail, what management says, and put the pieces together.  To get the whole list and figure it out correctly.   If you work hard, want to travel a lot, have some savings to get things rolling, pay attention to detail, and don't mind being a pushy sales person, you will make 70-150k.  To make that kind of money in the real world you need to either take a job no one else wants,  or work a job that is harder than others.  This is a job that is a lot harder than others and compromises one morals.  If that is worth 70-150k (I thought it would be too at first) then go for it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -appointments set by company are invalid.  The customers do not agree to the appointment and do not want you their.  We worked on pushy techniques to get into the house.  Things such as just picking up your bag and walking in when they open the door, and other intrusive exercises.  The commission they pay is great, but there are a lot of factors that will affect and pull out commission that they do not tell you about directly.  You can pad your numbers by overcharging the customer, but then, its are harder sell.  I did not research the company first and that is a mistake.  My girlfriend did the second day I started and brought everything to my attention.   After doing my own research I felt sick about the job feeling as if I was tricked and about to get screwed over.  I brought this up to management and they were very supportive of it and did not shy away from the issues.  The Minnesota branch is the most successful and honest branch, but it is still difficult to make money for the first 4 months.  4 month learning curve on the sales techniques (hard closes, putting pressure on customers, calling them out if they say no, and pushing their patience) and also on the presentation.  I would work a 10-8 and then spend 4 hours at home reviewing notes, presentation techniques and how to close.  I went to school for business and took sales classes so there were no surprises on the process, except how much you have to push the customers.  Other sales companies I've worked for use the same consultative selling techniques, but do it the right way and actually help their customer out.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Maybe just let the new marketing directors know how much work, money, and time they will need to start making money.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Upper management is inept and ineffective in an effort to manage cash flow”

</title><pros>Pros – Potential is there, with a decent payment system for Marketing Directors.  The actual work done for homeowners is quality, and the product is quality.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management abuses the 1099 status of marketing directors, and finds reasons not to pay them for their honest work.  The system is corrupt and ineffective, and most certainly not cost-effective.  Almost every corporate sales person in the United State these days is able to track their income online, and able to trust that their hard work will be rewarded with an actual paycheck.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You could make somuch more money, as in revenue, as in U.S. dollars, income, cash, bottom line dough in your pocket - by treating your sales force with respect, and by nurturing them as a valued resource.  I only speak $$ because that is the only way I can see that upper management might respond.  I have no hope that they will do this because it is ethical.  The CEO is ultimately responsible for this unethical behavior.  A corporate culture is determined at the top.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Believe what you read... it's unfortunately true :(”

</title><pros>Pros – I met some nice people</pros>
<cons>Cons – All of these nice people left K-Designers within 5 months.  Out of 15-20 MD's, only 3 of them have been there 2 yrs or more!  The manager tells you there's a really low turn-over rate, but he's lying!  I've never slept better since quitting this job.  Everything they tell you is a lie, they put their MD's in constant financial trouble, and the whole company is just unethical.I overheard a manager talking to a female MD who was uncomfortable going in to a home for whatever reason, and his response was "too bad.  You need to go back and knock on that door!"  I couldn't believe it.  They really don't have a clue what it's like to run a business with women in 2010.  As a previous manager, I know how to handle both male and female employees, K-Designers just doesn't get it.Last, when you do finally quit because you're broke, frustrated and you're car is falling apart, they keep your commissions.  If and when they finally give them to you, there is always some reason why it is substantially less than it should be.I wish I could take back the 4 months, $4200 in expenses (no exaggeration), and 10K miles on my car!  Lesson learned.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – STOP LYING to people!!!  The managers even put a fake positive post on this review board (the only one w/ a rating of 4).  They told us they do this often.  I've also been told by a manager that he was told to lie to the MD's about his sales.  Be honest and ethical -how do you sleep at night Mr. Judson?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible Job - Run as far away as possible.”

</title><pros>Pros – I really think that they have very good products and I would use their windows and siding on my house.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - You will work every waking minute.  12 hour days are common and I've worked as many as 17 hrs in one day.-The leads they give you are bogus leads.  Half the leads won't let you in the house and the other half are unemployed and won't be spending $20,000+ on windows or siding.-You will travel hundreds of miles to a lead just to find out they are unemployed, you will pay all your own gas, hotel, and food expenses.-Your only day off is Sunday.-Your presentation last for 3 hours and that if they don't buy.  If they buy you can expect another hour and a half doing paper work.-If you don't make the sale and don't take them to rock bottom price, you manager will send you back.-They flash copied checks of high commissions but will lie to your face or avoid any concerning questions you have.-Out of my class of 8 in training, I'm the only one that actually went on sales call.  A the rest quit.-The company has constant hiring and training going on to keep up with all the people that quit, turn over is about 90%, one question they will lie or avoid.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop lying to people and make this a ligament sales job.  You have a good product but your methods of practice are horrible.  Your sales people want to know that you are on their side, so offer some incentives to prove they aren't just disposable items to you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great idea - poorly executed.”

</title><pros>Pros – They are the first in-home home improvement company that followed through with what they tell their customers they will do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Bizarre compensation program - tiered so that the more volume you generate, the more they pay you. Problem is that it isn't any easier/harder the more you do.2. Bizarre appointment sets. Less than 20% of the appointments they set did the homeowner truly agree to the appointment. Usually they committed just to get the telemarketers off the phone.3. Bizarre ledger process. Reminded me of the "company store" setups that I learned about in high school. They make sure that anything they can charge their reps for, they do.4. Pricing to client is significantly higher than competition. Their products and service are great, but I don't know that they are 30% better than their competition.5. Initially I liked the sales approach as a Marketing Director. Unfortunately, the way the sales process is set up the rep quickly goes from being a marketing director to either pushy salesman or begging salesman. I ended up feeling like the stereotypical sales character in the Simpsons.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 1. Simplify2. Fully support the Marketing Director concept or drop it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Incredible Sales Training”

</title><pros>Pros – Great income opportunity & outstanding Training. The company has been in business for over 34 years. The owner is still passionate about the business, involved and works with everyone in the organization. They embrace a "work hard", "play hard" culture and go out of their way to make the work atmosphere lively, upbeat and fun. You get to meet many people from every walk of life to help them upgrade their homes appearance, decrease maintenance costs and increase potential resale value.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's not easy, the training helps but you've got to apply what's taught and build your skills. In time the income can be substantially above average for a good producer. Afternoon and evening hours are necessary as you meet with clients when they're not working.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-01</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Outstanding Sales Training, Leads & Compensation”

</title><pros>Pros – K-Designers offers a pretty incredible opportunity for sales people who are currently in, or looking to enter, the Home Improvement Industry. They provide high quality initial sales training, ongoing sales training, company generated sales leads, sales and administrative support & an outstanding compensation package.My personal experience has been fantastic. Having spent well over a decade selling in other industries where management constantly changed comp, bonuses and territories I found success with K-Designers. I can count on K-designers to provide me with the tools I need to succeed and the programs are lasting. I know what I need to do to exceed my targets and I'm confident that my financial goals will be met in the process.The support is great as well, which allows me to spend more time with prospective clients.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sales in the Home Improvement Industry can be challenging -- it may take a person a little time to learn and adjust to the dynamics. Some travel and occasional long hours. The rewards more than compensate for these factors</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Place to Work”

</title><pros>Pros – Great company to work for. Strive to be the best in the industry. Treats their employees fairly & provides opportunity for advancement. People are pretty nice and very helpful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing to be briefed in details.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Current Marketing Director In Omaha, NE (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I never thought making big $$$ could be so fun and easy”

</title><pros>Pros – They have a great training program, and the training never stops. If I need help, its only a phone call away.  When you are proud of the products you sell and proud of the installers that do wonders to make a "NEW HOME at the OLD ADDRESS"I have seen some fantastic before and afters results of some of the homes in my area, design work really makes a diffrence. Selling a product that will last longer than any homeowner will that transfers to the next owner, thats unreal.Plus all the different forms of financing that are available make it easier to work with all types of people, if K-Designers cant finance someone the no one could.Best yet the money that I have made doing something thats fun and exciting is unbeliveable.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours are long and there is alot of road time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Let Marketing Directors know in advance where are the areas that they will be covering are.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“cold leads, high pressure, low commision”

</title><pros>Pros – You get leads, the sales manager is good and wants you to succeed.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Leads are unconfirmed, denied appointments, gas and expenses not paid. commission structure much lower then what you are told. Out of town 2-3 weeks a month.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – car provided for out of town travel. guaranteed commission on more then just windows and doors. Use new ways to get leads like internet, radio, tv, anything more then cold calls.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“DO NOT FALL INTO THE TRAP......it can be good but later it gets worse”

</title><pros>Pros – If you are a one-time closer you can make alot of money.  You do recieve recognition for your accomplishments but they are limited.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I have to say the company overall is i it to make alot of money for themselves and if they don't make enough you make nothing. There are alot of extra fees they charge you that you are unaware of. There is a potential to make good money but you need to give not 100% but 150% of your time and money.You need to be a road warrior youmight get told you only need to trave one week a month but its not true, and you TRAVEL not 100 miles but 400-800miles.  You need to pay your way with gas, hotel, and food. Unless you sell while you're gone you will not get paid anything.  I myself went on a trip one week had some car problems and ended up spending over $1,000 in car repairs, hotel, gas, and food. During the trip I did not have one valid appt. so I got NOTHING but spent oer $1,000 to make $0. So if you have money to blow and like to travel this is the job for you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be prepared to be a baby to the company. They will have you doing everything a manager should do PLUS more. and you lose the chance in selling and making money.  Do not accept the job stick to being in Sales there. Your base will not compare to your commission you made as a MD.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Considering K-Designers... read below”

</title><pros>Pros – The income at K.D is what you make it. Several yrs. ago, it was very common for reps with little or no experience to make substantial $. Now, obviously, things have changed. You can still make $ but you can't just rely only on company leads. Another benefit, which can be better in some aspects than the $, is that you can make your own schedule.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1) The leads can be really be suspect at times. Higher-ups at K.D. refuse to admit this but from time to time you will run appts in very-low income/distressed areas. You will have quite a few denied appts. and no shows. If you rely on the leads, it truly is a numbers game.2) You will travel. I did a min. of 40-45K/yr. If you are a regular,commission-only rep, you will do this on your own dime.3)HIGH turnover - Very few reps make it long term. Most flake within the first month or two for various reasons (travel concerns, money, false expectations) As a result, morale can be very low and cynical.4)Company can be really shady when it comes to paying commissions. Issues can include being charged for the wrong product, wrong pricing. They will fix it although sometimes it's like pulling teeth but this can obviously be very frustrating.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Really doesn't matter. Larry is going to do what he wants anyway; that's why several of the branches are struggling, especially Denver, Phx. LA branch was closed last summer.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Given a combination of the economy and self-motivation, a great opportunity for limitless cash!”

</title><pros>Pros – No micromanagement, self-driven position that you can prospect anywhere residentially, flexible hours, amazing commissions when everything goes right, lots of employee/management feedback and training.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1099 position - everything out of your pocket!, pre-set leads could start at 8pm on a weekday, construction industry - lots of unknowns to be aware of,  prospects very sensitive to economy.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the trainings and motivational speeches! It's really up to the sales associate to succeed or not. One must be willing and able and have a financial cushion.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>