<name>Astrium Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Astrium-Reviews-E146359.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Internship”

</title><pros>Pros – Atmosphere, Job, area and subject</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salaries, Time, Experience and Restaurant</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Design Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Graduate Development Programme”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting projects on paper and the opportunity to work with schools and universities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – An extremely dull day to day experience with little to no challenging work for most starters in the company (reading documents for a couple of weeks is normal). A varied and unequal experience across all sites and countries makes it feel even less fair (see the variety in the reviews here). Advertised as a competitive working environment with technical training although this is non-existent for the first few years. The projects and the process (although this could be endemic to the industry) is so complex that I am not surprised by the non-profitable nature of the company and the inability to meet deadlines or budgets. If you would like a foot in the door and to develop just enough so that you can be poached by another company then go for it. Otherwise stick around for four or five years in order to get noticed and perhaps be given something interesting to work on.Starting on a team or in the company in general is fairly daunting with no real integration or "team spirit", it's actually a really demotivating working environment on the most part and it's very hard to feed this back to upper management. A lot of the day is spent chasing up expenses and problems regarding HR as they seem to be overworked however this doesn't make it easy when emails and phone calls go unanswered for weeks.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to be less self-interested and attempt to a create a more nurturing environment in which instead of overemploying and relying on a few to stick with it, you actually retain the talent you bother to let through the interview process. Retention amongst graduates is extremely low and in an ageing company this sets a dangerous precedent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exciting to work on space projects !”

</title><pros>Pros – It is very exciting to work on high-tech projects that are then launched and fly in space !Great commitment of the employees to delivering high-quality products.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The process looks heavy sometimes, but this is also what guarantees the quality of our products.Another drawback would be the pay, which is OK but could be better.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No particular advice, senior management is doing well.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Slow and Inefficient - Continually Hampered by Process Diktats”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly and helpful colleagues.Interesting technology and end product (even though it really isn't rocket science).Flexitime and ability to work paid overtime.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low salaries for engineering staff - even contractors are poorly paid.Odd culture - an awkward mix of Franco-German-British (ie. Marconi-esque for those that remember) management styles and culture.Frustrating place to work - Every aspect of this business is process driven, inefficient and seems to take forever. Yes, you've guessed it, the gullible management have let the consultants in to sell them a series of overpriced 'projects' delivered by 'expert consultants' with little knowledge about how the business actually works. 'Lean' is the latest buzzword - great when you're making cheap mass-produced widgets/cars (eg. Toyota) but is it really applicable to essentially a low-volume bespoke product? The very processes that management use to improve efficiency are the very processes that hamper efficiency when real people try to implement them. Extremely frustrating. I found myself spending 25% of my time on paper chases, trying to get various bits of paper signed by managers and QA staff that knew very little about what they are actually signing. Inevitably when project timescales slip, the engineers and technicians then get blamed for not doing the job quickly enough!Lack of career opportunity - little real career development. Yes, they love to bestow inflated job titles such as 'Higher Senior Engineer' to make people feel good about their plight, but in reality this just means a marginal increase in salary and no paid overtime as you try to climb higher. In the end, I left to work for one of Astrium's customers - 60% instant increase in pay and now with real scope to develop my career.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Answers to all of the challenges within this business lie with the employees and not overpaid management consultants. Empower your highly experienced and committed employees to find optimum solutions. Encourage people to better communicate across departments. Spend more money on training and development. I worked there for 6 years and was never allowed to attend any technical courses despite lots of HR training and development guff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting aerospace industry and work, great work life balance, slow pace of work in frustrating environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Really interesting industry and some of the most interesting engineering projects available. Work consists of Telecommunication satellites, Science missions, ground systems and launchers. Lots of opportunity to work in any imaginable area of a large multinational engineering company, Great work life balance due to flexitime and paid overtime. Good starting place to get a foot hold in the aerospace industry and/or other EADS positions and proactive people tend to do well.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Little pressure to deliver can make work very slow. Huge level of process, inadequate environment and IT infrastructure and flat management structure can make work life very frustrating. Large multinational company results in slow change and a tendency to do things they way they have always been done. Change is not encouraged. Due to flat structure, its very difficult to get promotions in management. Little encouragement or pressure to build skills and continue to develop. If you are looking to be under pressure, constantly challenged, want quick promotion and high pay prospects then look else where</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Spend time aligning priorities of all departments to reduce politics, ensure those who thrive on pressure and challenges are put into positions of more responsibility and spent time and money on streamlining IT infrastructure</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Acronyms rule the day”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly colleaguesImpressive end product (not that you'll ever see much of it)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Talking in acronyms is common to any sphere of work, but here it really does rule the day and I expect many of the misguided souls who work here feel proud to be 'on the inside'. Astrium is a company of one-trick ponies grinding their way slowly through meetings about meetings not to mention the endless paperwork. It's amazing to think that working products actually emerge at the end of this slow and inefficient process. Pay is in the lower quartile relative to other sectors and career progression poor. So many people here seem trapped with no transferable skills and boy don't HR know this. Ok for contractors as a last resort but again pay rates are low. If you really must work in the space sector, seek out opportunities in Canada and the USA.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Resign and make way for talented leaders from other sectors who could potentially start with a blank sheet.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No soft skills”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting projects and subject matter</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nobody appears to have any people skills.  Many people work here just because its the space industry, regardless of the role they do.  Have not worked anywhere this bad at actually doing software development before.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great professionalism and passion for the job</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some times it is too slow</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to Work in”

</title><pros>Pros – Thw work culture is really good. The HR department is exceptionally helpful. The company benefits are good as well. Management, safety and security features are admirable too. And above all awesome location of the site.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is no cons as such. a great place to be in true sense. Needs to match up with the German efficiency.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Development Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience at the design-team level, career and growth possibilities non-existant”

</title><pros>Pros – Team colleagues, manager were very knowledgeable and helpful. Work atmosphere was great. Lots of experienced colleagues to show you the ropes. Lots of respect for development processes. Modern development tools. Work-life balance good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of defined technical career path and seniority. Even experienced developers in our team (+10yrs) were not offered technical management roles in new projects.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Offer your already skillfull employees more formation and chances to acquire more responsability and a wider knowledge of the technical expertise involved in a project. Limiting them to become narrow-focus experts without any recognition is demotivating</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>