<name>Wilder Foundation Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Wilder-Foundation-Reviews-E148389.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-08-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was a great internship experience”

</title><pros>Pros – The staff and supervisors were welcoming and helped my growth</pros>
<cons>Cons – I worked within an internship capactity</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Moving in the right direction.”

</title><pros>Pros – Everyone from senior management to direct service employees is committed to serving the community.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is too much inequality in compensation and opportunities for advancement and growth. It varies a great deal between and within divisions. I think senior management value and respect employees and the work they do, but this is not always reflected in the workplace. They rely too much on middle management to tell them what is happening at the program level.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to work on improving communication. It will take time for people to feel comfortable being candid.Transparency in decision making is needed.Professional growth opportunities should be extended to ALL employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great starting point for my career”

</title><pros>Pros – Diverse staff and families! Pay was ok, but service experiences were worth it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Large organization. I worked in a school-based mental health program, and while I enjoyed the work, I always felt disconnected from the main office, last to get communication,etc.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>