<name>T-Systems International Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/T-Systems-International-Reviews-E14924.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2010-08-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I.T.C”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Benefits, multiple rounds of interviews and travel</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much travel at times</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Prep well for Interview. Multiple Rounds</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good opportunity to get exposed to a lot of areas of IT.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people who are willing to work hard.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Overall lack of competitive service offering and pricing</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – German parent company must accept need to invest in order to grow US market share</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Leader (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Be relaxed but don't expect to advance”

</title><pros>Pros – If you need a relaxed work environment and work less for a reasonable amount of money. Very safe job.Company is owned by a german communication giant and therefore pretty stable. In the area I worked in (consulting), there was lots of instability.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No opportunities for growth.Very unstable and constantly changing leadership team.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More communication and information to employees, especially about changes in partnerships.Mergers and aquisitions should be better managed and communicated. Give people an opportunity to grow based on performance, not only on contacts and networking.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Project Lead (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wonderful and Exciting Oppurtunities”

</title><pros>Pros – Good working environment and lot of opportunities within the company</pros>
<cons>Cons – No comments for Cons, loved the experience working there</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Upper Management (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Seems to become German focused”

</title><pros>Pros – Have some excellent people. Had good knowledge and in the past. Strong in Germany and Austria.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Have some excellent people but do all to lose them. No longer any Telecom know no know in upper management, loosing key advantages and now developments. Key is savings at any cost or consequences. Focus on Germany only. No real HR concept or direction, getting target to save on employee trainings, agree to stop all activities, can not be a good target.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Look at the market and competition and learn since not own ideas. Best change it completely since an ignorant political circus.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Systems Administrator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent Cloud Services company”

</title><pros>Pros – Very mature offering portfolio and extremely strong list of  customer names</pros>
<cons>Cons – Delivery is in bad shape with poor process management and complete focus on cost reduction. The messages from the top get convuluted below. the top management wants lower cost better quality, but the last 2 words get forgotten by the lower management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Spend more time on quality management and you would see much better returns .</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Executive Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great employer with a lot of job opportunities”

</title><pros>Pros – good development opportunities, great international presence,</pros>
<cons>Cons – no stable and long-term strategy</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working hard to improve, but hindered by lack of vision and German work councils”

</title><pros>Pros – Some excellent quality propositions and services</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is hard to transform when the work councils prevent many of the essential changes and executive not willing to stand against them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Define a vision for the company, and a clear strategy of what must be done, then get on and put that strategy into action.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Challenging”

</title><pros>Pros – Challenging environment,professional people with working guidelines and principles</pros>
<cons>Cons – HR needs to improve in providing better benefits and working in processes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – improvise on the benefits</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Mostly enjoyable.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great People, good working environment, you can get to travel to other sites, not just UK. You have the chance to progress move around your career fairly easily.There is a bonus scheme which does tend to get paid.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management don't always listen to the people on the ground. Somtimes the parent company Germany are a little too controlling, so making changes in the UK can get overuled if Germany don't agree.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees, compensate when deserved. Have more regular team meetings.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Support in AustraliaExcellent transfer of international knowledge</pros>
<cons>Cons – Left company because having won a major bid it transpired that the $8 million promised by the German head office to initiate the project was not budgeted for and we were therefore left looking very embarrassed.Note This was in 2002</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Continuous restructuring leading nowhere”

</title><pros>Pros – Work for really big customers</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inefficient way of doing projects- too many internal hurdles.The prices are not in line with the market.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop restructuringRemove at least 3 levels of management</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“T”

</title><pros>Pros – Large Company with many Development opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – Many restruction no salery increases</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Test</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Technical Architecture”

</title><pros>Pros – Global organisation, large accounts, cloud computing exposure. large portfolio. Opportunities to work in different regions. Loads fo d</pros>
<cons>Cons – delivery is difficult due to the dispersed nature of the delivery units. To much reliance on email and internal relationships. If you are connected internally you can make things happen. Can take 2 years to build apprpopiate contacts</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in knowledge management. Finding information is horrible. You are forced to keep info on your laptop. Sharpoint can do this succesfully when delivered well. Alternatlvly invest in a search appliancre</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Architect (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“IT Architect at TSI”

</title><pros>Pros – Good recognition of technical experiencesWell balanced set of regional capabilities</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low international profileChallening burocratic cultureCross department competitionLots of internal politics</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Transition to One Global Firm approachClean up management layers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good solid Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible and good Work Life Balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – Strict Hirarchy and always on duty</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good place to perform and grow”

</title><pros>Pros – international opportunities, diverse cultures and teams</pros>
<cons>Cons – long decision processes, often changes</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Many flexibilities, poor carrer options”

</title><pros>Pros – Many flexibilities about working time, Home Office...</pros>
<cons>Cons – Change of getting higher positions is limited, bad payment development</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Programmer Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Depends upon time..It has carreer risk now”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Money, technical knowledge , good Hike in pay, Good product</pros>
<cons>Cons – Carreer security, Carreer growth, TSYS acquired CTL so it is making bad time for ctl</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – All d best</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“one delightful company to have worked with”

</title><pros>Pros – culture, projects, infrastructure are the great this this company had</pros>
<cons>Cons – internal politics, size of Indian org are the not so good things about this organisation.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – too late</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Solutions Architect (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stable and growing company”

</title><pros>Pros – Mentors and opportunities are available every where</pros>
<cons>Cons – Red tape sometimes with regards to international approval</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Project Manager (Report to Board of Directors) (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“place for wait for retirement”

</title><pros>Pros – if you do not want to work, no-one is pushing you, many locations, possible to (not) work from home</pros>
<cons>Cons – salary poor (I earn 2x now in an US company), political decisions more than market driven decisions, management (most good managers left already in 2005), boring work, bad image at other employers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – now the third row is in charge, better manager changed to other companies already</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It business analyst”

</title><pros>Pros – Internationality expansion, good networking, it culture</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low salary in case of being a startup</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take care about people who is giving more than receiveng, which in most cases is very clear</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Service Delivery Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Global, but German culture, solid but slow”

</title><pros>Pros – Take care of emplyees, strong automotive and cloud know ledge</pros>
<cons>Cons – Structure very complicated and to many layers and matrix responsibilities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Re-org and fix the basics to become leaner and faster</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Network Operator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good”

</title><pros>Pros – it is OK, good place to learn</pros>
<cons>Cons – You have to follow the processes, even if they are not the best</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for beginners, not for proffessionals”

</title><pros>Pros – - benefits- training programs- good colleagues- mostly interesting work</pros>
<cons>Cons – - wrong people in management positions- very poor communication from management to employees- chaotic processes- very bad experience with project management (resources are shared on multiple projects and operation, poor support from line managers etc.)- poor salary (some small experienced newcomers have higher salary than people who are working in company for 3+ years)- quantity over quality</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - pay attention to your employees who work for you for longer time</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stagnant”

</title><pros>Pros – Work life balance ranges from good to excellent overall. There are opportunities to grow on the technical side particularly if you work directly with TSI's partners VMware and/or NetApp</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management practices penny pinching at a level that doesn't make sense, capex approvals get stalled even though orders are confirmed and customers are waiting.There's also very silo, non-global/non-enterprise thinking where different country business units compete with each other to get business at the expense of the employees and the end customer.Management also doesn't seem to get that technology moves forward at such a fast rate and the company needs to invest to grow and be more profitable. See my first point.For an IT company, TSI is so far backwards that I can only shake my head. Approvals are still done manually ie. print, sign, scan, email. This hasn't improved in the 2+ years I've been in the company!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more global, thinking, culturally and process wise. Look at the big picture, not at what the spreadsheet says today.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Can be better.”

</title><pros>Pros – * expending rapidly* some career advancement opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – * a lot of fire-fighting* lacks of direction and determination to do what is right* too German centric</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop jumping into fixing symptoms, spend some time to fix the root cause.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Architect (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Performance does not matter”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible working hours, more or less friendly environment, reasonable payment, sometimes interesting projects, financially stable employer, long hours are not compulsary</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management changes too often, absurd company ethics, no real aim, company proclaims that making money makes fun - forgetting about the joy of achieving something of value.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Making money is a great byproduct of a great product, it should not be your main aim. Stop with those constant reorganizations</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An average company for an mediocre employee to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – The company provides lot's of opportunity for the employees and have the intention and effort in rebranding the company for a presence as Point of Production. On paper, this is a promising company to work for. There's also positive intention to groom university leavers and enroll them into ICT Academy. As a results, young people began to know the company slowly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bureaucracy, internal politics, no proper process, lack of staff concrete development plan and "mediocre" leadership capability unfortunately have been impacting the overall company. In addition, the pay structure is not as compelling to other tech companies surrounding the area.On the other hand, huge culture gap between German headquarters and existing staff in Malaysia with mixed dutch folks felt the intense of having effective communication. The reason behind is prior the establishment of the company, a huge transition from ex-Shell IT staffs are being "acquired". These talents pool are very deep in their knowledge and experiences as a result of previous organization development structure and cultural bonding.As a result, these people came from true global company to a yet-to-be global practice company. Hence, it is hard for these capable folks to understand how they can be part of the company culture. In the end, they leave and today there are very few left over in the company. They maybe waiting to leave. However, even young newer joiners and some from Academy also have that intention too.Most of the establishing cultural with Guiding Principles are only good on paper but not in reality. Branding should be a good exercise, unfortunately the strategy of branding may seem a little exaggerating as the original company does not involved in retail. On superficial level, the branding works to tell public about us, but in reality there are very little effort of employees promoting the company as a place to work for.There are lot's of information that being cascaded down in a non-transparent manner and it is via LT in a silent mode and of course when the news delivered it is almost like breaking news. On second thought, all of us work like guerrilla mode. With that, many of the work, decision and new are either being implemented as in NOW or will never get implemented on time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – T-Systems International Leadership may know what to do most of the time. Therefore more advice would be unnecessary. It is more like turning the common sense into common practice. Building world class company takes time, but importantly world class company comes from well-developed employees and leaders need to prepare to relearn and listen what can be improved quickly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Storage Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“T-Systems Malaysia is really a young company with lot of shell vicious. It has to grow in maturity.”

</title><pros>Pros – It is one of the leading outsources. A good choice to have in your CV. They are dealing with all Shell internal IT.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's really an immature company with too much politics. They can kill even themselves. The dependency from Germany makes sometimes difficult to evolve in a way the company needs. Most of the times the German mentality don't understand at all this part of Asia and tries to repeat several times the same, as if it was not correctly understood.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Clean up the company. It's still possible. Put some more westerner management or local people that has been educated abroad as an interface with Germany.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>SAP Basis (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“its good”

</title><pros>Pros – lots of things to learn with very help full colleagues.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The salary is not on par with market level</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Dont be afraid to hire expert rather than paying penalties</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Database Administrator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“learnt alot, pity the cost driven culture stunts the pay”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity to work with some of the most up to date versions of Database software.At least one course a year.UK base has a very well structured, and mature, change and incident management process.flexibilty to work from home and management trust their employees to get on with it, which is refreshing in this market.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation. Contractors who came across as permanent staff from T-Mobile were paid 3 times what other permanents staff were. Even a promotion failed to improve my salary by more than £1000.Senior management referring to IT staff as factory workers does not have any positive reflections, and makes us think we are working in a sweat shop.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – IT technicians are not factory workers... if we were, we would come to work in overalls.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of growth opportunities limited by uninspired management and German-centric culture.”

</title><pros>Pros – There is good work-life balance and good benefits for employees. The location in Malaysia (Cyberjaya) is also reasonable with minimal traffic going to/from work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inept management, terrible communications between management and employees. Every senior VP wants to be involved in any operations escalation and operations teams seem to be blamed for every little problem that occurs that's outside of their control. We also get the feeling that no major decisions are made outside of Germany.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Know the company's strategic direction and stick to it. Micro managing does not help the technical team do their work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bad management”

</title><pros>Pros – Felxible working hoursMedical benefits are good</pros>
<cons>Cons – No travellingToo much into cost cuttingNo trainingManagement are not good in making decision</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to restructure the management group</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Everything's an escalation, there's even such a thing as "Advance Escalation"!”

</title><pros>Pros – Because of the global outsourcing deal from Shell IT services to T-Systems, most Shell ex-employees have their benefits with them (and they're good). Salary is not excellent, but competitive enough. Strong branding efforts to promote the company in Malaysia as a Global Delivery Hub.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management by escalation, constant fire fighting, weak processes affect overall service delivery quality. Management playing musical chairs, restructuring and changing ideologies all the time. No close communication between Germany and the rest of the world, always a border drawn around Germany processes and tools. Overall, the company is not a true globalized company, and it frustrates its employees.I've seen a freeze to everything from hiring, to training and travel freeze.Management objective is to maintain (or reduce) headcount, but increase quality, which is idealistic because there is no strong structure around the individual (silo) organizations around the world. LOADS of politicking and bureaucracies to go around</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in best talents in all levels instead of paying penalties to customers for not delivering. Observe the guiding principles that you want the employees to follow (lead by example), get more focused control over the services delivery management organization (right now, it's "overcommit --> under deliver"), have stronger billing/charging structure to recover costs.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“T-Systems team members are wonderful”

</title><pros>Pros – T-Systems is like a family.  Those of us in the trenches work together to get the job done no matter how bad things get.</pros>
<cons>Cons – HR provides very little value.  The global career path program in the Germany HQ is not rolled out at TSNA because upper management does not feel it is necessary.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Unfortunately, I do not think that leadership at T-Systems would even bother looking at this feedback, let alone accept this as honest input.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company.... have to work hard in order to be noticed”

</title><pros>Pros – A lot of flexibility, very decent pay, trustworthy colleagues</pros>
<cons>Cons – Structures are a bit stiff, very german thinking</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Accelerate Hr processes, you might be letting a lot of potential go without a fight</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Is good have a Job here but only for some departments”

</title><pros>Pros – The environment is good and some projects could be very interesting in technical area. Also the relationship between co-worker is fully  loyal</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you are looking for a structured company, look away it's not the ideal place and also for career grow</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Most of the people of management office need to be more technical and less "theoretical" but final relationship is good</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Java Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Java developer”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexibility, great professionals, learning opportunities, grow opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – low salary, managers let you alone, misinformation feeling</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hear employees, review of managers, feedback of managers from employees, feedback of employees from other employees, grant better grow opportunities</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“US headquarters too small”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexibility to create customer solutions based on individual customer requirements. Normal pace and productivity expectations</pros>
<cons>Cons – All the drawbacks of working for a company with 200,000 employees with very little of the pros due to small presence and investment in the US. Sales staff was not very professional. Difficult to develop pride in the services offered.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Convince senior management in Germany to make a serious commitment to the US market</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Conultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not bad at all”

</title><pros>Pros – Even if the feeling is of a large established company sometimes - fairly agile and flexible</pros>
<cons>Cons – Mostly opportunities in germnay, less in oter regions</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Adapt some better management practices</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Satisafied”

</title><pros>Pros – Satisafied, encouraged , Happy , Good , Missing</pros>
<cons>Cons – Neglegance ,  horizontal growth , no projects</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More projects , vertical growth</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Security Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No opportunities”

</title><pros>Pros – Different challenges every day. Very demanding scenarios crop up daily.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The management is not dynamic.. They look for the cheapest way out</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your engineers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not too good, not too bad”

</title><pros>Pros – Complexity of work not too high.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay could be much better.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Diversify.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place with work-life balance”

</title><pros>Pros – Normal hours, nice people, less politics, a lot of training</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very hierarchical organizational structure, slow progression, medium salaires</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Organize more activities to bond teams together!!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Solution Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“T-Systems - A large Company ready for the future?”

</title><pros>Pros – T-Systems has a very large global reach. The opportunities are high in terms of what department you work and of what work you want to do. Everything is possible.T-Systems operates with employees which have a high level of passion and integrity and offers a world full of opportunites. The overall diversity of the T-Systems is really impressive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – T-Systems suffers from the "normal" downsides auf large companies. Sometimes slow in chance, strictly covered in old structures.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to the employees.Show respect for given performance of longer employed senior employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>