<name>Unifrax Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Unifrax-Reviews-E15032.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-09-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The best and worst place I've ever worked.”

</title><pros>Pros – For the area, the pay is great with lots of fringe benefits.  The company needs a lot of improvement so there are a lot of opportunities to implement change.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unifrax has the worst qualities of a family run business AND of a multinational corporation. A really flawed culture.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It would do the company good to clean out management and replace with leaders who are committed to accountability at every level of employment.  General bureaucracy, racism, sexism, and homophobia in the company culture are keeping some profitable ideas and exemplary people stuck at the bottom.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unifrax is a very profitable company.”

</title><pros>Pros – Unifrax is a very profitable company. It has smart Engineers who work hard to improve their products and find new uses for old products.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The biggest Con about Unifrax is its workplace environment and politics. However, that is not uncommon to most companies. You need to have a thick skin and be careful about others backstabbing you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management is doing a good job, however, I would suggest that the constant emphasis on new products is stifling innovation.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sale Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I am working since last 18 years”

</title><pros>Pros – openness, simple, good working hours, good working climate</pros>
<cons>Cons – Medium scale, work load, Long traveling,</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good working environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Openness between superiors and subordinates.  This provides a good communication line and gives a feeling to express own opinions.  Freedom to set own schedule in order to obtain the best performance for employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Concern over size of company and the ability for advancement.  Even though there is an openness for communication there are times when it is hard to read situations in meetings, for example.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Salary competitiveness nation wide is not promising for this company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>