<name>J. Robert Scott Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/J-Robert-Scott-Reviews-E152905.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2008-10-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“J. Robert Scott is a mid-sized global boutique Executive Search firm that appreciates entrepreneurial ambition.”

</title><pros>Pros – J. Robert Scott fosters development.  The people are top-notch and intellectually curious.  Being a part of Fidelity, one is able to feel the benefits of working for a small company while at the same time understand the stability that a big parent company brings.  J. Robert Scott has a global view of Executive Search and is well-diversified during tumultuous financial times.  Everyone is ready to help each other on the team, a rarity in the recruiting world.  The review process is detailed - you always know where you stand with the senior management and your direct supervisors.  A great place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – J. Robert Scott is still a smaller boutique firm and must compete with the likes of larger search firms.  While this is sometimes a downside, it should also be considered a benefit.  J. Robert Scott breeds entrepreneurship and allows ambitious search consultants to make an impact.  Because it is smaller, the firm does not have the extensive training and learning development that is sometimes offered by other firms.  But again, this does not stand in it's way of having great mentors and supervisors who assist in personal and professional development.  The firm is growing and many of it's "downsides" are being addressed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – My advice would be to keep doing what you are doing, but to also pay attention to the organic growth of early-stage employees.  The organizational culture at J. Robert Scott makes it a great place to come to work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company”

</title><pros>Pros – Good management, nice people, work is not very intense</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not much room for career growth, salary is a on the low side</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>