<name>e-Rewards Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/e-Rewards-Reviews-E152787.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-04-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work hard and gain experience and friends”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are the best reason to work there. You gain lifetime friends.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is not trained to manage. Many of the people in management positions got there out of convenience. Most managers also don't seem to care to improve themselves or their management style.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Train your managers and do reviews to find out where to improve directly in management. When moral is low you shouldn't put policies in effect which cause moral to become lower.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Do Not Apply”

</title><pros>Pros – Great friendly, relaxed atmosphere, great training, decent benefits...that is all. Ability to work at home (if option is available). This is a place for newly undergrads and people who are in-between seeking a "real job", otherwise please seek elsewhere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very micro-management at times, favoritism and snitching of the blame game with Sales Managers and Project Managers when conflct arises with clients.  The pay is very low with what is required of you to do.  The bonuses are subpar as well.  Long unnecessary hours and if you love to gossip and snitch, this is the place to be.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upper</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun and energetic”

</title><pros>Pros – Great competitive advantage over competition.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Got too big too fast</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Prodution Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible, fresh and new.  Very Employee friendly!</pros>
<cons>Cons – limited VC, training lacks at times.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Grapevine”

</title><pros>Pros – If you love gossip, this is a Great Place to Work. The people who work there are great but the management is aloof.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management lets you find out information regarding your job and your career from others. They aren't proactive about getting in front of sensitive situations.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Gut the HR department, starting at the top. If the people who are supposed to "get us" don't get it, then who does?</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager, Client Development (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Used to be great - still ok but there are growing pains”

</title><pros>Pros – Good integrity w/ clients, good work environment, talented people.  Very good base comp, flexible work conditions, health benefits could be better though. from the perspective of the market this company is really at the top of its game in the field.  There is real feeling of momentum at times.  everyone works hard - there is no room for dead weight. some of the team leaders stand out as great but don't expect to be coached thru anything this is a fast paced environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's gotten too big too quickly.  Health benefits are only so-so.  Project managers overworked and stressed out.  Not much room for advancement.  compensation plans are being adjusted and have become very complicated  - aggressive goals are being set very high, people are working long work weeks to try to hit goals, the goals not always clear.  no pacing - too much room for burnout.  training has improved in some areas but remains critical issue.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Your employees and their talent/knowledge are your top asset - and they are in high demand elsewhere.  do not lose sight of the fact that new business in your field is a long-lead sale. create opportunities for your people and create an inspired organization (instead of a tired one)</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“tolerable a job, but a dead end in terms of a career”

</title><pros>Pros – company offers great benefits (including employee assistance and discounted gym membership) that begin on the first day of employment,  a comparable starting salary, work/personal life balance is encouraged. schedule is flexible and allows the opportunity to telecommute when necessary.</pros>
<cons>Cons – zero opportunities for advancement. customer service team is frequently called upon to perform a number of duties well beyond the scope of our job description, but that is rarely acknowledged and it certainly isn't compensated. the bigger the company gets, the less the CS team is valued.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – don't make us take the "great place to work" survey every year if you aren't going to take any steps to improve upon the points that rate low.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Support Executive (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It could actually be a great place to work - one day.”

</title><pros>Pros – The benefits are awesome.  Monthly bonuse structure was finally resolved to most of the employee's satisfaction.  Hours of operation and the ability to work from home were stellar.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of salary increase for sales support team.Lack of merit or longevity raises for sales support teamLack of proper trainingLack of director feedbackLack of supervisor training and promotions</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Promote from within.  Good people are waiting for the opportunity to shine.  Look for a replacement within the company before venturing out to hire expensive executives who leave the company within 1 year.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Project Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Kurt Knapton is  a great CEO.Employees, benefits. Pay for PM is good considering you don't need to know market research - if you do have MR experience - its not rocket science to cut and send sample so get paid more for less brain power</pros>
<cons>Cons – PMs are overworked, little to no MR experience for 90% of Client Operations. Mindset is volume vs relationship building...churn and burn. Little room for growth unless you are in Sales - no turnover in Sales as they get 10% of every project sold even though the "PM" builds the relationship.INTERNAL PROCESSES - horrible! Efficiency would be nice.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – While I selected Bus Outlook is upward - that's if they have the right people leading them into emerging markets. Mid Management and below with MR experience interacting with clients- internal and external would be a great place to start. Facilitating projects where relationship holder/builder is involved in each phase of projects = success. Just overseeing <>success</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Place to Work in 2008, Not So Great in 2012”

</title><pros>Pros – Staff and mid-management work hard and care about their jobs.Friendly work environment at the staff & mid-management level.Free beverages provided by company.Great location.Great work life balance for senior management  - only work 30-40 hours per week and receive unlimited time-off.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everyone outside of senior management works 55+ hour weeks.High employee turnover.Top heavy organization.Sales management is nowhere to be foundMost employees sit at trading desks or itty-bitty cubesUK managers are temperamental and volatileBelow average 401K.Schizophrenic decisions from senior management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take responsibility for your actionsCEO needs to provide adult supervision to direct reports.Train UK managers on basic interpersonal skills.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager, Client Services (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Great environment to work in and opportunities are available for those who are applicable.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary is a bit lower than standard</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Competitive compensation would be desired, and promotions for individuals that do well should be considered a bit sooner</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>