<name>John J. Steuby Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/John-J-Steuby-Reviews-E153713.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-04-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hell in Hazelwood”

</title><pros>Pros – The company will hire ex cons. They provide training for a valuable skill that can be used elsewhere. Soda from vending machines is priced cheaply.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The place is extremely filthy, disorganized and run down. Management is a dictatorship, instilling great stress on overworked slaves. A one-star rating is too high.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – This business desperately needs organization and professionalism. Clean up the place! Respect employees. Delegate responsibility to qualified personnel. Invest in modernization.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Total Crap Whole”

</title><pros>Pros – None.Dumping ground for white trash.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Your at rock bottom if you want to work here. Quit after 2 days.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Utility (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst place I ever worked.”

</title><pros>Pros – There are no benefits to working for this company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The place is filthy. The bathrooms are just a toilet around a toilet. Sometimes no paper towels.The windows are knocked out and it is hot in the summer and cold in the winter. A fire engine siren blows your ear drums out. There is no health care and never any paid vacation ever!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Totally revise management and employee benefits.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>