<name>George P. Johnson Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/George-P-Johnson-Reviews-E15301.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Way too top heavy, inflated titles yet no clear leadership (for fear of actually being held accountable for something).”

</title><pros>Pros – -Flexibility; can work from home-Friendly people-The work can be fun</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Friends promote friends. not based on talent or merit or leadership skills- Lack of structure (people have titles that don't reflect what they do, so you never know who does what)- Painfully slow internal processes slows production to nearly a snail's pace- A project that could easily be done with 5 people takes 20 people, 15 of which are just "overseeing"</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Leaders should be talented visionaries that inspire, not your mediocre buddies from high school.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Client Services (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My experience was rewarding and valuable.”

</title><pros>Pros – Do great work.Learn from one of the best companies in the business.Work with smart people.Good processes in place.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not supportive of working remotely.Advancement opportunities are limited.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide more management training for leaders.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good but tough”

</title><pros>Pros – There is an ability to work with a lot of high profile clients to do really interesting projects. They are a world wide company that have a casual work enviroment</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is a tough environment for a new employee. There is a lot of live or die by client budgets and the company is easy to lay off employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Encourage a more fun lively environment for employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Event Logistics Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience for resume, employees come last”

</title><pros>Pros – You work with some of the sharpest and most dedicated people in the event management business. The event staff are not just coworkers they are really good people and friends. Health benefits are great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is no real HR department who will go to bat for the employees for bonuses or annual raises. Raises come once a year if you are one of the lucky few even though all work tons of extra hours and travel constantly. There used to be a flexible work environment making the below average pay and management doable but that is no longer. Anyone coming into this office environment should know moral is very low and people are resigning almost on a weekly basis. Too much process and reprimanding for the blood sweat and tears put into the thankless job.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start putting your employees first like you used to. Give annual bonuses and raises to all who perform well. Hire an HR department and experienced people management team. Make your leaders more available. Offer more than an in the office happy hour to thank your employees for hard work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Account Director Review”

</title><pros>Pros – Biggest, global, vertically integrated, can do anything</pros>
<cons>Cons – Corporate vs Agency environment, stuck in their ways</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice place not to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Personell are at the top of their game. GPJ is an excellent training ground. They train you so when they let you go you can go to work for their competitors (the gpj of the south).</pros>
<cons>Cons – When it comes time to downsize Auburn Hills always gets wacked. Bob saves his people in the LA office even though AH does most of the work.LA couldn't bring a project in on budget if their lives depended on it and management lets them get away with it because if they don't mangement will look bad.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Retain your employees. They are your greatest asset. Stop treating your employees like they are second class citizens.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-29</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The rich get richer.   The hard workers get beat down further!”

</title><pros>Pros – Free beer in on Fridays between 4 PM and 5 PM.  Nice office as far as look and design.  Very high end look and feel.  Very clean!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Never heard from Directors, VP, and President you did a good job or Thank You.   Co-workers will tell you job well done.  Great forced unpaid work days in summer.  Sales staff sells projects below estimate and with reduced project duration everytime.  Production staff is responsible to make budget and timeline...and we pay the price if you don't.  Sales staff never learns and never is scolded!  Work too many hours due to lack of staff and lack of upper management help.  Contract workers help, but it is not the solution.  Hire more full time employees!   ESOP ESOP ESOP that is all you will hear.   They seam to hire people and let them go before they are vested.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat the all the employees like you would want to be treated.  We are on to your get rich games on the back of all the hard workers.  Quit purchasing other companies around the world and saying we are broke and can't afford this or that.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A trade show vendor posing as a full-service agency.”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent benefits. Coffee machines work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The way compensation is currently structured, middle management is discouraged to innovate or even produce good work. Don't expect a sense of fulfillment from any work you do.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop trying to pretend to be something you aren't by acquiring companies in spaces you know nothing about. It just ruins lives. Also, rewarding account managers by having them do everything as cheaply as possible is idiotic. Stop it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a real agency”

</title><pros>Pros – GPJ has some of the sharpest people in the Event Business.  You will be able to work on High Profile accounts with sizable budgets & dynamic teams.  GPJ is truly a global company with 24 offices worldwide and now one of several agencies held under the Project: Worldwide.  This is a good place to get your start in the Agency World & a nice company to have on the resume.</pros>
<cons>Cons – GPJ likes to call themselves an agency when what they really do is build exhibits & execute events.  You will not being inventing new ad campaigns or even have any input with your clients on doing so because GPJ typically executes a plan that has already been planned either by the client or a large Ad Agency (ie Chiat, RPA).  Probably most important, GPJ is not well diversified.  About 70% or more of their business is in Automotive making it highly dependent on the performance of that industry.  For example, there were huge layoffs in 2008 & 2009 for no other reason than the severe contraction of the Auto industry.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Sr. Management at GPJ is all about the bottom line. Don't kid yourself, if your account contracts so will your team.  I generally got on well with all of the Executives but it is really a superficial relationship.  My advice would be to actively engage their employees, do a better job of inspiring them to succeed.  The sense of entitlement Management has needs to be put in check because a large part of the success of the company is a result of the hard work of their account teams.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Reverse Sexism, Lack of Communication, Walking on Eggshells”

</title><pros>Pros – Job is very easy, almost boring. No additonal work to be done unless you want to organize the fridge or plan the next company birthday party. Hours are standard 9-5, sometimes even less so if you have things to do outside of work this is perfect. Pay is decent, perhaps slightly below similar roles but it's give and take here. Benefits package and PTO time is great. Management is flexible and understanding, most colleagues are fun and easy to work with. Unique culture.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There seems to be a bit of "reverse sexism" going on at GPJ - a company nearly dominated by female employees. Very cliquey, and as a male employee you really need to watch how you write your emails of how you ask for things to be done without being perceived as too "harsh" or "demanding". Man up ladies - this is business, not some sorority house. Ok, that was harsh/just a joke but in all seriousness, having to walk on eggshells is not an effective way of conducting business.Work is not challenging. The finance house is FAR FROM tradional FP&A. It is more like Accounts Payable, or clerical accounting. A lot of data entry, paper work, filing, etc. The budgeting, forecasting, cost center analysis, etc. is not done here. Perhaps at corporate, or upper level management takes care of it. Not good for development and growth as an analyst. A high school kid could work in GPJ finance.Lack of professionalism - ties in with the cliques and the reverse sexism. Colleagues hold grudges, takes things personally. There really should be an HR workshop on "interpersonal communications".</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Transfer some work from HQ down to the offices for greater transparancy, collaboration and career growth.HR needs to address the female-to-male ratio. Working with females is not a bad thing at all, but the atmosphere needs a balance. Too much on any side isn't good. This will help foster a balanced offering of ideas and thought/view points that the sexes each invariably carry.HR needs to offer MANDATORY classes on effective communication and business professionalism. Axe the clique environment.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great cross departmental team work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Team workPersonable caring management teamFocus, driven, "can-do" attitudePositive work/life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of a clear career growth path/mentoring</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“On the Upswing”

</title><pros>Pros – The people within the company are some of the best I've ever worked with.  Some can be challenging, but most really work well together.  The company continues to evolve with a highly volatile marketplace.  It's really an exciting time to be a part of the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This environment may not be for everyone, as the nature of this business is very fast paced and can be quite reactionary.  For those that are comfortable in that environment, it can be fun, but for others it may be overwhelming.  When times get busy, communication seems to falter between business units and/or offices.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There are times that senior management seems very removed from the employees.  Several years ago there was a strong push that employees are the most important asset of the company.  Many feel that mentality has come and gone.  Generals are built on the shoulders of good soldiers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“GPJ Environment”

</title><pros>Pros – The people and the benefits and flexibility</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of leadershipNo bench strengthUnderpaidToo much paperwork, process-old schoolProduction mentalityNot enough creative thinkingLack of collaboration between offices</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in your peopleGive them the tools to carve their own career pathsStreamline processesThink about a pay for performance model so employees have real ownership in the success of their clients</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Everyone is nice and works as a team to get the job done. Management is flexible in balancing home/work life.</pros>
<cons>Cons – When working on any type of event, it can get crazy at times. Weeks leading up to the event are very stressful and you are expected to work 24/7 to get the job done and make the client happy. However, this is the nature of the business. Some employees put into leadership positions really do not know how to manage people and can make the work environment a little negative with their attitude. You are expected to bend over and do anything for the client, even if it may not be in the best interest for GPJ and might affect the bottom line.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management should look a little closer at who they are putting in leadership roles and whether or not they truly can manage a team and motivate employees. This can really make or break an event. A negative, condescending person in a management position fosters negative attitudes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The worst job I've ever had!”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with interesting clients and casual dress code. There is nothing else I can think of....</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bad management, lack of communication, overcharging clients, pushing useless (and expensive) services to clients (especially IBM), lack of development opportunities, unethical employment practices, lots of unpaid overtime, lack of qualified HR personnel - the list could go on forever....The management at George P. Johnson cares exclusively about pleasing their clients - staff on the other hand is simply a commodity.As long as senior managers are generating profits - nothing else matters, i.e. a senior manager in charge of IBM account had a truly impressive collection of complaints made against him over the years (unfair treatment of staff, very poor communication skills, bad management and many more) yet he is still with the company, enjoying a promotion and an expat living.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employ a proper in-house HR specialist and start reviewing your managers' performance not only on the basis of $ they bring into the business, but also in terms of their staff management abilities.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Graphic Art”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people, Great benefits, great 401k plan</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hard to balance work/life. Lots of over-time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Client Services (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Forward thinking company”

</title><pros>Pros – GlobalExtensive capabilties in experiential marketing</pros>
<cons>Cons – Expensive, premium pricingHeavy auto and tech</cons>
<advice-to-management> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was an eye opener for me redefining my career.”

</title><pros>Pros – Colleagues, work atmosphere,  Clients, Travel, growth prospects</pros>
<cons>Cons – Certain Policies, Opportunity for the local team to travel to other offices.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great benefits, but Senior Management is distancing themselves further from work force and actual work force.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefit package, especially 401 k and ESOP plan.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Communication is not what it once was, Senior management out of touch with work force and favoritism prevails for certain groups or departments.Employees are not evaluated for what they bring to the company but rather the department they are in or the school that they attended.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – A few years back there were surveys taken by employees, one item was the distance between the understanding of today's work load between Senior Management and the work force. Bob Jr promised in a Town Hall meeting that he would make the effort to come to each department and spend some time with each employee to get a better understanding of what their job entails and get a fresh perspective. To my knowledge this has never happened. No one I know has had that visit from Bob to date. Why make empty promises?.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Could have been a great place to work if they cared more about their employees”

</title><pros>Pros – Great team of people to work with for the most part.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Do not care about employees. Do not give good raises or give any bonuses. Moral overall is low.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Care more about your employees and reward them for their work and you will have happy workers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Production Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to work, but not necessarily advance.”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent leadership, great work enviroment, good benefits, fast paced, exciting, changing, evolving, advanced, all in all a good place of employment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not a clear path to advancement, somewhat challenging to get the necessary tools to perform the job.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The people in the trenches are typically right...don't forget that.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Going down the tubes”

</title><pros>Pros – Project team made up of incredibly bright, motivated people who consistently delivered great results, and who worked as a cohesive unit. Management at the team/project level was top notch - the team was supported and kept as informed of important information as they could.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Amazing lack of foresight by upper managementVindictive and knee-jerk reactionary "solutions" from board membersExecs promise "transparency" and deliver anything butTouted benefits package no longer anything special</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You are not living or working in the 1950s - technology needs to be something you embrace. As long as you have board members who don't know the first thing about technology making decisions about something they don't understand at all, you're going to continue down a path that will be disastrous long-term. He probably doesn't care, as he will have left by then, but the company will pay dearly for his short-sightedness.Additionally, the story told by management about "The GPJ Way" doesn't reflect a triumph - it reflects a failure to plan. It illustrates how to create the least effective, most expensive, one time use solution that could have been avoided if someone had planned. That's not exactly a recipe for success, gentlemen.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Event Management Industry Giant”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to start off your career as an event planner, good benefits, ok salary for event planning professionals, fun industry to be in.</pros>
<cons>Cons – benefits and salaries have been cut in recent years due to the economic recession, there is not enough staff. Too much travel and long hours.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – management needs to look at hiring enough people to manage all the work at hand, company needs to reconsider providing benefits with no contributions</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It used to be about us, now it's the bottom line”

</title><pros>Pros – The ESOP (Employee Stock Ownership Program) was nice, and had a lot of income potential if you can stick around long enough.  The projects were interesting to work on, and you got to go to some fun destinations.</pros>
<cons>Cons – When the economy took a dive, so did a good chunk of the workforce.  A whole year went by as we all huddled in our offices/cubicles wondering who would get the axe next.  Those who were left behind were required to work harder and longer, or else lose their own job.  I can appreciate the need to keep the corporation lean, but the way they treated their employees was, well, very corporate.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You have (and had) good people under you with the smarts to help you keep and gain new business.  Trust them and let them help you.Also, remember that what you do to your employees during a bad economy will be remembered when things improve.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pros & Cons at GPJ”

</title><pros>Pros – Great experience working with worldwide clients in fast-paced environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – "Team" environment could be improved.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Encourage an environment where folks are working more synergistically to meet the goals and serve the needs of clients.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-02-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Event Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No better or worse than other conference companies”

</title><pros>Pros – It's quite a large organisation, but it doesn't take much to shine. People appreciate what you do. Freelancers don't have to wait too long to be paid, so I'm not embarrassed to work for GPJ.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The clients aren't handled as well as they could be: We had to do more for less money. As there is no overtime, it doesn't cost more for GPJ for us to work harder.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Lead the conference industry in working out what will replace trade shows and conferences, or all will be lost.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>