<name>TU/e Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/TU-e-Reviews-E156538.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Reasearch assistant”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent work environment; great interaction with student, professors and researchers; great campus with sport center on site; Salary is fair particularly compared to other European countries</pros>
<cons>Cons – No complaint, except maybe the quality of the cantine, but then again the slection is really large.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work, which helps attract talents from all over the world</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>PhD Student (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“PhD student in Electrical Engineering”

</title><pros>Pros – - I worked as a PhD student in TU/e for 4 years. The research (e.g. cleanroom) facilities were excellent, as well as the scientific level of my supervisors/colleagues. Low pressure, agreeable work environment. Very good courses for personal development.- Net salary: 1500 / 1800 eur (1st / 4th year) + Holiday allowance.- Holidays: 40 days/year.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - A bit too much freedom. You have to push yourself sometimes to make sure your project is progressing.- Dutch weather/food.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Student-assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Student-assistant”

</title><pros>Pros – Very open culture. Everybody is willing to help you.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I would like to see this university a bit more ambitious. To my opinion it is the best university of The Netherlands, and for some research areas they are competing with the best universities in the world. People do not always seem to be aware of this. Or at least, they do not communicate this.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>PhD Student (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very good place to start your scientific career”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice environment to work during master or PhD</pros>
<cons>Cons – Difficult career opportunities after postdoc</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>PhD Student (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good learning and research environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Well organized, good support of PhD students.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working in isolation is common for PhD students.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create better access to the researchers for the industry. Less red tape for shorter projects.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Lecturer/Coach (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very nice and straightforward employer”

</title><pros>Pros – Children's day care centreAutonomyA lot of time per studentInteresting colleaguesInnovative education model</pros>
<cons>Cons – EindhovenUniversity politicsLunchStuck to School holidays</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>PDEng Trainee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A pleasure place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Multidisciplinary teams, rich in culture, work with young and lead researchers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Old offices and buildings, service is not good enough in the city</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>PhD Student (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is a nice place to do PhD research.”

</title><pros>Pros – High level of academic research, not much external pressure, good technical support, opportunities for international conferences, reasonable salary for a PhD student</pros>
<cons>Cons – The quantity and quality of local bachelor students are declining, an unfavorable situation for maintaining the education system and high level research.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Dig into the student pool to get better students for the bachelor program as a technical university. Encourage interest from mid-school students on science and engineering.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>PhD Student (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Perfect  place to do research”

</title><pros>Pros – Good education, healthy working environment, a lot of  practical tools</pros>
<cons>Cons – very difficult to stay after PhD or Postdoc or to get a permanent position</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“where the innovation starts”

</title><pros>Pros – Tu/e has very good connections with many industry companies, like Philips, NXP, AMSL, etc. Many projects are cooperated with industry partners.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Dutch language will be a difficulty to the foreigners, although the working language in research is English. The classes for undergraduates are conducted in Dutch.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It is a very good place to carry out research work, but it will be better to further improve the cooperation between the groups.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>PDEng (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worth the effort”

</title><pros>Pros – Opens opportunities if you are non european to work in hi tech companies in Europe</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low SalaryProjects might be in other cities and you have to move</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Career prospects”

</title><pros>Pros – World leader in many fields from Architecture/design to Electrical EingineeringExcellent benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited career progression for postdoctoral candidates</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide longer term contracts as lecturers/Assistant/Associate Professors i.e. more opportunities for tenure track.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>PhD Student (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice place to do research”

</title><pros>Pros – 1) Access to a good network of researchers in the netherlands2) Europe's Top 5 University of Technology.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1) Need to find a right supervisor</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide acces to more employment opportunities for foreign students...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>