<name>X-FAB Sarawak Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/X-FAB-Sarawak-Reviews-E15785.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-02-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Quality Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pleasant”

</title><pros>Pros – Great teams and good management team with clear objectives</pros>
<cons>Cons – No contractual bonus yearly. Nothing much i can say on negative site.:)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep it up!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Process Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A place with slow pace development”

</title><pros>Pros – If you prefer a slow pace development in your career path, this will be a great place to be. People here are friendly and mostly close to each other as most of them are from a small local town. People here are more into building good relationship among each other.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Strong office politics between the top management. No overtime pay. Very low salary adjustment and increment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to be more creative on the strategy of the company</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Process Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to start off if you are local.”

</title><pros>Pros – Relaxed job environment, not as busy as other foundries fab, still growing potentially towards a stable state as compared to other well known fab in this region.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow increment for locals, too many expats which are coming just to live a good life with good money without really bringing up local technical experts. A training pool for locals where retention rate of these people are poor.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Appreciation towards local employees is important to really sustain XFAB's business. After all, those expats are just going back to their homeland or stay forever with their current high paid positions comfortably and not contributing much to the economy/people here.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Enjoy and fun”

</title><pros>Pros – Have the best benefit  between others company. Stable and no worried working there. have a lot experience people work there and able to learn more.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Need to work night shift for two months and need to work on weekend or public holiday. 12hours wearing bunny suit.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Let the junior staff have more oppotunity  to become leader and have more leader ship training to the leader.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manufacturing Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“X-Fab Sarawak”

</title><pros>Pros – Work only 3 or 4 days a week.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long working hours (12 hours a day).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“X-FAB in Kuching SARAWAK”

</title><pros>Pros – Government Link and Profit Looking for Supply</pros>
<cons>Cons – Reserve, Inward Looking and Limited</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More Chinese vacancy</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Process Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place for slow pace job”

</title><pros>Pros – Slow Pace jobGood relationships among colleagueHave to be independent, might not learn a lot especially for young interns and fresh gradsEasier communication among the locals.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A lot of miscommunication due to different nationalityA very pushy management techniquesNo compensation for working overtime, mostly trade offPoor management skills, managements are not setting good examplesUnfair salary package for the locals.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need a good examples.Need to considerate for the lower income employee</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Glad to have worked for X-FAB”

</title><pros>Pros – I don't know about other departments but I have had some good experiences with those in our department. They are willing to teach as long as you are keen to learn. The company has a pretty well established system and SOP that worked fine with me. I know some competitors around the area that are way far behind in terms of that.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Internal customers are even harder to deal with. The company had a hard time struggling to survive. At least that's how I felt back then.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Maybe it's time to establish a system that promotes better understanding among departments such that each department is not 'over-protective' about what 'belongs' to them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Process Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review of XFAB Sarawak”

</title><pros>Pros – XFAB Sarawak offers one of the most competitive compensation in the area of Kuching and Sama Jaya industrial Area. There are various opportunities for career advancement.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The overall management team is relatively inexperienced in managaing people. The culture of the company is still rather backward. However, it is improving gradually.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay more attention too the welfare of the people. If people are happy, the workforce will produce more exciting results.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>