<name>U-Save Supermarkets Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/U-Save-Supermarkets-Reviews-E16367.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent company to work for if you like food. They give you good employee discounts which is always cool. Decent company”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits, high company morale. Everyone is a team player so its all good. Hours are not too bad either.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not a lot, not a lot. More of a push should probably made to keep stores cleaner. Could potentially scare customers away.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop with the micromanagement and empower your employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Store Manager/Grocery Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was good until stores stated to close.”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy work, good people to work with, good pay plus a once a year bonus, family work place, some medical benifits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some of the stores need tlc, not good locations (bad neighborhoods), work 50 plus hours a week, drive to other stores about an hour from your store for meetings no comp for gas or mileage.</cons>
<advice-to-management> – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Learning experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Stability.  Everyone has to eat!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay, no retirement, and outside upper management ruined the culture of the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I wouldn't know where to start.  Outsiders brought in by owners destroyed the company culture.  Instead of focusing on the things that we "could" do right and growing the company,  they led by intimidation and caused the company's demise.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>