<name>Arthur D. Little Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Arthur-D-Little-Reviews-E16670.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-05-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good leadership for US operations</pros>
<cons>Cons – Consulting is a tough business</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Management Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing staff.”

</title><pros>Pros – Brilliant people and exciting work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – At this time it is</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very Dissappointing operations in the US.  Poor recuriting and retention practices.  Highly political environement.”

</title><pros>Pros – Brand name from legacy era.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Weak executive management and senior leadership</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Return to legacy ADL standards</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Arthur D. Little Review”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work/life Balance.  Average hours is not as crazy as other consulting firms.Friendly co-workers.  Very open culture.  Managers, Sr. Managers and Directors are accessible at all times.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low salary.  No salary revisions for the last two years. No bonus for 2009.  Average salary lower than average in the industry.Low opportunity for career advancement.  The firm is stuck with no growth potential</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Change of senior management is needed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Internationally respected company with opportunities for professional growth but limited in career advancement”

</title><pros>Pros – ADL is an internationally respected brand name with a wide network of expert advisors.  It has a fun, collegiate culture, with a strong entrepreneurial streak due to its small office nature.  It has offices all over the world, giving consultants the opportunity for international travel and working with diverse clients.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company is often very hierarchal, with sometimes very poor communication between management and junior levels.  The problem may be rooted in the fact that most of its locations have a very small office feel yet are a part of a larger corporate network, leading to somewhat autonomous, even rebellious, nature.  Adding to the tension and suspicion is the fact that ADL is owned by public company Altran.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Needs to be more of a meritocracy and a focus on delivering results (ie, selling projects)</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company with family run culture and supportive team mates”

</title><pros>Pros – Family feel; Development opportunity; Focus on training and intelligence management</pros>
<cons>Cons – Tough competition for consulting engagements in BCG, McKinsey, Bain etc - ADL is a smaller player and not as well regarded</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people, fantastic culture, company constantly in transition”

</title><pros>Pros – Diverse opportunities within technology domainOpen and flat culture - you can question anyone; only truth survivesCool company - lets you live with your quirks; almost no politics !Great people - within and in the extended network of expertsGood values.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor internal processes; Severely incapable HR post MBO; Low transparency;Low capabilities on non-tech domains</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Agree on broad governance and HR principles, communicate them transparently and please implement the policies</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very disapointing”

</title><pros>Pros – small company, good interaction with projects in other countries</pros>
<cons>Cons – No management organization, did not use my competences and knowledge to favor the company</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ordinary experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Good environment, good people, you can make a lot of friends here. People are nice and you can keep a good lifetime balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – low turnover among different projects, low focus on training. compensation not aligned with the top consulting firms</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – increase the turnover among the junior staff epsecially let the BAs work in different industries and different practices</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Most prestige consulting firm in the world”

</title><pros>Pros – Hard working nature and best team work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lower salary level than competitors</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – increase compensation level</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great culture, variation, responsibilities and growth opportunities”

</title><pros>Pros – Great culture, variation, responsibilities and growth opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long work hours, less international travel than many other firms, somewhat lower pay (currently)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in salaries to ensure retention of talent</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Enriching”

</title><pros>Pros – Learning and the heritage along with the brand and history</pros>
<cons>Cons – the firm is slow in building up geographies</cons>
<advice-to-management> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review”

</title><pros>Pros – You got to read and understand lots of information which will improve you a lot. And Also it wil expand your view of the analyzing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You could not have any recreation time, even vacation. Definitely there is no holiday.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hands-on experience of consulting in a live environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good growth opportunities as the  team size is small. Reputed brand name worldwide in the strategy consulting arena. Great management and seniors.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unstructured work. May lead to no work or sitting ideal sometimes.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great entrepreneurship spirit - great people - consulting with a difference”

</title><pros>Pros – Learning environment is really great with a good mix of training and on the nob case work with seniorsRespect for the consultants; people are not treated as bodies that have to deliver work for the due a dateADL has the ability to provide unique client work that stands out vs. repeated once size fits all assignments from other firms</pros>
<cons>Cons – not easy to find something that really has an impact</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-31</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“U. S Operations are Disappointing and Risky”

</title><pros>Pros – Work Life Balance compared to other firms</pros>
<cons>Cons – Cost constraints on almost everything, no initiatives for professional development, no training for new employees, no mentorship programs, jobs of junior staff depend on senior staff in the firm (e.g. if a senior management member leaves, junior staff is laid off as well), risky job and would not recommend if you have other consulting offers, no transparency in corporate culture, overstaffed in the U.S and utilization rates of consultants very low in the U.S</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Better professional development and employee retention programs.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“strong brand in France”

</title><pros>Pros – learn the ropes (if you are in your twenties)</pros>
<cons>Cons – uncompetitive in UKleadership in the UK destroys valueFatal hiring decisions at the top</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience and place to work and learn”

</title><pros>Pros – Arthur D Little is a global strategic management consultancy offering great opportunities for personal development and learning. All the package is supported by great teams.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As usual in the conslting industry especially in high project requesting times, clients are very demanding expexting superior work by the consultancy which requires significant work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting but not very dynamic”

</title><pros>Pros – From certain points of view it could be said that the general impression is that the team is an experienced team</pros>
<cons>Cons – Yet, it could be said that what was the general feeling about the internal environment and atmosphere is that it was not very dynamic</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Young and fun people and very interesting projects: great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great culture: smart, young, and fun people.Very interesting projects, and high exposure from day onePossibility to work accross different industries (mainly at BA and C levels)Strong in Energy & Utilities and Telecoms & Media, but there are also projects in other industries (Travel & Transportation, Pharma, Retail, Insurance, DDs, etc.)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of international projectsIn some projects work can be long hours</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Doing a good job in general lines, but need to bring back the former prestige of the Arthur D. Little brandTake good care of recruiting in order to maintain the office culture as is, and leave enough room at higher levels to guarantee BAs and Cs career development</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“valuable experience that was able to improve analytical skills”

</title><pros>Pros – opportunity to improve analytical skills and business skills through various projects. opportunity to experience various industries. good compensation level. new office looks great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – work life balance - there was no holidays. need more communication among team members. still use paper to log time and expenses.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – need more efficient approach to handle project. need more meeting to discuss not only about progress but tatics. There was an order not communication.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Still a good name, but...”

</title><pros>Pros – Good practices and no nonsense approach, flexible environment. TIME is particularly strong. Good relations in the GCC. Able to draw on super long history.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work culture not the best. Financing dept a pain with expenses. Lack of social activities. Generally suffering from a lack of new blood at the higher levels.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – New blood needed. Different approach to interns who have ample work experience. More training needs to be scheduled. And how about revising the view on bonuses and medical insurance!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review: Internship at Arthur D. Little”

</title><pros>Pros – still a strong brand among industry pundits, highly professional, more senior than other consulting firms</pros>
<cons>Cons – ADL serve considerably smaller clients than MBB, the have less structured processes (which, however, allows for more creative freedom in the daily work as a consultant)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – processes need to be streamlined in order to regain forces, maybe a merger with a strong partner would help ADL to come back to former glory</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“US operations are floundering, and unless new directors with sales skills join fast, it may be a sinking ship.”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity to work on an interesting range of projects, some with a strategic scope. Many projects involve limited travel to the client site, improving work/life balance. Reputation as a collegial firm is generally justified.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No understandable connection between effort and bonus calculation. Several good directors have left the firm in recent months. The few directors left can't generate enough revenue to support all the staff. With the corporate parent reluctant to invest further, the future for the US offices appears bleak.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Either invest further in the US operations (adding directors who can sell and staff), or consider either selling the US operations to another firm or disband the US effort entirely.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Brand but for How Long?”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting projects to work with diverse clients and skillsets.  Great brand recognition in the marketplace.  Great peer group to team with on assignments.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of coherent management strategy; lots of turnover just as progress to re-establish US business is taking off.  Uncertainty as to survivability of the US business.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create a strategy and stick with the people chosen to lead.  Fund the growth through the lean economic times.  Create less Europe dominant group.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-08-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Arthur D. Little has some important areas of opportunity specially outside of Europe”

</title><pros>Pros – Good projects in which work was interesting. The opportunity to work in multiple regions across the different offices is algo an excellent learning opportunity</pros>
<cons>Cons – Its a small consulting firm with limited research support.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus more on giving uniform training across lower levels of the organization as well as recruiting the right level of skills at the manager level</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-25</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“-”

</title><pros>Pros – unique work environmentsmart people with pragmatic approach and deep industry knowledgechallenging projectsthe approach is collaborative and means engagements are staffedwith a director, a manager and two or three consultants, to combine a range ofexperience and expertise in order to establish a strong relationship with ClientsADL coined the “side-by-side” principle to describe its involved approach to aclient’s business</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary is not as high as other firms, and this is a problem for recruitment of fresh MBAs</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – be more focused on strengthening the Brand</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good work but low compensation”

</title><pros>Pros – Good projects and high growth in the Middle East.ADL is present in the Middle East from a long time and is well established in the Middle East Market. Many of its projects are high-profile projects with both the government and private sector. Job satisfaction in terms of learning and contributing to the project team is also high.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low compensation and employee benefits.Employee compensation is much below industry benchmarks. To add to the dis-satisfaction, middle east is not hospitable either with its extreme weather, high cost, and limited social activities.Hence compensation is one of the prime motivators for a professional working in this region</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve compensation</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An Intern's Peek”

</title><pros>Pros – You are able to work with and around professionals from various companies and industries so there is a lot of knowledge and experience to be gained in a short period of time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours can get a little long at times so the work-life balance is lacking at times.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Set up a program to hire undergraduates and prospective MBA candidates to aid in the recruitment of tomorrows professionals.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>