<name>E! Entertainment Television Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/E-Entertainment-Television-Reviews-E16794.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Audio Mixer Sound Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“fW”

</title><pros>Pros – Amazing staff and management, great benefits 401K, comfortable work environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours, but you are always compensated for over time and missed meals.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing great work!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Freelance Transcriber/Logger (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Fun Experience!”

</title><pros>Pros – I worked on a reality show that aired on the Style Network under the umbrella of E! Entertainment Television. It was a freelance position so I was able to pick/choose my own hours. You had access to all levels on the production. You were able to work independently without a watchful eye hovering over your shoulder at all times.  Central Midtown location; close to public transportation.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The office was silent while we were working. It was a bit strange to me. I enjoy background noise.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – E! should seek out employees from under the umbrella of their other networks.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Producer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Young culture...and you better love pop culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Really great co-workers, the opportunity to handle multiple job tasks (this is a pro because once you leave E! you'll have a lot of experience that goes beyond your job title and that's valuable to your next employer), and when they decide to have them - really great company parties!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay (seriously everyone in the business knows how much E! underpays their staff), forced production staff out by changing their status from staff to freelance (no more health benefits, 401k, etc.), not a lot of room for advancement (unless someone quits, you're stuck with your title for a while...a LONG while), a lot of corporate red tape and pointless hoops to jump through when you're trying to remain creative and get the job done.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upper management really needs to sit down and talk with the production teams.  They're so disconnected from the reality of what happens in production that they fail to see why some of their requests / decisions are misguided.  Get to know your staff and find out how to run a more effecient, streamlined business - starting from which shows you greenlight to how each show is handled and by whom.  Oh, and pay your production teams more...or at least industry standard rates! Geez.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Editor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E! provided me with a wide variety of different programming to work on. Never got stuck in a rutt.”

</title><pros>Pros – A young place to start out, great diversity of people. People are supportive and help each-other out. Lot's of former E! people around town, so it's a door opener to mention that you worked there. You're  more likely to get hands-on experience and be trusted with new things than many of the smaller places.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salaries tend do be lower on the PA, Associate and Producer side. Things have gotten more fractured with productions being hired out to teams.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fine for a little while if you fake it, but really an inhospitable growth and development environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Bagel Thursdays, and the building/location is pretty cool. Salary, overtime and health benefits are great and free membership to LACMA. Positive ends there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most everybody walks around this place in fear of losing their job, which they are unsure if they even deserve. Very few innovators among execs and therefore a lot of deflecting to lower level employees to make them look better, this can backfire and cause misaligned allegiances or simply a lot of back stabbing. A culture of insecurity and confused protocol. No training for newly created positions, just jump in and swim, and beware of underhanded business moves among coworkers. Nothing you do or say is in confidence so remain neutral at all times.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in your young and taken advantage of talent, you have a lot coming through, usually in the form of assistants and interns (I was coordinator). Most of these bright minds are untrained, and overlooked and ushered out within a few months without getting any value from the experience. These kids might even save your network from drowning if you allow them to have a voice and a hand in. Some of them may even actually care about the health of the Kardashians franchise.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Only good for getting a foot in the entertainment industry door...”

</title><pros>Pros – Good place to start your career in the L.A. entertainment industry as they tend to hire people who are "green" to Production so it's easier to get hired compared to other studios/networks, but move on as soon as you have enough experience under your belt, a year at most.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management is literally crazy, and it trickles down the food chain as each nutcase hires another through the hierarchy.  This is well known in the industry, so people LOL if you say you work here.  E! has a bad rep for being the "National Enquirer" of TV, on par with TMZ.  Employees are offered benefits but only after 3 continuous months, which always coincides with the end of a project, so they let you go right before you get benefits.  That's their way around DOL regulations.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay benefits to all employees from DAY ONE.  Go back to the "old days" of E! and produce QUALITY programming.  Get rid of the TMZ mentality and anything remotely resembling the Kardashians --  you're the laughing stock of the entertainment industry!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E!”

</title><pros>Pros – good benefits, great location, young atmosphere, great coworkers</pros>
<cons>Cons – low pay, exploitative upper management, degrading management style, lots of baiting for promotions to extort more tedious, unpaid work out of you and never anything behind it.  lack of organization in post production.  management style is every man wins for himself with no regard for leadership.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“definitely worth it”

</title><pros>Pros – awesome people to work with, very flexible</pros>
<cons>Cons – difficult to move up from being an intern</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good work experience and opportunities”

</title><pros>Pros – Very cool environment, got to meet lots of people in the industry, supervisors were really helpful. Great experience and fun internship/.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Could be kind of boring at times. There were days where it was really slow and  at times lots if tedious work would be given, like filing and organizing, passing things around the office.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Not sure how management worked and how growth was there since i was only there for a summer. I do know that most people I worked with are all not there anymore for reasons unknown to me. So something must have to change to keep people there longer.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“absolutely toxic work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Medical and dental coverage is excellent. You can event get certain cosmetic procedures covered under the company plan.(of course only in L.A.)</pros>
<cons>Cons – HR department staff is inappropriately aligned with senior execs across departments. Nothing you share with HR is kept in confidence.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Total disconnect between senior management and employees. Turnaround is high. There needs to be more sheparding of talent within departments and existing staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – VEry nice work environment, cool people. great technology</pros>
<cons>Cons – salary is a little low</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – increase the salary a bit</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Casting Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company to develop entertainment industry skills...”

</title><pros>Pros – -Great Location-Good Culture-A chance to develop skills and network with people in the industry-Good to put on the Resume</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Somewhat low pay-Narrow focus in terms on industry-Can be long hours-Shows generally have short runs</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It would be helpfull if there was some sort of permanent structure where you could work full time for E! and got from show to show...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pretty fun place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Bagel Thursdays make everyone happy. Fun, relaxed environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Decision making is an issue... make a decision and stick with it!!! Management is notorious for going back and changing major campaigns at the last possible second, creating overworked, unhappy employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Overall, this is a great place to work, but management skills are lacking in some departments.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Finance Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“everyone should write a headline”

</title><pros>Pros – The company is a very young crowd. It is in a great location with many interesting and creative people. They have a great holiday party and a coutyard party. There is ample room for growth although many people do not stay longer than 3 or 4 years. You see celebrities, if that's your thing. It's casual so dress as you like, jeans, flip flops and tanks. Sometimes it feels like you are on a college campus - but its a great start in the enterianment industry. It is now owned by comcast, so it may be changing a bit... but overall the place is a great start.</pros>
<cons>Cons – very low wages,  and longer hours</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – higher pay</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to start a career straight out of college.  You won't want to stick around too long.”

</title><pros>Pros – If you are young and can't find another place to work in entertainment than E! is for you.  Just get out ASAP.  And watch out for G4, poorly managed throughout and they are clueless about how to run a network which is why they lose millions a year.  Stick to E! and style only.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor worklife programs, no investment in professional training / development internally.  It is a place to collect a paycheck and that is all.  Other entertainment companies will invest in you.  Also, poor environmental preformance, give very little back to the community.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – A culture of innovation is necessary to attract top talent...but you wouldn't be into that since it means your lack of creativity / business innovation would cause you to lose your job.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Positive experience on a personal level but the glass ceiling is high.”

</title><pros>Pros – The benefits are really good - especially the health insurance, or at least it when when I worked there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The salaries are low with very minimal opportunities for promotion.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There are too many people in certain departments and too few in others. Employees often feel isolated from the rest of the company. Too much communication via email, zero to minimal face-to-face communication with coworkers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I miss working there.”

</title><pros>Pros – There is always something happening at E! It was an exciting place to work, but there weren't many options for advancement.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Once in a production position, its difficult to get into the creative side of the business.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your managers and supervisors</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>