<name>Ann & Robert H. Lurie Children's Hospital Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Ann-and-Robert-H-Lurie-Children-s-Hospital-Reviews-E17140.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Desktop Analyst Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Enjoyable company to work for.”

</title><pros>Pros – Company encourage growth and promotes from within.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not-for-profit keeps the salary low.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue doing what you're doing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's fast-paced, intriguing and passionate place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Amazing mission and service. It's truly wonderful to work for a place that is directly working to make the lives of children better each day.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay is pretty low and there is a lot of work, but this comes naturally in most non-profit environments.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Lead Point of Service (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very comfortable working environment with opportunities for growth.”

</title><pros>Pros – Very good orientation and education department.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited possibilities for promotion (Management)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great hospital to work for, a lot of exposure to various illnesses/diseases that you could not see at any hospital”

</title><pros>Pros – Great staff, wonderful experiences, grateful families, beautiful facilities</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is not a lot of movement, if you are seeking management opportunities they are few and far between.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Clinical Research Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I felt honored to work here and was so excited to start, but I was saddened by some of the negativity in my coworkers.”

</title><pros>Pros – It's top ranking, people are generally really nice, it's for the kids, they're doing some interesting research that will hopefully have meaningful results</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management seems like a mess and it trickles down to negatively effect moral and performance. Human resources is notorious for not getting things done and for having ridiculous roadblocks that keep us from advancing. I think the system should be re examined.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve HR by taking out some of the red tape of hiring more or better people. Hire practice managers who actually have experience managing people. Fill vacant spots quickly. Find a way to make cost cutting discussions less negative.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>RN Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“satisfying work”

</title><pros>Pros – great culture, fantastic mission and belief statement</pros>
<cons>Cons – people are grandfathered into positions that they do not earn nor deserve</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This place may seem like a good place, but it's just false advertising”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefitsNew place with fancy equipment</pros>
<cons>Cons – There was a lack of management who basically didn't care about the issues in the department. They let the senior people do whatever they wanted, and didn't have the guts to either fire the inappropriate staff or at least tell them to get their act together. There was no team feeling, most of my co-workers hated on each other 24/7. Even with the move the pay is NOT competitive. I was severely disappointed with this place because their only excuse as to why the place SUCKED was "we do it for the children." As meaningful as that sounds, if you don't learn how to treat your team correctly, it's hard to wake up everyday and want to go to work "for the children", especially when you're not given any resources to properly do so.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Replace with new management and show that you at least care about your employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate I (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Former employee- great culture and people.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people to work with, great experience, great management and time off. Everyone is dedicated. Rewarding and challenging work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay could be more competitive.Opportunity for growth is somewhat limited.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None- they were great!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate II (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Meaningful work”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly atmosphere and culture, care for employees' welfare, good work/life balance, good benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of opportunities for advancement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Excellent management team</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate II (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company for entry level professionals”

</title><pros>Pros – Great atmosphere, flexible schedules, good benefits. After being here for 3 years, this company has proven to be a positive workplace to learn and grow. There are great benefits such as, emergency dependent care, affordable health insurance, and education supplements. Very mom friendly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not very competitive salaries, now that the location has moved downtown, it's my theory they should have more competitive salaries, but overall they are pretty good.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Nurse Practitioner (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice team atmosphere in which to work under high pressure.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hours can be trickey sometimes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate III (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Children's Memorial Hospital aims to better care for its pediatric patients by supporting employees' personal, professional, and social development. Children's provides employees with rewards for healthy lifestyles including access to Weight Watchers at Work, tuition assistance for courses to further your career, and an opportunity to get to know your employees through social activities such as beach volleyball.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In order for the hospital to care for all of its precious patients it had to spread out among several buildings, requiring families to take shuttles to go between appointments at the hospital and parking garage and those at the Lincoln Park outpatient center. This often caused confusion for the families who might arrive at one building with enough time to get to their appointment but find out that they were scheduled at another and then are late for their appointment. With the new and larger Ann & Robert H. Lurie Children's Hospital of Chicago, hopefully there will be less shuttling back and forth and less confusion for patients and their families.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I didn't leave CMH under the best circumstances, but I'm grateful for having worked there.”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Working with children.2. Fair compensation3. Good benefits.4. Likable colleagues.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Highly political. Certain people are kept around, even though they're a detriment to the reputation of CMH.2. Workplace bullying.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Workplace bullying is rampant. Stop ignoring it. Address it. Get rid of the bullies. Walk the talk, given that CMH presents discussions on workplace bullying, but doesn't address it among its own.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great mission and great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Great mission and full of terrific, highly skilled, nice, hardworking people. I love working here. People really WANT to work here and be a part of the organization. Great CEO too!</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is an extraordinarily busy time with the opening of a new hospital next June so there is a certain amount of stress in the environment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't let the culture change! It is truly a very unique work environment and a special place to work. Work to provide greater flexibility to people and relax the dress code (in the business functions), the world has changed regarding business dress.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exciting time to work at Children's”

</title><pros>Pros – The work we do at Children's is always rewarding and compelling.  Our hospital is moving to a new building and location next year, so it is an exciting time to be with the organization. There is a lot of energy and work into becoming the best Children's Hospital in the region and a top Children's Hospital in the country.  We have a dedicated and competent leadership team.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Health care is changing rapidly. With all of the changes in the market place as well as the internal changes associated with our move, it can be a very demanding time to work for the organization. Everyone is trying to do more with less.  We are generally succeeding, but it can be exhausting.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep an eye on the marketplace and stay ahead of the competition and changes.  A lot of attentioin and energy is being put into the new hospital and we may be falling behind in regards to some of the changes in the marketplace.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Respiratory Therapist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Gotta love the kids, thats what keeps me here”

</title><pros>Pros – The kids are awesome to work with, most of the doctors are kind.  RNs and RTs get along well</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is horrible, the director has no back bone.  There are many 'this goes for you, but not for you' rules.  many things are unfair about scheduling.  The general floor management is useless, and all management is allowed to act unprofessional.  This is the most negative place I have ever worked, starting with management and trickeling down.  We are understaffed and overworked and put in dangerous situations...and management will not show up to help....ever.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be fair to your employees.  Do something nice for them once in awhile, to show how much you appreciate, or should appreciate them.  They keep you going...without them, you are nothing.  Stop abusing your staff.  Listen to new ideas.  Stop treating different people with different rules.  Some people get away with everything.  Stop giving the 5% raise to the same people who do nothing</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Give back to the community”

</title><pros>Pros – A great fun atmosphere to work. Helping the community around you and having close encounters with young patients makes a world of difference in the day to day work load.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hospital is in need of some renovation. This is being remedied, however, by the move to their brand new hospital in Streeterville on Northwestern University's Medical campus. Looking forward to that</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Leadership is open about their expectations and this is what makes Children's a great place to work. Good job from up top!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Place to work / Mission driven”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly work environmentMission driven/ children and families come firstCompetent managementOpportunities for professional growth</pros>
<cons>Cons – I agree with what others have said about it being hard to move into other areas. Most opportunties reserved for physicians and/or nurses even when people with other backgrounds could do the job equally as well or better.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the excellent job of communicating the key organizational goals, objectives and accomplishements. Senior management is trustworthy and competent. I feel we are in good hands.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Accounts Payable (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice Place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good People and Solid Processes</pros>
<cons>Cons – Staff cut to the bone, Long Hours</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start taking a look at the level of work being heaped on individuals and staff appropriately.  Layoffs are done without regard to work load in each department.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Data Quality Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“overall good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – good educational opportunities, large organization, good benefits, generous time off, good location, easy to take pride in work, upper management is present and visible</pros>
<cons>Cons – a little frustrating to try to switch from one department to another, pay at some levels not very competitive, expensive parking</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – make it easier for employees to consider an internal switch from one department to another, remain clear and transparent about company goals</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Education Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Education Consultant”

</title><pros>Pros – The mission of the organization</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unwillingness of staff members to look beyond the statement, "that's now how we do things at Children's"</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Embrace new people and new ideas</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Administrative Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“CMH Senior Administrative Assistant”

</title><pros>Pros – Patient care is #1 priority! CMH offers full-time employees $100 monthly for dependent child care and other small incentives like chair massages, summer BBQ, and holiday lunch. They also offer seminars for first time home buyers, investing for retirement and tips for saving for your child’s future college needs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No pay increases, no 403b match, no bonuses, insurance deductible and out-of-pocket expenses has doubled. There’s no doubt that CMH offers exceptional care to its patients and their families – it would be nice if they extended that exceptional care to its employees as well.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – My advice seems pretty basic, but unfortunately it’s not practiced by most leadership – treat your employees the way you would like to be treated by your chief executive officer.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-08-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Data Quality Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – great benefits, good attitudes among staff, good education opportunities, the people who work there seem to genuinely care about their jobs and the kids</pros>
<cons>Cons – crappy pay, felt like there was nepotism at work in terms of promotions, also felt that positions were "already filled" by the time they were posted</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Can't speak for now because I no longer work there, but make sure employees are kept aware about what is going on and why mgmt makes the decisions they make</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-06-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Registered Nurse (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“"MHChildrens hospital"”

</title><pros>Pros – Average pay, with pension plan. Great place to get experience. Plenty of clinical areas to choose from. Good learning oportunity.</pros>
<cons>Cons – My unit has very young, immature and unprofessional management. Our unit manager does not interact with us in the floor. The acuity is very high, so the patient load is very heavy, it's very stressful at times.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen, comprenhend and do the critical thinking before making a decision. Value your senior nurses. Be on the floor with hands on to help staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-12-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Registered Nurse (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Employee happy with job at CMH”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a teaching hospital and I learn a lot. I also have a lot of autonomy.  I love that the administrators smile in the hallways.  I have worked other places where you are just a employee number.  Here I feel they know who I am and value me.    I feel supported by my management, and the open door policy is granted always.  The opportunities to advance are there and are encouraged by my bosses.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I dislike the way my unit does holidays, I don't mind working the holidays, just wish there could be a way everyone could be happier with it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more of a manager and not our friend</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-11-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Technologist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good hearted caring people.......unrecognized but still care for kids”

</title><pros>Pros – good hearted people who genuinely care about kids......work for the benefit of the children, not the benefit of management.......good benefits......creative financing......financial assistance for patients.......</pros>
<cons>Cons – too much management and not enough real workers.......many do the work but management get the glory......the ancillary staff  ie.  Lab  is always in background, first to be consulted but last to be recognized.......the same apples to housekeeping and food service.....focus is always on nurses and doctors</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – downsize management and promote from within.....recognize good employees and weed out the bad uncaring ones.....</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Foundation: Development Financial Services Specialist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Impersonal but Professional”

</title><pros>Pros – I worked for the foundation and you feel like you are helping children.  if you want to work a solid 9-5 job with few challenges, this is a good job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Jobs are overly focused and there is a strong feeling against learning other positions and doing more than your job description.  I found my job had highs and lows of work load, and during the lows I did very little work.  Rather than allow me to learn new things, or teach others, they encouraged me to wait for more work. In that sense, I thought the professional development was very poor.  Because the jobs are so focused, they were using only a small percent of intellectual capacity and so I felt most salaries were wasteful, and there were more positions than necessary.  Again, this was in the foundation, I'm not sure how the rest of the hospital worked.  My boss in particular had very poor people skills and was overly critical of other departments, without offering positive feedback or offering to better train other staff.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do a better job of personal relationships.  As a large company, there are many sort of fake attempts at buddying employees up with each other.  The opportunities for real connection could have come with smaller events targeting each branch of the hospital.  Our break room served a few hundred people, but wasn't large enough to hold a table and chairs.  Sharing a meal together is a great way to invoke real connections.  Shorten titles, no one could remember what anyone else's title was and the titles are so long that no one really understands what other peoples' responsibilities are.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not too shabby”

</title><pros>Pros – Enjoyed the atmosphere and the ability to interact with executive leadership. Leadership has a vision to provide the best care possible to children.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A continuous culture of change was dizzying. While it's important to continously improve in your workforce, the message needs to remain consistent.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good communication between management and staff.  Management really cares about the patients and employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – We really need the new hospital.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Reinstating the merit program and match on the savings plan was much appreciated.  Continue to make these kinds of improvements as possible.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Staff Nurse (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I don't know”

</title><pros>Pros – The ability to work with children.Very good reputation.Magnet status</pros>
<cons>Cons – I do not feel pay is compensated with years of experience.Currently, the company is not matching the 401K plan, which is highly discouraging. Additionally, there were no employee raise last year. Management is not keeping staff informed regarding 401K issues, like when will they start matching.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There definately has to be a pay adjustment for nurses.Communicate with staff the progress of the retirement benefits.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>