<name>B. Braun Medical Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/B-Braun-Medical-Reviews-E17609.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to work, depending on your career goals”

</title><pros>Pros – Very relaxed but conservative culture. As an intern, I worked very autonomously and was definitely not micromanaged. They are a friendly group of like-minded individuals who are (almost) always willing to help.  Many employees have worked there for several years because it is a great place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not very progressive in terms of work environment (cubicles) and work-life balance. There are very few opportunities to advance the 'ranks' due to low turnover.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work. Speed up hiring processes. Become a more progressive workplace.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Meteorology Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Minimum Salary Maximum Work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Benefits safe environment to work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low salary advancement limited for many</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – stop nickel and diming you employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>N/A (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Can't see the forest from the trees”

</title><pros>Pros – Overall the people are nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nepotism is rampantClique based structureManagers micro-manage every facet of employees day to day workHuman Resources Department is a large part of the problem there.  They instigate disputes between employees and managers. On more than one occasion, I have personally had HR department employees tell me confidential information about other employees within my department.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn how to treat your employees like people</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Technician (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stable private biomedical device manufacturing company.”

</title><pros>Pros – Worked in a technical capacity with the company for 8 years and saw no layoffs in the manufacturing or support areas. Average pay and benefits. Some good managers who only wanted the best for the employee's and the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unfortunately, nepotism and cronyism ran rampant from the former company, from the top right down to the bottom.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create a environment of cooperation and team work with your employee's. Value all workers thoughts and advice if your calling it the B. Braun family.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No future in this company”

</title><pros>Pros – Other than management, people are nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Incompetent supervisors and managers are running the show.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get your act together.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Typical Corporate Environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Low stress.  Great people.  Relatively stable medical device company.  Benefits are above average.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I never saw anyone get purely promoted in over 2 years.  Employees have to apply to 'higher paying' positions, interview, and get selected.  Basically, you have to promote yourself because your boss will never do it for you.  A lot of really good people simply leave the company because of this.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Overall, management should keep doing what they're doing.  They are doing well during tough economical times.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Changing Culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Great LocationGreat ProductSolid Foundation in Market</pros>
<cons>Cons – American Corporate FocusedLost German influence and cultureHealth Care Tax</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Go back to what made BBraun a great place to work. Understand and appreciate the workforce.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Controls Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great benefit”

</title><pros>Pros – Offer good benefit package and stable company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Stressful enviroment. It also depends on what type of work and department you are in.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to hire good qualified with technical knowledge skill employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-22</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>CPE (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“CPE”

</title><pros>Pros – Innovative company.  I really like working for them.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No real cons outside of obama care and new 2.3% tax causing strain on this and other major medical device companies</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Lab Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Company to work for, to much management”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible with hours. Professional Enviroment. Great place to gain experience</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor Pay, not much room lateral movement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Controls Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“N/A”

</title><pros>Pros – Hi volume production. Good place to learn</pros>
<cons>Cons – 24 hours, seven days on call</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Place to learn fundamental manufacturing process”

</title><pros>Pros – flexible work  hoursfamily like pocket of co-workers</pros>
<cons>Cons – slow to change against changing environment</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Adapt to the new and changing environment (Old working process is Good but New/Improved process is better)</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Nice Place to Work”

</title><pros>Pros – I'm not really sure why anyone would complain about B Braun.  It's family owned and stable.  I've been here 6 years now, and in everyone of those years we've recieved pay increases and bonuses - even during the recent recession when other companies were cutting pay and benefits.Management seems to care about it's employees, and senior management seems very approachable, even the CEO has an open door policy.  They still do a lot of stuff for the employees that other companies have cut like a Children's Holiday Party and Family Picnic.As far as how the company is managed, I'd say the fact that there were no mass layoffs or cuts during the recession in a direct reflection on management's ability to run the business even in tough times.  Most management seems very competent  and willing to listen to employees' ideas.Overall a nice place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some people are too comfortable with the status quo and change happens slowly.  It can be fustrating trying to get procedures changed when people cling to the way it's always been done.  Sometimes too many layers of approve to get things done.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Change needs to happen faster. Management should be careful not to become victims of their own success. At times management should hold people more accountable for producing results.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“B. Braun is a family owned company that cares about their employees, few companies come close.”

</title><pros>Pros – Family owned company that cares about their employees.  B. Braun invested in their manufacturing facilities and the training of their employees in the US all through the recession.  The company avoided general layoffs, gave out salary increases, did not cut benefits (even added free fitness center benefit) and paid bonuses to all levels of employees all during this long downturn.  Generally, management is credible.</pros>
<cons>Cons – At times, change comes a bit slower than other largely public companies.  At times this is a bit frustrating, however, a steady as she goes approach offers stability,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to invest in both our manufacturing facilities to offer good paying jobs with very good benefits and also invest in the training of employees.  Continue to be accessible to employees.  The Iron Pigs box is a great way for us to interact with management, please renew the box.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent Place to Work but watch for layoffs due to manufacturing automation”

</title><pros>Pros – Work/Life BalanceMost People are Friendly with good attitudesManagement is approachablePrivate Company owned by Germany FamilyGood Industry</pros>
<cons>Cons – Weak Management / Decision MakingNo Career Path / AdvancementResistant to changeHeadcount to be reduced due to forthcoming manufacturing automationLayoffs have started in some areas</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Support your employees.  Develop a career advancement plan.  Be realistic about what can be accomplished with limited resources.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work, but don't expect a lot of change.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefitsMiddle Management and below are amiable and hard workingGood area/location for families</pros>
<cons>Cons – Extremely conservative German companyUS companies are required to be "lean" where Germany and others are notMale drivenVery few minorities in management positions, almost none in upper managementBehind in technologyLack of team work with respect to VPsToo many management jobs being "combined/shared" in an effort to save costs resulting in inefficiencies/confusion</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Embrace minority programmingRemove stumbling blocks with respect to VPsRecognize other work groups other than "Sales"Improve/upgrade technology</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK”

</title><pros>Pros – Mostly good peopleNice facilitiesInteresting work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Achievements not appreciatedMiddle management not doing a good jobLittle chance of advancementNo parking at 12th Ave</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Appreciate your workers</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fine if you are male - females are just tokens”

</title><pros>Pros – Having a job - middle management and below are good people to work for.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No advancement or recognition if you are a female.  The good old boys take care of themselves, leave to play golf ("offsite business meetings"), do not record time off (seems unlimited time off). If you are not director or above, good luck.  Employees are considered expendable (especially the females).  There is no cross training or information given, you ask and you get one word answers, no matter how many times or in what ever way you ask.  Lots of focus groups set up but no one has any authority to make changes.  Company has an aging work force with no process to improve and reinvent itself.  Reactive environment instead of proactive.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get your act together and look around, your directors (not all but a lot of them) are going to bring the company down.  You can't always do things the way they have always been done.  Unless you change you will no longer exist.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company, too many direction changes”

</title><pros>Pros – Autonomy to do your job, and the ability to get some support if needed.  Teamwork with others and the employees drive to do their best</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of chance for advancement, a revolving door for the vp positions, and direction that always seems to change mid year.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Staff Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good, Relaxed place to work ...but that comes at cost of ok Salary and Career Growth”

</title><pros>Pros – Relaxed environment, very informal (most of times), good work-life balance specially if you going to school (part time) like me. very good people to work with. sometime works get crazy, as we are in production but mostly not bad at all.</pros>
<cons>Cons – low career growth, lower salary compared to equivalent firms, no sense of pride</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – look through in your organization as who wants to grow, select a strategy and stick to it rather than changing it all the time. work for employees and they will work for you !!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Where is the growth?”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people, good products, great reputation in the area.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everything was growth a while ago, now everything is at a standstill.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take time to look at the qualities of the people you already have on board.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-09-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“B. Braun - wish I was still there!”

</title><pros>Pros – Long term employer in area.  Good benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – German owned - although they mostly leave the US groups alone.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Build a parking deck at 12th Avenue site.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Nurse Educator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bbraun: Do they care about you?”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible schedule for current accounts</pros>
<cons>Cons – They don't really care at all about their employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve communictions between clinical and sales teams</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Territory Sales Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Low payscale than industry”

</title><pros>Pros – Stong and best product range in Orthopedics range.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Average in marketing and low  logistic support.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More aggresive and systemetic marketing and storng logistic support is to implented</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>R&D Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – Recession-proof products.  High profit margin.  Stable employment if you are in engineering or R&D.  Parking is OK.  Great location.  Food & entertainment is right next door (Asian food mall).  Traffic in & out of facility is good.  Good Irvine location.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Almost no chance to move up.  Middle mgnt is bad.  Turnovers among engineers is relatively high for medical companies because German-owned companies pay low & you work to death if you were in engr, R&D.  If you are in production, chance of getting laid off is likely.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get some good upper & middle management.  Make some changes.  Clean out the old culture</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very stable Company, good Leadership and great employee enviornment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Employee oriented companyLoyalty will be rewardedVery Ethical business environmentVery stable business with steady growth.High product’s quality.Big company with small company cultureNo hire fire culture.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not Performance oriented when it comes to employee promotions.Salaries are slightly less than comparable companies.No future oriented employee planCompany long term strategy and vision is not clearNo new business growth through new products.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Develop your own employee and talants.Start acting like a global company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Everything is perfect except for the salary”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent work atmosphere, professional management, good care of employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inconsistent pay scale: often unfair.Candidates: do negotiate your salary up, don't take the first offer.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up doing the great job, thank you!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“More Layoffs Are Coming to Irvine”

</title><pros>Pros – Was good until new executive managementSome promotions</pros>
<cons>Cons – Plant automation comingheadcount already being reducedLayoffsDemotionsPeople leavingLow Morale</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – How quickly you forget your #1 Asset is people, not the bottom line</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good work family balance”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits, Co-worker support, decent work load</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary is below industry standard</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management doesn't lead by example. Take ownership of actions</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lehigh Valley Medical Mfg”

</title><pros>Pros – Sector is recession resistant -- low chance of Reduction in Force (RIFs)Financially stablePrivately owned</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay scales -- retaining talent is difficultManagement is inconsistentPoor communication through the ranksContinuous hire freeze and skimming of benefitsConstantly worried about unionizationCutting corners can catch up in the long runEmployees are no longer treated like people</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upper management is disconnected from vast majority of the workforce</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company of Zombies”

</title><pros>Pros – The medicall device industry is a good field to go into.  I.V. solution containers are also recession resistent due to an increasingly aging population.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very limited job movement within the company and not many opportunities for advancement.  Facility is not maintened as well as expected for a medical device company!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to the experiences of the employees that have been there along time.  Experience with a previous product line should give clues how to handle future product line development.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“None”

</title><pros>Pros – People are friendly to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – No opportunity for advancement. Salary is not competitive.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – n/a</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>