<name>Y-12 National Security Complex Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Y-12-National-Security-Complex-Reviews-E17800.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Nuclear Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Summer Intern experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – The new engineer rotation program give employees the opportunity to rotate through the various engineering departments to determine which one will be the best fit for the individual.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No negative comments at this time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Another government job”

</title><pros>Pros – People that I work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – More concerned about making numbers than staff morale. Hard to make a difference. Lots of guns, guards, and gates.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Look at the people as an asset and realize that morale is important.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Program Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Job security (so far). Calm atmosphere (mostly).</pros>
<cons>Cons – May have to seek direction/development advice.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Develop the youth.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-28</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Reliability and Maintenance (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome people, good pay and very meaningful mission.”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are great. The pay is good. There is always new and challenging opportunities, and it's a very meaningful job field. Another great thing is the ability to transfer within the company, which leads to a myriad of opportunity in maintenance, operations, or administration.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As with any government job, a lot of bureaucracy.  People are also tend to move slowly, and punctuality is not a virtue</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Fire Protection Engineering Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun Internship”

</title><pros>Pros – Great HR teamHelpful colleaguesStrong security presence</pros>
<cons>Cons – Large campus, lots of walking</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Controls Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Benefits & Pay; Terrible Morale & Communication”

</title><pros>Pros – The benefits are the best in the area. Initial pay starts off well but plan on only getting a 2% yearly cost of living increase after that. Work schedule is very flexible and 4 day work weeks are nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Workforce is extremely aging. Small, if impossible, chance of advancement. Communication is HORRIBLE!! Company moral is non-existent. The company is managed top-down which leads to impossible tasks and deadlines. Upper and Middle management do not know the in's and out's of daily work. No bonuses.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees. The current pay scale strategy promotes mediocrity and alienates the hard-workers. Find ways to incentivize the high potential, high performance workers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Check your personality at the door.”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits & Job security. Plus it is a very slow paced environment--government work. IF you enjoy getting paid for 40, but working about 20, then it's the place for you.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Time getting in and out of the facility--it's largely due to the security presence WHICH is a GOOD THING, but sometimes it can be a bit time consuming and seemingly tedious."Some" groups at Y-12 make decisions without truly understanding and using all the facts. Unfortunately, one particular group has nothing to do with day to day operations and production requirements for the facility--they lie in wait lurking for a "problem" to solve. Instead of taking a more humanitarian approach, they choose to pretend to flex their muscles trying express just how much power and control they have. It would be more funny, but the sad truth of the matter is that they just don't have a lot to do so they make the most noise they can when they can.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make reasonable decisions. Use common sense. Enforce policy and make changes when they are required. Use good, sound judgment. If certain administrative groups needs something to do to make them feel good, let them get out in the plant to see just how good they have it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Nuclear Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Going along to get along so that management can get their precious bonus is a recipe for distaster.”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay has the potential to be good.  I am pleased with our mission, although I wouldn't necessarily correlate that with morale as the rating here does.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bureaucracy and lack of leadership and direction.  All time is spent cutting through red tape, and very little time is spent doing the important work.  Millions of government dollars are wasted on paperwork.  I know there must be acountability, but risk will never be reduced to zero.  Let's trim the "do nothings", streamline the paperwork, put dollars towards real improvement and not superficial programs to appease the bureaucrats.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay to retain good people.  Get rid of the people who either do very little, or mire everyone down in indecisiveness and red tape.  Someone has to accept the risk to make decisions.  Going along to get along so that management can get their precious bonus is a recipe for distaster.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>