<name>Glidewell Laboratories Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Glidewell-Laboratories-Reviews-E17929.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-04-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It had its ups and downs, but for the most part pretty good experience working there”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits, plenty of employee appreciation opportunities, paid training, diversity amongst employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – -If you are accepted as dental tech trainee Education department, you may get"tossed" from department to department meaning you will learn one thing for couple weeks and then be set up for an interview only to find out that position is already taken or no longer needed.-At times, during "slow season" not enough work/hours may be available.-Depending on department, there are constant changes you have to keep up with.-Strict meal violation policy-No part time positions-A bit sexist as management likes to allocate certain jobs to certain genders</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Connect more with employees, as previous poster said, often times some of the managers/QCs (not all) feel as if they are "better than the rest of us"  and therefore seem "distant" and hard to communicate with.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Advisor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I learned alot but the job is all about meeting quotas but the final product and final QC needs work.”

</title><pros>Pros – The customer service is great</pros>
<cons>Cons – The technical advisors have to lie to the dentists about everything including the final outcome of the case.  The QC is terrible.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat people and staff like individuals and not like they are a cad cam machine.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Diverse environment ideal for those who just want to skate by...”

</title><pros>Pros – This company is best suited for those who are just out of school. It offers good benefits, plentiful employee appreciation days, and a company-wide Christmas bonus (based on the number of years worked at the company). Yearly reviews offer generous opportunity for pay increase if you perform above manager expectations.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most employees must punch a time clock that is closely monitored. Only managers do not. Certain departments are glorified - be warned! Many long-time employees (most who are now managers) feel entitled to act however they wish -- and they get away with it. Only two weeks paid vacation and very few holidays paid off. Managers are all men, for the most part, so it's a boy club of sorts. If you are an ambitious woman, you won't be able to advance your career with this company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Recognize the talent among your employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Plaster Q C and Implant Triage (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Glidewell Dental Labs”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of work and a great facilities, game room, computer room, restaurant, etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The piece work pays low compared to some smaller labs.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-14</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>CAD Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Glidewell Laboratories was a waste of my skills. This sound bad but I can only speak the TRUTH!”

</title><pros>Pros – Glidewell had a lot of information meterial, design, waxing and able to grow.</pros>
<cons>Cons – take it and apply it for another company that better acknowledges you and understand what your SKILLS are WORTH!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I think the Management should re consider looking somewere els were they are worth more!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-09-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Supervisor I (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Glidewell laboratory-”

</title><pros>Pros – Paid training--minimum wageBenefitsSome managers are capable and ethical</pros>
<cons>Cons – No career advancementVery low payManagement not eager to protect employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – n/a</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A private dental laboratory that strives to achieve customer needs and ensure quality of dental products”

</title><pros>Pros – ability to change efficiently with different customer needs</pros>
<cons>Cons – High education should be a need for the company</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>