<name>Henry M. Jackson Foundation Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Henry-M-Jackson-Foundation-Reviews-E192724.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No complaints -- beats the alternative(s)!”

</title><pros>Pros – Work with awesome colleagues and work when busy can be challenging. EXCELLENT benefits. Easy work environment. I work with a great group of people so I have no complaints about our site!</pros>
<cons>Cons – The usual politics that come within. HJF manages our contract currently so we'll see what the new contract managers bring to the table. HJF is like any other company that has remote sites -- a phone call away but no presence.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make time to come out and see the contractors you are managing instead of being a figure head stuck up in DC. We are friendly out here!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent research foundation.”

</title><pros>Pros – -HJF really cares about their employees and I would likely come back to work for them later in my career if I am in the greater DC area again.-Very competitive compensation and benefits are the same as government (excellent)-HJF provides numerous free career trainings available on their internal website</pros>
<cons>Cons – -No major cons working here. Regulations at times may seem unnecessary/excessive/redundant but that is because they operate almost exactly like the federal government.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Your experience with this company is dependent on who you work with...”

</title><pros>Pros – I have learned a lot on my job. I have gained many valuable experiences. I am pretty much left to complete my tasks and projects independently.  There is also teleworking opportunities and my client is manageable and your client being satisfied with you, is your saving grace.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some people love HJF, others are dissatisfied. This is largely due to the variations in worksite environments, federal clients and HJF management practices. There is definitely a shortfall when it comes to communication from management. Ignoring the elephant in the room doesn't make it go away, and the workplace being what it is, people will find out  anyway, better to directly address issues with employees.Significant variation in compensation for employees with the same job with similar credentials. Company does not openly share salary grade ranges. In my opinion, this is largely due to nepotism and having "friends" who are managers.There seems to be a lack of consistency  and sometimes a lack of professionalism with how managers interact with employees and how they apply the rules.Take what i stated above with with a grain of salt, these things will all very depending on where and who you work with.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – People who are managers should be so because they possess the skill set to do so, not because they have been there the longest or because they have a terminal degree. Directly addressing issues of concern with employees is a must. Compensate individuals fairly for their work and for the additional responsibilities and tasks they take on beyond the scope of their PD. Just be fair, respectful and exercise common sense, that would mitigate most of the issues.</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Post-doctoral”

</title><pros>Pros – good hours, good place to work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management a little controlling, but a minor complaint</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Friendly workplace environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Fast growing company in niche marketFriendly coworkers</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow, bureaucratic decision making progress hinders workplace effectiveness</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Cut out useless middle management, reward top performers more within groups</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Lab Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best DOD Contractor to Work for...”

</title><pros>Pros – - Excellent health benefits that allow several options to choose from for lifestyle (PPO to HSA)- Excellent retirement benefits that get even better the longer you work for the company- Inclusion of those that know your work in your annual evaluation- highly competitive salary base- recognition of hard work- non-profit organization committed to military medicine & research</pros>
<cons>Cons – - middle management was lacking (if site problematic, it wasn't clear who to go to)- once contract was ending, there wasn't any assistance in other job placements</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please bid on more contracts at Fort Detrick!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Workplace environment and benefits are excellent. Employers match in 403b is 100% vested from day one.</pros>
<cons>Cons – None that I can think of.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Technician (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy to work for. Awesome cause, with great progress.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not very much mobility to be had.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Program Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A learning experience”

</title><pros>Pros – The benefits are pretty good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are very limited advancement opportunities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“HJF is an excellent place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – HJF has an extremely generous and comprehensive benefits package, has a rewarding mission to advance military medicine and health worldwide, and has ongoing training opportunities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Perhaps largely due to is fairly rapid growth, HJF does have some significant duplication of duties in various departments. This can result in quality that is not uniform company-wide. The ability to advance is quite limited, and does vary significantly, depending on management style of the department vice-president or director.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Recent management training efforts are helping. Try to allow employees to advance, wherever possible.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Mixed feelings”

</title><pros>Pros – The benefits are good, the labs are well equipped, there is work schedule flexibility and not much competition. Some of the research topics are definitely interesting.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A lot of office politics, lack of communication, poor management (but there are few exceptions ), salaries frozen, pending budget cuts.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Open the dialogue with the employees, communicate clearly what are the duties and the expectations,  discuss openly the job related issues.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good”

</title><pros>Pros – fiendly staff, easy work i think it is a fun place to work but sometimes there's a lot of work</pros>
<cons>Cons – low pay small company low benefits high turnover and such things happen in these times lay offs eventually okay company</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Benefits - very competitive in comparison to other organizations.”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits - i.e. 403(b) employer match and compressed work schedule</pros>
<cons>Cons – Need to work on better communication</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Regular communication, require departments to set quarterly, semi-annual, annual goals (long term and short term)</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Technical Advisor- Clinical Research (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“HJF has provided me with opportunities, support and amazing benefits”

</title><pros>Pros – diverse locations, great benefits, an array of positions in the fields of heath care, clinical research, laboratory research.</pros>
<cons>Cons – no pension plans, caps on annual leave carry over</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – solicit more feedback from the employees on topics employee satisfaction and suggestions</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Program Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Outstanding and rewarding working in Medical Research with the Dept of Defense”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent Salary $110,000plusRewarding experience working in Medical ResearchSupport of the military is very satisfyingGreat benefit package</pros>
<cons>Cons – As a senior manager, very few promotion opportunities.Limited career path as an IPA</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – diversify into additional areas of medical research beyond military funded.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“HJF is a good place to work with a good mission”

</title><pros>Pros – The mission makes you proud. The place is growing quickly. The benefits are great. There are lots of opportunities to move around and see other jobs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The silos are rigid. The internal communication is a bit iffy. Sometimes it seems like more than one group does the same job but doesn't always talk. Working for a government contractor can mean your coworkers aren't that motivated or bright.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The management at HJF should communicate with people lower down the food chain a bit. They should also think about the future more and embrace some of the forward looking things they can do.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place that I am proud to be working at”

</title><pros>Pros – I feel like I am making an important contribution to society, the company pays well and offers the best health benefits of any employer I have ever worked for.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The opportunities for advancement within my particular field are extremely limited.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing what you're doing, I think more people should know about you and the invaluable contribution you are making to the health and welfare of our armed forces.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good for scientists of all ilks”

</title><pros>Pros – Jackson Foundation has lots of jobs & opportunities- but most are for people with some scientific background. I am a generalist- English major- so there are fewer opportunities- but still some. the program is growing and will be. the benefits are good. Generally an ok place - depends on your boss like most places- but it is pretty good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – bosses don't delegate well. If you are not a scientist the future may be deadended- depending on your field- they still need all people like anywhere else- accountants, secretaries, etc.it is a place where they are trying to help mankind. You can be proud of that. there are soldiers, civilians and public health people. if you do not like the military- keep away. the army people have been a pleasure to work with in my experience.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Non-scientists want to grow and develop too. You CAN mentor people other than scientists. Don't forget to say thank you...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Fellow (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review of time as Postdoctoral Fellow”

</title><pros>Pros – flexible work hours and access to cutting edge technologies, collaborative environment with highly motivated people</pros>
<cons>Cons – no scientific freedom, poor laboratory management structure</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – please keep up the management trainings for all sites</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-12-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Clinical Research Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company to work for if seeking excellent benefits--403(b) matching immediately vested!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits are excellent, but there is a glass ceiling if you are in certain research positions. With this company, 403(b) matching is vest immediately, which is excellent compared to other companies that take several years to become 100% vested. Also, it's great that the company observed Federal holidays, so that you don't have to use your personal annual live. Another benefit is that if you have already been with the company, but then leave to find another job, it seems easy to come back to another position with the Henry M. Jackson Foundation. Also, they count your previous time with the company when it comes to benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This is a contract position, so if the contract is not renewed, there is risk of losing your job or having another company come in to pick up the contract.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Overall, I think Senior Management is doing a great job, and people seem to be satisfied.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-11-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great for the advancement of military medicine, but you can forget about advancement of your career.”

</title><pros>Pros – Decentralized work locations mean you forget who you work for.  It's nice to be a part of the military environment without actually being required to be in the military.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Absolutely no room for growth as a person or as a professional.  Every job is a deadend.  No matter how much you like what you do,  you're driven out of the company to find new opportunities.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be a more realistic part of your employee's lives; ask for feedback about the supervisors and the location.  How can you model strategic planning when you have very little idea about the daily work-lives of those who make up the company?  Start using a 360 degree review.  Military managers don't necessarily know how to be good managers for contract employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent Job for the New Grad”

</title><pros>Pros – Very professional and Very Pleasing</pros>
<cons>Cons – None; go to grad school!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Good working culture and i have learned lot over there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is no new projects and bad bench policy</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please try to get the new project</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – HJF provides an extremely fllexible schedule and excellent benefits. Depending on what project you are on, management is excellent at providing you with upcoming events.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upward mobility is not easy to come by.  Most people that work there stay there, so it can be hard to advance yourself.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I understand that funds are tight and will remain tighter, but I feel that the employees that have been there longer should be compensated so.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Better than average.”

</title><pros>Pros – HJF has really great benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hard to communicate with employer. No pay raise in four years.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Spotty- layoffs in the wind”

</title><pros>Pros – This is a good place for scientists- or has been. Some programs - specific ones- are looking at cut backs though exactly what and how much and when is unclear. It makes it very tense. Other areas are fine- some places are great with good management- others- really poor management. so look closely. Ask about layoffs. They may hire even though they know that is possible in the near/far future.</pros>
<cons>Cons – see above. some places are growing others planning layoffs depending on the program and the importance ot the area to the military. They have done and do good things- but the management style is very basic.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – give notice if you have to lay people off</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Adequate”

</title><pros>Pros – depth of work in the military.</pros>
<cons>Cons – inflexible, top had their fingers in everything.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Bioinformaticist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Kind of hit-or-miss”

</title><pros>Pros – HJF provide contract support to many defense agencies, so your experience will vary depending on the agency you work for.</pros>
<cons>Cons – HJF itself is a great organization however there needs to be better communication between HJF and individual laboratories.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Fellow (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience depending on whom you work for”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefit, flexible working hours, great experience but depending on whom you work for.  I am lucky working with an excellent and smart leader in military.  Expanding and achieving a lot in scientific field.  Compensation is reasonable based on your capability.</pros>
<cons>Cons – We are contractors from HJF to various military units around country, so there is uncertainty when contracts end</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep what you are doing and provide more trainings, like presentation, communication and management skills.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Postdoc at HJF”

</title><pros>Pros – Small Good benefits not too much pressure</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very limited help in moving onNot great compensation in comparison to the NIH across the street</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Compare minimal postdoc ssalaries to NIH + reward publications</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unprofessional”

</title><pros>Pros – The benefits are relatively good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The most unprofessional place I have ever worked for.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would highly recommend management training or hire people with actual management experience.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Depends on the department”

</title><pros>Pros – They provide an excellent benefits package.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Each department is its own entity. Some are well run and others are completely dysfunctional.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If a department becomes a revolving door and cannot retain employees for a reasonable amount of time - it would be a good idea to investigate why and remedy the situation.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Fellow (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It depends on the principal scientist you work for...”

</title><pros>Pros – the benefits are good, the pay is decent.   The company is great, but again, it's the government employee that you work for that makes the difference.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No complaints about the Foundation except that they should have someone knowledgeable to guide you about what to invest in your 403(b).  They give you all of these options and you have no idea what to pick.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would have a defined grievance process so that your employees can tell you about what the gov't employees are doing to them.  I feel like I'm just a pawn.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall, a good career opportunity.”

</title><pros>Pros – Supportive management, good benefits, fair treatment to employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work morale has dropped.  Awkward lines between government supervisors and contract supervisors.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More fluidity needed with supervisors.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>