<name>Robert W. Baird & Co. Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Robert-W-Baird-and-Co-Reviews-E19350.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Internship- Good Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Laid back culture, active and engaging intern activities, supervisors interested in your professional development. I really like the culture and values of this organization.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay was ok, not great but ok. I guess since it was an internship, I should be happy I was paid.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the internship program growing as it is. The internship presentation, volunteer activities, socials, etc help develop intern's professional network and skills.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company, but lacking in some key areas”

</title><pros>Pros – -Very good work/life balance, hardly ever worked more than 40-45 hours/week-Friendly atmosphere-Easy to contact any department for help with a task</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Slow to advance with new technology-Ridiculous regulations and policies intended to "protect clients" actually produce a hindrance more than anything and are borderline micro-management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to keep the integrity and friendly atmosphere that are necessary to make this a Fortune 100 Best Company to Work For, but don't get so caught up in regulations/policies that you make the jobs no longer enjoyable for your associates.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Private Wealth Management (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Baird deserves every one of its Fortune's 100 Best Places to Work awards.”

</title><pros>Pros – Baird is extremely transparent.  The management truly cares for its employees.  Many employees are stock holders which makes them that much more motivated to see the company perform well.  The structure is quite flat; I can look up essentially whoever I need to in the directory and contact them if I need assistance or more information (using discretion, of  course).  The HR team will work with you if you want to move to another department within Baird.  People who work there have a more moral and midwestern feel than other companies; everyone seems to get along and joke around.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not enough presence in NYC (personal preference of course)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Equity Research Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company with great people”

</title><pros>Pros – -interns are treated as analysts and contribute valued work-everyone is extremely willing to help-well structured intern program-people encourage you to explore other areas at Baird while being an intern</pros>
<cons>Cons – -long hours-your experience depends a lot on the team you are assigned to-stock pitches are pretty intense, have to present to salespeople and heads of research</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – keep up the great work!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Equity Research Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Most I've ever learned in an internship, but it's not spoon-fed knowledge. Expect a high level of independence.”

</title><pros>Pros – People will make time for you - from junior analysts to PMs, everyone is so open to sharing their experiences, it's contagious</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some roles are more interactive than others. It's not uncommon to go a day without talking to someone in a particular role, yet others require daily interaction.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-25</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>PWM Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people willing to talk to you</pros>
<cons>Cons – Intern program caters to those in Milwaukee</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Advisor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not the great place the surveys say it is. Beware of the hype”

</title><pros>Pros – Size of firm. Gives the impression of being family friendly but not true.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No a**hole rule is a crock.  Plenty of them around.  They do not honor their commitments to people.  Cannot believe they rank as a top place to work on those lists.  They must stuff the ballot boxes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop resting on your laurels and start living up to your promises.  Nothing that makes this any better of a place to work than other firms.  Actually pretty limited as to sophisticated product offerings.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I really like it here”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are wonderful and the company really wants their employees to be happy</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company they hired to do insurance auditing is absolutely terrible and borderline insulting</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hiring Consova was the worst decision you ever made.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Equity Research Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working with smart, motivated people every single day”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are some of the best I have met.  Everyone is always smart, motivated, and willing to help.  Overall just a great company</pros>
<cons>Cons – It would be ideal if headquarters were in Chicago instead of Milwaukee</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Solid company”

</title><pros>Pros – Employee owned, strong culture, work/life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – Technology is behind, not enough training opportunities</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“company that keeps its promises”

</title><pros>Pros – Management has integrity and has kept their promises to me over time.  The people are great - smart, hard-working, but also nice people. Mentorship is highly promoted and collaboration is frequent.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Milwaukee office is fairly incestuous.  Most of the men up there have stay at home wives taking care of them (they don't have dual-career family challenges).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to promote diversity.  Be quicker to fire/move underperformers.  Work to make internal moves between departments more common and seamless.  Be careful not to be too Milwaukee-centric.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Clear job descriptions and review process for advancement”

</title><pros>Pros – smart, competitive people without being phone throwers.  Reasonably decent compensation.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Culture of balance and title structure is not consistent across the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Registered Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Supportive culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of support.  Great customer service between departments. Client oriented values.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Raises are usually closer to cost of living.  Upward mobility.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“review for Baird”

</title><pros>Pros – good job and a good company</pros>
<cons>Cons – no specific recommendation for this company</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Potential for greatness if they can turn things around.”

</title><pros>Pros – Baird has many great benefits including a generous PTO bank, profit sharing, HSA contributions and annual bonuses. It is a very professional environment with many job opportunities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are a lot of egos and people clawing their way to the top. Many times the employee is not the one whose best interests are at heart.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees. There is a reason people are leaving but you are ignoring their advice and not fixing the problem.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Temporary Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Finance Intern”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Place to work. Great Flexibility.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay could have been better. Other peers earned more for similar jobs.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Advisor Aka Salesman (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overpromised and Underdelivered”

</title><pros>Pros – I think there are some genuinely good people who work here.  Like other wirehouses, this place has the full slate of products for the retail investor.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As soon as they lured me from another firm, they forgot about me.  Then, when I only attracted 2/3 of my clients from the previous firm, they swiftly cut my payout to 25%, then 20%.  In addition, as an advisor, they paid for nothing aside from the inducement, yet expected me to run my business on the 25% of gross commissions they allowed me to keep.  The business model is broken.  The technology is terrible, and this company is no better than Merrill Lynch or Morgan Stanley or any of the other dumps that take clients' money to line their own pockets.  Don't walk from this place...run!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Instead of trying to grow your business by pandering to the river of advisors looking to take a check, take a look in your backyard to see who you can grow organically.  Work on engagement.  And, drop the manic attachment to your "help the client" baloney.  My manager and my regional manager couldn't tell me one significant thing about my best clients.  Rule 404 may only pertain to the advisor, but should be extended to the empty suit in the corner office.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Investment Banking Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hours can be tough (as with any bank), but opportunities for career development and knowledge building abound”

</title><pros>Pros – - High deal velocity provides ample opportunities for personal development.- Senior management team has been consistent and predictable; during downturn, very few people were let go, as management took a long-term view- Platform growth provides room for upward career progression</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Like any investment bank, work hours can be brutal- Some mid-level bankers (lateral hires), still learning middle market (vs. bulge bracket) territory- Some elements of the workflow are non-value added, and could be eliminated to improve the lives of the junior team</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to groom talent from within; look for lateral hires with prior middle market (vs. bulge bracket) experience</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work, real family atmosphere”

</title><pros>Pros – For a large company they do a great job of making each employee feel like part of the family.  They believe in work/life balance and are very supportive of personal issues.  The management is conerned about employee growth and did a lot to help me advance my career.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They same time and again that they have a "no a**hole" hiring policy, but there are plenty of them around.  As with any financial instinution there are a lot of people who feel they are more important because they are the ones who bring in the money.  The back office folks often get looked down upon by these people, and are also overlooked when it comes to perks.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to help your employees grow!  Provide career paths for them and foster the desires to learn more.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Private Wealth Management (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Command and Control, Unethical Boysclub”

</title><pros>Pros – Some really nice people.  A few really smart people too.  Once in a while they surprise by taking a chance or making a big change.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They reward loyalty, and that's it.  Regardless your competency or performance, you will get NOWHERE until you've been there many years.  The artificially make their book value increase each year, so stock holders get richer.  This means they don't invest in the business very much - and even in GREAT years your salary/bonus don't go up much (usually just inflation).   All things infrastructure and IT are living in the stone age compared to other firms I've been at.  It's also very hard to hire people or get help/support to do any sort of "change the world" project.  They are OK with just running the business year after year...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management needs to upgrade their operating system.  They believe that holding a bonus in front of the troops is the way to motivate us.  They have people in management positions that are unemployable at any other firm.  They need to shake things up in a big way.  Unfortunately, there have been a few instances of getting a forward thinker in a mngt position only to have them fired a year later....</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Department Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't be misled by the Fortune 100 listing, the culture is gone”

</title><pros>Pros – Compensation and some good people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Good ole boys club, bad behaviour at the highest levels, cover ups and poor ethics I saw lots people get cheated and hurt</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get back to basics and rebuild the culture and stop lining your pockets</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Equity Research Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Headed for tough times”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice people, decent starting salary</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor office environment, "flat" organizational structure is non-existent</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Equity Sales (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You better get in good with the right people then keep quiet”

</title><pros>Pros – Big city opportunities in Milwaukee, privately held - which keeps daily market fluctuations from being a distraction but demands you put all your trust in upper management, located on the lake</pros>
<cons>Cons – Good old boy network, locker room environment, many department leaders have questionable ethics, management is willing to throw employees under the bus to save themselves, enable a finger pointing environment, suppress feedback, overlook indiscretions of connected employees, captive Board of Directors</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Your people are worth more than your personal stock accumulation</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not as great as they made it sound!”

</title><pros>Pros – Efficient work place, relatively low dysfunction and great benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sadly quite a lot. I worked with all women (HR) & am a women who at the time was finishing a MBA, was 25 and got noticed a lot by upper management. I'm down to earth & have a silly sense of humor so I usually get along with everyone I work with but at Baired, I felt like I was repeating middle school. There was sadly constant gossip and backstabbing in my department. I was really surprised by this behavior as the company was listed as one the top 100 places to work in the US.My last job was as an International Corporate Trainer for IBM. I never ran into this situation at IBM; which by the way a great place to work. Robert W. Baired however has asked me to return again as a consultant and had a great offer financially speaking but money isn't everything. The hiring manager didn't remember me, or how she treated me! haha :) so it felt really good saying no.If you really want to work there just beware. My advice would be to document everything to "cover your butt :)" tell the ombudsman everything even if you think its not important because the women who work in HR are doing just that, so be careful! If you need an example a co-worker of mine literally was "spoken" to for looking at someone the wrong way. Now that I'm not there, its kind of laughable!</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-10</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I consider myself extremely fortunate to work at Baird.  I love coming to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Incredibly talented associates, incredible culture.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not as diverse as they should be</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Equity Research Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great, solid company.”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible, structured, low-leveraged firm with solid growth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Good 'ol boys' club - few women in upper management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Summer Experiences”

</title><pros>Pros – Real deal experiences and lots of exposure to senior management team</pros>
<cons>Cons – They lack the good training on people.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire local people when expanding into new markets</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Advisor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Financial Advisor Insider”

</title><pros>Pros – Baird historically has a wonderful culture and the employees work as a team.  The firm remains a wonderful place to work and stay for a career</pros>
<cons>Cons – The recent changes in the challenge of the marketplace were felt by all especially mid to small size companies as Baird is.  Unfortunately of late they had to make diffcult decisions of where to focus reinvestment and the unit I was with did not seem to take a priority.  However, one unit does not make a firm.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to do well and provide a wonderful client experience through a great culture.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Investment Banking”

</title><pros>Pros – Laid back culture for an investment bank. Great client exposure. Good people. Good place to learn the business. Solid reputation.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's a tough job that requires long hours and you aren't always adequately compensated for it. Less brnad recognition than wall street.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More transparency in decision-making. Think ahead and consider how decisions are going to affect the junior staff and elicit feedback.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-10-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great firm, but a step behind the times”

</title><pros>Pros – Baird treats its employees very well, in terms of both compensation and work/life balance.  The firm is more employee-centric than competitors, and being privately-held is a huge benefit.  From my experience, the firm held the trust of its clients and respect of its middle-market peers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The attitude toward risk-taking is fairly conservative, and the company seems content to maintain its moderate pace of innovation and growth.  However, I don't think many employees (who are grateful for their jobs right now) are second-guessing the company's strategy at the moment.  The people are sharp, but the firm isn't on the cutting edge in terms of technology or services offered.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – At last check, it seemed they were doing a fine job of keeping the firm safely out of the financial sector's worst troubles, and taking share from competitors too.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Executive Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This use to be a great place to work - times have changed.”

</title><pros>Pros – Prior to all the layoff's it was a great place to work - they really seemed to go out of their way to make sure the employees were happy. Great hours and beautiful office space.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Since the layoffs morale is low - each employee is doing the work of 3 people.  Medical insurance is a high deductiable plan $5,000 - it's like not even having insurance.  Human Resources is not helpful.  Pay is lower than you would expect for this type of company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't fire employees on the day of the office Christmas party and right before the holidays.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Investment Banking Financial Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to build a career”

</title><pros>Pros – CEO Paul Purcell successfully bought back the firm from Northwestern Mutual and Baird is now employee owned.  Baird is ranked No. 1 by Greenwich for "most trusted" research and "overall research and analyst service quaility".  Work hard, play hard attitude creates a good work/life balance. The 401(k) match and profit sharing is solid.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The Healthcare benefits need improvement. The company recently switched to HSA but deductibles are higher than other firms and copays are expensive.  The Investment banking, Equity Research/Sales areas have grown tremendously in recent years but the marketing and human resources departments have been left behind.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep growing the firm, continue to focus on the employees, improve the healthcare benefits, upgrade the weak departments.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Equity Research Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Relatively nice place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Robert W. Baird does have a relatively reasonable work/life balance.  You're not usually working 90 hours/week, and there's really no need for "face-time" and pretend work.  Benefits are good; you do get shares in the bank after 3 years, but it's private, so don't expect to sell them on the open market.  Tech support and travel are also generally good.  If you do work in Milwaukee, you're living the high life, as your salary probably equates to $300K + in New York City.  So, overall, if you don't like New York, have a family that you actually want to see, and live like a King in Milwaukee (or a duke in Chicago), it's a good place to be.  They also don't do mass lay-offs and other morale-sapping stupidity.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The firm operates on a Milwaukee pay-scale, which is fine for Milwauke, not so much if you're in Chicago</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Allow more lateral movement in the firm.  Other firms you see more movement from research to banking or sales to research and such.  If you don't work out in one role here, you get shown the door.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Baird: A great place to work!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Baird is a great place for new college graduates to gain experience and develop their skills.  There are plenty of opportunities to network within the organization and gain insight into the inner-workings of the firm.  All in all, my experience at Baird was a pleasant one and I would highly recommend the company to anyone who is seeking a job in finance.  For the most part, Baird has weathered the current market environment with ease and will continue to gain momentum as some of the larger financial institutions conduct lay-offs and reorganize their operations.  Baird also has world-class Equity Research department and a highly-competitive middle-market investment banking arm.  A great place to launch or continue one's career!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Since it is based in Milwaukee, financial professionals could feel as though they are out of the traditional Wall Street Network.  However, given the recent market turmoil, I think Baird's location is a blessing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing what you are doing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people but unattractive total benefits package”

</title><pros>Pros – Located in downtown Milwaukee, intelligent leadership that put the company in a position to survive the economic downturn, great coworkers that care about you and provide advice when needed</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is disappointing - barrier to attracting qualified and talented associates, workload varies greatly from one associate to another in the department, benefits lacking in comparison to other firms in the industry that are also located in Milwaukee</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Public Finance Intern”

</title><pros>Pros – Great balance of work and social lifeGood people to work withManagement respects my work and ideas</pros>
<cons>Cons – The amount of work given is inconsistent at timesPretty average work settingTechnology needs updating</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>M&A Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting.”

</title><pros>Pros – much to learn, good intranet offering materials for further study</pros>
<cons>Cons – face-time (long hours even without work), not all colleagues supportive</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more contact to normal employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Support Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good co to work at”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice company and nice people...enjoyed my time there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – salaries are not that great or maybe was just mine :)</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Terrific place to Intern”

</title><pros>Pros – challenging, great on the resume, not a public company, small cohesive teams, exciting projects, entrepreneurial, ability to work on what you find interesting, easy to talk to people/willing to help</pros>
<cons>Cons – may work more hours than you think</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – continue to promote that the firm is a "top 100 company to work for"</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Branch Operations Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I was very unhappy with my experience with RW Baird.”

</title><pros>Pros – Small office environment.Decent pay.Boutique firm environment without the super stuffy feel of most wirehouses.Tuition and licensing reimbursement.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Small office environment.Poor Senior management.No room for advancement.High turnover of Senior Management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Was a good company with a great culture. Over the past year, changing rapidly and not in a good way.”

</title><pros>Pros – Family life balance is great, some very good people still there. Used to be a great company to work for. Good Benefits and Employee Owned.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Former culture is rapidly declining in some areas, many good people have left/ been let go. No longer the Baird that made the Fortune Top 100.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You have brought in elements that do not fit the old Baird Culture. You have lost some very smart, loyal, and talented people. Expect to see you drop further down the Fortune 100 list, as you have compromised your standards and way of life.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – They seem to care about employees, their well being and balance between work and home.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Health coverage.  Some areas of technology.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have a clear vision and stay the course.  Goals of the firm seemed to change frequently.  Decide what you want to be and stick with it!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>