<name>Pick n Pull Auto Dismantling Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Pick-n-Pull-Auto-Dismantling-Reviews-E193270.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-10-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You will work every day, and they are half days... 12 hours is half a day.”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay check looks great. Freedom to make changes if it will make the store money. Bonuses are solid, lots of swag if your team stays injury free and hits goals.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Goals YOY are unrealistic. You will not likely bonus 2 years in a row. You will never see your boss unless it is to get complaints about performance. Goals can change daily and especially at the last minute when its too late to hit them. You will not get ahead from the bottom without being related to a RM or higher.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop beating up your top performers. Allow your money makers to keep making money for you instead of trying to ruin their credibility when they start making too much on their checks. How many great employees have to leave before you realize the problem is at the top, not in the stores. Stop promising promotions if you aren't going to give them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Let's work the managers to death...”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits package and reasonably priced for the employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – The required Sunday -Thursday or Tuesday - Saturday schedule for the managers is not reasonable. The upper management will Not allow the managers to take days off to be with their family as needed, however the upper management only works Mon-Fri... The Requirement for store managers to work Every Holiday is not reasonable, especially when the upper management is at home with their family on the Holiday. The total lack of support from upper management is unbelievable. They do however enjoy enforcing the "Pick & Punish" method of management. The number of Store Managers that have left the company in the past 6 months should be a "wake up call" to the Stockholders that this company is falling fast.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Ask your store level employees why they feel that your Stock price is only 50% of the value that it was last year... they will likely all tell you the same thing, that there is NO Support for the stores. The work schedule encourages the Excellent employees to leave PnP and find a position that respects them as human beings and encourages them to spend time with their families.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Site Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Business, great teaching from company, and great perks. i.e. Travel”

</title><pros>Pros – It is fulfilling if you are committed. They take you to great locations for manager meetings and truly do care about all levels of employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes the accountability that should be held on mid level management is not handled properly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Commit and follow the plan. It works.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Accounts Receivable Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sometimes I don't know how this company managed to stay in business”

</title><pros>Pros – Pick N Pull Auto Dismantling seems to pay pretty well on scale for all of their employment opportunities. The corporate office is conveniently located.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The executivet team hired managers that did not appear have people skills nor management skills. The 401K match was cut. The benefits were so thinly padded that we always had extra bills even after routine appointments that were supposed to be covered in full. The atmosphere was grim, never fun. I saw good employees let go mere weeks before the announcement of a division sale; one could easily assume this was to avoid the expense of management severance packages. When numerous HR complaints were made about one particularly abusive manager, after a full investigation, he was able to keep his job while the rest of his team laid off. Their HR department is a joke.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do a more thorough screening of the management team you hire. Go further than the word of someone they worked with before. Work harder to ensure that you allow your employees some freedoms and don't discourage them from taking time off to be with their families.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I'd rather flip burgers than ever work here again!”

</title><pros>Pros – Interest and knowledge of auto parts</pros>
<cons>Cons – Favortism/Senority has no relevance hereVery critical and nitpicky rarley praise employeesBad Attitudes from co workers and managementIf you have a problem or concern you feel like you are bothering them & that they are to busy.Poor communicationHave a commision based situation that is cut throat and causes employees to constantly be bickering.Do not listen to feedback to employees its their way or the highwayManagement depends on employees to much to train new employees. That is managements job not the employee, unless you want to pay them management salary!You only get Christmas and Thanksgiving day off and your "set" schedule can change when management feels like it, so you may get stuck with the crappiest one available &  who cares how long you've been there it won't matter!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat your employees like they are valuable to you and you may see improved work ethic.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent Benefits, and Hours are OK, but Management is a joke”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent Pay, hours are OK, flex. for P/T employees  Is an OK place to work if you are waiting for something better to come along.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Worked for this company for 3 years in a managment position.  The benefits are decent for the type of industry it is, but every year your coverage will change since they try and save money by changing coverage types yearly.  Human Resources is almost laughable in how they handle issues, they either ignore large glaring problems becuase they are over worked or they will make you feel like a fool for even trying to report the problem in the first place.  Most of the management and regional managemet act as though they have never completed high school (which is the case for some of them) they company is filled with back bitting and slander amongst managers that you would almost think that no one wants to work with eachother.  The bonus program was really good, but they cut it out with the recessions which turns around to an almost 18K a year loss in pay from one year to the next.  The company has purchased several new stores around the country and has money to spend on getting them on board, but yet does not take care of the employees they already have.  It really is hard to move up in the company if you are not a family member of one of the regional managers or corporate lackies.  As a manager you are expected to work either Sun-Thus or Tues-Sat. and you are almost encouraged not to take time off since there is no coverage for managers vacation.  Plus you have to work on all holidays except Christmas so dont expect to have any time off for a while.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Find better ways of supporting the sites and making sure they are successful</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very Challenging, a lot is asked of Retail Management and sometimes only the negatives get recognized.”

</title><pros>Pros – Celebration is emphasized when goals have been achieved. Weekly process training, safety training and management training is very good. The company holds environmental and safety as #1 priority. The company gives managers weekly reports that keep all measureable matrixes up to date and lays out exactly where you are for the month/year. Production and Sales Directors are hands on and very open to idea’s and always available for help.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Revenue Goals not achievable the year after a successful year. The District Managers have too many sites to take care of. The higher management depends on them to let them know what each success and struggle is at the moment and a lot of times they don’t have the time to do the research needed for a clear picture of the causes. Managers don’t have the power to reward the high performers monetarily and this leads to unrest and causes lack of focus. Human Resources make decisions on how likable the employee is. Most of the time they don’t give the manager enough of a penalty to make a statement with the employee, but if you are management……..the Motto is ”Pick N Punish”.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The amount of hours and expectations of site managers is not being monetarily compensated and recognized at the moment. The regular employee’s need to be compensated for the hard work they do and sometimes the dangerous work they do. The cost of living weighs on these people just to support their families on $10 to $11 dollars an hour, especially when it was reported that record bonuses were paid out last year to executives.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>