<name>John C. Lincoln Health Network Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/John-C-Lincoln-Health-Network-Reviews-E19440.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worked for a great company!”

</title><pros>Pros – Good environment and friendly co-workers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Having to wake up early and work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to check some of the Supervisors complaints.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Registered Nurse (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best place to Work”

</title><pros>Pros – Community oriented, great team work,</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most of the time during  night shift we flex to 6 patients,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Ultrasound Technologist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“POdfj”

</title><pros>Pros – Medical benefits is about the only thing</pros>
<cons>Cons – Corruption, Favoritism, Wrong Management, buttkissers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Resign</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Registered Nurse (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“We Always Care For You, Unless You Work For Us”

</title><pros>Pros – There are some excellent nurses.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management so worried about keeping their jobs, they do not care about the patients. The department directors do not support their staff members, will do anything upper management tells them to so that they may keep their jobs. This place was wonderful when Dan Coleman was in charge, now it is awful. The management has successfully destroyed the family environment and made excellent patient care impossible.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upper management: obtain medical experience so as not to base decisions regarding patient care on finance. Department directors: support your staff, investigate issues prior to action, remember its about the patients.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Registered Nurse (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Company, but used to be Great !”

</title><pros>Pros – Great floor team work, Clean work environment, Flexible scheduling most of the time, decent Insurance, Magnet status.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too top heavy, need to really listen to employee suggestions rather than listening and not making any changes with received input. Changing supplies based on price and not quality of product. Having to work a lot of weekends and holidays. Low end of pay scale. Heavy case loads with minimal staff.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More competitive salaries, consider employee input especially on the products that is used; since we use it we should have a say in the products itself which would result in a better experience for our patients. Be more aware of whats actually happening on the units to schedule enough staff to properly take care of the patients.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>EMR Project Manager (I of V) (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An organization with exceptional potential, but...”

</title><pros>Pros – One of the very best positions I have had the opportunity to work.  I had the honor of leading a fantastic team of talented professionals with top-notch skills in their respective areas of responsibility.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Without question, the absolute worst case of upper level micromanagement of individual project team members I have ever seen or experienced.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Reevaluate situations of multiple HR complaints against a member of upper management for veracity - sometimes those complaints are actually true and accurate.  Your organization has the potential to be a 5-star place to work.  However, it only takes one bad upper level manager of a large team to really drag you down.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Department Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“High quality patient care, community service mission, a great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – I am happy working at John C. Lincoln. JCL has deep roots in the Phoenix community as a social and health services organization, and its leaders strive to remain true to its original mission. The people at Lincoln demonstrate a passion for excellence, focus on continuous quality improvement, and sincere caring for employees, physicians, patients, families, and community.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There has been some turnover in the executive management team over the past few years. Several of the executives at both hospitals have changed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – As JCL continues to rapidly grow and change in response to the pressures of healthcare industry reform, I encourage management to remain true to your mission of community service and to continue to strengthen relations with your employees and physicians who are the backbone of the organization.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-29</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Surgical Tech (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stinkin' Lincoln”

</title><pros>Pros – Trauma surgeons are amazing to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Employees are rewarded based on the friendship with management and butt-kissing abilities.  Try to affect change and you better start looking for a new job!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pull your head out of the sand and learn that change is good!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Going downhill fast as far as employee relations.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good medical/dental/vision and other benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They laid off the entire medical transcription dept. 2 years ago and now the work is being done in India. They weren't even going to give us severance pay until we decided to get a lawyer, and then they saw the light. One weeks' pay for every year worked up to a maximum of 6 years, although some of the ladies had been there for over 20 years. Disgusted by their treatment of longtime employees!</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Community Educator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“So-So”

</title><pros>Pros – It is pretty hard to get fired from this organization, you don't even have to perform your job, just show up to work and you will get a paycheck and probably a promotion!</pros>
<cons>Cons – HR is doesn't keep information confidentialGeneral lack of communication between administration and subordinatesGrey areas in terms of policies and proceduresUnqualified employees are put in position of top management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Require more strict oversight of department directors, speak with employees within the department about how the department functions rather than soley taking updates from the department director.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Executive Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Promises Not Kept”

</title><pros>Pros – Very Friendly employees and easy to work with bosses. Highly Respected.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Took temporary position with the promise of being considered for the permanent position when the new CEO was selected. Never notified when position was available. Not allowed to join pool of candidates.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take a strong look at HR policies and promises. This leaves a very tainted feeling about the hospital's personnel policies</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The gold standard for customer service”

</title><pros>Pros – As an employee, you are also a customer. All staff give special attention to provide support and follow through. It is like living in a small town where everyone is kind and friendly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Non medical staff had a second class standing in the organization. Special programs were developed for medical staff to recieve advanced training, education, salary increases etc that were not available to non medical staff.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – All staff should be offered the same opportunites in order for the leadership to communicate that all employees are valued. Despite this problem, the mission statement was one of everyday life in the workplace. Good job!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Health Unit Secretary (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I never thought I'd love going to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – I love working for John C Lincoln Health Network because they have given me the perfect work schedule to go back to school.  It is very fast paced, most of the employess are top notch!  The Physician staff is the best I have ever had the honor to work with.  It's nice to see all the departments come together and work so smoothly together.  As a staff member, I know I always have many resources at my finger tips. I always feel appreciated by management and physicians.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Really the only downside I have run into working for JCL is that some of the co-workers feel it is ok not to do their fair share of work. Socializing, text messaging, surfing the internet seems more important than working. And yet some of them are paid much more than some of the hard working ones with more experience.  I see this happening on multiple levels of workers from house keeping to RN's.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Evaluate and adjust pay according to performance/experience.  Take action with employees with multiple complaints against them.  They are replaceable.  Make sure all rules are enforced equally.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Nurse (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bad”

</title><pros>Pros – Money was not to bad</pros>
<cons>Cons – politics game in every department even HR and VP</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Fired people with multiple complains,fired bad mangers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to work, with room for improvement”

</title><pros>Pros – Small company, family friendly, everyone knows your name, great benefits, people who truly care about people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – too many cooks in the kitchen, management comes down hard on the peons who are not nurses or higher</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – give the secretaries some breathing room</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It  is like working with family.”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits are pretty good, the co workers are wonderful. The pay is very good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Priorities seemed to be a bit mixed up.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you are not going to enforce the non-smoking policy for visitors and patients, then you should not enforce it for employees, I see this happening on a daily basis, it pretty much borders on discrimination.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Management (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Changes at JCL”

</title><pros>Pros – Good peopleFriendly staffSmall hospital environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Changes in managementIneffective HR department</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Spend some time with your employees to get a feel for how things are really going in the hospital.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“John C. A great place”

</title><pros>Pros – This organization is by far the best I have ever worked in</pros>
<cons>Cons – A little top heavy in the "C" suite</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep listening to staff</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Office Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Start listening to the smaller people, they do count.”

</title><pros>Pros – Promises of growth potential and generally good people to work with and great benefits.  Dan Coleman struck me as a person who really tried to get to know every individual who walked through the campus wether you were the kitchen help or the director of the billing department.  Every person matters in this organization.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay, low pay...  Other directors need to take Dan Colemans leadership skills and apply them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Really listen to the people below you, they really do count.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Patient Care Techs under loved and 'sitters' are frequently abused.”

</title><pros>Pros – Pool employees are 'self scheduling' so flexibility is high.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Off season cancellations are murder. Sitters are required to basically reenact the Bataan Death March. No reading , no electronic devices, no phone. TV ONLY if pt is watching it. If pt is sleeping, good luck staying alert for 12 hours.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have the accountants worry about the budget and have nurse resources concentrate on what's best for the patients.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Opportunistic”

</title><pros>Pros – Floor management was wonderful to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Financial situation could be better</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>