<name>Circle K, Inc. Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Circle-K-Inc-Reviews-E195842.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ok company”

</title><pros>Pros – starting pay is a little above average, fast paced most of the time, break every two hours,good for a second job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – raises suck, do not give enough hours to run store properly,and they want things done a certain  way but dont allow you to have enough people to get it done then if you go into overtime they get mad.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – allow more hours per week so the shifts can be staffed properly</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a bad part-time job”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible hours. I could request important days off. Time and a half on holidays. Nice people. Good part-time job for students or young people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is not great. Received only a 10-cents raise after 6 months at minimum wage. Definitely needed a second job. Only a manager (not even an assistant manager) made enough to hold one job. Not a great job for parents or major bread-winners. I hear they are cutting hours under 30 per week so they don't have to comply with Obamacare rules. When I was working here in 2012 I could always count on 38 or 39 hours per week.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to raise pay (or benefits) for employees that have been around a long time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“overwhellming”

</title><pros>Pros – great customers able to work</pros>
<cons>Cons – poor management make it hard to work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – work on communication</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“long hours lots of work”

</title><pros>Pros – circle k is always looking for people and advancement, but be patient to move up.</pros>
<cons>Cons – long hours, on call 24/7/365, vacation time is decent especially when tenured</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – remember where you came from, most upper management were former store managers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My experience at Circle K was okay.”

</title><pros>Pros – Always got to do something different.  For example, you were not always behind the counter, but instead you might be stocking the coolers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They never let anyone go more than 40 hours a week and if you did you would get into some serious trouble.  The only time 2 people were allowed behind the counter was when it was busy.  Even when everything in the store was done.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat your employees like humans and not like garbage.  Make a list for your employees to do and not boss them around as soon as they start their shift.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Looking for a career in C-Stores? Go to QuikTrip”

</title><pros>Pros – The company doesn't perform drug tests, so if you're a habitual drug user, you have a future at Circle K.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Recently, management at Circle K's Tucson headquarters changed. At the same time, a competing store chain, QuikTrip, entered town, and they're devouring Circle K whole. As a result, the new company motto of Circle K is "Be like Quiktrip, but don't spend any money doing it." They want their thirty-year old stores to look as nice as QuikTrip's, without renovating them or replacing any of their antique equipment. They want their employees to be like QuikTrip's employees while only paying them minimum wage. The management is overbearing, micromanaging, and eager to fire.Assistant Managers are expected to be available and on call 24 hours a day, but they can't get overtime, so an Assistant might get called on an hour's notice to come work a graveyard shift, and  would have their hours cut the next time they worked so they don't recieve any extra compensation for the disruption to their lives.What makes this all the more frustrating is that prior to the management change, Circle K was actually a decent place to work for. Not perfect by any stretch of the imagination, but every problem I just described was created by the new management. These days, if you're in Tucson and want a job, you would serve yourself better going to work for one of Circle K's competitors.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn where your desks are and stay behind them. I can't imagine much of your own work is getting done when you spend all of your time badgering your employees about doing theirs.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stressful with amount that's required, low pay”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible schedules and depending on the manager can be enjoyable. Sometimes stressful with its standards.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay for the amount of work required. Hard to want to stay when cost of living is so high.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Look at pay rate for assistant managers, 8.50 per hour is horrible compared to most jobs.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Job is a joke”

</title><pros>Pros – I cant think of any...</pros>
<cons>Cons – Crappy Pay, Crappy people, You have to give your life to these people</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try looking at other gas stations to see how they should be running</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Never Again!!”

</title><pros>Pros – None in my experience. Insurance package was decently priced,but I could never get time off to keep appointments.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Training program a joke, hardly anyone finishes the 12 week training before being put in a store. I was told one salary and first paycheck when I went on salary was almost $100 less,DM flat out lied,no support from DM or other managers. This company will work you to the bone and you will have no life outside of it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Monitor District Managers and keep on touch  with area managers that need help with staffing issues.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was horrible.”

</title><pros>Pros – You were always close to a gas station. And got to meet really interesting people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The bathroom, People never showed up for work, You never got moved up, no bonuses.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Lead Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun, simple and straightforward job requirements.”

</title><pros>Pros – Get to meet a plethora of people and a good chance to network.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working in a low income area attracts transients and rowdy children.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire more employees full-time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very laid back, nice coworkers, great atmosphere!”

</title><pros>Pros – My particular store was always clean, coworkers were enjoyable, easy tasks, decent pay for a starting job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working holidays, an employee or two were not good employees, but hat happens.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep it up!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-02</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lowest of the low in many ways”

</title><pros>Pros – ....a free cup of coffee</pros>
<cons>Cons – You will attend mandatory meetings that you will provide your own transportation and cost of fuel to attend with no reimbursement.  At times they may be an hours drive.  The Market Managers don't have interpersonal skills.  Some will use foul language frequently, some will try to meddle in your store unnecessarily.  Many of them got their skills growing up on third shift at Circle K as entry level employees.  You will be required to maintain all aspects of the store, scrubbing and plunging toilets, cleaning gas pumps...if your store has a roadsign with the price, you will have to change it with a pole which is very unsafe as they often fly down and you have to dodge them or be nailed in the head.  Sadly, many employees are dishonest because the company pays the minimum wage and if some  managers can cheat you out of hours by getting you to do a little for nothing (working off the clock) they will take advantage of you. You will count every package and carton of cigarettes in the store every week.  Perks? NONE...oh, yea, you get a free cup of coffee if you bring your own cup or a free soda if you bring your own cup. If your looking to go into management of one of these stores, you should know, after working 65-80 hours a week, you will still be expected to visit your store on your personal time, known as a "night ride" twice a week and make a report of such on location at time of visit.  Forget about enjoying a day at the beach.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Educate yourself in interpersonal skills, because you are required to work 18 hours a day, don't take it out on your staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – you can climb up the ladder pretty fast</pros>
<cons>Cons – management unstable, a lot of stress for store manger</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – get some better upper mangement skill</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Low morale and multiple changes ruined a previously good position.”

</title><pros>Pros – Fairly flexible schedule assuming you have a good district manager who will work with you on it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The expectations were becoming more and more unrealistic, many managers had only a few days off over the course of a few months.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Quit adding more and more to the job without taking away a few of the tasks.  When hours were cut and managers needed to run register more often that took away from the multitude of other tasks that we are given.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Upper management is disconnected from the reality of running a store.”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits (health, dental, 401K, vacation).</pros>
<cons>Cons – Ridiculous expectations based on number of labor hours given to run an efficient store.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work in a store for one week to understand what it truly takes to run a store.  Work at a store at two different types of stores.  One that has lower socio-economic clients and one that has higher socio-economic clients.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't Work Here, Especially Not on Third Shift”

</title><pros>Pros – -An extra dollar for third shift-Nice co-workers</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Poor pay-Poor upper management-Poor treatmentI worked for Circle K for just under a year. Though I can't argue much for other shifts, third shift was particularly bad compared to other jobs and the occasional second shift I might have picked up. I was trained for four days before being put on third shift by myself. Without a coworker to ask, I was left to fend for myself on any new tasks, customer questions and register making many customers angry. For instance, I wasn't shown how to complete a refund until I'd been working there for about a month.Aside from the substandard training, there were many safety concerns. BGSU is a heavy drinking college and my store was just around the corner from all of the bars. I felt more comfortable than most girls feel working alone, but even I felt uncomfortable with the large amount of drunk students yelling at me, trying to touch me, flirting with me or damaging property within the store. While I never expected that to change (there's only so much you can do being so close to a college and many bars), I never felt it would have been a problem to have someone stay until the bars closed every night or some kind of minor security. After the bars closed, I was fine because the students went home, but except for Friday and Saturday, I was on my own to deal with many drunk students who often started fights in the store or the parking lot, who shoplifted or, again, damaged property.I never received breaks because they never let me work with anyone. If I wanted to eat, I had to do so between customers. I wasn't allowed to sit down at all even if the store was empty. One co-worker, who was 7-8 months pregnant was told to stop sitting down between customers though her doctor told her she wasn't to stand for long periods of time.If I didn't finish all of my work by the time I was supposed to leave, I had to stay over and finish while getting yelled at. I was capable of doing the work on any night except for Friday and Saturday due to the huge influx of customers from the bars. Eventually I learned that the only way for me to go home on time was to skimp on my duties and try to finish them on other nights because I couldn't get all of it done.If people shoplifted in the store, I got in trouble for not noticing them even if I was at the counter helping someone else. There's only so much one person can do.If you were sick and no one was available to cover your shift, you either had to suck it up and work or (if you worked with someone else that day) your coworker worked alone. For a time, I had one second shift every week. Once, my coworker was sick and had to leave customers frequently to vomit and I sent him home because the managers wouldn't and I was on my own during my day shift.Other times, when they sell the balloons or pumpkins for charity, if you didn't sell enough each shift (usually around 30) you got in trouble.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to remember that people, not machines, work for you. There's only so much any person can do and yelling at them for every mistake isn't going to help at all.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible, do not work here”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a job, that's about allFlexible schedule</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long shiftsWorking by yourselfHorrible pay for the workExpecting you to not only handle all customers, but also keep the store straight, the money in order, and all your additional tasksFirst time your money is short you're out of thereI was fired today after working only 6 nights over 3 weeks(this is a 2nd side job so I was only working 2-3 days a week). My 3rd night I was left by myself for an entire 8 hour shift and everything went to hell and all I heard about the next day was how my money and lottery was unacceptably short. But I came back, did better for 2 nights, then last night I was by myself again, thought everything went decent, but today when I arrive after driving all the way over there(a 20 mile trip), I got wrote up for the incident the 3rd night... and that led into me being short on the money/lottery last night with no proof(I understood the first time because I made mistakes but not here), and an automatic firing. I am disgusted with this company and have a LOT of respects for people who do cashier work in gas stations now. The managers pretty much just sit in their little office and shuffle papers, and go home by 3pm. Fair warning to everyone out there, do not work here!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat people better, or you're not gonna have any employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst place to work for! And I'll never come close to any CK stores in my life! And I would not recommend it to anybody.”

</title><pros>Pros – There were some hard working people I worked with..</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very dangerous especially when you're working alone. You have to work in the cash register, fill cooler, fill merchandise on the sales floor, clean store, and it can be scary especially at night.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Practice what you preach!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Just getting worse.”

</title><pros>Pros – -Guaranteed forty hours for Store Assistants, thirty for everyone else.-A week of paid vacation after a year of employment, two weeks after three years.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Poor or non-existent company culture, varies by store and Market Manager-Hard workers aren't appreciated, employees treated like dogs by upper management-My high volume store lost hours weekly, horribly understaffed-Terrible customer service because of being understaffed. Inability to properly maintain the store, provide customer assistance, and keep a clean appearance.-Went through four managers in two and a half years. They're mistreated just like every other employee in the store.-Market Managers are manipulative, liars, and backstabbers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employees are people, not dogs. Show the slightest bit of appreciation for hard work instead of the constant nitpicking and yelling about minor store flaws.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting”

</title><pros>Pros – They have benefit packages for full and part-time, advancement opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working alone, entry level is relativity on the lower end of the pay scale</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Remember your employees make you, don't forget to recognize them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“customer service”

</title><pros>Pros – The chance for advancement is very rewarding and they promote within the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is not on the same page.....You get contradicting information whenever something new comes into place. Customer service reps are not given correct information.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They need to get their story straight and provide correct information. Maybe hold more meetings so the reps are not being told different things and are properly informed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Store...not so good company.”

</title><pros>Pros – I worked with a fantastic group of people and an amazing manager (whom I will not forget).Had a nice store, a bit under staffed, but kept us busy.Also had quite a few great customers that came in all the time and they made the job worth it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Had some difficulty with members of the corporate structure and other area stores...a lot of drama involved in between stores.Also had some very nasty customers, which sometimes resulted in calls to police.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My favorite job”

</title><pros>Pros – Circle K is willing to give you as much, if not more, as you are willing to give to the company. As long as you are capable of doing your job, you have the opportunity for full time hours, and given time, advancement opportunities, as well. If you don't want to work for your money, want to complain about absolutely everything, or want to just have a horrible working attitude altogether, then no, Circle K is not for you; this behavior really isn't tolerated. This is a job that requires multi-tasking, dedication, integrity, customer service, and common sense.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hours are competitive, here. This is not an issue for me, but it seems to be a popular concern, so I will address it. You will achieve full-time hours because of one, or more, of the following:A.) You have an open, flexible scheduleB.) You work your butt off on every shift, causing management to depend on you to get stuff doneC.) Your store is extremely low on employees/people are on vacationYes, it is extremely beneficial to your cause if you are able to work multiple shifts. The manager (and even managers from other stores) can depend on you to cover call offs, or the shifts that other employees' schedules won't allow them to work. This alone gives you a giant boost in image. If you actually complete your shift duties, that boosts your image, as well. You don't have to run around like crazy and stress yourself out all the time; just don't be a slacker. Use your time wisely, don't stand around like an idiot--do your job. If you owned a business, and paid people to work for you, how would you want them to work? Would you want them to put forth some effort for your money? Or just stand around, complaining about how unfair work is? Work isn't meant to be "fair". How many crappy employees do we know that get by on just the minimal amount of work allowed (causing us to have to work that much harder)? Now imagine that, in a "perfect" world, they had one year's seniority over you. In this "perfect" world where you work your butt off to pick up where they slack, you get to watch sadly as they get promoted, simply because they're employed longer. Not so perfect, is it?</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I love my job, and I feel like five stars are definitely deserved.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Typical minimum wage job”

</title><pros>Pros – The job was ridiculously easy. Co-workers were pretty cool to work with. We got paid every week instead of bi-weekly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Same cons as any other gas station. Drug dealers and addicts hanging around. Managers that keep getting fired for stealing money.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a good company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – Good co workersWorked around schoolWeekly pay</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible payManagement expected too much and constantly insulted and yelled at employees in front of customersBenefits are terribleRude customersThe only way to get promoted is to brown noseVery high turnover rate in my nine months there were 2 managers and 4 people quit/transferred</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The customers is not always right, just because you get a complaint does not mean that the employee necessary did anything wrong</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“work hard, management will get a bonus.  not you.”

</title><pros>Pros – There were a few pros when this was still Holland Oil, but it sold to Circle K back in 2007.  Unfortunately, Circle K didn't take the opportunity to get rid of the supervisors (Pokorny) when they had the chance and now these people are still there, and the job is worse.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay is a slave wage....raises are about 15 cents a year.  and there's a salary cap for anyone who isn't management.  Speaking of management, they get really nice bonuses on the backs of their employees, who get nothing when the store looks great and the numbers are good.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You really shouldn't expect as much as you do from employees you don't pay well.  Some employees have put in decades of service and barely make $10 an hour.  That's pathetic.  Management shouldn't get bonuses or vacations based on the performance of their underpayed employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Professionals need not apply, if your smart...”

</title><pros>Pros – Weekly pay and decent benefits.My staff is awesome.  They work long hours alone but stand up to the task and try to complete all their assignments.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company runs their stores with a culture of threats and intimidation towards their managers.  The lack of respect is palpable.  Terrible communication between all levels of management.  As a manager you will be told you need to work 50 hours/week but, in reality, if you want to complete everything you are required to complete, you will need to work much much more.  Do not expect any positive feedback for a job well done, you will not get any.  You will have to be happy with no negativity.I know I sound like a disgruntled employee but I REALLY want to let any prospective managers know that this is the worst company for which I have ever had the displeasure to work. (Over 20 years with the previous owners)  I was not directly hired by them but our stores were purchased by the company and i was promised a job.  I should have taken unemployment.  I will be leaving the company soon as I have found a position elsewhere.If you have to work for Circle K because it is the only paycheck you have coming in, you have my utmost sympathy.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ok place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – advancement oppertunity due to low pay</pros>
<cons>Cons – VERY bad health insurance- it will not cover anything. do not waste your money.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – pay more</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I love my job”

</title><pros>Pros – Awesome boss, great hours, mostly good co workers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – lazy co-worker and not enough money.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Circle K is not a terrible employer, as far as convenience stores go.”

</title><pros>Pros – Circle K helped me to grow from a minimum wage job to a career in management. They promote from within the company, making it possible for someone with no college education, like me, to be successful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Circle K does not treat their lower level employees, like cashiers, very well. They have high performance expectations for low pay. And their benefit package is terrible for store employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay these poor cashiers more! Or at least give raises more often, maybe performance based? I get paid pretty good, but my employees do not.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Lead Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“In under a year I've received 3 raises and 2 promotions.”

</title><pros>Pros – Depends on the neighborhood.  In my experience the customers are generally friendly, the work is easy, and the pay is adequate considering the skill level required.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Dealing with belligerent customers and lazy coworkers are the only really tough things that have to be dealt with at CK.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give some people a chance.  Just because someone had a dui charge 10 years ago is no reason to not allow them the chance to make a living.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Lead Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Discussed”

</title><pros>Pros – you get to know really nice customers and they will be very miss when you are know longer working there</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you have I any kinda of injury after being employed they let you go</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Maybe you should be an equal opportunity employer instead of picking and chosen your employees I've worked for this company for 5 yrs and because i had a back injury in Feb and which your company still let me work up until Oct. 2012 then decided to let me go. Because  your company doesn't promote light duty there's your loyalty to employee's and you guy's need to train your management to have come compassion towards there employee's</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Easy to get a job here...”

</title><pros>Pros – Regular customers, shift preference if you work hard, savings plan, weekly pay.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work alone with no backup, cannot move up unless available to work multiple shifts, minimum wage.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay a living wage to hard workers, advance hard workers not just kids with more flexible schedules, stop cutting hours (it takes more than 200 hours a week to run a 24 hour store).</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“most of them are negative people”

</title><pros>Pros – convenice  close to my house</pros>
<cons>Cons – rude people poor mangment rude employes</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – better employes</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not the best”

</title><pros>Pros – Various clientele and different every day</pros>
<cons>Cons – hours, pettiness, no honor, back</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cashier”

</title><pros>Pros – Fast Paced. Weekly pay. Customer based. Can be full time or part time.Good to pick up some extra cash when needed.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can be dangerous at night in some areas.Customers who get mad at you because they cant pay for gas/items.Usually part-time only, some full time.People treat you like mud.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If your employee has a family, have a little bit of a heart. Life happens.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“getting unorganized”

</title><pros>Pros – Benifeits and they have a great training process.was very happy until they had a change in managment,they seem to gone down hill from this and lost a lot of good managers, this past year.</pros>
<cons>Cons – change in managment has caused a lot of experience managers to quit.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They are a good company but need to watch who they hire in upper mangment</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“its ok for what it is”

</title><pros>Pros – you make money and meet people</pros>
<cons>Cons – you get screwed if you work with the wrong ones</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – you should find a different job</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“circle k”

</title><pros>Pros – there are always many job openings and many possibilities of getting jobs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – minimum wage start as a customer service rep and not too many opportunities for full time placement unless under management or working the graveyard shift</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – just because you feel pressure from upper management doesnt mean that you should take out that frustration on everybody on the store level</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Store Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – I was able to work with hard working employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – High labor turnover!! No matter how hard you work for this company, you are underpaid and not appreciated.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upper management is so detached & people at the store are so under appreciated. Make goals that are attainable. Be involved & seek suggestions from store management or store personnel. Too much petty policies are coming out of corporate that store personnel are having a difficult time accomplishing these goals. Teach what you preach!!!! And walk the talk!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Limited by company policies”

</title><pros>Pros – Fast paced, quality products, great locations</pros>
<cons>Cons – Dangerous situations, angry customers due to company policies, lack of high movement product and supplies</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make customer service number one goal for real, change policies to be more flexable and reactive to the market</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“sub-par”

</title><pros>Pros – numerous locations, room for advances , quarterly bonuses</pros>
<cons>Cons – you are only a number to them, unrealistic goals, upper management disconnected to store employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You need to focus on your employees. Circle K has become a horrible, and insensitive work environment. Many if not all of you have no idea what it is to actually work in one of your stores, and the attitude you have to those of us that do is despicable. I am incredibly disappointed in each and everyone of you and you should be ashamed of yourselves</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“k”

</title><pros>Pros – nice hour when you are in management</pros>
<cons>Cons – - k never closes 365 days a year</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more competive pay for less than store manager status</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cashier”

</title><pros>Pros – Meeting and taking care of customers needs</pros>
<cons>Cons – Impatient customers and rude customers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I like my boss he is cool</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Lead Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unhappily Involved”

</title><pros>Pros – With such little supervision you can do pretty much whatever you choose.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No supervision, no organization, unclean, more about themselves than the employees, little training, little to no accomodations for short term disability/maternity, etc.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay more attention to furthering customer service in each individual, make your employees actually clean their working environment, be more available to employees and praise your employees for jobs well done instead of always criticizing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Shift Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Last Priority”

</title><pros>Pros – The pros strictly depend on your immediate supervisor and your familiarity with the customers.  If you are fortunate to have a good supervisor, the work can be enjoyable.  The customers are another factor that will shape your overall work experience.  Customers are frequently loyal and good relations are important.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company slowly has eliminated incentives, bonuses, and even the number of work hours.  Basically, after 5 years of service, I was making less money than the day I started.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Job satisfaction should be a priority for your employees.  They are the front line to your customers, and unhappy workers reflect poorly on the quality of service your customers receive.  Turn-over rates, employee loyalty, and shrinkage can all be positively affected through a focus on making your employees feel valued.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Frustrating”

</title><pros>Pros – The customers are great...... most of the time</pros>
<cons>Cons – pay, overworked and underpaid......the hours are long and stressful most of the time!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Remember what it was like when you were in the store working, it seems they move up to office positions and forget the chaos that is involved on a daily basis at the store level,be available when there are situations and we need help!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A waste of time”

</title><pros>Pros – They have good benefits if you want to pay for them.  They are good with time off, if you need it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The have the most disgusting locations and care very little for their employees safety. This is especially true for those working overnight.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“GREAT”

</title><pros>Pros – you can move up really fast with hard work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the pay isn't great but you can chage it with time</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – pay should be better</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A place to be mediocre”

</title><pros>Pros – You are paid every week, the work is easy, the hours are consistent, managers are flexible, benefits are available, upper management is accessible</pros>
<cons>Cons – Seniority is rewarded rather than achievement, there is a disconnect between corporate and actual workers, difficult to move from CSR to corporate</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Decisions seem to come from cubicles without the consultation of the people who do the job day-to-day. Promote hard workers rather than the guy who has done nothing in 10 years</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Frustrateing”

</title><pros>Pros – My wonderfull hardworking manager, the team spirit and the clients</pros>
<cons>Cons – A lot of presure for minimum pay.   Lack of breaks,   Disconnect between corporate and store level.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give more autonomy to managers who earned it.  Make corporate employess work a week at a store, once a year.    Give an incentive based compensation plan based on merit to CSR.   Pay extra to night shift employess, again based on merit.    Set a maximum amount of hours managers can work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“At first okay but went downhill fast.”

</title><pros>Pros – Steady pay check, constant shifts (either 6-2, 2-10, or 10-6) over all easy job to do on most days, and it seems like anyone can get a job there. Evidently it doesn't take much!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Extremely high turnover rate. I've only been there 8 months and watched at least 10-15 people come and go. No to mention having two different store managers just in the time I've been there. in the time someone else has been there we've had 4 different store managers. NO respect from people higher up on the totem poll. Asking questions is a sin. Not enough money for the bull you have to do and deal with on a day to day bases.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take control of your store! This store is going to hell in a hand basket and fast. If things keep going at the rate their going you're going to lose a lot more good employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Retail Sales Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awful Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Meet new people-different people every dayGood co workers-good people work thereBusy locationsGood VendorsProvides for a need</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible hours- plan on working 60-70 hrs a weekHorrible pay- plan on making less than minimum wageDM's that are unavailable</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do your jobs, support your managers.........your job is to make our life easier, to help.  Not for you to sit in the comfort of your house while we work 70 hrs  a week</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unfair Policy”

</title><pros>Pros – Fair hours, somewhat okay benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unfair company policy, favoritism, management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Quit screwing your employees over.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's a good place to work for  a small town atmoshphere”

</title><pros>Pros – Everyone pulls together well in order to complete tasks and projects.  Most of the employees are very friendly and close knit.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay starts low, communication gaps cause last minute scrambles</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – take time to implement more development programs</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Questionable Management”

</title><pros>Pros – -Hours were decent; time off fairly easy to get with enough notice-Free refills on drinks during shifts-Interesting and amusing customers-Easy workWorking at a gas station is rarely considered a fun job, but I enjoyed it a lot of the time. Depending on where and when you work, it might be good for a student. Though there were busy times, some days were completely dead, so a student might appreciate the time they have to study, since once you're done with your necessary tasks you won't have anything else to do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Usually scheduled alone; almost impossible to get breaks/use the restroom-Boring - the work is easy, but if it's slow you'll have to find something to fill your timeSince you're usually scheduled alone, you'll have to deal with rush hours by yourself. Most hours are slow, but you'll get rushes that last for a while where you might have a line of customers ten people deep. For second shift workers there's a concern as to whether or not the overnight person will come in. There are less than 10 people on staff, so if they decide not to answer their phones, you'll be stuck overnight.Customers can be a con, as many of them are under the impression that gas station attendants are all high school dropouts unable to count. Rushed customers might snap and yell, and lottery customers can create a long wait for other, already impatient customers. Also, some people just don't know how to use a gas pump.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I've heard accounts of several people working for this company being fired for "missing money". When I got fired, and filed for unemployment, even the guy doing the interview for it said that "missing money" is what he hears most often from pepole fired from this company. There's never any explaination, and most of the the managers just tell you over the phone. It's terribly unprofessional, and, most likely, completely false.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Less Paper Work, More relaxation !”

</title><pros>Pros – This company doesn't give you hard time regarding merchandize log-in into store account, you can change it according to your schedule and fill it up the way you like. People associated at the top are very helpful and friendly. Also, the company top official know how to do business, so if wana ask them something, they will come to store and help you out.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No work-life balance, no job security, have to deal with a lot of different stuff even if you are a manager.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to recognize those who are doing good for the company brand name, reward them, so they can do more.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Positive”

</title><pros>Pros – Outside the marketing department, it would be a great place to work. There is a high degree of flexibility and trust.  Compensation is good for the area and there are ample opportunities for advancement.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Marketing Department management shows no loyalty to employees.  Management was chaotic, with major changes to the org chart every 6 months with no training or even communication of expectations or new job descriptions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“In one word "unsatisfactory".”

</title><pros>Pros – The customers are the best. At store level management is helpful and understanding. The employees are fun and generally friendly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management is unhelpful and unreasonable!They couldn't make it more obvious that they've never run a shift in their lives,if they had they would realize that they expect too much from overworked ,underpaid,and unappreciated employees. We are always alone with no help because they won't even give a 24hr. store enough payroll to cover the shifts let alone have more than one clerk at a time,even the midnight shift has to work alone.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try meeting your own expectations,and watch how epically you fail. Your standards are impossible to meet if you refuse to give us the tools to do so!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“nothing short of miserable”

</title><pros>Pros – its a paycheck and a job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad scheduling of hours, inconsistent hours, low pay, promotions of undeserving employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – you need to keep watch on your stores better for how your management staff runs them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Shift Manager Soon to Change to Assistant Manager Without Overtime (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Circle k  only cares about how much they can make.”

</title><pros>Pros – Well for now you get time in a half when you work over forty hours and shift manager get 45hrs a week. You get a raise every year like 25 cent. I guess something is better than nothing. You can be promoted only if you ask cause they don't really recognize anything you do. Asking as you do your job you ok. Then after you ask you have to prove your worth promoting.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Well I work for circle k for 1 1/2 yrs. They expect you to do everything. Inside and out. No reason to hire anyone els if we have people we are already paying. I painted the window seal for circle. That wasn't in the job description. Customer clogs a toliet your job to unclog it. Now they sent out this lovely letter talking about how they are going to make the business better by changing shift manager to assistant manager. Giving us less hours and no employee is to het over time anymore. Hiring mor e CSA's who they pay less that work 24hrs or more to cover the hours they are taking away from us. Nice I barely make enough to cover the bills now.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Everyone should leave this horrible place how can they do this to people. We have bill and stuff to pay I'm looking for a new job asap. Hopefully I find one soon. Also for them to pay more attention to the camrea before they accuse the employees of stealing. We have so many camreas on us and the management still are so stupid. Fausly accusing us of thing and with customer complaints instead of just assuming that we did it after we already told you stupid people it didn't happen go back to the camreas that's what the are there for us. Custer still somthing we have no way of telling</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Where do they get these people???”

</title><pros>Pros – you have benefits,which most companies nowadays dont have or is just too expensive.....depending on your manager you can have a workable schedule</pros>
<cons>Cons – senior management, store managers do not give the employees the respect and recognition they deserve....circle k is cheap...their machines are always breaking down....debit/credit goes down constantly.....they are really good at putting u in a catch 22 situation.....raises suck....they dont have a plan or constant work system on what to do with cleaning and stocking....so the stores is a mess and nasty</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – u should really pay more attention to the employees needs and give them recognition for the hard work that they do....dont put your failures on the employees we do what we are paid to do....circlek is losing its ground with employees and management.....stop being so cheap and fix your equipment correctly and that will save you alot more money</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't work for Circle K”

</title><pros>Pros – Good hours and your set your own schedule within guidelines.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No help from management, and if you mess up your fired.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – give more attention to store managers, and don't be so quick to terminate</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I Love Candy”

</title><pros>Pros – I love the interaction with people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours are difficult, but I love them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I love you management. You're great.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Circle K - a 800 lb. gorilla with too many independent heads”

</title><pros>Pros – Operations team has clearly defined career path for their employees, decent benefits for non store employees (when compared to similar companies), company is aggressive in expanding into new geographic territories.  Company has strong tradition of promoting within at the business unit level.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Couche Tard is broken up into separate business units across the US and Canada.  Some units are very similar culturally (especially the heritage Circle K units) because of Couche Tard's tradition of absorbing stores and leaving operation teams in place.  The company does very well on revenue generation and M&A, but the independence of the business units (roughly 500 stores each) strains the lean retail business model that Couche Tard has become famous for.  The regions often have different operating structures, accounting systems, advertising, global purchasing, fiscal responsibility, marketing programs, fuel agreements that under cut any "clout" that management can muster by using CT as a single company.  Couche Tard's reputation of being driven to save money on the front end has given them an impression in the industry of being cheap at any cost.  This is great for quarterly/yearly results, but the rapid growth has hidden the long term sunk costs in overhead and operating costs of constantly negotiating service contracts, buying new software, marketing systems and purchase agreements.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The company has nearly 6000 company owned sites.  If we are serious about cutting overhead and operating costs, let's start acting like the 800 lb. gorilla that we are!  Use our clout to get the BEST at the best price, not the cheapest thing right now and hope that in 2 years we can put it out for bid again and get it cheap again while ignoring the switching cost (hidden because it gets dumped to the regions to handle with their R&M budget).  If there is a long term company strategy, it is not being communicated well down to the workers.  Cut costs, buy more stores! is the message that is being heard on the front line.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-05-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Staff Accountant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No regrets working at Circle K.”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a relaxed, friendly work environment.  Free Polar Pops.  It was a good place to gain hands on experience without having much prior experience.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay and room for growth in my department were limited.  I felt that upper management did not pay enough attention to employees and give them credit for quality work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stay more connected to even the low level people.  For the most part, upper management seemed out of touch with what was going on with most employees.  Training was also an issue for me.  I hit the ground running without much direction.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Site Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This is what the retail business is all about. It is not for the faint or weak of heart.”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a challenging job for the "spaz' type A people. Balancing time and training others for your success is the goal. The money is not to bad.....feel sorry for the next generation of managers though.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Life work balance is always a challenge with retail. Consistant turnover can present road blocks to the balance any one would want to have. A lack of coherent communication from a central person vested with the future of the company dilutes effective productivity from the most capable employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I think that Senior Management should be forced to come back to the trenches to get a reality check from time to time</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok part time job if you don't care about having a personal life”

</title><pros>Pros – You can form relationships with regular customers you know their names, what they want, etc. The benefits actually are pretty good. Being able to schedule a day off in advance is okay as long as nobody else has requested it as well. Once you adapt to the pace the days actually go very quickly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Erractic work schedules that leave you exhausted, example work 11 p.m. to 7 a.m. on friday and work 9 a.m. to 6 p.m. on Sunday then work 4 p.m. to 1 a.m. on Monday. Lonnnngggg Shifts 9 - 10 hours with no breaks of any kind not even to use the bathroom. Raises are a pathetic 5 cents a year and do not go up even if min. wage does. You are essentially a maid, psychiatrist, and fast food worker all in one. You are supposed to clean all the machines, fill all the cups, etc., stock coolers, put new roller grill, pizzas, and popcorn once an hour, as well as waiting on customers without making a single customer wait. You are supposed to let people scream, curse, and throw things at you without any emotion whatsoever. When you are robbed at gunpoint you are told you have to stay until the end of your shift and are yelled at for having more money (or any money) in your register, you are not offered any couseling, you are just expected to go on as usual. The management that constantly belittles you and attacks you and tells you you aren't doing enough. And if you have to take off a day due to being sick be prepared to be yelled at some more and then put on a schedule without a day off for 2-3 weeks.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give more respect to your associates.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Increasingly dissatisfied”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent pay. Paid vacation and holiday. Bonus if you qualify</pros>
<cons>Cons – On call 24/7/365. Micromanaging DM's. New requirements, more is required, hours are cut, manager is working longer hours due to hours being cut, running the register to keep at budget leaves less time to do your own work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Implement one change at a time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its okay for now until i find a new job”

</title><pros>Pros – The hours are pretty good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay is okay, but just okay.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – na</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Losing Touch”

</title><pros>Pros – Customers are the best thing about this job. They share their world and you are the part that came make or break their day.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The bad customers are the ones that can drag ya down some.Management is changing and it isnt for the best for the customer or employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get back tot he basics and care for your employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Like any other gas station job”

</title><pros>Pros – You get a paycheck every week</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay is very minimal</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Enforce the NEED for multiple employees on late shifts. Especially if the store is located in a darker area of town or off of an interstate.Increase the minimum start pay, most of your employees are middle aged and trying to get by in this horrible economy. Or at least give gas discounts, or even for that matter employee discounts period!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not what was expected”

</title><pros>Pros – Great staff, good message as a Christian company</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary issues, bad hours, no time for family life, too many family members of the owner working there</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to follow through on salary promises, cut down on employing family members, treat everyone equally</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Assistant Manager and Cashier Position”

</title><pros>Pros – Paid weekly, Health & Dental options, No drug tests, No prior work experience required, Time & half pay for Holidays, Overtime pay recieved over 40 hours.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Yearly raises anywhere from .05 cents to .20 cents, hard to move up in the company without years of employment, most stores open 24 hours & every holiday.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“In retail and customer service”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly, various kind of customer react</pros>
<cons>Cons – no work fix timing,pressure at work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – To take care of employer</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Deputy Manager In Merchandising and Marketing Department (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast moving.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good environment to work with, besides, salary and benefit  are rather good and competitive with the market.  Is the place I can apply and improve my experience.</pros>
<cons>Cons – High pressure with the heavy workload.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Customer Service”

</title><pros>Pros – Very friendly coworker teams and customers and one is allowed to use all their talents even if not in job description.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is a minimum wage high stress job because it is a gas station, and operates with the least amount of associates possible.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Limited advancements in for Advertising focused individuals.”

</title><pros>Pros – If you are interested in Sales/Marketing and Retail Operations then this will be the best company to work for to gain solid experience.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow and limited room for growth within many of the departments.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be open to gaining young employees so you are able to teach.  It is very easy to get stuck in your own lane with this company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-31</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Miserable but generally pays the bills”

</title><pros>Pros – High job turnover, so positions are often available when you apply.Makes a steady wage an hour.No special knowledge needed to begin work.Often meet interesting people (both among co-workers and customers).Generally very flexible work hours. (I'm also attending school; my manager has been very generous while working out my schedule)</pros>
<cons>Cons – High job turnover, so you may get fired at the drop of a hat.Makes only 7.25 to begin with, too little for the time put in.Sometimes there are terrible people and situations. Angry customers threatening to make you lose your job, managers that seem to do the same.There's always a chance you could get robbed, even in full daylight.Also, I've had trouble getting paid some weeks. I'm glad I've started keeping close track. I've had to call my manager about amounts from $7 to $45 missing from my paycheck. She's fixed them every time, but the money still doesn't come in until a few days later- can be hard to pay the bills. My advice to employees: be patient, polite, and double-check your paycheck.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be patient with your new employees, be flexible with their hours, be understanding when an emergency has come up and they're late or can't come in, and try not to terminate them without giving them a few warnings first.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Summer Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great! I loved the experience and getting to work with using a database”

</title><pros>Pros – People are friendly and communicate well.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Day to day tasks were a bit monotonous.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – great internship!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was okay.”

</title><pros>Pros – You have a good balance between working alone or with others, if you're into that. The pay is pretty bad, but you get a lot of interaction with people. It's also a simple job. Free Coffee!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Minimum wage.Secret Shoppers are what your performance is based on.You often have to deal with "sketch" people.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Change the performance appraisal system. I don't like being judged based on the observations made by a person hired via e-mail</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a positive Company”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a Job and a paycheck</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hours,Incompetent senior management, no control all responsibility, senior management does not take responsibility for their failure, they have systemic internal IT issues they transfer to local management as the cause, conflicting directives, internal back biting by senior management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Clean up your act and focus on the company instead of yourselves</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't expect anything working here.”

</title><pros>Pros – Some of the co workers are nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bad management, they expect too much for too little and no personal life.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Tell your managment to get off their high horse.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't work for this company. They don't pay and they expect too much for $7.25an hour”

</title><pros>Pros – I like a few of my co workers</pros>
<cons>Cons – Don't work for this company. They don't pay and they expect too much for $7.25an hour</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – get a rip</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's a job, not a career”

</title><pros>Pros – If you are lucky enough to get a good manager, he/she will work around your schedule and allow time off on short notice.  Circle K also offers (overpriced) health insurance for all full-time employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of downtime, upper management seems to enjoy and promote the suffering of employees, manager bonuses (trips, large cash bonuses, etc.) have no trickle-down effect.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't make it obvious that you enjoy seeing someone work different shifts back-to-back.  When you do a promotion for managers who up their store's sales, acknowledge that the cashiers have a hand in that as well.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I am neutral about this company...it's a job”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a job where you receive a paycheck</pros>
<cons>Cons – Your superiors may treat you as though you are a small child while including you with all the store managers under them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat each store manager as an individual and do not ever group them together when disciplining.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Circle K Stores”

</title><pros>Pros – Good place to start in retail and sales. Able to run your own store. Able to become market manager (district manager) within 2-5 years.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low salary. Might work all 7 days. You think you have all the control but you don't. No freedom . .</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Raise salary. Give freedom to managers. Target market while working with store managers. . . . . . . . .</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>