<name>Gen-i Australasia Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Gen-i-Australasia-Reviews-E196228.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people, respected in market”

</title><pros>Pros – People, breadth and depth of services, clients, career opportunities, best in market, benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow moving, too many meetings, no accountability, poor performers got moved rather than removed at times, politics</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The culture and values had people want to work at Gen-i and clients choose you.  It's now feeling like it was back in the Gattung days - that would be sad if it doesn't get addressed</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Constant restructuring”

</title><pros>Pros – Pretty good company to work for, good perks and overtime pay.Generally managers treat you well, but it obviously comes down to the individual.Very good at being flexible with work hours.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Constantly in a state of restructuring so job security is not very good.  The new CEO has slashed a lot of benefits and generally the feeling around is that this isn't a great place to work anymore.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Long term, been here over 10 years”

</title><pros>Pros – interesting role with good people around to work with and learn from</pros>
<cons>Cons – over busy, 'transformation' has lightened the personal numbers but customers expect more these days from the remaining team</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – work out where the next 10 years revenue is coming from, then dedicate staff and time on working out how that's going to be delivered to - and don't just think staff will stay to do more for the same remuneration - there are more options available now than ever before and as niche specialities increase we will not always have the best people internally</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Head of (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Frustrating, Political, Convoluted and a load of internal marketing that just isn't able to be executed.”

</title><pros>Pros – There are some great people!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Highly political. Very process driven which gets highly convoluted and prevents execution</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Change the people</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Enterprise Architect (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Reorg after re-org - its enough already”

</title><pros>Pros – The biggest game in town</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very little consideration for people that matter</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start thinking about the people who make the business what it is, use people who have the experience and have succeeded in other places doing the same thing instead of re-inventing the wheel.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Miserable, all talk no action, do not recognise employee contribution”

</title><pros>Pros – There are some great emmployees at Gen-i, who make it at least worthwhile to turn up every day.  The expectations in terms of performace are quite light so there work is generally easy.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management do not understand this market, service offerings are disjointyed and it is dificult to find who we are, what we sall and what benefits we can bring to our customers.  The talk is big but theaction  and application are abysmal.  ALl talk and no action.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get your hands dirty.. Understand that you are dealing with some experienced people who actually talk to each other. and the decisions you make, or do not make.  It is nonsensical to to deliver one message to an employer, and a completely differnt message to another, we talk, we know when you are not telling the truth.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No long term prospects”

</title><pros>Pros – Brand name is great on resumeFlexible working hoursGood co workersFairly interesting projectsDecent to average salary paid</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sales team is ineffective and cluelessNo long term prospects, just stay for a year or two and then jump!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Just come out of Telecom, and Gen-i will be a great place to work again, what with all the troubles of the XT network!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-12-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technology Strategist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Watch out - here we come”

</title><pros>Pros – Creating our own identity within Telecom New Zealand - an ability to build from the bottom up.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Politics and old style silo thinking!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create a map to the future</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>