<name>Lester E. Cox Medical Centers Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Lester-E-Cox-Medical-Centers-Reviews-E19674.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-03-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company, decent benefits, proud to call Cox Health my employer”

</title><pros>Pros – There are numerous opportunities for advancement if you are willing to stick with the company. Cox tends to promote from within for those individuals who are willing to devote many years to the organization.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unless you are a well-paid clinician or a in a senior management position, the compensation is just about average for the regional health care market.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Overall, senior leadership does a good job of directing Cox Health. Clear, consistent communication throughout the enterprise should be a focal point within the near future.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager - Administration (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This is a very hierarchail organization that should spend more time worring about patient care.”

</title><pros>Pros – They encourage friendships with co-workers and the lower-level management really cares about the employees.They offer a wide variety of benefits to employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are too many layers of management to go through to get anything done.  With such a big organization, one can feel lost in the shuffle.They are down-sizing and many employees are getting their jobs eliminated with little or no notice at all.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Show you care about your employees by listening to them instead of making up reasons why the employee surveys come back with low scores.  Please take some ownership in it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor working environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Cox has very good (expensive) benefits, and it's a large, respected healthcare system. They have state of the art equipment and competent providers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor management in the clinical setting. Numerous employees went to HR to get help with manager, but nothing changed. The work is enjoyable, but the environment is not.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take employee complaints seriously.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity to participate in decision making</pros>
<cons>Cons – Run like a family business</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Delegat</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-06-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hospital review”

</title><pros>Pros – Great education department, great people to work with,plenty of overtime available, good benifits package including pension, employee recognition programs, tuition reimbursement</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management lack of ability to see past the numbers of nurse to pt ratio, low pay scale, mandatory overtime,removal of bonus money for overtime</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take a look at what is really happening to the employees who work on the floors and when the numbers come back that  show dissastisfaction with the mgmt, evaluate the results fairly.  It should be a time to learn, not intimidate the employees and ake them feel threatened  amd unable to approach mgmt if a problem comes up.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You have to shake your head sometimes”

</title><pros>Pros – Patient services are some of the best in the country.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too large of a gap in the treatment of different departments. Benifit packages are not the same from one place to the next. Schedules can be grueling when you are required to run with a skeleton crew because of porductivity standards.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – listen to your employees other than the nurses.  It takes more than a nurse to keep a hospital running.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>