<name>C-DAC Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/C-DAC-Reviews-E199851.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-03-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good learning experience, get to work on different areas like networking, web security, web”

</title><pros>Pros – good for freshers, wide range of areas to choose from, stability</pros>
<cons>Cons – after a certain point, financial needs / aspirations to be considered, based on the inflation and cost of living.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – stick to your roots, stronger / deeper the root, success will be infinite</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good To Work For”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work/life balance. Freedom of R&D and implementation.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Do not recognize true workers,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop working like Govt. Org</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK”

</title><pros>Pros – Good platform to learn, new technologies, focus on open source technologies...</pros>
<cons>Cons – Typical government lethargy and work pattern. No trainings. Illiterate top mgmt. Really do not deserve the position. Unrealistic deadlines and work plans. Utter mismanagement.Huge govt funds being mishandled literally. No concern for software developers, their growth, their development. Been treated like insignificant commodities by really undeserving seniors.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – For once, try to educate yourself and talk sense instead of making stupid decisions and plans in group meets</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Government organization”

</title><pros>Pros – work life balance , opportunity to work on your own</pros>
<cons>Cons – Basic deficiencies that a government organization has , low and same yearly benefits for everyone</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Life at C-DAC”

</title><pros>Pros – It's good be at C-DAC.</pros>
<cons>Cons – it is a Government Organization.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Programmer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best for the Freshers to get the feel of the Industry”

</title><pros>Pros – Open Environment, Opportunity to learn & experience the best of the technologies along with the other aspects of the jobs</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much freedom & no control or responsibility on individuals</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Officer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good organization to start off one's career”

</title><pros>Pros – Scope of work in R&DSelf learning opportunitiesWork-life balanceCompetitive salary</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work cultureFuture VisionEmployee benefitsHuman Resources</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok for a short stint”

</title><pros>Pros – Flat structure. Inspired individuals can follow their passions in open source. Most of the projects are done in the latest bleeding edge technologies and frameworks.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor pay - they catch up with the market rate every two years and then the pay becomes ok. No career growth. Very high attrition rate.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get more involved in projects. Try to really understand employees. Offering a career path is not optional if talent has to be retained.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>IT Security (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I have taken training in Penetration Testing.”

</title><pros>Pros – They are given Live Project or R & D work given and expert guide are there.penetration testing can be defined as a legal and authorized attempt to locate and successfully exploit computer systems for the purpose of making those systems more secure</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you are miss this opportunity then lot's of miss in your life.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working in CDAC is mixed Feelings”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Place to Work. If you are self driven.Free to Express your ideasCan try to work your own ideas</pros>
<cons>Cons – Problem with salary, Hired in terms of Contract, Resulting in Low Salary and minimum Increments.Office Politic is too high. Less Opportunity to work on.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have to Increase salary for Consolidated Salary Employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-27</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>PROJECT ENGINEER-1 (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place for a fresher to kick start his career”

</title><pros>Pros – Can have hands on knowledge on all basics,large fund of practical knowledge in communication and programming areas. CDAC is one of the prime research centers for learning computing and advanced applications of Computer Science in various domains. CDAC has good collaborations across India and Globe and is widely respected institution, working at CDAC helped me to work on pretty good networking concepts,wifi,LINUX kernel level and all communication basics of OSI layer has quenched the thirst of practical knowledge. CDAC has excellent training facilities and esposure from CDAC is countless.</pros>
<cons>Cons – CDAC is a semi-government organization; so there are few less incentives as one may find in private ones like Infosys, TCS, Wipro etc;most fo the employees based on contract of 3 to 5 years</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company runs under without rules and regulation”

</title><pros>Pros – It is the best research place in India for NLP.</pros>
<cons>Cons – People are unfriendly. Seniors like CHAMCHE type person. Admin always think about officers or senior officials never for the employee.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They should not depend on the middle managers. He should talk to the lower employee, so he can cross verify the report presented by the middle manager.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Member Technical Staff (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unusual Government JOb”

</title><pros>Pros – Has a lot of groups working in different domain. Gives ample opportunity to give back to society. Depending upon group one get to work, in completely different working environment. Though being a Government has a lot more like private sector company environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A few limitation like any other Indian government sector company. Need to be more competitive.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Most of project are resrearch project so you get good exposure to recent research topic.some projects are really good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – you have to make compromise in salary if you join as temparary employee.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They should give appraisal to employee according to their performance not according to their experience on paper .</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“it is for people who are highly self motivated”

</title><pros>Pros – freedom to do your own work</pros>
<cons>Cons – no research guidanceworst senior management</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Technical Officer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Super computing people”

</title><pros>Pros – Lot of scope to learn and share knowledge. get opportunity to work on social relevant project, get opportunity to teach students.</pros>
<cons>Cons – professional growth is limited as being a govt organisation. No sales division to promote our work and work culture is not as industry standard</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please make a proper path to professional growth of employee, the things should be more transparent as compare to current situation</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A very good environment for research and development”

</title><pros>Pros – I can work in up-to-date technology, innovative ideas can be experimented, developed and deployed. The work environment is conducive for research.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Being government organisation, recruitment process is tough and we are not getting good manpower resource suitable for research activities. With govt. pay scale, manpower attrition is very high.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Every year take candidates through campus recruitment from reputed institutions .Identify resourceful staff members and motivate them to come out with new projects .</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for some time but bad if one stays for long, excellent place to learn”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent place to learn new technologies.Great exposureFreedom to choose any platform, language</pros>
<cons>Cons – No growth prospects. Low salary.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increase the salary, and provide proper growth.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“not satisfied”

</title><pros>Pros – knowledge sharingcopensation if you are MTS</pros>
<cons>Cons – politics and poking natureno proper mgmt.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“C-DAC”

</title><pros>Pros – Good place to start your career.Complete freedom in granted in terms of design and development.Flexible timing.Good for people who want to work (or don't work)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unclear goals. Undefined deadlines. Unfinished projjects.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – q</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Government money spending facility.”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Good Freedom for employees.2. Deadlines are usually extendible, so work load is low. In some cases deadline virtually does'nt exist.3. Great company for people who dont want to work or for married women who dont have to worry of . Believe me you can sleep here with head down on the desk.4. Full unrestricted net access. Usually the download speed is more than 500 Kbps. I have seen 3 MBPS.5. In out timing does not exist. so you can roam around the city after sign in and come back in the evening and sign out. Provided your TL does not find out.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Highly incompetant middle and senior level management.2. Highly partial work allocation strategy.3. Absolutely a worse company for career focussed candidates.4. Usually takes up Government of India Projects. Hence onsite is in India Itself.5. Absolutely not a company for people who can't stand reporting to incompetant seniors who are hilarious when it comes to technical suggestions to problems you face during development.6. HRD is not co operative at all when you resign. Entire system tries to HARASS you once you put down your papers.7. Not good for starting your career. Absolutely a worse company to switch to. But a fairly good company to retire from (Provided you settle for the peanuts they will pay you despite the experience you will have by then).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please dont quit the organisation. You are'nt fit to go anywhere anyways.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-05-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>SRF (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“CDAC- My opinion”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of opportunities to learn and work in cutting edge technologies. Excellent work-life balance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Remuneration is poor.  Some companies don't seem to like people from CDAC. Maybe many people who work there dont understand the pulse of he industry.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The senior management should be less partial. They should be aware of what is happening in the entire department. Beuraucratical hassles should be removed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-02-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Member Technical Staff (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“CDAC : A great place to start career at.”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent career growth chances; CDAC is one of the prime research centers for learning computing and advanced applications of Computer Science in various domains. CDAC has good collaborations across India and Globe and is widely respected institution, working at CDAC helped me to work on pretty good hardware, high performance computer systems, software and domains like Bio Informatics , Scientific Computing, Parallel Computing. CDAC has excellent training facilities and CDAC alumni is famous across the globe.</pros>
<cons>Cons – CDAC is a government organization; so there are few less incentives as one may find in private ones like Infosys, TCS, Wipro etc.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide more opportunities and compete with Infosys, TCS etc.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>