<name>X-Rite Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/X-Rite-Reviews-E2048.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>CNC Operator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Solid Company with a great future!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to work and an understanding management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – None That I can think of!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep it up you're doing a great job!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cost Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company, rewarding career”

</title><pros>Pros – Very casual atmosphere, good work/life balance, great benefits, and with the recent Danaher acquisition there is opportunity around the globe to move within and up to advance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Danaher top down structure and reporting requirements have come slow to adapt for some of the veterans in the company. Pay could be a little better, especially for the ones in the back of shop who never get hired in.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep it up.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company used to tackle the tough challenges industrial color”

</title><pros>Pros – If you like color instrumentation, they are the largest manufacturer in that category.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots of focus on color for the masses.  Generally warming over their once flagship line.  Not a lot of re-invention and re-investment in a very profitable category.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Machine Shop Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good company to work for and grow with.”

</title><pros>Pros – As a verticle manufacturing facitlity there are many departments to work in and learn from.  Very teamwork oriented.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management has been realigning to meet global expansion goals.  Changing managers often led to insecurity in the work force.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the goals and plans of the company clear to all employees. Coporate as well as departmental goals.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It used to be a great place to work, it could be again.”

</title><pros>Pros – The people and the technology are what keep me at this job. It also helps that X-Rite holds the major market share for many of it's segments and has few competitors.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are currently little to no opportunities for advancement. The product road-map is seemingly still being hammered out from the merger that took place two years ago.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get back to serving and delivering quality products to the customer. Stop focusing on the lower-end measurement devices, we're not making up the difference in volume.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“New to the team”

</title><pros>Pros – Lot's of great products. Unique offering with few competitors. However the economy and bad decisions have impaired product portfolio growth. Timing is everything, right now X-Rite is striving to be the leader it once was.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Internal battle over who owns what product and what product should be kept alive and what product should be terminated. I think that the bottom line was the only criteria when choosing this and the customers were the first to suffer. There is still time to recover, human nature will not allow it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to the customer, not just the CFO. Look at the impact of not serving the customer as opposed to saving money. Initiate a program where employee suggestion that are implemented are well rewarded. The answers are from within.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-06-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“XRITE..  looking for focus”

</title><pros>Pros – Good compensation level with fair bonus payment.  HR department and management were fair and understanding of personal needs for time off and the schedule was intuitively flexible.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very poor communication between executive management and the rest of the company.  information is dictated.  Q&A is during communication sessions is discouraged and employee feedback is not solicited.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The company is struggling with finding a cohesive strategy for the future and executive management is not at all inclusive when it comes to information exchange.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people, good products, poor management planning”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are the best part, they are dedicated and loyal</pros>
<cons>Cons – The way certian departments are treated</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – To look at everyone as an equal</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's not Google or Apple”

</title><pros>Pros – Small but international company, only if you're hired at a non-American office.People are probably satisfied.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Differences in work culture definitely exists between those in America and those outside of America.Projects can be 'on' one day and 'off' in another.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Strategic Direction”

</title><pros>Pros – X-Rite is a very diversified company for the size company it is.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too small a company to support the necessary resources to support the aggressive growth requirements of management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on ways to prioritize efforts and communicate strategic direction to employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-12-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Promising but...”

</title><pros>Pros – Fascinating work and colleagues, flat hierarchy, open discussions.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much unnecessary turbulence.Lack of focus on core topics due to merger and financial problems created by senior mgt.Merger still not digested.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Cash is king - too much debt.Get competent outside help for mergers.Low head count causes quality problems.Process needs work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>