<name>J. Alexander's Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/J-Alexander-s-Reviews-E2060.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Server (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hard work”

</title><pros>Pros – The money is good, I've made great friends</pros>
<cons>Cons – A lot of physical work. Management is very demanding</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Chill out!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stifling”

</title><pros>Pros – Because the menu is so expensive, it's easy to make 20 bucks and hour on a dinner shift here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The conservative style and corporate vibe made this a very dull and soul-crushing place to work. It's hard to have fun with your guests and enjoy working around people when you're essentially following a script and trying to blend in with all the other servers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The money was good”

</title><pros>Pros – The money was good, made a lot of friends.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The mangers were really uptight and long hours without a break.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Foodrunner (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Foodrunner's Perspective”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly Coworkers/ManagmentDecent PayFoodrunner's Normally turn into serversTakes care of their employeesGreat Hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – Takes too long to become a sever as a foodrunner.Their scheduling isn't convenient.Location CLOSED with little warning</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get rid of the matrix system. 2 weeks notice should be enough time for you to change a schedule.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Perfect job for a broke college kid.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Upscale Atmosphere. Decent pay. Amazing food. Not too difficult.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some of the clientele are very rude. Not most though. Management can be difficult to swallow depending on who you're working under. (I went through like 6 different managers in 3 years. Certain mgrs were easier to work with than others.)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Quit playing favorites in regards to pay.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Server (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awful”

</title><pros>Pros – Nothing! This company looks out for their bottom line, not their employees. That is why they have so much turnover.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Worse company ever! They care nothing about their employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop worrying about your bonuses and start worrying about your employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Hosti (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great pay for part time work”

</title><pros>Pros – Set weekly schedule. Nice discount on food. Very busy shifts.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Besides the pay, which is why we are all there, there isn't much encouragement by way of verbal positive feedback.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Encourage your very hard working employees every once in a while. A smile and a "thanks" is free.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Host (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to grow and great pay”

</title><pros>Pros – They have a great management program that you can work into.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You make what you want out of it. No cons</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Restaurant Manager/Coach (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst Career Move ever made”

</title><pros>Pros – The only pro is that all of their food is fresh. Other than that, its a craps shoot, unless a military environment is what you are looking for.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Overworked and uneducated managers make for a long day at this joint. General Managers comparing being at work to being in a jail cell. Managers micro-managing every move you make.  Yes, picture suffication from the time you walk in to the time you walk out. 50-55 hour work week is few and far between. 60-65 hour work week is the norm. for chefs, 70-75 is normal. Advancement, doubt it. Managers are brought in straight out of college with little to no experience and have no idea what guest experience is. Guest focus is not important.One manager actually told me she actually hates working on the floor.One GM told me table visigts werent important. Its micro-manage, ,micro-manage, micro-manage until the day is done and the guest will be happy. Management could care less about its staff. Management treats the staff horribly. Management walks around like robots "trapped in a jail cell" to quote a GM. Didnt see one new menu item in my brief time, so innovation is out. Corporate chef came to restaurant I was in dressed in a suit and never stepped foot in the kitchen or expo window. Played on his laptop and spent most of his time on the phone. Some chef. These people are snobs and out of touch.  What was billed as a growing concept to me is a place full of rude, stressed out and out of touch people who can not communicate properly with staff members. Just a horrible career move for anyone. Try something else, where you will grow. i almost forgot, they have their own "lingo" which kind of makes it feel like you are working for a cult. Best decision I made during my time there was leaving.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you actually let people do thier job instead of constantly breathing down thier necks and micro-managing them, you'd get more out of them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“"We will use and abuse you"”

</title><pros>Pros – Top notch service training, quality product, high standard of service, lives up to "casual, fine-dining."  There is a sense of pride in the work you put out, but it is slowly deteriorated when management fails to reward your hard work, and displays a lack of care in their work, which causes you to lose that sense of pride.  They are too busy playing games on their smart phones in the office.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some of the poorest, immature managers or "coaches" I have ever worked with try to "manage" this restaurant.  Power goes to the heads of little men who care too much about what you think about them.  Rules are created out of thin air, favorites are spared of said rules, and the hard-workers who come just to get a paycheck are ridiculed behind their backs. I've heard inappropriate remarks from managers about every single employee (myself included) in the building.  Deals are made, but never held up by the coaches, and the employees suffer because of it.  Also, working as a bartender or server will not guarantee you good tips.  Maybe, if you're worlds ahead as a server, but the business is so slow because most people don't realize the building exists.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop caring about what other people think about you and get the job done.  Be men (or women) of your word and don't go back on deals you make in order to fill empty positions on your schedule.  Stop sitting around in your offices playing on your mobile phones and fantasizing about the hostesses.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Restaurant Manager/Coach (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company with intense training”

</title><pros>Pros – Great training program, very thorough. Good benefits,</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow communication between upper management and operations.  Work Life Balance</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Dedicate yourself, and be patient</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Hostess (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“gained understand of corporate restaurants”

</title><pros>Pros – good pay, get tips from the bar, not too long hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – unflexible hours, hostess have to clean the tables</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – dont have any</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Bartender, Floor Coach (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You get out what you put in. Those who work hard will be rewarded.”

</title><pros>Pros – Positive environment!  A fast paced environment that allows for advancement to various position within the restaurant.  A professional environment that not only allows you to make great money but network with client.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Young management with little industry experience can be hard headed at times.  J Alexander's lacks any backwards integration.   Corporate needs to focus on how EACH location can meet the specifications while maximizing efficiency.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management is only as strong as the least skilled employee.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Server (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Make or break you”

</title><pros>Pros – (depending on your location, I worked at the one in West Bloomfield, MI)FlexibilityOpportunity to work a lot of shiftsOpportunity to make pretty good tipsGreat trainingDisciplined environment (lifelong servers, you WILL learn what good service is here!)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bad management. This is the main reason why I would be wary of working here. It is BAD. Real bad.Bad team atmosphere. There's some weird team-based helping system, which might seem like a good idea, but you will quickly find out that it doesn't work!Unclear chain of commandYou will WORK. Very hard. I'm not kidding you. This is the most fast paced, hectic restaurant I've seen in my life.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Human Resource (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Job”

</title><pros>Pros – Good salary, opportunity and way much more experience to get than other company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow Progress in Management, shouldn't let down even there are minor error in anything.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Speed up the progress</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Bartender (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Long like jvhh Hyatt Excellent”

</title><pros>Pros – Large tips for work done</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sidework at the end of night</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Lead Line Cook (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sweat shop”

</title><pros>Pros – Eat for free.  Somewhat good pay for cooking.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Talked down too al the timeLots of pressure to put out fast foodsweat shop</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more positive</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Waitress (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“do not work here”

</title><pros>Pros – The meals are a lot of money so the tips are good</pros>
<cons>Cons – the coaches are rude and easilly angered. everything must be 110% perfect which is not humanely    possible. greeting a table in 45 seconds sounds a bit ridiculous to the rest of us when there is a million other things going on.  everybody that works here is stuck up and they do not want to see you get ahead.  just save the aggravation and do not work here!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – be nicer to your employees and understanding when there is a minor mistake that could easilly be fixed.  there is no reason to be negative all of the time.  I felt very uncomfortable when talking to the management because it was always very negative.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall very disappointing. Had high hopes.”

</title><pros>Pros – Corporate structure is there positive but also there downfall. Everything has a written procedure. But those procedures are not necessarily efficient.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots of corporate drama. Some suits in Nashville who haven't ever actually worked in a restaurant tell you how to do your job better. It's all about the bottom line. No long term plans.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Hosti (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Management makes work atmosphere horrible.”

</title><pros>Pros – I loved the people I worked with (servers, hosti, and pubkeep - not the managers).  Pay was decent as well.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management was very disrespectful, often times patronizing.  Corporate offices the same way when I called to ask a question about payroll.  The fixed schedule with no opportunities to request off is just awful.  Job description does not include the extra duties that the managers expect you to do such as cleaning/bussing tables and running food.  Dress code is too strict (plus, who wants to clean tables when we have to wear a $100 cocktail dress to work??).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Honestly?  Just treat us with a little more respect.  I understand that our job as a hostess is super easy, but we're not idiots.  All of the girls at that stand are intelligent young women who are either working towards or have finished our college degrees.  Follow the platinum rule you so heavily try to advertise to us: treat us the way we want to be treated.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Hostess (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nasty Rude people that work there”

</title><pros>Pros – the pay is decent, and you can get time off when ever you want, if you are a server then it is very difficult to get time off.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The over all work, and managers that work there.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good money but horrible management”

</title><pros>Pros – The tips are really good and the customers are very friendly. Very professional and good training.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management does not treat their employees like respectable people. Everything has to  be done a certain way.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – treat people like they are students who will make mistake and learn from them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Hostess (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – nice pay, fun work atmosphere</pros>
<cons>Cons – long shifts with no break</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – give a little bit more recognition to employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Server/Trainer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This is a great place to be a server if you have some experience. I would not recommend a novice starting here.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good moneyPotential for Regular customersSchedule based on seniorityAvailability to promote to trainerfast paced and friendly environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bar tenders seem to be promoted based on looks and physique as opposed to ability.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Ensure that all job placements are based on knowledge, skills and abilities instead of looks or body type. Good customer service matters more in the end than good looks.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Server (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of side ork but its woth it”

</title><pros>Pros – Modern company, very hard working management, the system they use to run the floor is modern and practical, the only flaw is that sometimes managers are not strong enought to make everyone work the same as all the team. The system is based on team work, you run in circles through the floor running food, then delivering it, them scaning tables, them picking up dirty plates and them dropping them in the dish pit and them all over again but in order for this to work you need manager to ensure that everybody does their share, when their is no manager with leadership this doesnt work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – LOTs and LOTS of side work, no benefits for hourly employees. Ask for the day off if the big wigs are in town, Lonnie Stout  can be very rude same as the members of his entourage.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The system is very good, food is very good as well, but benefits are minimal and managers are stresed all the time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Server (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good teamwork, decent pay”

</title><pros>Pros – Working as a server for J. Alexander's is very team-oriented, and it's easy to get to know other staff once you pass through the strenuous training program. Picking up shifts for extra money is always pretty easy, unless your location is very busy, and covering shifts is fairly easy if your location is reasonably staffed.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Schedules are set up to three months in advance, and you are responsible for covering any shifts in your weekly schedule that may fall on days when you have another engagement. Senior Management changes their minds about server uniforms every year or so, and some of them are way too formal for the upscale casual environment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Ask for, and incorporate, more advice from individual markets.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Hosti (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Can the crappy music”

</title><pros>Pros – The people that work their are fantastic.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The corporate bull.... employees are called "Champions" and managers are "Coaches".  If you want to become a bartender, even if you are experienced, you must complete training for the server position as well.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Times change, you need to as well.  Listen to your employees, they have good ideas about how to keep the flow of the company moving.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Creative”

</title><pros>Pros – its hard to handle the real performan ce o company</pros>
<cons>Cons – its easy to take the life esay</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Server (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best restaurant I've worked at”

</title><pros>Pros – Teamwork environment=always someone ready to help if you get overwhelmed.Good tips, especially the holiday season</pros>
<cons>Cons – Strict dress codes (black collar shirts with creases down the arms, black tie, belt, shoes, apron must be heavily starched and have a hard crease down the center.The only way to show your personality is to your tables, if they even care that you're there.No upward mobility in terms of career</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Get some BALLS!”

</title><pros>Pros – It is very possible to make money and you you can meet great people. they have great food and great reputation around the city.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management do not know how to treat nor speak to people. They treat and speak to people (including trainers and other coaches) like they are stupid and they only hire people in their ethnic group.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They always talk about being on the same page and communication, and they do not do it themselves. Be friends with other coaches but treat others how you would like to be treated, and if you do not like them speak up and have some balls!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Great Company”

</title><pros>Pros – J. Alexander's truly cares about all of their employees, line level and management.  Its a great company overall.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Managers work 55-60 hours a week</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – N/A</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-31</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Good/Bad of being a "Champ"”

</title><pros>Pros – Learned alot about fine wines, as well as pairing them with certain meals to enhance overall taste. The staff was taught a new level of teamwork unlike any other restaraunt in this town. It was learn to work together or the restaraunt goes down.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Communication between management (Coach's) was poor. Set schedules by school semester, you have to get all your shifts picked up rather than a request off book. Uniform requirements almost impossible to achieve on your own. Therefore, get used to a $10 a week dry cleaning bill.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – When your staff is explaining the troubles they are having within the restaraunt, listen to them. Otherwise, say goodbye to alot of hardworking individuals.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>