<name>Susan G. Komen for the Cure Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Susan-G-Komen-for-the-Cure-Reviews-E21233.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best internship experience hands down!”

</title><pros>Pros – The culture is great- the ladies are all super friendly and always willing to help. i enjoyed my year-long commitment at the Affiliate and walk away with a thorough background in how a non-profit operates day to day. Honestly, I felt very much part of the team and I also had the chance to raise awareness in honor of a lost loved one.</pros>
<cons>Cons – October is the busiest month so don't be surprised if you're asked to man an event when they have a volunteer shortage.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great organization with hit-or-miss affiliates.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great mission, strong admin and marketing support from corporate.  Thoroughly enjoyed my time working with some other affiliates, and everyone from corporate.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some affiliates might as well not be part of Komen.  Thoroughly disliked my time working for Komen SWFL.  Director and Board President spoke out of both sides of their mouth.  Would have been proud of my job at other affiliates, but embarrassed by the hypocrisy, elitism, and and vitriol at this affiliate.  Constant turnover for a tiny office.  No health benefits of any kind, even for employees at high risk and with family history of breast cancer.  Retaliation for HR complaints.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Manage your affiliates!  Many of them provide zero benefits, are completely unaware of (or blatantly ignore) employment laws, and openly badmouth corporate, disregarding policies and intent.  Make sure your Affiliate directors share your values and management philosophy if you want the Affiliates to succeed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Start Line Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Start Line Coordinator”

</title><pros>Pros – See every participant cross the start line</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very early hours, can be very cold!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Communications Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice”

</title><pros>Pros – Hands-on experience. Great resume builder</pros>
<cons>Cons – Supervisor could provide more feedback</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall good internship experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Susan G. Komen allows you to directly get involved with events and marketing. You will work with the general public on a daily basis and provide them information. It's a great place to get involved with the community.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The internship is short so it's hard to gain a lot of experience. Some events that interns have to participate it do not seem to be that beneficial.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Public Policy Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“SGK review”

</title><pros>Pros – Very nice people and comfortable environment to work for.  Co-workers and clients are open and loving.  Race for the Cure is an amazing event to be apart of.  You will never be bored</pros>
<cons>Cons – You wont get rich, which most will tell you, but very satisfying work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None that I can think of.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Never again”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of perks and freebies. Great benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Where do I start.....let's just say that i wanted to love working here because of Komen's mission and cause. However, in my department, there is zero to no chance of making it up the ladder. There is a "good 'ole boys" network where friends of upper management (with no experience) are hired before anybody else is even considered! Long list of negatives that I'd rather not revisit.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I wanted to love this company so much because of its mission, but there are some serious issues that need to be investigated internally.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Office Aid, Internship (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very insightful and great experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great experience for an even greater cause. Quality organization and people to work with. If unavailable to work next year, will definitely volunteer my available time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Due to the fact the Lexington Affiliate is a up and coming sector of the Komen for the Cure foundation, the positions are limited and seasonal.  Wish there was more too do for the organization year round.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A very pleasant atmosphere to work in.”

</title><pros>Pros – The people at Susan G. Komen are wonderful! Every department is great! There are always learning opportunities and chances to grow within the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is a small company so there are not too many job openings and getting promoted can be difficult.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Race Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Internship - ZERO pay”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with the Susan G. Komen team was a pleasure - great atmosphere, great employees, lots of fun and very satisfying to do such great work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you accept an internship, be prepared for a lot of work and ZERO pay.  Literally, zero.  They usually have enough money to pay for one intern, but that's it.  It's pretty unfair that the paid intern is working just as hard and as many long hours as the rest of the interns but they are the only one getting paid.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay all interns - even if it is a little, pay them.  They're giving up their summer to be with your company because it is a great cause.  It's the least you could do to at least give them minimum wage.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“HQ may operate on a professional level, but the Affiliates are still "Grassroots"”

</title><pros>Pros – Well known non-profit, good cause</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inexperienced managers with poor communication skills and inability to direct their staff. When staff tries to accomplish their goals, management continually plays to volunteers doing work to smooth their egos instead of relying on the talent of the staff that they *pay*.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – As long as you continue to live at the mercy of volunteers calling the strategy shots instead of "volunteering" and let poor managers run loose, you will never be as successful as Komen National.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Feels good to do good”

</title><pros>Pros – Helping your community and making a difference</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is low, lots of weekend and evening work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Na</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't be fooled!”

</title><pros>Pros – Their mission is important and there are many well-meaning people. The affiliate staff and volunteers are passionate about the cause. The pay is competitive with other area nonprofits and the benefits are good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Where should I begin? This place is a mess! Employee moral was already low, but after the Planned Parenthood debacle and subsequent drop in donations, it is horrible. The senior staff are self-centered and their attempts to develop and support employees comes across as contrived and superficial. The board provides no real leadership and defers entirely to the founder and CEO. It is a prime example of Founder's Syndrome. There is an unhealthy tension (to put it mildly) between the affiliates and the national office that makes it hard to get things done. The good staff have departed or are looking to leave, and the ones who remain are too incompetent to find another job. Don't be fooled by talk of "work-life balance." How can an organization be balanced when its senior staff don't know the meaning of the word?</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The board needs to clean house starting at the very top and bring in experienced, ethical, and psychologically-balanced leaders.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fulfulling”

</title><pros>Pros – It was nice to be working for such a good cause, and was altogether a very pleasant daily office atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working for a nonprofit means often a smaller payscale, and working environment can be slightly chaotic around the time of big events.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The leadership should keep doing what they're doing. Keep focusing on developing all people who work in all levels of the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“rewarding”

</title><pros>Pros – The proud feeling to work there, the people that I worked with, the atmosphere that I worked in and overall just the experience</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay isn't the best, but what do you expect its a non profit job, but it is rewarding, so it makes up for it/</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I have no words I feel like what they do there is perfectly done, and Nancy Brinker does a great job leading the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>