<name>X-IO Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/X-IO-Reviews-E21341.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2011-06-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Principal Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I've learned a lot from a lot of very smart engineers”

</title><pros>Pros – The engineering talent at Xiotech is incredible. I've learned more working there than at any previous company. Some of the technology we've come up with is amazingly advanced for a company of our size.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In Xiotech, like many companies of it's small size and engineering background, middle and much senior management is made up of engineers that were promoted. This has caused the problems you typically see when this happens, a lack of communications from management and management being too involved in making low level engineering decisions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You've got a lot of smart people working for you so communicate high level goals to them and then let them do their jobs!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-31</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“account exec”

</title><pros>Pros – There are some truly good, talented people who want to make a difference but cannot because of management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – i would concur with what most have said, there has been talk of  change, and lots of action with little to no results.  Pay is going down, no true support.  You are on your own.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire managers, people who know people and can motivate others, not tear them down.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“schizophrenic”

</title><pros>Pros – very much on your own, if you like that. lots of freedom, heavy emphasis on selling each month. great product, and the engineers have great passion for their technology.</pros>
<cons>Cons – it is run by the investors. has lost money for years, and they are running out of patience. the market place sees Xiotech (XIO Storage) as yanking itself around all the time, never focusing on what works, just chasing the dollars. in 2010-2011 they got rid of most of the employees, and the service department went completely downhill. Got rid of the Magnitude product, which was the bread and butter (much better than Compellant ever was!). In it's place is a very fast, performance storage array, called the ISE, which few companies really need. If you think of XIO Storage as a startup, it might help understand what they are doing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I believe they realize they are only selling one product, to a very small market. The ISE technology is great, however, it's not what people want. Hopefully things have gotten better. Used to be an awesome place to work. Resellers are actively replacing Xiotech gear with other storage vendors' products.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lukewarm”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible Schedule, work/life balance is very good.Technology is very interesting and challenging.Good group of competent people, friendly atmosphere.Not afraid of innovation or fixing what isn't working.Very open with employees about current business status.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management has been very bad in the past, starting to come around.Startup mode forever.  No raises, no reviews, no career advancement.  Layoffs have been brutal (although where hasn't it been).Seems to be a glass ceiling there.  The same group of people get all the promotions, recognition and compensation while the rest are in the pit crew regardless of contribution.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need some morale improvement.Less favoritism for the old guard.Show some love to the sneeches without stars for a change.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Troubled company looking for second wind.”

</title><pros>Pros – The employees of Xiotech are outstanding individuals.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management has had instability that has caused repeated changes in direction. Communication from upper management limited.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Current management seems to have a strong direction. Communicate to the employees taht direction and empower them to assist you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sr system engineer”

</title><pros>Pros – A lot of knowledge in current staff</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unstable company. Layoff every other year or so.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to those in the trenches</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Some Good People, Good Pay but your on an island”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Pay, the company has a good niche that they are trying to cut out for themselves. They have some loyal customers. Employees are able to influence change.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor customer service with very few support people in the field.  No communication at all to the field and inability to make decisions at mid level.  Lots of "no we can't".  Lots of lost people to other competitors.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Lots of communication is the key and making decisions quickly and not having to go to the CEO/CFO for a decision.  More focus on customer service.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Slow to start but upside is tremendous”

</title><pros>Pros – Xiotech has some incredible technology and tremendous upside.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A lot of long tenured individuals with narrow band of experience.  Marketing and focus are erratic.  The company, even though over 15 years old, is still very immature when it comes to process, procedures, training, field readiness, communication and such.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more realistic and conservative.  Do what your best at and fill in the gaps with industry veterans, not just "locals". Communication, training, and an overabundance of marketing would be first on my list.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Field Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Field Engineer”

</title><pros>Pros – People are great that you work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary is not the best</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be up front with employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Things here get worse with time.”

</title><pros>Pros – - Flexible timings- Being a small company if lucky one may get to do some good work</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Too much politics- Promotions and recognition depend on who you know rather than the work you do- Its been a small company (in startup mode ) for too long</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Its tough being a small company but mgmt needs to have a long term vision that can help increase revenue.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Mixed experience”

</title><pros>Pros – flexible timings, good peers to work with at least when i joined, cafetaria, challenging schedules lacks of heavy weight processes.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Perpetually desperate to earn revenues resulting in tight schedules, ill conceived projects. Lack of communication between developers and management, lack of recognition.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – For any organization to succeed, the management should clearly and meaningfully distinguish between those who work an those who pretend to work and reward them accordingly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>