<name>Jimmy Choo Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Jimmy-Choo-Reviews-E21857.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Compared to other internships-not bad, but not great”

</title><pros>Pros – Lunch and Transportation reimbursed. Gain insight into a successful company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not a lot of camaraderie among different teams. Employees are very stressed, may take it out on interns.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A total joke.”

</title><pros>Pros – The product is actually worth the hype.... The shoes are incredible quality!</pros>
<cons>Cons – low pay, poor management, lack of structure, poor standards, horrific uniforms</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Buying/Planning Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good company culture (NYC office internship review only)”

</title><pros>Pros – the people at jimmy choo are fantastic! the office is beautiful, the hours aren't bad. fridays in the summer are half days. the fridge is well stocked with free juices/drinks. interns are reimbursed for travel and $10 for lunch, and they typically invite you to big company events. my bosses even took me out to lunch on the last day and gave me a Jimmy Choo bag!</pros>
<cons>Cons – buying/planning can get very repetitive and boring. be prepared to make starbucks runs, salad/pizza/lunch runs, and possibly vacuuming. unpaid internship can be annoying, but if you can afford to do so, jimmy choo is a good place for that.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great pay, great product, and terrible hr/management.”

</title><pros>Pros – Such a great opportunity to make a living while having a great time.  The pay structure is fantastic and encourages success while also guaranteeing a minimum income during slower seasons. The power of the name alone connects to the customer and provides you with a foot up against many other brands. Hands off approach lets you build a successful business without micromanagement, pending your ability to do so.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A ton of upper movement within the company in the past two years leaves the future direction of the company a mystery (stepping down of original founder at the same time as the president). Complaints go unheeded by management. Hands off approach leads to cliquishness of sales associates. Poor handling of matters by HR leads to a "tell on them before they tell on you" style of relationships in many stores indicated by constant firings.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Put in place more development plans, corrective action measures, and refrain from personal relations with associates. Your associates are only as stable as you are.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits packageGreat discount on itemsPotential for great incomeGreat coworkersNice to be located in South Coast Plaza</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can be slow sometimeslack of respect from previous managerunrealistic goals set by corporatescheduling can be difficult at times</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Thankfully a new manager has been put in place and she is wonderful. A more realistic approach to goals would be appreciated from corporate.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tight Ship”

</title><pros>Pros – Powerhouse in the global fashion industry, the products are notorious for celebrity attention and media recognition. Fun clientele to work with, you can make lots of connections.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Tight ship, sales people packed into usually small boutiques and asked to clientele and sell, sell. sell. Lots of catty politics and egos in managment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep an ear to the street thats where the actions at, listen to your employees they are your soldiers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Management (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company”

</title><pros>Pros – Buying own stock, business is run as if your own.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of support from middle management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Management is a joke! Customers are awesome!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great customers. Good shipping systems. Base salary + commission.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inconsistent paychecks due to variances in commission. Cut-throat Sales Associates who consistently try to steal clients from one another. Hard work goes unrecognized. You will not get promoted or offered a raise. The Manager gives the best hours, schedule, and all holiday's off to their favorite employee. The hours are horrible!Sales Associates develop cliques. If you work hard, and they are lazy, you will be isolated. Management leads the pack. Management gossips on a daily basis, talks about all the Sales Associates behind their backs, and has frequent angry outburts. Those outbursts include demeaning Associates.Human Resources never takes time to get to know the employees. Especially the ones that are working hard and making their sales goals. They always take Management's word at face value. I have witnessed a lot of good, hard-working, people loose their job. H.R. doesn't have a clue that most of these Associates were set up, and falsely accused, by Manager's that simply don't like the Associate. If a Manager, or their Associate clique do not like you, you will be fired!  H.R. will not support the Employees. If a Sales Associate brings forth an issue, directly to Human Resources, they will be next for a pink slip. I have witnessed a handful of people get fired, for those exact reasons, in a short amount of time.The company has a return/exchange-only policy that customers loathe. You frequently lose business to adjacent department stores who accept returns. If you try to abide by the Company, exchange only, policy and a client doesn't like it, the company will not stand behind you. They will throw you under the bus. They always allow the client to return an item if they argue loud enough.January and summer months are really slow. Your commission reflects that. It makes it difficult to keep up with personal expenses at that time. Upper Managment is very numbers oriented. They do not care if the economy is effecting a clients ability to shop. They want you to sell, sell, sell!The new design team is not reflecting her vision and product quality is steadily declining. Clients are starting to move on to competitors for a more fashion forward look.Many of them that do purchase the product, would bring back shoes after 3 uses, with a broken heel, stones that fell off of the shoes, and straps that popped, within the first few months of their purchase. Handbags are poorly made. Threading comes loose and buckles tarnish and fall off. Sunglass lenses would frequently pop out. Be preapred to write out a ton of repair tickets!85% of the shoes we sell have to be sent out for stretching in the toe box, calf, and for ball of foot pads, etc. The quality is so poor that they all need to be doctored before a client can wear them. A lot of convincing comes into play.You have to wear the shoes on the sales floor. They are too narrow and painful for being on your feet all day. Many of us have developed permanent foot problems and deformities.We sales associates sell the product, through hard work and dedication, as it does not sell itself!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Some of your Managers are getting over on you! Half the time they are not even in the store. Support your hard-working sales associates. They are the reason you are in business. Listen to suggestions from Sales Associates. We receive the feedback from our clients. Come out of your office and visit the stores more often. You will get a better perspective on the difficulties we face.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of oppurtunities”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with a brand which is globally known</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working with a franchise is not the same experience as working with a directly operated Jimmy Choo boutique</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Convince franchise owners to create a similar work environment as it would be while working with a directly operated boutique</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>