<name>C Squared Technologies Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/C-Squared-Technologies-Reviews-E221737.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-04-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Solid human performance improvement company”

</title><pros>Pros – Small company atmosphereNimble and innovativeOpportunities for advancementLeader in the training industryMultiple locations to work at in US</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can show a lack of structure and processHighly dependent on Federal sector</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Server (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's a fun and dynamic place”

</title><pros>Pros – Ample opportunity to make money</pros>
<cons>Cons – you work a lot of hours to make your money</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Needs work in the managment department.. Crooked management</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Instructional Systems Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Many contract, many opportunities”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay is goodSupport from the mother shipInteresting projects</pros>
<cons>Cons – Married couples are not allowed, in spite of the husband/wife owners.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Instructional Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pretty good.”

</title><pros>Pros – The work life balance is great. They are very understanding about school, traffic, problems, or just a need to run an important errand. The environment is very relaxed.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I've never worked for any contractor that can control the client. They all seem to cave which results in periods of more stress or work that isn't to the level you want. But these are less frequent than the periods where the client is behind and time is ample.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Control the client and ask employees how much time is needed for a task before assigning it so it can be efficient.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>