<name>Triple-I Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Triple-I-Reviews-E22391.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Taking a Different Approach”

</title><pros>Pros – Definitely a company that is focused on living up to its words.  The projects are challenging and very different from the typical fare.  Recent projects have been on SharePoint 2010, enterprise mobility and some really innovative approaches to responsive design.  Leadership is demanding but accessible. Great support staff.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Many projects with sometimes competing priorities, so, days can be pretty fluid, not a bad thing just the environment a growing company has.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep sharing the vision and spending time with the employees.  Most company VPs and CEOs don't.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Learned a lot but left out to the wolves”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of changes and learning opportunities. Bagel and Doughnut Wednesdays was nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – After landing contracts they didn't support the employees.  Staff is underpaid and overworked. There is a high turnover in employees because they are run into the ground. They taught me what the phrase over promise and under deliver meant.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – When landing contracts be sure to allocate the proper resources for the task.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A backstabbing, greedy, aloof company who has through the years held many government contracts”

</title><pros>Pros – It's easy because all you need to do is keep the seat warm for them. In the beginning you really feel like you will have the chance to really contribute to a team.  Looking from the outside the salary fair but its obvious to all soon after they are hired that Triple-i is charging embarrassing rates to the taxpayers of the United States.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Backstabbing in their changing of policies to suit their monetary needs. It seems that as a contract ends they remove your ability to use time that you earned throughout your time with the company. Many employees of Triple-I recently see this happen. It appears as though its illegal but I do not think they really care.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Go to church and gain some morality in the way you run your business. The way you run it is shady and it is  obvious to everyone after a few months it has been that way for a long time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great People, but Not Many that want to Do Their Job”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people, no micro-managers.  Great work/live balance especially if you have children.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Keeping people when their positions end and trying to have them perform job functions they have never performed before without any training or controls to make sure client work is completed at a certain level of quality.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Replace the top 3 and get some real leadership in those positions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Help Desk (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unexperienced management low people skills”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent pay and benefits no overtime.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management was horrible, a coworker was denied changing shift for an emergency surgery he had, he ended up leaving the company to take care of his condition.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – learn people skills, firing people for being 1 minute late shopwing there was an accident on the highway, bad weather, or family emergencies is play wrong.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Provided consultant support for more than a year and was treated very fairly.  Management team actually made sure rate increases were fairly shared, not something you see very often.  Overall great experience and enjoyed working with a great group of professionals.</pros>
<cons>Cons – None really. Have since moved on to another short term project, but would enjoy working for this company again.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep treating people fairly.  It may not be as profitable but will keep people coming back to work for you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Applications Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Growing Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Tons of new work in mobile apps, TFS, and with microsoft. Very experienced people. CEO is actively involved and completely accessible.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Benefits are very good, need to keep costs down.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep bringing in great talent. Keep focusing the company message,it is working!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Architect (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Professionally Rewarding”

</title><pros>Pros – More than 5 years with this company and have seen them continue to evolve into a very capable organization. Increasing focus on solutions and capabilities. Very fair. Administrative staff is excellent.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Needs to better market itself, should be better known for a 40 year old company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get out of the government business. There is no money in it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>QA Tester (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company with a Vision”

</title><pros>Pros – Fast paced environment. Heavy emphasis on mobility and system integration. Everything from enterprise level to smaller projects. Awesome use of TFS and SharePoint 2010.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Will challenge you technically and professionally. Not for people used to working banker's hours!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep pushing and sharing the vision!  More happy hours!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-14</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>QA/Automation (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Inconsistent pay and a completely untrustworthy HR department”

</title><pros>Pros – Starting pay was good when it was paid correctly. Direct management seemed interested and engaged when contacted.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Benefits were limited and expensive for contract employees.Pay statements were rarely consistent and the HR department always tried to muddle the conversation and gave different responses to the same question every time.HR department tried to withhold thousands from last paycheck for no reason.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get your pay periods correct and quit changing them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“So bad here it makes Cerner and Sprint look good.”

</title><pros>Pros – Office location is good. Easy to get to from any direction.  Some excellent people on staff, but they've lost some major talent over the last year.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management lacks a clear understanding of how to be a solutions provider - you first need a solution or niche.  Communications are by rumor mill only, staff lacks motivation.  Development group project manager drives people away she's so abrasive.  So bound up in process improvement and project management they lose money on fixed bids through to many meetings full of chiefs who just want to hear themselves talk.  Tried to be all things for all people, now they have no true expertise and are losing customers left and right.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have Bob Spachman drop the current crop of VP's and go back to staffing before the company goes under completely.  At least in staffing Triple-I still has a decent reputation in the area.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Demanding but great opportunity for people who are driven to succeed.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great opportunity to make a difference and succeed.  You will not be micro-managed at Triple-I, but you will be expected to perform - not just in word but in deed. Leadership rewards performers, weeds out those who don't/can't. If you want a place to make your mark - this is a good place for you.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company has been evolving during the past 4 years and has experienced some turnover. This is largely due to brining on additional capabilities and weeding out those who aren't a fit. Interestingly, even those who fail to perform are treated with respect, unlike so many other local companies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stay focused on your business niche.  Don't let the noise get in the way of continuing to hire strong people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's the classic case of bait and switch.”

</title><pros>Pros – The promise of being able to add value in a team environment.Promise of advancement</pros>
<cons>Cons – CEO preaches about the importance of leadership but lacks the ability to lead.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Let the people you've hired do the job you hired them to do. CEO needs to stop micro-managing and lead the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Machiavellian cutthroat environment taking over the business”

</title><pros>Pros – Vacation policy is excellent and team members communicate well.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Theyve stopped being a family and turned into Sprint or Cerner - churn and burn. Unrealistic expectations on deliverables and low staffing levels.  Thats why they've lost so many key players in the last 90 days.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Go back to being a staffing firm, you're not doing well at being a solutions provider at all.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Politics have taken over”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice people, good benefits package</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management has unrealistic expectations.  Decisions made using models for Fortune 100 firms, not a company with less than 100 employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Instead of listening to each other, go find out the facts yourself.  Figure out what the solution you're selling is, then market it instead of trying to be everything to everyone.  Realize that project managers tend to blame the workers instead of managing scope creep.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Arrogance at the top.”

</title><pros>Pros – They curn so many employees that there will always be openings. The mid level people are great and very professional.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Do not support employees. Extreme arrogance at the top. Failure to understand the situations that the business is evolving into.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide employees with more than just lip service. Need to be more intouch with the day to day business and less focused on the past.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – I like to work for this company. Nice people, nice management. Not a lot of opportunity. In whole positive experience. LIke it</pros>
<cons>Cons – No prospective, no potential, no growth. No increase in pay. Short term opportunity.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep working and doing your job the way you're doing it now. Don't have any more advice to the management. What can I say.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>