<name>Dr. D Studios Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Dr-D-Studios-Reviews-E223675.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-01-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Production Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dr.D was a great place in gaining valuable experience”

</title><pros>Pros – They were a very inclusive company, in that they always shared what was happening at every step along the way.They looked after their staff extremely well, and I always felt valued and able to contribute</pros>
<cons>Cons – The workplace was a cool, but very inhospitable old warehouse. At times it was so inhospitable that they had to send some of us home due to the heat.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Let me know where you are setting up next, I really enjoyed my time there. I learned a lot and hope you did too. Please remember to keep up the information flow, as the company got bigger and bigger, it was getting more and more difficult to get on time information. I know you did your best, and I appreciate it all.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“it was a disaster”

</title><pros>Pros – got to develop cool technologies</pros>
<cons>Cons – thought I was working somewhere for the long run, then it got shut down</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – do something else</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Talented team but poor management let to downfall”

</title><pros>Pros – Good compensation with excellent and talented staff.Flexible working hours and colleagues were friendly.Generous servings of food in the pantry and after hours meals.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very poor management. A lot of unnecessary work could have been avoided it proper planning had been done. Poor communication between certain departments.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Lead (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Most imcompetant supervisors in pretty much every departments”

</title><pros>Pros – nice city (location). Fairly good HR.</pros>
<cons>Cons – pretty much everything in production.  Lack of leadership.  Incompetant supervisors.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Animator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dr.D is fun and frustrating.”

</title><pros>Pros – The pay is decent. The work is light. The location is interesting. Good leadership and experienced artists.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The work is not very gratifying. The building the studio is located in is poorly heated and poorly cooled. Basically falling apart. Bad pipeline and the depts don't talk to each other.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They need to listen to the artists more. Also, update the pipeline to current standards.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>