<name>Charles G. Koch Foundation Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Charles-G-Koch-Foundation-Reviews-E225517.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2010-05-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Koch Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“KAP Program”

</title><pros>Pros – A good career advancing job for people interested in politics.  So far it is very well expected around Washington DC and hooked up with some great orgs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is only a year long position and it can be tough to find something to do at the end of the program.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – So far so good.  It is a good program.  Would do again.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Low quality employees”

</title><pros>Pros – The reach of the foundation is truly impressive. Everyone in the policy world have heard of the Koch Brothers, so that is a plus.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most of the employees, especially the interns, are not very intelligent. They come from these really weird conservative colleges that specialize in making you a talking head for the right. While that is fine and dandy if that is your cup of tea, they are not very knowledgeable about ANYTHING else. If you went to a normal college, there is a definite divide between those kids and the Christian/Right Wing coalition.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They need to do a better job of getting real talent. Also most of the work you do is fairly worthless and you dont really seem to have any real progress. They lose most of their real talent to the Hill.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Avoid at all costs...”

</title><pros>Pros – If you end up becoming one of the chosen people who upper-management likes, you'll enjoy this and the culture will be great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Where to start.  The atmosphere is incredibly cliqish with management choosing who they like and who they don't based on how receptive associates are to MBM.  MBM is a management philosophy that Koch thinks is unique to them when in actuality most successful organizations utilize the tools this so-called trade secret philosophy preaches.  As much as they preach challenging and providing feedback, if you ever question the way things are done or any of the tenets or applicability of MBM, you will receive talking-tos that chide you for not fitting in with the culture.  Beyond this, I'm not entirely sure what the function of this place is besides spending money on a bunch of conservative organizations that get negative press and do next to nothing.  Likewise, the Foundation sells it self as Libertarian but in actuality is more in-line with the principles of the Republican Party as evidenced by the organizations it aligns with and the types of speakers they bring in to speak to the associate class.  The school recruits mostly from small, conservative colleges with a Christian worldview.  Pay is terrible but the majority of people are unemployable elsewhere.  They claim to be great at evaluating talent but they have people with world class educations doing administrative work.  They really under- and misutilize talent not from schools like Grove City, Hillsdale and assorted other small schools.  Most people who went to large, state schools really hated it there.  Many of which turned down better opportunities in the private sector because they thought they'd be making a difference.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It's a shame to say that this place needs a full overhaul.  Senior managers make six figures and do almost nothing from what I can tell.  The problem here is that there is no incentive for management to change or get better when they're compensated so well.  Get rid of the MBM and Talent Development teams completely, they need overhauls.  The policy team needs to be disbanded completely as they don't accomplish anything.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-31</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Koch Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great training”

</title><pros>Pros – Great training, great network and great support</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not all projects or tasks are engaging and can last months</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>