<name>Kaiser Family Foundation Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Kaiser-Family-Foundation-Reviews-E22537.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-27</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Kaiser Foundation was a wonderful place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Fantastic benefits, flexible hours, great people, very professional work environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can be very hierarchical and bureaucratic.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None that I can think of.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great program”

</title><pros>Pros – Great media outlets and extremely kind and helpful program leaders.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You may have to move somewhere else for the summer. That's it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – This program offers people an invaluable experience writing for top-notch newspapers and media outlets.  I would recommend it to anyone, if you can get it. The one downside is that you often don't know where you will be placed until late in the application process. For those with families or significant others, that can be difficult.  Also, the stipend is very generous for every city, with th exception of maybe New York. It might be difficult to live on the stipend in that city.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Behind the public smoke screen”

</title><pros>Pros – Your medical /dental coverage is paid for with a minimal co-pay.  The pay is good for union work with overtime benefits as well on-call.</pros>
<cons>Cons – poor management style, unfair labor practices, promotions and new hires are based more on who you know rather than what you can actually produce.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Immediately flush out outdated management/management styles based on managing people by fear instead of working with employees and providing them with the training and support needed to create a positive pro-active environment and produce on the job.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>