<name>X-FAB Silicon Foundries Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/X-FAB-Silicon-Foundries-Reviews-E22786.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2011-06-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Design Engineer Co-op (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Like semiconductors, opportunity is directly proportional to one's engineering capabilities and know-how.”

</title><pros>Pros – The best part of X-FAB is the freedom. They ask you how to do things rather then tell you how they are done. They give you process requirements and then it's up to you. My project was great. It was deriving physical models of the CMOS and BiCMOS fabriation proceses and attempting to put them into FEA software.The project required quantifying microscale behaviors that were so powerful they produced macroscopic effects that interacted with macroscopic fabrication processes. If you're into materials science, MEMS, computer chips, or IC technology you'll enjoy the intellectual challenge.</pros>
<cons>Cons – When you start doing things that are far beyond an engineering curriculum there is little expertese to provide the means to an end. Unfortunately, they don't have experts to prevent you from getting stuck on a problem.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you want to gain some experience in a chill environment and small city  then I highly recommend the job, but if you want a glamorous job in a big city then this may not be for you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The building felt like a jail but the people were real nice.”

</title><pros>Pros – Proximity to food and everything else in a small town.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The building is too big and easy to get lost in.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing a good job.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Average at best”

</title><pros>Pros – If you like Lubbock its an ok place</pros>
<cons>Cons – low pay, confused management, lots of chickens with no head</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“BETTER THAN NOTHING”

</title><pros>Pros – WORK EXPERIENCE and some friends</pros>
<cons>Cons – people are lazymost projects are delayed and never get doneproject managers do not know what is going on with the project</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Staff Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fabulous”

</title><pros>Pros – Small organization. Friendly people. People are practically knowing each other making jobs easy and straightforward to accomplished.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of creativity. Lack of strong leadership. The management is not bold and brave enough to keep the talent from leaving.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be bold and strong on decision. Don't flip flop.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Operation engineering”

</title><pros>Pros – Learn more about high tech and clean room enviroment</pros>
<cons>Cons – salary too low seem there was no others semiconductor competator</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Salary need to review</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good”

</title><pros>Pros – great culture, happy people, nice company</pros>
<cons>Cons – small firm, not a bad place to work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>