<name>Caron Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Caron-Reviews-E229870.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-08-28</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Admissions (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dream come true employment!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great coworkers, supportive management, and incredibly dedicated employees commited to excellent patient care.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Location in the winter months.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen with open ears and hearts to your staff.  Remember that "good job" and "thank you" go farther than pizza.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Educational, but I've seen many ups and downs.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits, yearly and Christmas bonuses, friendly staff, education reimbursement</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very fast paced, political pressures, difficult customers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Allow those actually performing the tasks to have a greater day in any change process.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-31</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Counselor Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not bad if you know the "right" people and constantly kiss butt.”

</title><pros>Pros – Many of the employees love they're jobs at Caron and support one another extremely well. The campus itself is very nice, excellent food and amenitites for patients and staff. Pay is quite good, better than any other local drug rehab.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I worked on the adolescent side of the campus, the amount of pressure and paranoia placed on counselor assistants was ridiculous. They don't have a thorough written manual, there are constant emails about what new protocols are in place, then they're retracted days, weeks or months later. Often, one singular incident would result in unit-wide protocol change. Yearly reviews seemed to dig for one or two negative aspects throughout a year; not nearly enough praise for working double shifts, managing extremely difficult patients or entire communities or taking extra time to creatively implement ideas or tools that work in one situation. Also, as this is a private pay facility, too often clinical decisions where swayed by what management needed financially. Too often clinical judgement was thrown out the door and people not qualified to have as much say as they're given, called too many shots.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop the favoritism, get only clinically certified and educated staff in on staff meetings discussing anyting regarding patients.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>