<name>XPRIZE Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/XPRIZE-Reviews-E22931.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Dream Job Come True”

</title><pros>Pros – I get to work with talented interesting people on projects that make the World a better place. I get to wear jeans to work every day and work in a relaxed and engaging atmosphere. I get a comfortable office and pleasant coworkers and I actually get paid to do things that I want to do. I get respect and autonomy without being overworked and every day is a new and exciting challenge. I'm happy.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In my wanderings around the office, I often encounter people who are doing even more interesting projects that I am, but I can't just drop what I'm doing and join their team. The ever-present supply of fruit, snacks, and beverages in the kitchen is making it difficult for me not to gain weight. I still haven't figured out how to get one of those cool XPRIZE jackets.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work on putting more efficient processes, technology and systems in place to make it easier for employees to get everything done more quickly. Need to work on orientation of new hires to make sure they get all the information and connections that they need right away.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome concept, frustrating execution”

</title><pros>Pros – Change the world, work with some amazing people and innovators and learn about fascinating things. Good benefits package, workplace food, often get extra days off!HR really tries. Looks good on resume (for those who don't know the organization).</pros>
<cons>Cons – Leadership with limited/no experience in running successful companies/non profits, yet some of highest salaries in non profit field and also a bonus package. Both leaders have two assistants.  Board of Directors (not Trustees) full of friends of leadership so does not take a stand. Senior management likes to empire build. Relationships with related companies / personal business interests for leadership leads to self interested decisions. Inefficient and rigid processes and practices lead to poor donor stewardship and poor funds stewardship as well as frustrating good employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Clean up the entanglement issues before they cross the line. Think about what wouldn't look good if the LA Times did an investigation and get it sorted. Hire people who actually know how to lead a non profit. Focus on sponsors and donors and proving great value or they won't return and will say bad things to other potential donors and sponsors.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Please pay attention - flock won't follow”

</title><pros>Pros – ideas that could change the worldPeople that care to make change in the organization</pros>
<cons>Cons – The leader, the leader, the leader and then other 2 musketeers (president and cfo). Totally don't get it. Focused on their own wealth increase. Tyrants, egos, narcissistic megalomania</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat people with respect. Get out of the way. Stop unethical practices. Stop feeding your own other companies with XPF donor funds.The board needs to get on board and make this stop.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Non Profit Sweat Shop”

</title><pros>Pros – Name recognition.  Looks good to have it on your resume.  That's it, especially if you can survive for 6 months</pros>
<cons>Cons – Arrogant and cocky culture.   Need to drink the kool aid and be a gopher for management or you will find your self the door with out any notice.  They burn thru employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve employment culture, reward low to mid level employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Making the Possible, Impossible”

</title><pros>Pros – - In its rawest concept, the X PRIZE Foundation is a great idea: think up some seemingly impossible task, and dangle a large cash prize to lure the best and the brightest to complete it.- There are numerous employees who are brilliant, kind people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - In actuality, the creativity is lacking.  The prize ideas that get funded are completely within the realm of possibility currently, and are frequently things that have already been done.- The brilliant, kind people get fired at Christmas time after devoting years of service.- The approval process is dismal, and entirely too time consuming. Frequently, the people you need to approve things are not in the office (Senior management takes numerous vacations and unnecessary travel).- Senior management and consultants are overpaid, and normally only in the office a maximum of 4 days a week.- After securing a multi-million dollar donation for operations, two key workers were fired for no apparent reason.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Streamline the approval process.- Eliminate the ADP time tracking system - it's a colossal waste of time.- Don't fire people around the holidays; it's bad for morale.- When you do fire people, at least pretend to be remorseful.- Listen to your employees; we can make this place run smoother. Also, as others have said, let people do their jobs.- CEO needs to think bigger.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The idea is great, but the workplace is not inspiring.”

</title><pros>Pros – Being a part of big ideas, and helping make them happenCompetition and competitors are inspiringUnique opportunitiesA well-connected company</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor managementLow salaries for most employees (but high salaries for upper management)DisorganizationUnreasonable expectationsBig egosConstant struggle for budget on projects</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Trust your employees to do the job you hired them for.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Maturing and growing in an exciting field”

</title><pros>Pros – Exposure to world class thinkers, visionary leaders and fascinating concepts and challenges.  Huge sense of impacting the world and making a difference.  Maturing organization that is self critical, learning and evolving.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Suffers from mission creep, still learning how to pare down to key strategic initiatives, building the muscle to say no to "new, exciting" projects and to develop organizational discipline.  Getting better, but still further to go.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Empower the new leadership and focus on successfully completing the active X PRIZE competitions and designing and launching new X PRIZE competitions.  Do less, stay focussed, do it better.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Where Careers Come to Die”

</title><pros>Pros – The only pro I can really think of is that you are exposed to some pretty interesting people and ideas.  Unfortunately, that's about it for the pros.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Where to start? How about advancement and pay.  If you join the foundation to grow and advance a career path, you're making a terrible mistake.  Of the 3-4 years I worked there, I only saw two or three promotions.  However, I did see them hire and fire upwards of 40 people from outside sources.  Talk about high turn over.  If you don't meet management's expectations within 6 months, you're gone.  As for pay? It's pretty meager compared to elsewhere I've worked.  Unfortunately, it's been a down economy, so this was all I could get at the time, and it was even tough finding another position to jump ship to.  Hang in there ex-coworkers! It can get better (once you leave)!Structurally, this business is extremely top heavy, and the furthest thing from efficient I've seen.  Ironic considering their goals. They pay their prize development team upwards of $1 million a year to do something that the public has shown a complete willingness to do for free/significantly less.  Doesn't anyone remember "What's your crazy green idea?" Oh yeah, probably not since nobody from that time actually still works there.  On top of all that, almost half of the prize development team is only in the office 3-4 times a year.  And those are the people making $100K a year? Not good for morale.I won't even go into the fact that the top two hold up almost all of the projects and work to be done because of constant revisions and assigning new tasks. Seems to be pretty well documented, and yes, it's 100% true.Wonder why not a single sponsor has re-upped a contract, or sponsored another prize? We're awful to do business with, and probably have a negative ROI for them.  We should be an asset, and have companies fighting to collaborate with us.  Instead, we're begging them to let us associate with them.So sad I wasted so much time there. I could have been a VP by now, or at least a Senior Director, had I spent my last few years elsewhere.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire more low and medium level employees, and pay them better.  Management needs to back off and put trust in their employees.  And stop cutting the fat, then adding it right back in.  Get rid of some of the top heaviness, and actually INNOVATE instead of just following the same path you have for years.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awful. Unprofessional. Lack of leadership and accountability. Do NOT work here or give them money.”

</title><pros>Pros – They have a quality reputation from the outside looking in.  Very high-profile board of directors.  Offices in Playa Vista and easy access to freeways.  Quiet work environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Very under-qualified individuals in charge. The two main leaders are (Bob Weiss) an unemployed Hollywood producer and (Peter Diamandis) a space enthusiast with very little interest remaining.  Zero successful NPO or for-profit successes under their belts.  Zero management experience except for within the entertainment industry where individuals fear for their jobs - not work to "benefit humanity."- Funds are constantly inappropriately allocated (high salaries (400k+), lavish travel, two assistants with one for personal use, etc.).  No budget discipline.  Lavish fundraising events and travel equaling significant funds from operational budgets, which later equal the termination of a staff member to "budgetary constraints."- Staff members are never trusted which makes it impossible to simply do your job.- Poor work environment.- Zero loyalty.- VERY, VERY, VERY poor reputation among past significant sponsors and donors (Progressive Insurance, Lance Armstrong Foundation, many, many, many more).- Lack of communication.- Not rewarded or recognized for achievement.- HUGE employee turn-around.  Over 100 staffers (all levels) within two years.  The entire foundation only has about 50 employees.- Unpredictable deliverables equaling very long hours resulting in... nothing.  Seriously.  Nothing.- The board has little to zero interest or activity.  They all remain active to simply network twice a year among each other.  Which is very sad considering who is involved.- Constant "plans" and "deliverables" produced resulting in zero forward momentum within the foundation.- Lack of vision.- Lack of professional respect and qualifications.- It's a fearful work environment.  Meaning, you will be terminated at any point for any reason senior staff can create.- It is just an awful place to work and grow.  I was offered three positions when I took one at the X Prize Foundation.  I kick myself almost every day for accepting X Prize's offer.  DO NOT WORK HERE AS LONG AS CURRENT MANAGEMENT IS IN PLACE!!!!!!!!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Quit.  Realize how bad you are at everything you do and simply resign.Ask yourself, "What have I done that is positive within the last ___ years at the foundation (besides the original Ansari X Prize?"Ask yourself, "How many extremely qualified individuals have come through these doors and quit?  Why did they resign? Why do all of them hate us?"Ask yourself, "How much time, in the amount of years, have I wasted looking over plans or budgets that were never implemented?"Before you depart, send a note to the board of directors demanding them to be more active!  Tell them to put down the drink at the board networking parties and to roll up their sleeves.  The X Prize Foundation needs a clean slate to have any hope of retaining a legacy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unrealized potential”

</title><pros>Pros – amazing missionexciting workability to make a global impactstrong external support for the organizationgood brand image</pros>
<cons>Cons – micromanagement at a level of detail that rapidly becomes value destroyingpoor or stalled decision makinginability to prioritize in any sort of disciplined way and then even more trouble sticking to what ultimately get decided as the top prioritiesinability to think about the future of the organization strategicallysustained periods of very poor moralehighly dysfunctional leadership at the top - inability to set direction and inspire confidence</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus and get rid of the dysfunction.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“filled with egos”

</title><pros>Pros – work on some truly interesting ideas</pros>
<cons>Cons – there is ZERO execution on any of the projects which are guided by inexperienced managers and incompetent senior management.senior management are more concerned with maintaining their high salaries and pictures in the newspapers than actually doing anything.they go where the money</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – leave.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Member - Senior Management Team (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“GBU”

</title><pros>Pros – The opportunity to meet and interact with thought leaders across a variety of verticals including Life Sciences, Cleantech, Aerospace, Social Entrepreneurship, etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Marked by excessive founder hubris and faulty corporate governance; it is a case study in moral hazard arguably pushing the frontiers of non-/mis- and malfeasance and extreme instances of agent extraction of corporate resources.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – This is a case where Senior Management (specifically CEO & President) should immediately be replaced.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>