<name>Walter P. Moore and Associates Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Walter-P-Moore-and-Associates-Reviews-E23053.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great working Environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible ScheduleGood EnvironmentUpper mobility opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – Occasional long hoursField workNo upper mobolity if non-performing</cons>
<advice-to-management> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Structural Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great job, but not great compensation.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great projects, excellent coworkers, and extensive training.  A wonderful place to learn and grow as an engineer.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Fewer and fewer milestone projects.  The company is top heavy due to the downturn and this is limiting growth for younger engineers.  Compensation and benefits lag behind other companies, particularly after the first couple of years.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Many great people work for this firm, but some tough business decisions need to be made to ensure it succeeds in the future.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Women Need Not Apply”

</title><pros>Pros – Lot of the people were really great</pros>
<cons>Cons – Ray Messer is a jerk.  Women need not apply.  If you are not an engineer you are garbage to them.  No appreciation for anyone but themselves</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get over yourselves.  The employees are the ones doing the work and earning your huge salaries.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Civil Engineering (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company to Work For”

</title><pros>Pros – The people and the culture</pros>
<cons>Cons – The compensation is low for the amount of hours you typically work in one week</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Selfish Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Some of the people are good to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In every single transaction of employee to the company, the company looks to short the employee.  They are on the low end of the salary scale.  They make you pay travel expenses out of pocket then tale 2-3 weeks to pay you back.  Even the 401K (which they do not contribute) they hold your disbursement (my money 2-3 weeks before wiring it to the 401K fund.  In addition, I was pressured to work a minimum of 50 hours a week so my utilization would remain constantly over 100%.  The day I left it was still at 100%.  Then come time for bonuses, oops not enough money for a real bonus.  In one year I worked nearly 300 hours of overtime on salary and my bonus was $500.  Do the math!Too many overhead employees that work 7 hour days while the production people are forced to work 10 hour days.Lastly, the location is a problem being downtown, unless your new out of school and live uptown, then it's great.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You need to reward the people doing the work and cut the non-essential overhead employees that drag on the profitability.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Structural Summer Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“structural summer intern”

</title><pros>Pros – Gave me a good amount of varied experience. Went onsite for some really cool projects and learned from seasoned staff. They did give good, critical evaluations at the end of the internship that helped me later on in my career. The company's culture is pretty awesome. I even got a few benefits even as a lowly intern!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Majority of time was spent on shop drawings. No one can declare that as..."exciting experience." The worst part though were the lay-offs of other employees later and knowing I wouldn't be able to become full time later as they only had a handful of projects.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – keep up the good work!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Young guns are selfish!”

</title><pros>Pros – Fantastic reputation, will do wonders for a resumeFair compensationMany many good family oriented peopleMany employees who care deeply about doing a good job</pros>
<cons>Cons – Group of selfish leaders that back stab their way to the topA few bad apples -willing to bring the house downDown economy brought out the worst in everyoneClients find some of the leaders arrogant</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Understand selfishness while it may producing short-term gain, will bring down an organization</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good opportunities, failing corporate culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people to work with, the best projects, and a lot of opportunities to learn.  The office locations are very good.  I go to work every day and enjoy what I do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The benefits and pay are not good, I wish they would contribute to 401k.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management should truly support the core cultural values.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great projects, long hours, no upward movement”

</title><pros>Pros – Great projects, great staff. You get to work on some of the best projects in Houston in the civil group.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is almost no room for upward movement if you are a a civil engineer. You get stuck as a project manager and can't advance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great culture and strongly believe the firm is will continue to strive toward greatness.”

</title><pros>Pros – Project variety, diversity, and challenge is second to none.Office, technology, and personnel is very good</pros>
<cons>Cons – Employee validation and recognition doesn't seem to be as high of a priority as it should.Life/work balence is often a challenge</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve communication and retention plan.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent reputation, used to be a "Best Place to Work," but when money for perks runs dry, there's no reason to stay.”

</title><pros>Pros – The reputation of Walter P Moore is second to none. It's powerful and enthralling to see a small group of young, motivated engineers designing the coolest structures in the world. Certain departments focus on building a true team, which is why I took the job in the first place. Many of the principals of the company are true masters of their craft-- brilliant, affable, and eager to pass along their wisdom to younger staff.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Other departments are not so dedicated towards building a team. There's little trust to go around in those departments, and there are drastically different philosophies between service groups. The successes and failures of the service groups are reflected in how they recruit and treat their engineering staff. Too much emphasis is placed on tangible perks like free lunches and snazzy workspaces. Too little credence is given to the idea that happy, trusted employees produce good work. Too many instances of mistrust add up to a borderline-mutinous staff.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value your employees... Don't rely on nice lunches and pretty parties to make people want to work here. Transparency, recognition of personnel achievements company-wide (not just in SESG Houston), trust of employees, cutting back of red tape and non-work, and allowing people more flexibility will go far.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best Firm to Work for .... there's a reason.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great leadership, management, mentoring and training.  Management really works hard at creating a great atmosphere.   Throughout the company there are many talented people who are always willing to provide help when you have a question.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not enough information about some of the work we are pursuing or have recently won.  It would be nice to know what's on the horizon as far as projects.  We could also do a little more to celebrate our successes, especially during these difficult times.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It would be nice if management were more open to adding some additional benefits.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Structural Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – Work life balance, depends on office manager.  Great knowledge sharing practice, great opportunites for prominent projects.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not all offices have the same workstyle, do not follow same corporate culture - internal seminars, meetings, attending phone calls, happy hour, office decorum differ completely.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It is the way it is, cannot advise top management, they know what they are doing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cad-Operator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cooperate politics suck”

</title><pros>Pros – The Pay, and seminars. The Food and fruits on Tuesday.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management, People, Location, and stressfull environment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay more attention to your employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company, solid benefits.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good company, solid benefits. The locations of all the offices were ideal, and the people were generally quality.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lackluster work at times -- all of the really cool work goes to the bigger offices.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide more opportunities for mentorship, work-life balance.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Really nice people”

</title><pros>Pros – Very nice group of people to work with. Great president. Awesome projects. High quality staff.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Seems to be a lot employee dissatisfaction from the newer staff.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Thanks for taking pay cuts to preserve jobs. Keep up the good work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Pretty good at sharing information/best practices</pros>
<cons>Cons – HQ office in Houston is preferred over other offices.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-10</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“one of the best places to work at”

</title><pros>Pros – pros:excellent projects, great learning environment, respect for junior members of team as well, opportunity for growth, very nice working environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – cons:too many deadlines interfere with personal life, salary range is not that good for junior engineers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – -</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>