<name>Jim 'N Nick's Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Jim-N-Nick-s-Reviews-E230215.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I enjoy working for company.”

</title><pros>Pros – Management cares about staff and overall atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Isn't a lot of room for growth</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Server (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I waited tables here while pursuing a degree, and for a brief period between jobs”

</title><pros>Pros – Their menu is easy to understand, and therefore easy to describe to a customer. The average customer is not very discerning, and therefore easy to lead. A lot of the customers are genuinely good people, especially at the location I worked (35205).</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management makes rash decisions on a whim with no knowledge of the day to day operations of any given restaurant. Many of my coworkers were barely qualified to breathe, let alone wait tables. I felt that the overall reputation of the restaurant, influenced by the aforementioned servers, limited my prospects as a server, by reducing volume.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Require your employees to know how BBQ works. Don't just do some bureaucratic "training session", test every single employee on the inner workings of this cooking method. Pay for the people that actually know what they're doing, and respect them. Don't just hire whoever will accept your wages.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not run like a typical company”

</title><pros>Pros – They pay very well.Two weeks Paid vacation is better than most other restaurantsAll managers get a cut of bonus not just the GM</pros>
<cons>Cons – LOOOOOOOOOOONG hours sometimes 75+ a week with no compensation at allthe way the restaurant operates relies heavily on labor and its sometimes impossible to hitAs a manager, you are constantly overrulled by the owner of the restaurantmost weekends management is there till one or two in the morning when the store closes at 10 pm!!!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – let the managers manage!! if you work your managers more than they're alotted 55 hours...compensate them either by less hours or by paying them for their hours</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was good.”

</title><pros>Pros – It paid good for a summer job. They were nice and the management was willing to work with my summer hours.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They did not always help me with my summer hours.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Hostess (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok for part-time job, but staff was low caliber”

</title><pros>Pros – - Great food & Customers. It really is a fun atmosphere to work in if the staff was better. I loved interacting with customers. I think the staff was unhappy with their lives and that is what caused the negative work environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Horrible staff, put on a show for customers to get good tips. Many of the staff members were on drugs or would step outside to take them in between tables.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on improving your corporate culture. Training would help for staff members to be more engaged with the products sold.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Server (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Jim and Nicks”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Food with 50 percent off. Relaxed atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Empty Promise of benefits. Only managers favorites are promoted. Not hard workers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Promote hard workers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>