<name>U-Haul Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/U-Haul-Reviews-E236315.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“First Career Move Ever”

</title><pros>Pros – I started working with the company March of last year and just recently became a General Manager in Michigan. I worked hard to get where I am now and I owe it to my General Manager for providing me with the work ethic to strive in this company. Great company to work for and with. Looking forward to the future.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I don't necessarily have an issue with the work and life balance. It is just finding that balance then everything will be golden.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – My advice to management as of now would be to not be on a need to know basis ALL THE TIME. A little heads up would be nice.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Development and Marketing Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Phenomenal Internship Program at Phoenix HQ”

</title><pros>Pros – Working at U-Haul headquarters in Phoenix offers a broad range of in-house projects and room to grow within the company. The internship program for college juniors and seniors is a great opportunity to gain exposure to the company's many different departments and affiliated companies. The internship program was well organized with weekly site tours, workshops, and luncheons. My manager was also a great mentor giving me constructive and valuable feedback.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The effort to keep everything in-house seems to spread management thin. At times it seemed that department communication and collaboration was, in reality, an attempt to manage multiple projects with as few resources as possible. Because of the tendency to hire from within, there appears to be a slow rate of technology and process innovation.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's not that bad  after all, U-haul is not a bad company for those who need a part time job and like this type of work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible schedule, lear new things</pros>
<cons>Cons – hard to get full time job</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-27</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome!”

</title><pros>Pros – Convenient, very helpful, and the manager Erik is awesome and Christina is definitely a keeper!</pros>
<cons>Cons – In this economy they don't even come close to paying their employees for all they do.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The team working in Murrieta together really hustle and they keep customers happy!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Web Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place, despite bureaucracy.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great co-workers, personally excellent boss...time scheduling is usually pretty free, but last I heard, it's changing. They are very flexible with life events, which is a real nice thing too. Decent cafe, for snack runs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Benefits, squabbling managers tend to get projects slowed, which only hurts everyone. And it wouldn't hurt to have bonuses, especially after you see how well the stock is doing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Empathize with your employees. It'll generate respect.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Area Field Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Area Field Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Field support was ok. The dealer's within the route for the most part were an extended family, and the company benefits were good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Local management constantly pulled you off of what you were doing to address something that could have waited which simply created more work. Long hours for little pay</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Markeing Company Presidents have to much freedom to add to the Area Field Manager's or General Manager's work, which is in direct contrast to company policy. Usually at the request of their supervisor or Area District Vice President. The quality of the work done is poor and simply has a trickle down effect to customers, and company employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dog eat dog.”

</title><pros>Pros – Less restricted and less monitored working habits.Most locations do not monitor employees dress with congruence to corporate code.Unity among staff promoted teamwork.Always work to do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Zero control over distribution of hours, regardless of work experience or knowledge.Unfair favor shown to other associates.Management's one goal is to delegate all of their responsibilities to their staff.Frequency of associate favoritism by management across multiple locations is extremely high.Problems will likely not see solution as company issues begin high in leadership and infect downward.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Distribute responsibilities more fairly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Center Storage Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall a good company with good intentions, but they don't always get carried out as predicted”

</title><pros>Pros – #1 Benefits are excellent#2 Immediate management is super#3 Recognition for accomplishments and support for advancement</pros>
<cons>Cons – Scheduled nights, weekends, holidays#1 Job description highly inaccurate#2 We deal with a very difficult customer base, as they are almost always in a "stressed-out, ready to explode" mood b/c they just had a horrendous move they completed (one of the major life stressors). Customer Service is extremely difficult.#3 No training and most employees are Part Time (as required by U-haul) so there is large turn-over and no real loyalty to the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Training, training, training...in a uniformed, organized method (possibly should have a position that goes to several locations and focuses only on training).</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Personally fulfilling but difficult for family life”

</title><pros>Pros – The ability to help people relocate was a great aspect of the job. The teamwork between all the locations was a great thing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The long hours were a very hard thing to deal with along with all of the changes in management made it difficult to stay.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Moonlighted (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome for stay at home moms”

</title><pros>Pros – You get to drive all the trucks</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working in all kinds of weather</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its a lot of”

</title><pros>Pros – As General manager the company give you a lot of freedom.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A lot of hours. Hard work. And if you don't preform your gone Anaheim</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Third Key Holder (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No hours, respect, recognition for part-timers”

</title><pros>Pros – You keep busy here cleaning trucks.....</pros>
<cons>Cons – no respect, recognition, hours for part-timers. only mgmt is the ppl there that are full-time and get 40 hours</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – start a recognition plan for your part-timers.  Offer more hours to part-timers not just certain stores because the store manager there is family of an mcp. Need to do MORE audits of the storage units to reduce loss revenue b/c store managers storing their belongings in a unit.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Ecenter Sales & Reservations (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't care about employee's or customersbout customers and employees”

</title><pros>Pros – Work from Home, decent income during the busy times.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Customers are very unhappy and stressed because they are moving. If they were explained things more they wouldn't be. Most of the consultants will hang up if they can't answer a caller questions because they want to get their commission. Lot's of technical problems with the computers at corporate that are outside of your control and then you loose commissions as a result. They don't give you the hours you request, and I was pretty open. All I wanted was to have two days off a week together for at least half the month. They didn't need to be weekends.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the good employee's who care about the customers even if they have technical challenges outside of their control due to the purchase of a new home.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for a college job”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy job if you don't mind rude customers</pros>
<cons>Cons – pay sucks, customers are mean to you</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – pay the people that deal with your customers a remotely decent wage</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's ok”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a stable company.Great benefits for part time and full time employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working for corporate it's great; however, some of the kids from the management team do not know what being corect means</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Some of yhe kids you have working as managers at the corporate office do not know what is it that they are doing. They are selfish and vengeful and they have high school like behavior. I was one of the best agents on my shift...one of the agents who were testing new programs and new requirements. My calls were used for training purpose, as an example on how to handle a call.  And because I changed shifts and one of the kidmanager did not like me because I corrected him previously , I got the boot. My advice is to question these kids before they toy with other ppl income and living.  My experience with the my previous 4 managers was excellent and i know 100%  that they have great things to say about me as an employee.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Sales Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Customer Service Sales Rep”

</title><pros>Pros – Job consistencyKeeps you busyEasy JobWork from home optionExcellent training</pros>
<cons>Cons – Training varies on the person in charge, some people are more prepared than othersNot many choices on when to take training, either VERY early in the morning or VERY late at nightIt's a sales position, so you will get the expected in this position</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep training specificWork on the system crashing because of too many callers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wow. U-Haul Really need to do better for there employees. No Respect!!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – co-worker were like family to each other.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay for what the company wants you to do daily. Low and Very low hours but want to work in extreme heat, cold and rainy weather. No holiday paid and only closed 1 day out of the year. Not enough worker because they don't to give more hours to cover the shift but complains when customer complain about the wait time or other issues. The assistants managers work full time hours and is consider to be part time worker with no benefits.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give the worker more pay and more hours. Treat everyone equal because 25 hours is not worth anything this company offer.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very Pleasant Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people, great benefits, plenty of opportunities!</pros>
<cons>Cons – None that I can think of</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep treating your employees as well as you do.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Customer service rep.”

</title><pros>Pros – Learn how to deal with different types of customers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not a lot hours if your not salary</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Let part time have more than 25 hours a week.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not the kind of U-Haul most people knew it years ago”

</title><pros>Pros – Paid on time; Aside from that, I really do not know what else to put.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor training; Some rude and condescending employees; Some people in management are sarcastic; They try to get by with customers with the least amount of assistance they can provide, if any; People at the lower end of the Totem pole are basically put in a bind and burdened with unrealistic expectations; Outdated software that cannot accommodate bandwidth workload</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You need to retrain the management staff and employees that you have at the locations. Inconsistence with information is bad enough. But being sarcastic, rude and condescending towards other employees or subordinates is just asinine and unethical. Making a change brings results. Simply saying that "We are the best" and such are just rubbish propaganda. Customers call Customer Service "not to compliment", but because they need assistance. Telling a customer that your said employee(s) is an excellent or reliable employee is not in any way or form the kind of assistance that a client going through a move is in dire need of.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Tax Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“upper management was crazy family members who were dishonest”

</title><pros>Pros – Made a lot of good friends there, hot women to date; I worked in Corporate headquarters as a professional</pros>
<cons>Cons – Extremely low pay, I was there 11 years and had topped out the pay scale.  The new company I went to doubled my salary</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – keep the equipment maintained; their were a lot of customers that got killed while I was there, raise wages, quit cheating - they did the same thing as Enron</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Was okay when started, but dreading during the last year”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible with schoolOpportunity to be pay well as a sales repEasy going co-workersBonusesLocation</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours on SaturdaysVery busy during the summerManagement sometimes difficult to work withParking structureUnpredictable hours during slow season</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“okay company as long as you don't want to move up”

</title><pros>Pros – nice manager, easy hours, customer service</pros>
<cons>Cons – mediocre pay, no advancement opportunities, policies not always followed</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do something about the reservation guarantee..seems to be the most complained about area from customers.  Needs to be better described to customers that a reservation is NOT a guarantee.Also the U-box program is very difficult for customers AND employees to understand, and there is always problems with shipping time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Low pay, high expectations, flexible hours”

</title><pros>Pros – Very flexible scheduling, management respects you, welcoming environment to work in, and I've learned a lot from working at U-Haul. Now that I've finally earned my Bachelor's degree its time to move on.</pros>
<cons>Cons – High stress with relatively low pay compared to what's expected of you, basically everyone is hired as part-time, work weekends and holidays with no holiday pay. I earned $10.50 per hour busting my butt and running the entire center. Sometimes I worked 40-50 hours per week but since I'm technically "part-time" I don't get the benefits of full-time employees (paid holidays, sick and vacation pay)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't be so cheap. We work hard and deserve full time positions</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Uhaul Customer Service (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Customer Service Employees are Only Temporary”

</title><pros>Pros – Paid training program. Wort at home opportunities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Cut down hours. Even though they schedule you hours they tell you to log out early because they don't need you. Managers do not communicate with you or respond to e-mails. Low pay AZ 8.50/hour. No raises. No real benefits, just some discounts on healthcare.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Customer service is your front lines, and this company is getting a terrible reputation thanks to the indispensable employees you are using.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Center Sales and Reservations (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working at U-Haul as Reservations Agent”

</title><pros>Pros – Mostly flexible schedule - opportunity to swap and drop shifts w/o manager approval as long as someone can cover youKnowledge at your fingertipsCan easily double the base salary through bonuses. Awesome bonus program.Most customers are niceCo-workers are nice and helpful</pros>
<cons>Cons – Saying the same phrase repeatedly, for every phone call can get annoying.Rude customers who make it difficult to want to help themCustomers who do not understand that there is a reservation process and a lot of questions are askedYou can receive coach's for small issues, which could be avoided if managers are more proactive in answering/assisting agentsManagers want the benefit of being placed in 1st place for sales but do not want to answer questions/guide agents.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do not encourage questions to be asked if they are not answered. In order to be an effective manager, you have to not only manage, but also guide employees. Yes, it's a simple job, but questions will arise and it would be great if they were answered.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Until You Get Promoted”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits and work atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of Training.  It is assumed that if you do well in one position you will do well in another, but they will not train when you go into the next position.  You're set up for failure. Upper management will not listen.  When there's an issue, they do not get both sides of a story.  They will automaticly take a manager's side.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Train people when you promote them into a new position, especially if they were considered "a valuable employee" in their old position, and the new position is in a totally different area.  They were valuable because they knew the job and will continue to be valuable when you train them in their new position.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A decent minmum wage job for someone looking to get work while working on other plans.”

</title><pros>Pros – Fairly relaxed environment with other employees and pretty low stress duties. Most people you deal with on a daily basis are reasonable and the hours were quite flexible.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most facilities are very understaffed and thus there will be times when you are overwhelmed by the number of customers and simply unable to keep up.Moving can be a very stressful time in people's lives.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Left due to problems with interpersonal relations amongst staff. Improve camaraderie between the people who work under you and with them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If nobody else will hire you...”

</title><pros>Pros – You will learn what hard work is and appreciate any former/future job that much more.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Absence of training, mediocre income, extremely stressful, management unavailable/no chain of command. This is the worst work experience I've had in my entire life, without exaggeration.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Train employees for the real-life situations they will encounter on a day-to-day basis. Offer a consistent schedule with one weekend day off every week. Pay according to market and the skill-set required to perform the duties at hand. A CSR, at my center, always works alone, yet does not have the authorization to resolve customer issues, thus giving the employee and Uhaul a bad name/review. Do away with the 6 months of service policy in place before an employee may transfer to a position which will better suit the employee and the company. I have never had a conversation with upper management. This is discouraging.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pay Rate”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy work, works with schedule</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay rate is low not enough hours,</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Customer Service Representative”

</title><pros>Pros – flexibledecent starting pay not greatdon't expect to get a raise everhonestly I can think of anything else</pros>
<cons>Cons – upper Management dose not care about anyonethis companies dose not ever give raises to anyonedose not know how to handle injuries</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – take better care of your employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>AFM (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Do as I say, not as you are payed to do!”

</title><pros>Pros – As long as you complete and enter info into system daily, no problem. Person I reported to did leave you alone, didn't bother you or call unless problem arouse.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Traffic manager would talk down to independent dealers on matters. Changed SOP daily to suite uhaul and not the general public, also told dealers to send UHAUL customers to competitors on a regular basis. After training dealers how to service customers correctly, traffic would tell them to do as they say.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Put people in the right positions to ensure exisiting independent dealer customer base stays with UHAUL. DO NOTPUT A UHAUL INDEPENDENT DEALER ON EVERY CORNER, DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE NUMBER OF DEALERSHIPS IN ANY GIVEN TOWN JUST TO MAKE MC #s LOOK GOOD.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Center Sales and Reservations (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It has been an advancement opportunity.”

</title><pros>Pros – Work from home, flexibility, decent pay, family affiliated.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Non stop calls, no in between time kind of gets boring.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Area Field Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Shocked”

</title><pros>Pros – Solid company will be around.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They do not treat there people as an asset. They do not pay there crew enough for what they have to go through.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make sure your MCP is qualified and working the hours he says he is.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A relatively easy-going company, with random but frequent enforcement of silly policy”

</title><pros>Pros – -Very little bureaucracy with their open-door policy-Flexible work schedule for part-time employees-New things to deal with every day-Available bonuses if managers choose to give them</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Open every holiday except Christmas-Long, long hours for managers-People who are moving (U-Haul's target clientele) tend to be on edge and unfriendly</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make sure to keep your employees motivated. Regional managers - be involved, be friendly. Don't be the boss everyone is afraid of. Be knowledgeable, don't act like you are above customer service. It reflects VERY poorly on your character and makes it nearly impossible to lead effectively.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Rental Clerk (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Eventful, challenging, rewarding”

</title><pros>Pros – Meeting new people. Helping people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can't always satisfy every customer.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Always have a manager onsite.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Understaffed,stressed, and not paid enough”

</title><pros>Pros – Helping happy customers with their moving needs. Working in customer service at U-haul is not a fun experience</pros>
<cons>Cons – Manager does not listen to his employees. Constant fear of getting fired if you do something wrong. The place was understaffed so we did not get any lunch or breaks required by law.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire more people and stop looking at your numbers and start listening to your employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Reservation Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“U-Haul Reservations Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Part-time, flexible hours, offer some benefits to part-time employees, company discounts, relationships with many company associates and dealers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Part-time jobs with no future for full-time in the respective position.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Cross train employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Center Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst training, for work at home”

</title><pros>Pros – Paid on time, other workers are mostly nice, even people calling in were for the most part nice, sa not so nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not proper training, you get two different ones each say different things, then SA say another! Then you lose your bonus for everything!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Better training</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>E-center Sales & Reservation (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great job for students, mothers, & part-timers!”

</title><pros>Pros – Virtual Job, Great training!! Management have friendly attitude.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is very low chance for incentives, bonuses</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to upgrade salary.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Too much work for little pay”

</title><pros>Pros – They offer Great full time benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Doing way more work than what you are getting paid for.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make sure to hire general managers that aren't afraid of confrontation.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Hours are flexible. Alot of freedom to make decisions and there are opportunities to move up.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay not worth the amount of work load. Not much you can do since it is result based pay at a moving company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“GM”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of turnover = opportunity?</pros>
<cons>Cons – The rental equivalent of Wal-Mart -- rigorously anti-union (have shut down entire shop plantations over it). The payroll is absolutely embarrassing and ensures that the totality of things to be completed will never actually happen, which means that blame must be placed somewhere on the retail level. Center was given enough to payroll to run the entire operation with just me and a single counter person MOST OF THE TIME. At the time I was hired, I realized I was one of many, as 95% of the GMs in the entire region had not been there more than 10 months or so. If someone wants a hitch done you are supposed to drop everything and either the manager or counter person is expected to be able to do it. That's right, they will tell you to your face that anyone working there with zero mechanical experience will be held liable for the quality of the piece of steel they are often drilling in, and the wiring that they are splicing in to a customer's car. You will be given no mechanic at all, and be expected to actually maintain a fleet of 60something pieces of rental equipment with a series of part-timers making 10/hr. They expect you to "manage 30% of the time," the rest being regular old manual labor: cleaning trucks, working the counter, hooking up trailers, installing wiring on someone's personal vehicle. Trucks will regularly be gone for a month to get any kind of repair done because the off-site shop is absolutely swamped, at their own admittance. And if it goes there and something's not actually wrong then they will look at you, the mechanic-less manager, and act like it is your fault.They want to believe they are special and that it takes some kind of "special U-Haul person" to get in with their little game. This is really just another way of saying 'no one wants this job for a reason.' There is a reason why 7 different GMs were fired in 7 weeks.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You are not special, and believing so is just a way of excusing yourself from that facts that are plain to see for the rest of society. They are laughing at you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“HORRIBLE MANAGEMENT They lie about bonuses.”

</title><pros>Pros – Work from home opportunity if you have super fast Internet speed. The calls are diverse and can be interesting.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They pay 8.25/hour. Training is silly and repetitive. Three different trainers contradict each other. Management is penalty based not reward based. My manager literally screamed at me accusing me of lying. I would have to wait for his tirades to end to be able to calmly explain my question or customer situation. My manager was unprofessional and almost illiterate when sending email.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't hire illiterate young people for management that can't handle the pressure and hate their jobs. Teach managers to have fun and give positive reinforcement.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Joke of a company, but the service they offer is a necessity to the public”

</title><pros>Pros – Ample amounts of customer service experience.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay, no guaranteed pay increases, 1 full time employee per store, other staff work a maximum of 25 hours in an attempt to avoid the Affordable Care Act, significantly more responsibilities than your job title will describe(cleaning, auto and building repair, forklift operation, etc) zero support from upper management other than getting your job threatened every day over technicalities.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Show some loyalty to your staff in the form of full time work or decent wages and you'll attract more competent and devoted applicants. The cost in health care can't possibly be more than training someone new every 6 months and paying for the last person's unemployment for ~2 years.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good work experience with this company”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefitsProfessional environmentPlenty of supplies and materials</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bad organizationLack of oversight by higher managementpoor communication between departments</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“All depends on your General Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – I had a great experience because I had a great general manager. He understood that we did our job when we needed to, so when it got slow, he let us do our own thing. I would have HATED this job if he had not been as great as he was</pros>
<cons>Cons – HOTTTT! Working outside/inside in the summer in FL is never fun! The pay isn't the greatest, but its money so can't complain.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Everything was great</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“it has its ups and down.”

</title><pros>Pros – great customer service experiencegood knowledge of trailer wiringlearn how to multitaskyour handed a lot of responsibility</pros>
<cons>Cons – work by yourself a lotpromotion through the company is a little difficult</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – u haul is a house hold name. the trucks market themselves. dont worry about the small minor things. ie displays and how each equipment has to face.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent income as a dealer”

</title><pros>Pros – No franchising fees, sport from uhaul corporate</pros>
<cons>Cons – Small commissions and issues with reservation software</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep a closer eye on area field managers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Customer demanding”

</title><pros>Pros – If you like the outdoors this is the job for you.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Way too many to list with a 20 word min.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Should atleast give out raises once a year for improving store numbers. Give credit were credit is due.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-22</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Uhaul is a good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – stable company/ good benefits package</pros>
<cons>Cons – The customers are in a league of their own</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Center Sales and Reservations WFH (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Calls, calls and calls.”

</title><pros>Pros – Very flexible work hours especially in the winter months.Summer hours 20-40 hours per week.Winter hours 10- 20 hours per week.Reps are required to get 2.25 reservation per hour and if you fallow their rules it's easy to do.Management does anything they can to help. Always nice and respectful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some customers can be vary rude and policy's change at time with for communication and notice.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people to work with..  people with tons of years working at the company.. benefits are ok.</pros>
<cons>Cons – not so good pay for many positions</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“way too much work too little reward”

</title><pros>Pros – people at the store level are great but are way under paid expexed to do full time work and comitment  while only getting part time hours and min wage</pros>
<cons>Cons – no direction once you are "trained" they ecpect you to treat this as your business but wont pay you what you are worth</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – listen to your fornt line emploiees  they know what is going on</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>E-Sales & Reservation Agent (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Underwhelming”

</title><pros>Pros – Choose your hours, bonuses are available</pros>
<cons>Cons – bonuses are easy to lose, no benefits, part time only.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in people, fulltime employees will be happier.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible hours, tons of advancement opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – non that I know of</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Customer Service Representative”

</title><pros>Pros – None so far,  its a job. Coworkers seem ok.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay for the work expected.  Bad hours, no benefits, no breaks</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible Company, exploits workers”

</title><pros>Pros – it is a paying job, somewhat flexible hours, tons of training, great if you love the colors orange and brown, not stuck at a desk all day</pros>
<cons>Cons – there are no raises (at least not in our region) employees that have been there for years at paid as much as new hires, they will make you make bank deposits off the clock and you will not be compensated for it, pay is barely above minimum wage, they will sell you a health care package you will later find out is "not health insurance" and you will be stuck paying for it for a year, they claim to be a green company but they totally are not (tons of waste, no recycling trucks get very bad gas mileage), no matter how good you do it will never satisfy upper management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Reward experience, if you expect more out of certain employees then pay them more, currently there is no motivation for veteran employees to try harder. Stop telling call center agents to act like there are in a location that they aren't it frustrates both customers and CSR's. Pay your employees to make bank deposits not only is it unethical but it's illegal.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-14</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This company treats hard workers like garbage. Hot garbage.”

</title><pros>Pros – There are no pros about this company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay, management needs to be trained.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay you're employees. Notice good workers. Give reviews as policy shows.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tax Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't work here at all costs; poor benefits, low pay”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people to work with, made many friends there, the company did put on a giant summer party with good food, beer, games and sports.  But it stopped doing it..</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very poorly managed, corruption, the family that owns the majority of the company (Shoens) fought constantly.  There used to be endless memos that came through daily from the founder of the company, a lot of which would degrade employees.  The company had dozens of lawsuits at anytime because they didn't maintain their equipment and it was dangerous</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hell, sell the company, someone can come in, provide good customer service and provide safe vehicles. They need a massive overhaul of their reservation system, people would reserve their needed equipment, then the day they would go to pick it up, the equipment, it was there.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hard work and dedication will pay off!”

</title><pros>Pros – Working for U-Haul has been a great experience, they treat their employees well and want you to learn all you can about the business. If you ask questions and get involved you an learn a lot about a company that's been the leader in the industry for almost 75 years. I've dedicated a lot of my time to this company over the past 7 years and I feel like I have gained more real business experience than anyone else my age. This is not a place to work if you want to show up at 8AM just your job and leave 5PM, you'll never advance. Our CEO, Joe Shoen, works harder than anyone I've ever met, he's a great example for young professionals. Hard work and dedication to making the customer's experience better is part of our company culture.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I could leave tomorrow and do the same job, probably work less hours and make more money, but I probably wouldn't have the opportunities and exposure to the business that I do at U-Haul.  I have plenty of time to make more money, the business experience I've gained here is invaluable.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Always make sure everyone you have on your team is there to support the customer and other team members.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Relaxed work environment, low pay”

</title><pros>Pros – Relaxed work environment, low stress, tuition reimbursement, give opportunities for people with no degree</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay, no advancement opportunities. Does not make effect to retain talented people, prefer to hire mediocre</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please make an effect to retain talented people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Customer Service Rep.”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible hours and schedule are really nice.  There is generally a lot of down time in the winter, which can be used however you please.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is a lot of hard physical work and mentally the customers can be difficult to deal with.  Customers will take out their frustration on you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Area Field Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Family feel; in Corporate America”

</title><pros>Pros – The training and ability to grow within U-Haul is limitless.  Once you are part of the family; they like to promote from within.  Their benefit package is beyond belief and is structured to take care of you and your family.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As an Area Field Manager the expectations to add more and more Independent U-Haul Authorized dealers becomes canibalistic to the current dealers in a small area.  You also have to combat Village and County ordinances with absolutely no help except from a sustainability packet; someone in Arizona will email it to you.  If you have a degree in Real Estate Law or Politics, then you will be fine.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible Management”

</title><pros>Pros – relaxed, variety of tasks, good co workers and getting to interact with a lot of different people. Learned a few new skills, raises every few months and able to keep busy with things that needed to be done around the business.</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad higher management, bad communication. Nothing was ever correct between management and corporate management. Never knew what the correct policies were, because store management would say one thing, then corporate would say another.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – better communication!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“More done with fewer people at lower wages”

</title><pros>Pros – Work with good people. All U-Haul employees are smart, hardworking and enthusiastic about their jobs. Access to U-Haul equipment at discount prices, sometimes free. You'll learn a lot about trucks, trailers and the moving business. Get experience driving a forklift and dispensing propane. U-Haul definitely looks good on a resume.</pros>
<cons>Cons – High turnover while the bad get weeded out. if you're one of the good ones its not uncommon to get stuck working by yourself for 12 hours. Depending on location, stores profit goals can be unreasonable. If store is not profitable, you'll never see more than $8 an hour. Full time means you work 60+ hours a week at $9-$10 an hour equivalent salary.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Rule by respect, not fear. Treat your golden boys and girls like gold, not like replaceable cogs. Don't rely on someone behind a desk who has never worked at a center to tell you how a center should be run.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not the best”

</title><pros>Pros – Work outside, good training in customer service, learn general knowledge about trucks and vehicles in general, basic sales knowledge.</pros>
<cons>Cons – high stress environment for extremely low pay, no real room for advancement, no benefits with part time (all employees except management classified as part time), only holiday off is Christmas Day</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – treat your employees with more respect, we may not do that much in the grand scheme of things but without us you dont have a business, with one word we can turn customers to the competition, we deserve what we've earned</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its a job .”

</title><pros>Pros – keeps you busy, something new every day.</pros>
<cons>Cons – dealing with the public isnt allways fun.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more company employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stressful, but potential to move up.”

</title><pros>Pros – - Plenty of training opportunities- Ability to transfer- Ability to move up over time</pros>
<cons>Cons – - High-stress environment- Some quotas- Logistics are not the bext- High turnover</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve the quality control for all rental trucks. Simply checking fluids will not do in all cases.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Forget having any life outside of work”

</title><pros>Pros – Lot of customers are really fun to deal with and have a good conversations with. I really enjoy the work itself it is not a bad job just stress and trying to learn a lot of things.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The manager I have is very disrespectful, and always talks down to me reminds me of mistakes i made that are not relevant. Also tells me all other managers are worse than he is. I am sure there are decent managers out there at U-Haul and other companies but have yet to see them. Tells me the days I have off and I make plans on those days and always have to break them because he always calls me in. It is like I have to wait by the phone like a dog just waiting to hear or seeing a text message.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please when you hire managers make sure to follow up with the employees to work under them on how they feel of their treatment.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>E-Sales & Reservation Agent (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Okay if desperate, NOT a career”

</title><pros>Pros – I've made some good friends at U-Haul among my fellow coworkers. The pay during the summer can be VERY good. When you're actually able to help a customer, it can be very good. The dental coverage for part-time workers is pretty good; especially since many other employers offer NO benefits to their part-time employees.If you happen to work in "the towers" (headquarters in Phoenix), or have to go in there for the training period, they have a very good cafe. Subway is across the street, but the cafe offers a very nice selection of food and beverages for decent prices. The coffee, especially, is very good.There are many discounts on things, including a 20% employee discount on U-Haul products. There are also discounts on Apple products (even though we can't use Apple computers), Ford & GMC vehicles and other things.In addition, U-Haul has its own credit union, which offers $500 quick cash signature loans to just about anyone whose been employed for 6 months or more. This can actually be a decent way to improve your credit score.Scheduling flexibility is very good as well. In most teams, it's VERY easy to swap shifts or give up shifts. As long as someone else takes  your shift, you are fine and won't get a mark on your record. However, when people are scheduled for 40-45 hours already, it can be difficult to find someone to cover your shift.If all you want is a temporary summer job or a job while you find a "real" job, this isn't a bad deal.</pros>
<cons>Cons – During summer, the hours are very long and grueling. You may get scheduled for a 2 or 3 hour day, then 4 ten-hour shifts. During this time, customers are especially antsy and angry because there simply isn't enough equipment available for everyone who's decided to move at the last minute. There is simply no time to breathe and management is very little help. Maybe there's not enough management, but getting answers to a frustrated customer's queries can take 5-10 minutes. If you're trying to get ahold of the customer's local branch for them, forget about it. Not happening. This just makes the customers even more irate.Failures at the centers are often blamed on "the call center", whether or not that's actually true. "The call center" has absolutely no control over what equipment breaks down or isn't returned, which is how most locations end up being short of equipment to rent out. Be prepared for a LOT of customers hanging up on you if they suspect that you're not actually IN Bangor, ME or Burbank, CA or wherever they're calling from.It doesn't help that many trainees are turned out on the unsuspecting public wholly unprepared. It's definitely unrealistic to expect that training will cover EVERYTHING, but every training class gets told different things. Some people had no idea how to look up certain types of reservations, some didn't know what our bonus structure was like, some weren't told important details about hitch or U-Box reservations. It's a mess.Things get less hectic after Labor Day, but then you also get much fewer hours. Some coworkers are already getting 2 hours scheduled per week, which isn't a living wage. But we're still expected to have very open availability. Taking on a second job is quite difficult with this expectation.The bonus structure was recently changed so that you're penalized for there not being any calls. This is not something you can control. Even if you're scheduled for a time when you only get 2 or 3 calls total per hour (which happens for overnight shifts), you're still expected to meet your quota which is based on scheduled and not actual talk time. When I was hired, it was based on talk time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More organization. QA (quality assurance) is worthless if we're not all on the same page. Ask 3 different managers the same question about certain things and you'll get 3 separate and conflicting answers. This is NOT GOOD and DOES NOT help our customers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“HORRIBLE !”

</title><pros>Pros – flexible schedule....there really isnt anything else. Be lucky if you have a great GM</pros>
<cons>Cons – No advancementNo job securityTreated like children</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give your employees a thank you event! Aflac is amazing!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Go in with your eyes open”

</title><pros>Pros – good training with their UHAUL university</pros>
<cons>Cons – 6 day, 55 hour work week.  Management is COLD toward employees... It's like they forgot where they came from once they make it that high.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management style needs to change.  when you require so much from your employees for just mediocre pay, you need to be more engaging in their daily work lives. Not constantly telling them they are not doing everythig right.  There is no pleasing management at UHAUL... Constantly under pressure of losing your job.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working with the public sucks.”

</title><pros>Pros – Wages are competitive for the area.  You are usually always on the go and makes the day go by fairly fast.  You get to do many different things throughout the day so it doesn't feel repetitive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working with the public just plain sucks.  People will whine and complain about everything and they won't understand a single thing about how you operate so you pretty much have to simplify things down into baby terms.  Also getting everything done that needs to be done in a day can be hard at times.  More employees are needed in the summer months.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire more employees during the summer so operations can run smoother.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Housekeeper (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great, Great, Great, Great, Great”

</title><pros>Pros – Always Something To Do Daily</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing, Wouldn't change a thing</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No Comment</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager/Uhaul (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“U-Haul General Management Salary”

</title><pros>Pros – Company pays great with great benefits and stock options after a Year of experience</pros>
<cons>Cons – 60 hours a week 6 days a week for only 39800 yearly salary USD.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-22</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>STARS (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“STARS , Roadside Mechanic”

</title><pros>Pros – Company Vehicle, Good pay, Excellent tools and equipment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working on vehicles outside in heat.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Great people, Great service.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company Poor upper management”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits, good advancement potential, secure futures, growth, transferrable positions, nationwide company</pros>
<cons>Cons – Local upper Management lacking in employee loyalty, highly stressful, employer expects 60 hr wk week, high pressure</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn how to work for your employees and customers. Stay off your pedestal</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“very rigid corporate structure but many undervalued perks”

</title><pros>Pros – fitness, healthy cafeteria, stable environment and close to a lot of lunch places</pros>
<cons>Cons – rigid structure, very tight with money (i.e. limit on paperclips allowed to use in a week)</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-31</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I enjoyed working for U-Haul.”

</title><pros>Pros – My husband was a manager of a storage facility and we lived on-site. We enjoyed the every day work of storage customers and renting equipment such as trucks and trailers as well.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It was hard to get away with both of us working there. But we had some co-workers who were there for a while before we were and could be trusted to run the place efficiently ,so we were fortunate!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upper management has enough problems without my input.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Disrespected, underpaid, all around stressful.”

</title><pros>Pros – The medical, vision, and dental benefits have good coverage. Close to home, 1 mile drive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Constantly disrespected by customers and other employees.  Management cannot have a single meeting without cussing at everyone.  60 hours a week of work but only 40 hours pay.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more professional with your employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Keyholder (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not the best, but it's a job.”

</title><pros>Pros – -There is great job security there.-Room to move up in company pretty likely-Very flexible with scheduling (important because i'm a full time student)-Some employees are passionate about being there and they offer good advice</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Pay is not the best, but it's a pain in the rear to get a raise (worked very hard compared to the average CSR, NEVER showed up late, ALWAYS came in on time, promised a raise twice before, finally got it after 18 months).-Communication is VERY VERY poor. Rules and protocol changes alot with no mention of it from management, so you are kinda left there in the dark.-No breaks whatsoever, even on the weekdays. Really?!?!-As a keyholder (opener/closer: one step below management), I am the punching bag for the management and the MCO. Basically, when there is no manager there, I have to take over. Here is the thing: I cannot properly manage the place. In the system, there are ALOT of things I cannot do, and that require management's approval for even the simplest things, so I have to constantly make phone calls, which makes me look like an idiot in front of co-workers and customers. Co-workers pretty much do whatever they want because I am not a manager. Being only 20 years old doesn't help the situation either. I was not given a raise to become a keyholder, which is complete bull if you ask me. And then, at the end of the night, when my co-workers do not properly close, I get yelled at the next day by management. When I tell the co-workers about it, they shrug it off because I am not a manager. I tell my boss, and he says "If they don't want to do it, then do it yourself". Like I said: PUNCHING BAG.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you want to promote someone, TRULY promote them. (stated above). Breaks should be given out, not asked for. There is nothing wrong with starting out around $8/hr. However, give your good employees raises once and a while, and maybe that will show them that they are actually a part of the team. Schedule meetings with management and employees more often in order to increase communication about the new changes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“uhaul”

</title><pros>Pros – they are flexible with your schedule</pros>
<cons>Cons – hard to advance in the company</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – be prepard</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“it was a short experience,start at the bottom for management postition”

</title><pros>Pros – there is steady work here</pros>
<cons>Cons – there is not a good work home life balance</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – treat employees fair</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Area Field Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Over worked and under paid!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Meeting new people and great co-workers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management thinks they know it all.  All they do is look at reports that analyst sends to them and they think they know the market as well as the people in the field.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – We the people in the field pays your salary.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager Area Field Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Entry level management only.U-Haul is not a good place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – If you are a store manager or an Area Field Manager you feel like you have some independence.Get to know good people.Sundays off.</pros>
<cons>Cons – U-haul is a good place to get Management expirence and move on to another company.You will work long hours,customers are nasty in this business as the reservation department will overbook your store and then you get to deal with the angry customers even though it was not your fault this happened.Stores are understaffed by company payroll so GM has to cover for any understaffing.They give bonuses but they are a joke in most cases and the pay sucks.MCPs rule with an iron fist and they get rid of long term employees for no reason just because they can.I would stay away from this company as they treat employees like slaves and act like they can replace you at any moment with someone better.This is a company that a Union needs to be involved in to secure your job.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat employees better and stop being so cheap on the payroll as the front line managers and CSRs are who make you lots of money and this should be passed on to them.If you dont pay the front line employees they lose money for the company I have seen it first hand.Money is why we go to work and when underpaid and over worked this is a bad combination of unmotivation.U-Haul CEO should wake up and understand understaffing is bad and bonuses should never be paid on cutting much needed payroll.Read the reviews Joe as all the customers say store was understaffed and I thought the customer is always right?Up the GMs`AFMs`and CSR pay and you will make more money as no one wants to work for minimum wage and work like a slave.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Center Sales and Reservations Agent (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Trial in Patience”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent pay, fairly flexible about schedule swaps between employees, the call-center environment is brand-new and nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Ridiculously grueling schedules with long periods of the time on the phone with no break, communication with management regarding requested time off, no-interest in the work (same thing day-in day-out), chained to a desk, rigid about phone talk time (have been disciplined for using the bathroom too often, even if ill), management is uneducated and often unprofessional--sometimes reading e-mails was painful, handling customers who have issues seems to be a low priority--the company is more concerned about getting the reservation even if we are not sure we can get a customer a truck on the day they want it anywhere near where they need it, the scheduling system and reservation system is seriously flawed, pricing systems are seriously flawed, dealing with the aftermath of workers at the centers is a nightmare.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work on your reservations system. Too many people fall through the cracks and there is no priority to those who call early and reserve--they still may get a truck 25 miles away.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>E-Sales & Reservation Agent (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent and legitimate work from home position.”

</title><pros>Pros – Extensive support from management staffTechnical support for at-home issuesGreat training program, covers everythingGood job for short-term (promotions after 6 months)Incredible facilities at headquarters in Phoenix, AZ</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low base payDifficulty picking ideal shiftCan not check email/browse web while workingStrict guidelines and goals for quality assuranceZero-tolerance policy on noise, including outside noise you can't control (sirens, honking horns)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have more social functions to bring in work from home representatives and make them feel like more of a team and a family.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>E-Sales & Reservation Agent (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was fine for the time being, perfect as a transient position between careers.”

</title><pros>Pros – They know they get alot of turnover, and embrace it. I was looking at the job to bridge me between career and school paths; that worked out well and they paid me well for my time. If you are a go-getter then they recognize you for your ambition and reward you well via bonuses.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working in the call center can make you feel less than a pawn at times, which for me was not a great feeling.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Managers never really got in the way, which is the way it should be, and this allows the center to function. Never let this change.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unfair treatment of employees”

</title><pros>Pros – Employees get a discount on truck rental, and a turkey at Thanksgiving.</pros>
<cons>Cons – More concerned with Quantity rather than Quality; parking situation is really bad - sidewalks and lots are in bad shape and not enough lighting to be safe at night.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Better communication with employees, give feedback to new employees, pay should increase to market rates, benefits should be similar to other companies,</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Management (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great”

</title><pros>Pros – working with the people of my comminity</pros>
<cons>Cons – alot of toll on your body</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – work better together</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>7</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Work From Home (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“At least its at home”

</title><pros>Pros – steady paycheck, I get to be at home</pros>
<cons>Cons – technical programs are sub par and work intermittently, when this happens the employee is docked pay and considered absent when company programs do not work properly. To avoid this issue managers suggest you log in to work at least an hour before.Your schedule availability is not relevant on holidays. Nearly impossible to get time off. Minimum wage pay, though ads say at least $10 an hour (everyone starts at this pay, no matter your experience). Bonus is available, but expect to jump through multiple hoops to get it.Docked time on your "availability" (which affects your bonus) if you take your scheduled breaks and lunch. If you receive a break and lunch, even if you work a 10 hour day.Antiquated HR policies such as counting consecutive absences individually. If you are late more than one hour, you are considered absent for the whole day. If you must go into the office to work, it is business attire required. No vacation time or personal time before 2 years. Behind in industry standards for pay, vacation time, medical, and breaks/lunches.Training is more of a suggestion, with very little company consistency to its standards and regulations. Opportunities for advancement are not openly discussed with employees, you need to "find your own way". Employees are discouraged by management from submitting ideas that would improve on company practices and training. Very little support from any management when working with an unknown product or unfamiliar situation, and expect a different answer any time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get real trainers, with real experience. Make consistency with the standards of what customer service tells customers, and what locations actually do. Promote people to QA and SMS who actually have experience and can help reps, so we don't get a different answer every time. Get up to industry standards as far as pay and hr policies go. Stop posting ad's that you pay $14 an hour, only to reveal you only pay minimum wage.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to work for sure</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes the hours required to work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“boring and tedious”

</title><pros>Pros – you get to drive to other uhaul locations and drive the trucks that are picked up back to your location.They work with your schedule.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Boring, Theres rarely any promotion except when a former manager resigns. Management doesnt care about you because you can be replaced. You work outside all year long.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Web Team Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to Intern”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Work EnvironmentFriendly PeopleEase of parking close to buildingManagement is very competent and makes expectations clearOpportunities for advancement within companyWork from home opportunities every week to balance personal life.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Advancements often only include title change but no real pay increaseSenior Executives are distant from what is going on in the companyPeople become complacent and don't strive to adapt</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok , Not long term job.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good experience, friendly employees, lots of work to be done.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible management, co-workers can be lazy at times.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have better management of the employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a great experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – The job itself is pretty easy, installing hitches and working on wiring is easy to learn and fun to do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Uhaul is much more concerned with making money than treating customers fairly, so be prepared to deal with upset customers a lot.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Let customers know that just because they reserved a truck to pick up doesn't mean that they will be able to pick it up at their preferred pick up location, instead of letting them think that they will until the day before their pick up.  That way they won't yell at the customer service reps for your terrible scheduling program.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“renting death traps to the public”

</title><pros>Pros – good money and great bonuses</pros>
<cons>Cons – pushed from upper management to rent all trucks ,,, safe or not</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – if it isnt safe.... park it</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Long day with little to show for it”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy work and very repetitive</pros>
<cons>Cons – Rude customers, no appreciation for what you do</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop treating your employees like morons!! (MCO 791)</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-29</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Welder (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Treated like a robot if work stops for anything feel like you could be fired. bathroom etc.”

</title><pros>Pros – Its a low paying job and in this economy thats something.  They are taking full advantage of the bad economy.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The majority of work is all done by temps.  They will keep a temp who gets no benefits for over six years and longer. Downside is trying to get hired.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire some of the people you have as temps they are the back bone of your company.  Get to know the people who work for you look at there background they could be a great asset to you if you use them in the right way.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-14</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Dock Worker (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I was by myself most of the time, unless I was helping customers retrieve or return the equipment”

</title><pros>Pros – outside is good.  I got to do thing myself.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I felt underappreciated most of the time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – be more respectful to your employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Inbound Sales Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is a grind”

</title><pros>Pros – Good pay rate for entry level position. Hourly + commission.Good new employee training program.Work from home.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Obscure hours and poor middle level management.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Pilot (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good schedule and good airplane to fly</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay needs to be upped to industry standards or better.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Slave Shop”

</title><pros>Pros – the only reason to work for U-Haul is if you need a job but couldn't find one somewhere else.</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad pay, have to deal with difficult customers, managers often do not back you up. creativity and innovation is suppressed as all the customer service reps have to follow a script when answering the phone. no company culture.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – treat your people right</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Okay job, but.”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent benefits for full time employees once you are eligible.U-haul is nationwide so plenty of opportunities to work for U-haul</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low paying job for the work that is expected.Lack of formal training for employees.Management of the company is somewhat old school and stereotypical, there tends to be the idea that females belong in certain rolls within the company and males belong in others.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay people better or lighten the workload some how. Also come up with some type of formal training program for general managers</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“entry level position”

</title><pros>Pros – They have a lot of locations all over the country.</pros>
<cons>Cons – To start out the pay is low how ever if you are smart enough you can advance and work your way up.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to provide more stability for employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“SOLID internship!!”

</title><pros>Pros – very good pay. Exceptional work opportunity. I had the opportunity to work with top level management while in college and learned alot about working in the corporation.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the work could be more defined. I had alot of projects that I had to complete without a definite timeline.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Very supportive of interns. I had the chance to work with very bright individuals who helped me learn everything there is to know.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Friendly co workers, and a few groups of bad customers”

</title><pros>Pros – you get to learn how to drive trucks</pros>
<cons>Cons – can get very very hectic with little amount of help</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hard Work good friends poor pay”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun environment great friends fun work</pros>
<cons>Cons – No future overlooked for promotion</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Promote those who work not those who complain</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Always something to do”

</title><pros>Pros – Meeting lots of different people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Dealing with frustrated people, after having done their move.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>French Center Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Flexible hours, work from home respecable bonus system”

</title><pros>Pros – Working from home, good bonus system</pros>
<cons>Cons – Strict rules when giving part-time working availability. Besides that, no complaints</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing your job and being understanding of attendance mishaps</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great entry level management experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Hard work gives u an advantage when going to another company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Life changing! Intense hours! Advancement is not promised!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upper management should take more time to understand the operations of each store.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-14</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dishonest practices / Rip-off”

</title><pros>Pros – Their automated phone system only makes you go through 3 menus instead of the usual 6 most companies make you wait through</pros>
<cons>Cons – They rip off customers who don't ask the right questions and the prices shown on the website when you book are not the prices you pay, but they only show that at the end.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – U-Haul asks if you need a truck for 4 hours.  If you say "Yes" you get charged the same as if you said "No", except you might then get charge "EXTRA" if you miss the 4 hour mark.This is a shell game.    Hey U-Haul - don't ask customers if they only need a rental for 4 hours without telling them they don't save anything and should just say no in order to avoid paying you extra money for no reason.I don't do business with companies that pull this sort of crap.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A company that values mediocrity”

</title><pros>Pros – Pretty hands off management.  They don't micro manage.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay, out dated computer program.  Too cheap to use MS office software.  Insist on using Open Office.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It's 2012 try to keep up.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“One of many long term short-timers”

</title><pros>Pros – Clearly presented company policies and programs in place for each aspect and function within the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay scale does not seem to attract talented people, minimal room for growth.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager/Uhaul (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Satisfying job !!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexibility with your work schedule</pros>
<cons>Cons – It requires an extended amount of hours when you become a new GM in order to get a store running smoothly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be fair with with employees, and give reviews</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is an OK temporary job.”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent pay for a temporary position.  They are normally flexible with hours, and you can work a lot of hours if desired.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You are renting out poor equiptment, therefore you deal with a lot of angry customers.  Also, I disliked there strict script, because customers responded to it poorly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Relax a little on the script, and have more faith in your staff.  If you hire the right people, they will do a much better job selling</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>E-Hotline Agent (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My experience was fair and training was minimal.”

</title><pros>Pros – You can work from home.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The shifts vary each week.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management needs to provide standard shifts to accommodate employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A learning experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits, great people, learning tools made available to all employees. I love the company, most of the upper management, and my job in general.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Customers can be very demanding and sometimes outright rude.  It really requires a certain person to work for the company.  You have to be very patient and be able to handle screaming customers professionally.  I feel many of the positions are under paid.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – In promotions, it would be great if women were considered more.  It seems this is a male dominated company and "special positions" are created so that the company satisfies that requirement.  However, those positions never pay the same and don't get the same recognition.  An ironic fact--the largest percentage of our customer base is women.  I have also seen too many people looked over for promotions that have the potential.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – many different tasks to do, you always can find something to work on, diverse people, knowledge of many things that you must learn</pros>
<cons>Cons – working alone on busy days, working outside in bad weather, heavy lifting, communication between management and employees isn't very good sometimes</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – communication must be better, some security procedures should be changed to protect employees, management needs a better sense of what is really going on</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“U-Haul is a terribly managed company with no respect to lower level employees.”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy work if you don't mind being yelled at by customers all day. As long as you show up to work you will not be fired. Seems as if they promote within the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay. Always working weekends. No respect given to you. Full time benefits are an embarrassment. OK for a temporary job, but keep looking.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work on making customer service more efficient. Make your terms more well know to the customers so they aren't shocked when they are not actually GUARANTEED equipment.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company, old ways”

</title><pros>Pros – This is a long known company with great internal advancement opportunities for all employees.  They are always open positions nationwide</pros>
<cons>Cons – Old ways times a million.  Technology advances yet computers in their stores remain seven years old,  they say help customers faster but when you wait literally a minute for pages to load and then managers just say there isn't anything we can do, they refuse to upgrade</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Step into the twenty first century.  A new computer costs $500. Think about if you could help a customer one minute faster. After a month you'd save literally $100 per store. ROI would be five months.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No planning, no rush”

</title><pros>Pros – Working at U-Haul is a liitle different. You have a lot of freedom, no one is micromanaging you or looking over your shoulder. Easy to get time off. Pretty good benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – does not pay as well as other companies. Low pressure environment sometimes breeds apathy. No long term planning. Not much room for advancement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management needs to do more long term planning. Try to instill a little more enthusiasm in the workplace. Implement some timelines and deadlines to get things done and to light a fire under some people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Reservations Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Laid back atmosphere”

</title><pros>Pros – Laid back office atmosphereEmployees are great to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Call centerNot much room for status(position growth) with companyNo bonuses are given to those who deserve them</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Bonuses should still be given if one department is entitled to one, then all should be entitled.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Area Field Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sounds great but the manager dosnt give any support”

</title><pros>Pros – The company has excellent benefits that's the reason I went to work for them. And the position sounds to be a great job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The management style is horrible there is absolutely no support given and orders are pushed down threw another employee instead of the boss handling it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Uhaul needs to open their eyes and figure out  way my area has such a high turn over and look at the man that should be running the show and not doing his job correctly</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“lots of work”

</title><pros>Pros – steady paycheck - good employees if you hire the right people</pros>
<cons>Cons – too many hours for the pay</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay your managers more - hire people with college degrees - then pay them well to keep them and your company will profit more</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall a good company to work for...”

</title><pros>Pros – Their benefits are very good, with a great medical plan.  They tend to be rather family first -- although that is dependent overall on local management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They, like most of the corporate universe tend to take a "your lucky to have this job, now get back to work" attitude.  They are very "right to work" orientated; what have you done for me lately...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager/Uhaul (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok, but lot of work”

</title><pros>Pros – work outside, stay very busy</pros>
<cons>Cons – pay so, so. could be better</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Thrown to the wolves to handle diverse situations and learn some valuable professional skills, but management sucks”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to learn a lot of professional skills to carry to a worthwhile employer</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is corrupt and will tell you incorrect procedures to benfit them</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop stealing and pointing the finger at your employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good temporary job”

</title><pros>Pros – Very reasonable with schedulingWork isnt that difficultReasonable break timesFriendly environmentAverage discountSlow during the middle of the month</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unruly customersIrate customersToo many calls during beginning and end of monthsAlso very busy during school starting and ending</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It would be nice to add more people to the staff, the amount of calls and representatives becomes very overwhelming.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work here if you have to, but keep looking for other jobs”

</title><pros>Pros – You will get some pretty crazy stories from dealing with customers.Co Workers are usually pretty cool.No short of hours to be given</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay is miserable.  (They would rather have a high turnover rate with employees then pay them what they're worth).Long, long days with no lunch breaks.Half of the customers are pretty decent, but the other half is probably about the worst around.Working 7 days straight isn't uncommon around here.It's very corporate.You will work full time hours with part time benefits (i.e. nothing).Upper management expects you to be able to do everything by yourself or at best with one other person (Dispatch trucks, receive trucks, fill propane, install hitches, troubleshoot customer problems, repair our broken equipment, to periodic inspections before they come overdue, and more in just one days work).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Happy employees do in fact make happy customers.  So make the employees happy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Okay”

</title><pros>Pros – Can make your own schedule</pros>
<cons>Cons – 55 - 60 hour work weeks with low pay for the position</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay employess for the hours they are actually putting in</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Office Clerk (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its ok...”

</title><pros>Pros – It wasn't a bad place to work, due to the people I worked for were laid back and really nice. Benefits package wasn't bad</pros>
<cons>Cons – there was no room for advancement in my position and the pay wasn't really up to par for my job description.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They should give more feedback to employees on their performance and conduct reviews to allow employees to know how they are doing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>