<name>Square D Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Square-D-Reviews-E238367.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-05-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Meaningful work in a place where both results and relationships are important.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great opportunity to work across businesses, changing functions, and building networks and a diverse work experience.  Culture of respect and collaboration.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Things don't always move fast; compensation is average.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company”

</title><pros>Pros – Good growth opportunity for all!</pros>
<cons>Cons – they are no cons to this company</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Executive (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Square D”

</title><pros>Pros – Professional mangement with integrity.  Opportunity to move up within the company as they typically promote from within the organization.  Good feedback and support from managment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes the course of action by managment is too conservative without consideration of creative means of accomplishing the end result.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The advice would consist of gaining momentum within the organization to think "out of the box" at times.  Not necessarily a wholesale change in style, but lettting in a little outside influence.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Assembly Technician”

</title><pros>Pros – The best thing about Square D was the amount of pay versus the amount of work required.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much indifference to personnel.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Look @ the little people before making major decisions</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overview of working at Square D”

</title><pros>Pros – Great products, industry leader.  Big company worldwide.  People with great knowledge.  Some handicaps in the empowerment of people.  Good working environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is hard sometimes to get recognized due to the lot of people that works there.  Must work on an appropiate balance scorecard</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Promote your people.  Give them more empowerment.  Strategy of the company should be well know by all of their employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Square D is a good place”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Training and has good locations.  Most Manager's are progressive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Didn't consider the family implications when requiring relocations</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You used to be more compassionate to employees about their family issues.  The french connection eroded that.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“SQD/Schneider Electric was a solid employer”

</title><pros>Pros – Supportive manager, and solid benefits.  Great exposure to a wide breadth of people and products.  Lots of directions to take with one's career.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Heavily matrixed organization with an identity complex.  Numerous divisions of Schneider Electric are functioning independently and without synergies.  Poor onboarding experience.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I enjoyed my time at Square D and hear many concerns over the recent RIFs.  Don't cut it too far back or SQD will become one of the undesireable places to work.  Provide opportunities for cross-functional advancement.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Executive Sales Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – They promote within the company</pros>
<cons>Cons – They need to focus on employee morale. They recently went through many layoffs that effected the performance of existing employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – When you execute layoffs, you need to improve morale.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>