<name>R/GA Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/R-GA-Reviews-E23929.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good tech, too much turnover in other departments”

</title><pros>Pros – Very low turnover in the technology makes for a high quality core of people to work with over many years. Lots of room for self-starters to lead new internal initiatives.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Producers rarely last more than a year, leading to frequent management changes in the middle of projects. This leads to more work for everybody.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give producers the support they need to succeed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“R/GA is what you make of it”

</title><pros>Pros – Super-talented and hard-working co-workers.As a producer, you have wide latitude and autonomy to build the business.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work/life balance can be a struggle.The location of the offices in Hell's Kitchen leaves a bit to be desired.  Would be great to be downtown.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Producer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work, lots of flexibility and autonomy”

</title><pros>Pros – As a producer, you have complete ownership of your projects and your relationship with your clients. People are generally smart and engaged.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The content of the work can be dull.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart people, exciting work, entrepreneurial.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Growing pains, can be reactionary.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Think about executive development</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Office”

</title><pros>Pros – Great culture, amazing co-workers, super talented individuals. The office is growing and the work we do for our clients is some of the most innovative that I have seen.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Since it is a small office with some newer people, more social events or parties would be great.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to mentor junior talent and recognize people for their achievements.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Producer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to learn the ropes”

</title><pros>Pros – Great culture, awesome talent. There's a very strong work ethic that is inspiring, even if it does mean long hours sometimes.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Experience varies very much from account to account. Some are great, others not so much. And it can be tough to switch between accounts.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Planner (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A place to pay your dues and get experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – I worked with with some really smart people and on worked some interesting projects.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I was low-balled with salary and sometimes got lost in the shuffle.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value the people that work for you. They're hungry and want to do great work, but they can become disillusioned if their wonderful performance doesn't lead to better opportunities.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-25</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Digital Agency with talented, humble, and hard working people”

</title><pros>Pros – People and mentoring program at r/ga is great. especially for jr and middle level</pros>
<cons>Cons – late hours is the biggest con. but it is expected since its an advertising digital agency. its not like you are the only one pulling over time. everyone in your team does if it happens.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The pay's OK, the politics aren't”

</title><pros>Pros – You may work with some great people you can learn a lot from - depending on the account.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Engineers are chattel here. The company recently expanded, way too fast, and radically reorganized, and the results are internecine warfare.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Most of you should be fired for incompetence. The rest of you, ditch the ridiculous new group structure and stop chasing away your best and brightest by treating them like dirt.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Creative Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Probably the best digital shop”

</title><pros>Pros – Great creative lead, very respectful and intelligent</pros>
<cons>Cons – R/GA became to big, sometime the bureaucracy is killing the creativity.  Outside of the main building, the office space is depressing,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in good furniture and proper lighting, hire a good architecture firm. Invest in a creative lab type of project, where a proper culture can actually grow outside of the day to day client work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Interaction Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Top talent with rewarding work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Diverse clients, and rewarding work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are no cons that are applicable.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There is no advice that applies.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Visual Design (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great name and reputation, undervalued emplyees”

</title><pros>Pros – Great name and reputation, and they do churn out a lot of interesting, award-winning projects. R/GA is a great name to have on your resume</pros>
<cons>Cons – R/GA has gotten too large for its own good. It makes you feel like a tiny, expendable cog in a huge system. This has also made it hard for people to reach out to higher management to discuss anything related to your career or other matters. It definitely got clunky. For instance, you could get stuck on a boring account for years and it would be very hard to get yourself heard and moved to a different account to keep learning and growing. That can take its toll on your portfolio, as well.Office space is quite nondescript and depressing, and there is very little sense of integration and community, despite the open layout. Mostly people silently starting and their computer screens.It is also incredibly difficult to get promoted, or even get a raise. I have worked there for 5 years without a single actual raise worth speaking of, even when I got a change in title.  And I know many people around me who are in the same position—many of which are resigning or looking forward to do so. This phenomenon has more to do with office politics than the work of their employees. I have done my share of 60+ hour weeks and weekends and felt very little acknowledgment or appreciation—and forget about time or monetary compensation. They definitely need to work harder to make their employees feel valued and have their efforts and dedication acknowledged.On a similar note, there is very little mentorship, coaching or guidance. Many times, I felt like I was being left to my own devices or out of the loop altogether, with very little knowledge of what's going on internally or with the client.Oh, and people with big egos abound and can make your experience there really, really miserable.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Creative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lacks leadership and talent management”

</title><pros>Pros – Thirsty Thursdays and biweekly staff breakfast. Snacks, fruit and soft drinks</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low energy and moraleManagers that are lazy and don't provide mentorship, no investments in or desire to develop talent - this is across all departmentsLack of energy/enthusiasm from senior level managersLack of exciting work. Mostly digital banners, barely any mobile or social. Lackluster work that doesn't win any awards, led by ECD's that are clueless about digital (they come from traditional/branding)Long hours. Lack of time management leads to long nights and weekends which burn out the team and have caused many to leave in less than 6 months</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Fire the senior managers and start fresh with a new team that's vested in the agency and talent</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great agency to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – I love the people I work with - so creative and collaborative.</pros>
<cons>Cons – work/life balance is rough. I work incredibly late hours for a position that's non-billable. I would appreciate more support around the benefits as well - lots that's offered, but no support to partake in anything.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It's inevitable - please accept we are moving forward and allow the new departments to have input.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Interaction Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Big agency with great opportunities”

</title><pros>Pros – a lot of new ideas, focused heavy on interaction design</pros>
<cons>Cons – sometimes stressful, people is a bit impersonal but overall it was a good experience</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interns are a path to greatness or unemployment”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart people, interesting accounts. Lot's to learn</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not much in terms of culture.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Either have a path for internship programs or don't bring on interns.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“SF office needs to turn it around”

</title><pros>Pros – Located right on South Park, a great place for lunch outside and fresh airAT&T ballpark is a few blocks away</pros>
<cons>Cons – Senior management is in its own bubble and does not provide enough communication or direction to the rest of the staff. It's dominated by men and women barely have a senior presence in this office.There's no emphasis on mentorship which leads to consistently high turn over, dissatisfaction and low morale. Managers are not doing a good job of managing and growing the careers of those they are responsible for.There's no recognition or compensation despite the long hours, nights and weekends spent to deliver excellent work. The staff feels unappreciated and unrecognized, and while senior management is aware of this, nothing has been done to address it.Those that tried to inject fun, culture and life into this oddly quiet office are quickly discouraged, shut down or pushed out.The vibe is weird, you sense there's something wrong, but can't exactly put your finger on it until you've started working here. Do not work here if you want a career in digital advertising. Work here if all you want to do is create banners that nobody clicks on.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take some management courses and learn how to effectively manage and communicate with people. You are rock stars on your own, but terrible when it comes to managing talent - you need to invest in learning how to manage talent at all levels.Be more energetic and enthusiastic in order to motivate and excite people. Your lack of energy is disappointing and uninspiring. Stop treating it like a job that pays the bills and start showing some passion in your work.Socialize and hang out with the rest of the staff in order to get to know them</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Flash Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company!”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits, great culture, helpful people, superb environment for learning</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some work can be boring</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“widely known company”

</title><pros>Pros – It is both agency and production company which is pretty rare. you get to work with creative people creating ideas and at the same time, you make some nice visual projects. It is very big and everything is very well organized.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The quality of the project is some what limited because the digital studio is not really big enough to produce some fine projects.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Management Supervisor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for your resume, bad otherwise”

</title><pros>Pros – This job did wonders for my resume, and certainly helped me expand my digital experience.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Dreadful upper management.Jumbled system for handling creative.  Very little accountability regarding deadlines.No opportunities to work outside of the brand you were hired for.If I hadn't been tied to a one-year contract, I would have left much sooner.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Streamline the workflow and provide more council to middle management about their career paths within the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Interaction Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“To be or not to be a rockstar”

</title><pros>Pros – The projects were interesting , processess are well defined and the good reputation of the agency is great for your portfolio.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working with rockstars that think they know it all. Not friendly environment to work with.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of great people; but company culture stifles opportunities for growth”

</title><pros>Pros – A lot of smart, very hard-working people. A few very cool projects that you'll be lucky to work on.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Highly process-oriented. Monolithic creative culture.  Lots of bureaucracy.  Feels big and disconnected with little sense of direction or mission communicated to the lower ranks.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try harder to inspire your employees.  Try to make work feel like less of a grind, and not with token gestures.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Producer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cutting Edge Digital Shop”

</title><pros>Pros – Great sense of community across accounts.  Weekly meetings give disciplines a chance to review accounts from other brands.  Ideas are welcomed by any level employee.  A great shop for anyone with an entrepreneurial spirit.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Workload can be heavy, but I personally like that.  Definitely a shop where you're not going to find yourself sitting at your desk bored.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – R/GA will always be a prestigious agency and I am honored to h ave had the chance to work there.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Interaction Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A daily grind that taught me some things but ultimately I was happy to leave behind”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a great shop to learn about the industry as some amazing people end up there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you're mid career it doesn't have the best opportunities and the amazing people don't stay. Retention isn't R/GA's biggest goal.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Friendly environment and ton of smart and creative people. Strong leadership”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting and challenging projects. Startup-like environment. Creativity is welcomed and encouraged</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some projects might be stressful. Fast-pacing projects might not be for everyone</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You do care about the people that work here. You do promote health workplace. Keep it up. Think about how to lower the turnover rate which is high for the agencies like this</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Planner (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ahead of the curve”

</title><pros>Pros – Intelligent people, collaborative, motivated - surrounded by people who want to make a difference.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Culture of "who can stay the latest"</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Intense and enriched”

</title><pros>Pros – Intelligent culture passionate about what they do.  Strong management support system.</pros>
<cons>Cons – R/GA way or no way mentality.  Need to evolve new model to adjust to the new world out there.  Too production driven.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create cross departmental exchange.  Balance account services with production, drive stronger conceptual development driving stronger creativity.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Interaction Design Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to learn and grow”

</title><pros>Pros – R/GA strikes a nice balance of company structure and internal chaos. This allows for lots of learning to happen within a supportive environment. If you can prove yourself and do good work, you will get put on the better projects and management will support you. There are so many things going on in so many different areas, that whatever your passion is, they should be able to find you a project that matches your interests</pros>
<cons>Cons – The ramp up time. It takes a while to prove yourself at R/GA and a lot of good people leave because they get frustrated with the more mundane work they are doing.The review process makes it very hard to get promoted anytime except MarchHell's Kitchen</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more open to promoting people when they're ready and have proven themselves, figure out ways to get good people to do exciting work early on in their career.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Interaction Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Smart, creative people. Interesting work. Somewhat chaotic.”

</title><pros>Pros – Incredibly smart and talented people to learn from and work with. Some great clients with interesting project opportunities. Though its big and established now, it still feels like a small company in some ways.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not a great work life balance (ie more work than life). As with most creative jobs, projects can sometimes be unorganized and chaotic.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Producer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Smart people at an innovative agency”

</title><pros>Pros – large agency, breadth of potential experience, great mentors</pros>
<cons>Cons – sometimes easily lost in shuffle</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior CopyWriter (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great company, but used to be nicer”

</title><pros>Pros – A lot of smart, creative people. Unlike other agencies, the producers and account managers don't run the show. The creatives and tech people are valued and respected.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The culture of the company has changed. It's less collaborative, with more politics involved now.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>QA Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people, more process needed”

</title><pros>Pros – - Really talented, dedicated people.  Hard to find someone who is a screw-up.- Salary is on the better side of competitive.- Very relaxed work environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Very little oversight from upper management- Tends to rely on talent rather than good organization, resulting in slightly skilled water treading instead of power swimming.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take a more active role.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Group Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“rga”

</title><pros>Pros – R/GA is full of good people. smart people. It's at the forefront of advertising business.  there's a lot room for growth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the pay isn't what it is elsewhere.  they'll ultimately need to start to compensate better if they want to attract the best talent in the business.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Visual Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't get pigeonholed”

</title><pros>Pros – High salary and great benefits with pretty nice offices. The agency is constantly pitching and winning new business and has a roster of great clients. If you can get on Nike you're career is probably set.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you don't get on Nike you might get stuck doing some really boring work and toiling away on low profile projects. It can be really hard to get anyones attention within the agency and placed on new work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Rotate your designers around more. If there are people with specific niche talents get them to work on all sorts of projects or else they'll go stale. If they've dedicated more than a year to a crappy account or a thankless task, give them what they ask for and put some other poor sap in their place.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior CopyWriter (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A tremendous learning experience but became more about endurance than enjoyment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Really smart people. Great client roster. Leading-edge thinking. Strong in-house tech and studio capabilities. Tremendous emphasis on user experience and interaction design. Probably the best digital agency out there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not a very nurturing environment – very much sink or swim. Long hours encouraged and expected. Egos to match the size of the intellects. More competitive than collaborative. Not the prettiest part of town in which to work. Three separate buildings and "boutique agency" account structure can feel isolating.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Visual Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I love working here.”

</title><pros>Pros – great environment, great people, and great talent</pros>
<cons>Cons – long hours, located in midtown and food around the offices isnt that great.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Producer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Really like the Agency, Simply don't like the pay”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are extremely smart.  I learn something new every day I go into the office.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The low pay and rate of promotions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Many departments are understaffed. Folks (junior & mid-level) are leaving because of pay and sometimes title issues, but primarily pay. Increasing deserving individuals salaries by even a small amount (e.g., $5K) can make a huge difference.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Media Supervisor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun people, good work, terrible hours and quality of life”

</title><pros>Pros – People at R/GA are very enthusiastic about what they do.  For the most part everyone is energetic, passionate and really talented.  The building is also cool.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They will work you until you can't work anymore.  They don't give you recognition or raises until you threaten to quit.  It's also always very dark in the office.  No one believes in lights.  There is also a lot of red tape to go through.  You spend 80% of your day in meetings and every person on the team, usually 30-50 people has to see what you're working on before it can go to the client.  Being a media person in a creative agency like R/GA definitely has it's challenges.  The location of the office is also not the best.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't charge your clients so much, reorganize the agency so that there aren't so many hurdles to put out good work, focus more on quality control and innovation, and show some appreciation for your staff that you make work 60-80 hours a week.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – The people there are great, everyone really seems to enjoy their jobs. There is a nice variety of accounts. This is a very fun environment!</pros>
<cons>Cons – There aren't any cons, this is honestly one of the best agencies to work for.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Creative Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worked hard, learned a lot, but left with very little to show for it.”

</title><pros>Pros – The people – overall, they are talented, smart, and friendly. I didn't run into too many a-holes, which is kind of amazing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The account groups are extremely siloed, and it's quite common to only work on a single account at a time. And you better hope it's the Nike account, because everything else comes second.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If it's really "about the work", then dump the clients that about the money.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Interaction Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very intense but lots of fun and great learning if you want to work in the field of digital agencies.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great clients and colleagues. Sharpest minds and skills being put to the test constantly. Projects vary between long term digital products and services to shorter term campaigns and digital objects. I've learnt a lot by collaborating with the best visual designers, copywriters, developers and other talented people here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Its a lot of hard work and often focussed solely on the development side of work. You'll have to be very lucky to join a project right from the earliest concept phase and see it through till the end.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent Place”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay is good. Benefits are decent. Usually not asked to work insane hours. Lots of perks around the office and at offsite get-togethers. Easy going atmosphere. Managers aren't running around yelling and cursing at people. Produce high quality work. Get to work with major industry leading clients and often cutting edge projects.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A little disorganized at times. Some drama kings/queens who act like life/work is always in crisis. Creative folks can be a bit egotistical and emotional. Enormous focus on selling, selling, selling more work (part of regular agency life I guess). A little too big for their britches, in that many people internally are slow to realize that the rest of the industry is fast catching up to them in competency and quality.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They are already aware of this, but really need to get busy in teaching people/soft skills to managers. Just because people are smart and talented doesn't mean they will be good managers of people. It would most likely cut down on some of the huge turnover in personnel if people were treated better by their direct supervisors.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Visual Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Big and clumsy”

</title><pros>Pros – Big name, Big clients, talented people, decent pay upon coming in</pros>
<cons>Cons – This company is far to big. For all the good things R/GA offers (clients, talent, name) they have a sprinkle  of bad that ruins it. For every talented designer there are 5 that are just competent but have egos that will knock you on your back. Beyond this the organization is AMAZINGLY political and full of drama. Give it a year, give it a month, give it a week in the end you'll see that its just like every other large agency. It'll chew you up and spit you out and leave you with a great name for your resume........</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Appreciate your employees and make sure they can do there jobs with out the excess of BS</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Art Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Smart, talented people are the driving force behind R/GA's success”

</title><pros>Pros – People, commitment to quality work, competitive salaries, range/variety of work</pros>
<cons>Cons – process, too many cooks, experience varies a lot depending on account</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Something In Technology (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Do yourself a favor...research well and think..”

</title><pros>Pros – - Some really creative people to work with.- Benefits not too bad- HR and support functions do their work- You get to work with hi-profile brand names- Good for producers (aka client/business managers) since they are kept on a pedestal unlike any other agency around.</pros>
<cons>Cons – So what are you looking for?- Work/life balance? Well either you will be working like a dog or not working at all.- Great compensation? Very very debatable.- Opportunities for Growth?You will NOT grow on the basis of meritocracy. So you better know how to play politics. Tech. Management is a farce here. Most have grown by not delivering software, infact they don't even know how to write serious code. Atleast you would hope they are good people managers, but alas. Not to mention your managers will run away to save their ass when its decision/support time and let you burn.- Extremely inflated titles?  There would be no respect for you unless you are a Tech Director for eg. Otherwise you are a developer treated like dirt, especially by producers, irrespective of whatever you are called whether junior/senior/lead etc..- Professionalism? Yeah right! You should really find out what kind of derogatory emails one employee would send to another on official mailing lists here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You need a major shakeup. You need to be serious about this being a full service agency. Your focus has only been on creative and production. That works fine on a short term. On longer term don't be surprised if you are run over by the Sapients and the Razorfishes of the world.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work, the people are great, but the shop it totally run by production.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work/life balanceCompensation is good, but negotiate from the beginning, raises aren't greatGood Benefit packagesQuality of people are good, there are some really smart people there, (also balanced out by some not so smart people)Your experience will depend on your account, agency is completely split up by account.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Your experience will totally depend on the account you work on, the agency is totally split by accountThe shop is 100% driven by scopes and production. Which isn't good, b/c you end up arguing with clients about money on a regular basis especially on what work is covered and what isn't for each project. This is a a hold over from the early days when it was a video production shop.The agency is split across 4 buildings on West 39th, and some accounts have it REALLY bad. 333 is a DUMP.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Solid Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – - Great knowledge sharing- Good culture- Positive atmosphere- Coffee bars!</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Work/life balance is not optimal- People advance irrespective to performance- A very, very flawed and self-contradicting review system- Long waits to get replacement hardware</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If they truly care about talent retention, they shouldn't have inconsistencies with their promotional / career advancement structure. They should be honest when challenged.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“R/GA was a roller coaster . Too much work - too little work -”

</title><pros>Pros – R/GA is filled with super smart and nice people . Literally, all of the leads are approachable and cool .</pros>
<cons>Cons – R/GA has become so large and its  practices are so formalized that as a creative you are bucketed into doing the one thing they decide you can do. Once you are tagged its tough to get  out of that bucket.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – find a way to make time sheets easier</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Slightly Disenchanted”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Excellent career boost - add R/GA to your LinkedIn and it will blow up2. A lot of talented, great people3. Great salary and benefits4. Opportunities are present to work on important, portfolio building projects</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. R/GA will make your resume stand out, but if you don't gain the portfolio to back it up...2. A lot of egos and hacks too. Some of the management seems to have become friendly with the right people and move up to where they are today, yet they are horrible managers that are severely outdated. They tend to float on the work that's actually done by the lower level creatives by taking all the credit for it since they provided "direction." It's really sad as the lower level creatives become disenchanted by the whole experience at R/GA, thinking that they busted their butts to get the job (very tough interview process) only to find that they're stuck doing routine, uninspiring work on an account they have no interest in for a manager that they can't even look up to or learn from.3. Ask for the money you want to be making from the start. Don't low-ball yourself, or you will be placed on a low-ball salary track that's hard to break free from.4. The opportunities are present to work on important, portfolio building projects providing you are on the right account. But you have to pick your battles: A) Sign your life away and work on one of the big thinking, award winning, sexy accounts OR B) Choose to have somewhat of a life by working on mundane accounts. It is R/GA and you will have a hard time balancing work/life no matter what account you're on, but you have maybe an 80/20 rather than a 150/0 if you work on the boring accounts as opposed to the exciting accounts.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make more of an effort to ensure your employees are satisfied with the work they're doing and the account they're on, rather than just finding an opening somewhere and sticking anybody in there to fill a gap. Evaluate managers with more scrutiny...sometimes managers take advantage of their lower level employees by taking all the credit for their hard work. Weed out the dinosaurs that manage to coast by and promote the lower level employees who have consistently been doing great, cutting edge work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Strategic Planner (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Uneven”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people to work with. Great place for knowledge sharing and collaboration.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management does not keep their word and does not appropriately compensate its employees. Rides on reputation.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep your word. Acknowledge your employees and compensate them appropriately.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Interaction Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good resume builder”

</title><pros>Pros – I got to work on major brandsappreciation for innovationgreat co-workers -- camaraderie helps when you're all in it together, from late hours to difficult clients</pros>
<cons>Cons – admin and hr are disorganized and takes a lot of reaching out to get what you need</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Rewarding!”

</title><pros>Pros – I love working for a leader that is inspiring and respectful of his employees. I think Bob does a fantastic job running the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The internal processes do not make sense, they could be more efficient and smarter.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The management is fine, from what I've seen so far the leaders are great.  Obviously, there are a few bad apples and I think wrong hiring decisions were made.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Do the time, move on”

</title><pros>Pros – Name recognitionAccess to high ranking individuals client sideGood opportunity to find a mentor when starting outTalented peopleWork here for a little bit and watch your Linkedin blow up. Makes getting the job you really want easier.Good parties</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is no longer a design firm. Most decisions are driven by money and the integrity of everyone's work is suffering as a result.Lots of people competing for limited promotion spots. Senior management however, seems to be adding letters to their titles on a daily basisNot much of a challenge on retainer accounts. They tend to hire really smart people and make them do production work. A lot of creatives burn out quickly due to the assembly line nature of the place.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Promote internally moreFix the place up, the main building is ok, but this is not a creative environmentLet people move around accounts more, so many people are leaving due to burnoutDo something innovativeStop hiding behind the bureaucracy telling us that you can't do things for us because of x y and z</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Agency with very clever people”

</title><pros>Pros – - good clients- great team- intelligent</pros>
<cons>Cons – - bad work space- bad hours- advertizing</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Producer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Satisfied, but demanding more out of management”

</title><pros>Pros – Gifted talent, fun work place, great pay, great perks, great name. You will feel compelled to devote yourself to your team, since everyone works their tail off.Great place to learn how to manage projects with a lean and mean team. Great gut check for those who think they know their stuff. R/GA does a great job of weeding out those who just cant cut it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The work is a little dry since senior management's main goal is getting a larger retainer. Think about it like this - If I am calling the shots on a huge account, it isn't my concern about whether the team is happy with the work, since that isn't how my success is measured, it is more like...How big can we get? How much can we get? What profit can be turned due to running lean?</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Read your incoming employees resume's. Don't think of everyone as a number, or a gap fill. Give people the opportunity to work on projects that will satisfy their need for innovation while you take care of the tactical delivery of what is called for by the clients business.LISTEN!!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Never a dull moment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Fast pace; interesting clients; mostly smart co-workers; entrepreneurial atmosphere; great coffee bar; humor appreciated; great team work; good place to learn a lot fast</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours; often a lack of clear direction from the top; inadequate number of staff often assigned to gargantuan tasks</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Find people for the top spots that actually have experience running a company of this size. Actually walk the office and come see us sometimes; try to know your employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Copywriter (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to learn and grow.”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunities for career advancement & growth.Learn about digital advertising at its best.People are pretty knowledgeable in their respective disciplines.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Digital advertising isn't always cool.  Lots of banner ads and email templates.Every team is completely different.  So moving from one to another is sometimes a culture shock.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep it up.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Producer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“work hard but produce good stuff”

</title><pros>Pros – R/GA provides a chance to work with super talented people and world class clients. They are innovative and emphasize quality of work</pros>
<cons>Cons – the hours can be long, and many of the clients are frustrating.  since r/ga is a great reputation, clients can expect a lot.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – provide more feedback to employees.  manage expectations of clients better and push back when necessary.  monitor morale. and fix phones.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Art Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“i'm learning something new everyday”

</title><pros>Pros – work with really talented folks</pros>
<cons>Cons – only get to work on one account at a time</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – wish i had more mentoring</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Planning Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Diverse, multi-disciplined, yet incredibly collaborative.”

</title><pros>Pros – Lets start with the reasons stated above: it has a fabulous pool of talent: you find people who are just great at thinking, conceiving, and making: simultaneously. And people are very good at understanding what the other person brings to the table. Unlike other agencies where the loudest person gets ahead, R/GA is setup in such a way that the wisest and the most talented have the ability to steer the conversation. To the major extent, I would say that this level of openness and collaboration is inspired by the people at the helm: BG, N-Law, and the leads of the range of disciplines.We have some of the best clients the industry has to offer!The work is consistently good.It keeps attracting great talent.There is a warmth to the agency that you dont find at other places.People are happy, and that says a lot.Every project is approached like a "start-up".</pros>
<cons>Cons – Time is a really really precious commodity at R/GA.Because of the sudden and unexpected growth, the agency culture is taking a bit of a beating.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give people the freedom to create outside the boundaries of business.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good place for go-getters”

</title><pros>Pros – - really good at rewarding hard/persistent workers- good mentoring system- the people are really smart, talented, awesome, and well-rounded</pros>
<cons>Cons – - communication isn't always great- there's a split between system/platform design and the advertising people- there's a lot of talk but not always a lot of action- not creatively driven - very production-led</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – celebrate creative. be less "responsible" and cautious about interesting concepts. less talk, more doing. address agency issues head-on and discuss them internally with everyone before they become bigger problems.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tech Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun job”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun Beer Hard work cheese</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours stressful clients cheese</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work harder</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Visual Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good People, Difficult Advancement”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart, talented, and intelligent people.  Generous vacation time.  Decent benefits package.  High profile client work.  Bike racks and picnic tables in courtyard.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Difficult to advance beyond a certain point.  Difficulty moving around the company (between accounts).  Less than satisfactory salary increases.  Offices near the Port Authority and tourist hotels.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work with your employees to find solutions with the clients rather than sacrifice your employees to meet every whim and demand of the client.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Producer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of hours and responsibility, little pay or recognition”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of responsibility and exposure to complex business problems. Freedom to run your projects as you see fit - no one micro-manages you (or even manages you).</pros>
<cons>Cons – Little pay, tiny raises. Very little support or awareness of what you do day in and day out - unless something goes wrong. Hard to escalate problems and grab the attention of management. Even harder to get help solving problems.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Consider people's skill set and interest before placing them on an account; support the teams that are working long hours day in and day out - not just once a year during their review</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Copywriter (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work, some tough competition”

</title><pros>Pros – The people here are very smart, motivated and talented. If you get on a good account, you'll work with some of the best in the business.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There's a small group of top talent at the top that get to work on the best pitches and projects. It's tough to break in and prove yourself sometimes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Creatives crave change. Although it's good for a client to have a dedicated creative team, it's not great for the creatives themselves. Moving people around more often and diversifying the work would be greatly apriciated.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“headline”

</title><pros>Pros – smart people great use of tech</pros>
<cons>Cons – too much turnover not enough cash</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Presentation Code Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company but some awkward processes”

</title><pros>Pros – R/GA has a very relaxed atmosphere, with great people. Middle to upper management (some at least) are willing to listen and address concerns as necessary. The pay is good, and the roster of clients is impressive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some of the processes can be tiresome, and not as efficient as they could be in this day and age. Also, the company is very design centric, leaving tech with very little say sometimes in the final product.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – To be more flexible and modern (i.e agile) and to promote forward thinking as well as productivity tools and methods/patterns</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Interaction Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“R/GA San Francisco - 360 Degree Design”

</title><pros>Pros – Variety of projects from big to small on variety of subjectsGreat project mobility not to much not too little, every few month ability to participate in something new weather it is brainstorming, researching, sketching, ideation or productionGreat people: smart, international, humble, pleasantSmart and respectful managementWonderful work location</pros>
<cons>Cons – A lot of work is done with the New York office, long distance, time difference and alternative work culture take effort.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – San Francisco management - greatNew York management - be more open minded and have trust</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a bad place to meet some talented people”

</title><pros>Pros – some very talented and smart people, small account teams and little bureaucracy mean you have an opportunity to make a big difference for your account</pros>
<cons>Cons – if you're stuck on a bad account can feel like a sweatshop, quality of work, talent, and mangement on teams is uneven</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – management seems disconnected from the day-to-day life of those who really work in the trenches there</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Flash Programmer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to learn and get coffee”

</title><pros>Pros – The culture tends to be focused much more on getting work done but doesn't get all "serious business" about the work being done.  Fairly casual atmosphere and you can come in past 9 and no one will bat an eye so long as you get your share of work done.  They also have a nice, cheap coffee bar inside the building so you can keep focused on what you're doing and stay caffeinated.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The focus on results tends to also mean that the less monumental achievements get overlooked.  At times there will be situations where producers or non-technical people drop the ball on key issues, and communication between different disciplines/teams in the company can be rather slow or unclear.  Overall, most of these problems aren't too bad but pretty par for the course.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – A greater general technical competence of staff such as analytics, producers, and designers would greatly aid communication and help drive better decision-making throughout the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Some of the smartest people in the business”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a big company but it acts like a small one in that it can change quickly to the marketplace, adding new capabilities and finding the right people to run them.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes a lack of transparency from the senior leadership when it comes to why some policies are implemented. I think it's due to being beholden to IPG...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Understand that most of the people at R/GA are talented enough to find jobs just about anywhere, and though the economy is tough, keeping people happy and secure is a way to make sure everyone STAYS at R/GA once the economy inevitably picks up.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-09-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Flash Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“There's Nike, and then everything else.”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay was good in comparison to most competitors. I know the Nike team is always insane and relatively unpleasant if you want work-life balance. But since I wasn't on Nike, I worked pretty consistent hours.</pros>
<cons>Cons – R/GA isn't a bad place to work but I certainly did not enjoy it. I worked on a non-Nike team and it was a total waste of my time. My manager(s) were fine, but all of my co-workers were definitely incompetent. I was lied to about the work I was going to be doing, I was lied to about my benefits and PTO time. So... very bad HR. They basically told me anything to get me hired on and after a short period of time I decided I needed to work in a more professional, higher caliber office.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop hiring bench warmers. There's no sense in increasing head count when the heads have nothing in them...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Visual Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you have a chance, suck it up and stay there a while. I'tll pay off.”

</title><pros>Pros – R/GA basically propells your carrer like no other place. They just won "Digital Agency of the year" so, just to have R/GA on your resume will help you out a lot in life. And through a number of big clients, it's usually a place that is able like no other to do new and exciting things</pros>
<cons>Cons – Because it is so big, it's a bit hard to manage talend. Everything has to be packed into little boxes, and that might not exploit one's full potential.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Creative people need creative jobs. They can't just be making the same thing all day long</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-02-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“R/GA is a great place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Solid company.  Great clients.  Pushing the envelope.  Interesting projects.  Fairly flexible schedule.  All in all, I like the vibe at R/GA.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes it can get a little too big, and one can feel lost in the shuffle.  I think it's definitely a place where you will likely need to make yourself visible in order to advance.  I also feel like sometimes the projects could be a little more efficiently run.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would say, be sure to examine the efficiency of the projects at hand.  Sometimes, with many people on a project, things can get a little out of hand, causing extra work to be done that is not needed.  Making sure everyone is always on the same page can help mitigate these issues.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-31</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work, but not enough variety.”

</title><pros>Pros – The work environment is quite laid back.  The employees are great.  The work is generally top notch.  Compensation is very fair. Great parties.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Account structure means most people work on only one account at a time, so variety of work is lacking. Somewhat difficult to be promoted from within.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Let more employees help out on pitchwork.  Give employees more flexibility to work outside of their home account.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Copywriter (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Put in your time, build your book and reap the benefits at your next gig”

</title><pros>Pros – From a strictly professional standpoint, if you work at R/GA, especially in a creative capacity, you will have the chance to do great work, build your book, and win some awards.  Also, you'll get to work with truly innovative people that if you are lucky, you will touch base with down the road on bigger and better projects.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you want to have no personal life than work for R/GA.  The hours are crazy, they expect you to commit every fiber of your being, personal life be damned.  A lot of people get burned out and there is a sense of smugness in some of the people there.  If you didn't go to the right school or aren't into the latest, micro-trend you might get looked down on.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide a better environment for personal improvement, everyone can get better with a little guidance, it shouldn't always be sink or swin.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-12-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Producer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“There's R/GA Nike, and then there's the rest of R/GA”

</title><pros>Pros – The work can be interesting and innovative. The people are smart and fun to work with. There's a surprisingly small number of ego-centric jerks, and most people are humble and down to earth.Your checks won't bounce! Get on the right account and you'll fill your resume up with awards.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The  buildings are in really bad shape and the work areas are depressing, dirty and sweat-shop-like. Once you get placed on an account, it's very hard to move. A lot of the work is slogging through very dry, low level pages of corporate websites. Not particularly focused on building memorable consumer experiences.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The company is pretty big but it feels like it's still trying to be run like a small shop.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-11-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A place to learn and develop your skills... if you are self-motivated and has a liberal mindset.”

</title><pros>Pros – Cutting edge projects in the field and a top notch technical team makes R/GA a great place for techies with an art sensibility to develop their skills. The company's technical hierarchy is very flat and the enforcement of positions almost non-existent. That means that you could be doing anything at any time and while most work is related to your core activity, you will be doing a multitude of things in a project - from physics motion development to xml cut and pasting. The work environment is very liberal and people are expected to take responsibility for their work and run with it. There is minimal oversight, but help is always available if sought out.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much freedom does have its drawback. Lack of oversight and loose management generates a lot of extra hours and an extremely high workload. Weekend and/or late night work is pretty much a constant. Work tends to flow without much process and there is quite a bit of confusion on communication and client relations. I repeat another reviewer's comments that because people are expected to take responsibility for a project on their own, when that sometimes doesn't happen, a project can fail just out of owner, or someone has to pick up the extra load to make it happen. In the end of the day, because little oversight doesn't provide good info for management, people get rewarded by perceived instead of real competence - and it is not uncommon for quantity of work gets confused with quality and personal politics to trump excellence on promotions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get information flowing up and down. Don't just expect things to happen and take action to promote communication. Start striving for productivity and optimization instead of brute force to get more of the quality work R/GA is known for out.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Visual Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“R/GA is the cat's meow”

</title><pros>Pros – The talent at R/GA is phenomenal. There are a lot of interesting things happening at once and at times can be a little overwhelming to keep track of things that are happening across the company. It's growing rapidly but isn't  getting out of hand. Kris Kiger, VP of Visual Designer is awesome and very personable as well as all of the other upper management, Creative Directors included.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's a fast paced environment, and sometimes you can get lost in the mix because the company is growing so fast so if you want to expand your career, you have to speak up for yourself and voice your opinions. Also, the company is spread out into three buildings so it's hard to converse and get to know other coworkers outside of your existing team.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I think the Senior Management does a fantastic job in keeping the entire company up to date, so I'm not sure what feedback I have to give. They are very motivating and care for the people who work there. They care about the quality of work, unlike some places I have worked for in the past. It shows through their portfolio and client list.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Flash Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Resign, get rehired with a huge promotion, repeat”

</title><pros>Pros – The work is very interesting and R/GA has many high profile clients. The people are also extremely talented and one of the best things about R/GA is being able to work w/ these people (although I would exclude a good portion of the recent hires from this description). Also, the company compensates people very well as far as salary and health benefits go.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is very little recognition for regular, everyday employees and the tiny bit that exists often times gets directed at the wrong people/person. Also, employees ping pong back and forth between here and other ad agencies. When people quit, you know that you are going to see them working again at R/GA again within a year or so, and that somehow they are going to end up being your boss. Another thing is that the work day can be a very long day indeed, much more than the standard 8 hours.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The work environment is really overcrowded and this problem should be more seriously addressed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Mostly great work and smart people striving for excellence, although sometimes fighting for recognition.”

</title><pros>Pros – Mostly highly creative people and a desire to create excellent work. (As the company has grown, they've been forced to hire less talented individuals across the board.) There are some very, very smart people that can be found there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compared to other companies, management doesn't display much concern for employees. There's a bit of a sense of being a piece of the machine. Additionally, R/GA has many shifting visions of itself and doesn't do a great job of communicating this within the company, or training people to succeed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay more attention to your employees. Set people up for success. Reign in the dysfunctional infighting at a senior mgmt level.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great at work, could be better at business”

</title><pros>Pros – The company has a very flat hierarchy, the team structure on accounts is very much like working a free lance environment.  You are very much responsible for your own time.  The roles of people tend to evolve organically out their specific interests related to their discipline which can be very powerful with a highly proactive group of people together on one team.  The atmosphere is very causal and relaxed no hard hours, you are just expected to get your work done on time and on scope.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The lack of structure can also be a weakness if a group comes together where no one champions the project and if individuals responsible for their discipline do not own their work.  We also seem to have staffing issues, we can never seem to fully staff and account.  There are also issues regarding properly scoping and scheduling projects, rarely is appropriate amounts of time given to programming, although I've seen improvements as of late.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – budget, staff, and schedule better</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“R/GA- full of smart, passionate people!”

</title><pros>Pros – It's exremely innovative,there is a lack of ego compared to most agencies, full of smart/passionate people, and the work is diverse.  It's an entrepreneurial environment that provides individuals with the autonomy to make things happen.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The Agency has grown extremely fast in the past few years which can make for a chaotic environment.  The growth has slowed so there is more process being implemented than in the past.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – R/GA is a fairly flat structure, which can be one of it's greatest strengths, but I would encourage Sr Management to find a way to weave in some layers that allow for more growth.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“R/GA -- an exciting company, a chaotic environment”

</title><pros>Pros – R/GA does great work, win many awards (mostly design and advertizing awards) and does come cutting edge work.They are in a good situaltion which has created job stability and growth.Technically there are oportunites to try many different things.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Because most of the executives never leave, opportunities for growth only appear as new positions appear.Also, there are many postitions (though not all) where people are expected to work unreasonable hours.Often partly due to client expectations partly due to internal culture  project schedules are compressed. Tech, on the end of the schedules is often impacted when creatives can't deliver ontime.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It would be great of Management was more strategic, and communicated and followed though on those stragegies. It often feels like they are reacting, not planning.s\</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Flash Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“R/GA has its weaknesses but it also has potential for extraordinary growth.”

</title><pros>Pros – Compensation and benefits are generous.  The company generally is a good place to work and the people are easy going and friendly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The structure of the company is largely beginning to reflect traditional agency influence.   The atmosphere of the company does not promote strong creative or interactive work.  Advancement is generally time based and ability is not recognized or rewarded.  Personal career development is normally a outside of job activity.  Also people are viewed more as resources and treated as production pipelines rather than organic teams.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I feel the influx of people from traditional agencies is hurting the company greatly.  There is a growing number of employees whose work is not proportionate to their salaries these are usually director level hires who do more management than good work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-01</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Producer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“R/GA”

</title><pros>Pros – Great company, highly innovative, feels like a family.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hours are a bit insane and clients will be taken on before a team is assembled.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Interface Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great team. They hear you, even if you are an intern.”

</title><pros>Pros – Advanced technology and always willing to implement innovative ideas.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working long hours sometimes, but i think thats common.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Nothing much to say.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Talent on the stage. You always find new technologies or new experiences.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Complex to share your work internally.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – ---</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Creative Development Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very solid, learned a ton as an intern”

</title><pros>Pros – Worked with some amazing interaction designersLoved the office atmosphere, really chillGot to do solid work as an intern, was pretty impressed</pros>
<cons>Cons – Didn't get to see the client side of an agency, although I requested toIt's hard to contribute anything meaningful with such a strong team already. Not a con, I learned a ton. Just saying the value is in education and experience, not necessarily as much in creation/contribution.A lot of pitch deck assembly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Doing a fine job overall.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hard work, but worth the effort”

</title><pros>Pros – Good clients, exciting projects, amazing people, talented design and tech departments.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Production can be weak with clients, work / life balance needs improving.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Let the teams mature, less pressure from above, more time for learning and reflection.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – R/GA has only continued to evolve in my time here and it's definitely a place where you can make your own path and work with both great clients and team members.</pros>
<cons>Cons – At times it's find your own way, but that can and should be flipped to an opportunity for growth.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – somewhat better coordinated communications could be better ... there's a fair bit of crowd-sourced information gathering, though that's certainly not unique to R/GA.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“World class team”

</title><pros>Pros – The people.  Some of the best & brightest in the adv/marketing industryLive & breathe tech & UXStrong offerings - Strategy to prod dev to marketing communicationGlobal offices really work well together (and support each other)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Big & highly politicalUnderstaffedQuality suffers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on qualityKeep hiring world class experts</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart people, great environment, relaxed community</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours and sometimes inefficient communication</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Handicapped”

</title><pros>Pros – The chance to work with very talented people, very good accounts and build your portfolio.</pros>
<cons>Cons – So big and so many people that most of the time your work will go unnoticed. Most of the time your success depends on having a good or bad relationship with the leads.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try not to dumb down the experience and positions of your employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Art Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very professional, high global level”

</title><pros>Pros – Build your experience with the best of an international team</pros>
<cons>Cons – A dull client portfolio and lack of hierarchy - every senior staff on the same level.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More time spent organizing stuff around is greatly needed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Flash Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“quality of work doesn't match reputation”

</title><pros>Pros – -paid well-company has a great reputation which helps a lot with your career-good insight and experience into business marketing techniques</pros>
<cons>Cons – -a lot of big egos, favoritism.-management imagines they are still a cool small start-up company and are oblivious to the employees who do the work which make the company successful.  they seem to sometimes resent newer employees for ruining their small,cool,rebel self-image yet are happy to reap the benefits of running a large company-didn't keep promises.  I volunteered to do extra work in exchange to be put on a better project, got a pat on the back, and then they promptly forgot about me- you don't get any credit for doing good work unless you are senior.  however you can also easily slack off and you won't get fired.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay more attention to employees.  Reward talented employees by putting them on more meaningful work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A company that has grown too fast and doesn't know how to handle or take care of its employees”

</title><pros>Pros – A great company to move from because of its name valueNice and kind people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Does a terrible job of taking care of employees and their career</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employee's growth and their goals matter as much as the company's growth and both help each other. Right now the management is ONLY focused on the company's growth.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to work at.</pros>
<cons>Cons – no cons really other than management have to listen to their employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your staff</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Visual Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Micromanaged to death, miserable politics--like high school.”

</title><pros>Pros – High profile clients and high profile work. Good salary and half-decent benefits package. Lots of young people and parties--if you're into that.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management feels the need to constantly tout the same R/GA success stories to their employees, trying to reassure them that they, too, will eventually get to work on "their" Nike+... but that never happens. Creative leadership is mostly "old" R/GAers who have just stayed put and been promoted by seniority (and plenty of politicking) rather than earning it with skill. Long, long, long work hours for projects barely supported by project managers and account people.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Clear out deadwood! Don't just promote those who hang around long enough, and fire employees who haven't met their side of the bargain. Most of all, though, fire CLIENTS who are making your team's lives miserable.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible”

</title><pros>Pros – Good clients. Nice office space and locationThat's really all!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horribly mismanagedTerrible work life balanceLeadership team have no integrity.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Sack the London management</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“R/GA: Innovative and Hard-working”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart people. Great work environment.  Innovative work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Highly politicized environment, very hard working.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Place to do your best work - but you'll pay for it”

</title><pros>Pros – A good place to do groundbreaking digital work with a lot of reach</pros>
<cons>Cons – Feels like a sweatshop sometimes</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take better care of employees, retain key talent.  Also, focus on either preserving the old culture or creating a new one - the limbo created by the unprecedented growth is numbing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast paced, innovative thinkers, large agency”

</title><pros>Pros – Exceptionally bright coworkers, great clients</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's a large agency, not extremely collaborative</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Get in bed with the right people and you'll be fine”

</title><pros>Pros – Great reputation when you go to other placesSome very cool brands have been therecoffee barpockets of very talented people</pros>
<cons>Cons – if you don't kiss the right asses you won't get promotedpoor management structure - its easy to get lostquestionable rise to power of some people</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – People need small management groups to have someone responsible for their career development and to be their champion in a large and unruly company atmosphere.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>6</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place from the outside. A sweatshop on the inside.”

</title><pros>Pros – The reputation of R/GA in the marketplace is great. They are fantastic at PR and that creates a certain image about the company and people who work there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – First, it's a sweatshop. I had never worked that hard in my life. After sleeping in the office for two weeks, I went to my boss to ask for 1 or 2 comp days for the people on the team. The answer was simply "no."Second: titles are so inflated. Someone who was a mediocre art director at one shop went to R/GA to become an Executive Creative Director at R/GA (yes, ECD - they have like 40 ECDs in NY alone).Third, the management layer is so think that if you are joining the company, you are just one of the hundreds of minions that rotate in and out.Fourth, the pay was horrible. Period.Finally, if you work at R/GA, you just accept the fact that you work FOR (not with) Bob Greenberg and to make HIM rich and famous, not you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Bob has made more money (and fame) than he'll ever need. He needs to think about spreading that a bit more to his employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place - as long as you don't want/need a life”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are amazing and innovation, including crazy/different thinking, is encouraged.  The environment is truly collaborative and creative.  I learned so much and was able to try so many things while at R/GA.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working at R/GA is a lifestyle.  The only thing in your life is R/GA.  Since the people are great this isn't so bad except the work never ends.  No matter where you are or what you are doing, you will have work to do.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't lose the unique R/GA personality as the company grows.  Encourage employees to take a break and allow space/time for things outside of work.   When not at work, allow employees some time to turn off their phones, ignore their email and go off the grid.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“R/GA a very innovative environment and some really talented people.”

</title><pros>Pros – Some very very talented people. It is a very collaborative and egalitarian environment. Company is  starting to grow its conceptional/marketing (versus design) prowess and making strides.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Output of work is not consistent and usually either very good or very bad. Varies depending on whether you get the "A" team or leadership is paying attention. Teams (especially creative) can get very large with no one "on first" making final calls, until up against the deadline.  Drives a lot of doing-over at the last minute. If I were a client I'd be concerned about this driving up my fees.They are still a very production-driven shop with many of the senior executives not really fully on board with the migration to marketing/advertising work. So there are camps, which makes for mixed signals from leadership sometimes (even though from the very top it may be clear)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Company is too large now to be just "people-driven," it needs process improvement and more structure for its current size and in order to continue to grow.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>