<name>I-Behavior Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/I-Behavior-Reviews-E241004.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-05-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stressful and demoralizing”

</title><pros>Pros – Compensation is good and they are good with food and fun events.  The financial management is good and stable.  Great personnel and camaraderie.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company relies on long hours and shortcuts to compensate for lack of investment in tools, personnel and training.  Very much top-down management by edict, which leaves people scrambling and reactive.  Communication is abysmal.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on your employees and not your bonuses, and collaboration over command.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Development (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Left out to dry”

</title><pros>Pros – Most people are likable, and they love to party.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No training, management unreachable, supervisor more concerned with own commissions not helpfull to team.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do your job. Be available to team for questions and help. Don't say you are and then never available. Foster team so they can produce and grow.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-08-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Energy draining”

</title><pros>Pros – Compensation was very fair for the work compared to competition. Good, smart people. Products seem to be keeping up with the competition.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Benefits are lacking. Energy draining environment. Depressing. CEO doesn't seem to really understand the business or have the drive to grow it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to spend some time and money on Employee morale. Share the long term plan with the employees as there doesn't seem to be one.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>