<name>IDeaS A SAS Company Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/IDeaS-A-SAS-Company-Reviews-E241944.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people and great company”

</title><pros>Pros – Growing at an explosive rate, interesting work, performance driven</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much micro management sometimes</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok if you aren't ambitious”

</title><pros>Pros – IDeaS is owned by SAS, who take pride in their benefit package and like to make Fortune's top places to work list.  If you are a coder or an accountant in a cube, who just wants to work 9-5 and go, it's great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Power is centered in very few people, who are generally not open to new ideas.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Only perks are good, the overall culture needs an improvement.”

</title><pros>Pros – -> Good Pay package-> Can get lots of work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -> No Onsite opportunity-> The work is monotonous and you will keep getting the same work for the long time, the learning curve eventually goes flat.-> I doubt the talent of few people working there, you might never feel that you are working with best talent in the market.-> Nothing will get done unless you cry for it, its not performance driven its requirement driven.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please get open to feedback</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Startup For Freshers”

</title><pros>Pros – Balanced Life and Career growth</pros>
<cons>Cons – No Cons since company is growing</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Learn, Implement and Experience..:)”

</title><pros>Pros – with every year working here one can get experience working with new technologies and be a better employee in all terms.</pros>
<cons>Cons – process implementation is quite on the slower side.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't stuck in that company for more than 3 years”

</title><pros>Pros – Good for freshers, 25% night allowance, breakfast, lunch snacks, dinner available, annual trip, good infrastructure, good computers, nice internet speed.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No appreciation from seniors if you have done some extremely well..less man power...that's why some times you have to work more than 12 hrs..poor management skills from seniors..on work loads..most of the seniors never help to trainee product engineer and lead product engineer and in this work load if some issue occurs..then they blame in such a way that your really very stupid that you work here and you have proved your stupidity here..that u can't do such simple work they will never count your man power and work load..management will curse you</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please use some more man power..and more technical stuff..your work is increasing but not the man power..</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its a good company”

</title><pros>Pros – its a healthy culture company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is no on site opportunity.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It used to be a great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – - Great people, a lot of smart and very talented employees- Interesting and challenging projects, sense of as part of a big thing- Great benefits plan- Good work-life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – - A 'fire,aim,ready' culture that takes its direction from sales.- Too much chaos and lack of communication from VP level down to middle management and employee base, causing lack of stability to build long term plans.- Brand new senior leadership not trusting or understanding the roles of front line managers and support personnel.- Reinventing the messaging wheel every year. "Our target market is now this, no wait this is our target market this year. Our new market messaging is going to be this, wait it’s a new year, let’s coin a new phrase that our customers do not use or understand and re-position the company, again!".- Improper focus on the bottom line versus product innovation, quality and serving the customer.- Employees no longer the #1 asset of the company, which does not align with parent company of SAS Institute. Revenue -  regardless of how we get there, who we alienate (partners/customers) and how we treat employees is the main focus of the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen and trust your middle management and support personnel who, at one point, took pride in working for the company. Too many pinheads with so called “know-how” are placed in senior management positions - those with poor leadership, interpersonal and business skills.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>