<name>General Motors R*Works Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/General-Motors-R-Works-Reviews-E242639.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-10-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Contract Administrator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Educational”

</title><pros>Pros – They had liberal personal time off days. You received ample PTO plus time four additional summer days, holidays, and the week off between Christmas and New Years.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay was a little low. There was high turnover with management and organizational structure. It created a chaotic environment at times.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Promotions Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Over worked under pay - Sounds Great But Run”

</title><pros>Pros – PerksCo-WorkersBenefitsOffice LocationThere is room for improvement</pros>
<cons>Cons – Clients are not progressiveManagement is fakeToo many long hoursStop bible thumpingThey really don't care about you or your career</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop trying to be a freind to employees - stop gossiping about your clients and coworkers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Experiential Marketing Specialist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of travel, little time off”

</title><pros>Pros – You get to work on some cool promotions.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very little time off, especially during the summer. Sometimes employees have to take PTO because weekends are spent traveling.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Communicate with employees about changes at the company. Also, avoid the politics.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great job for experience building and looking to advance outside of the agency”

</title><pros>Pros – There are a lot of great people that work there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Communication amongst HR, upper mgmt</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Everyone has talent and a skill set that offers something to the organization.  Utilize your talent to its fullest potential.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-08-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Strategic Planning Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great client, exposure to industry and top notch vendors and opportunities.  Average place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Large client with large budget to explore.  Hands down, best new hire training I've had at a company.  Great office location.  Good IT team and solutions.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of transparency from upper management.  Hired several people and then laid them off.  Stemmed from poor planning from upper management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Great potential never realized is still only a thought.  Experimentation requires planning from beginning to end. I would be great to have seen the results of some of the initiatives we implemented.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Floor Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – salarygood peoplegood working hourshad good training programbennefits were very fairenjoyed people i worked withenthusiastic</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad mamagementbad vacation timecould use more people to develop products</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – please have more peson to person training</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun Environment, Great Benefits, but Always Working”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits and time off, fun work environment, opportunity to work on fun and exciting projects</pros>
<cons>Cons – Standard office hours are 8-5, but you are usually expected to stay late to impress the client (GM). You are attached to your Blackberry 24/7 and often have events in the evenings, weekends and holidays. Very demanding and fast-paced.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An almost successful company...”

</title><pros>Pros – Very good benefitsGood locationGreat time off</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor management communication between all levels across all departments within the company.Not enough emphasis to gain more clients to keep the company growing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Put more effort in to find out all the work that goes on behind the scene before making "quick" decisions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>