<name>Kennedy Center Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Kennedy-Center-Reviews-E24386.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Program Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing arts job. Great addition to your resume.”

</title><pros>Pros – The Kennedy Center is a great place to get a strong foundation as an arts administrator. It looks impressive on your resume, there are no limits to what you can learn (except the limits you put on yourself), and the people who work there are some talented folks.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There's some elitism that goes with working at the Kennedy Center. It's competitive, and can be cliquish.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Mix up the departments - find ways to work in cross-functional teams.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice place to be”

</title><pros>Pros – A truly unique workplace with some amazing co-workers. One has the opportunity to see and things on a daily basis that most people get to experience only on great occasion.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The IT Department. If you need anything, forget it. These are some of the least helpful people ever.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It does well at some things.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good financial management under Kaiser. Not as political a management system as most DC nonprofits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No focus on quality. The only accountability that exists is for Development (fundraisers) and ticket sales (Marketing). Everyone else makes decisions based upon whatever code of conduct they elect or is elected for them by their team manager. As such, it's filled with fiefdoms, antiquated and unproven programs, and, in the end, budgets that make sense only to those who draft them.However, accountability exists where it must--at the points of entry for income. At least we get paid on time and stay out of the news.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Unify your strategy and/or promote people who can develop a strategy and manage well enough to implement it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Special Events Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Valuable exposure to a career in arts management in a paid internship.”

</title><pros>Pros – Access and exposure to some of the best performing arts in the world. There is a never ending variety of work that the Kennedy Center brings in and produces. There are many opportunities for promotion in the development department.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Because of the Kennedy Center's reputation they can bring in high quality employees at a lower salary.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>