<name>X-ES Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/X-ES-Reviews-E245702.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-08-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting field with flexibility, but still a young company”

</title><pros>Pros – The products X-ES makes are great to work with - it's exciting to work with all the different kinds of technology. The company culture is very laid back and there's no micro-managing (to a fault - see Cons). It's a small company so it's easy to just walk to anybody's desk to talk to them if you need help. Overall the people are friendly. My background was not in Electrical or Computer Engineering but they gave me a chance anyway.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The managers don't actually do any "managing", at least in my role. Everybody who works here technically starts out as a temp employee, so after 9 months they can decide to offer you a full time contract or not. Throughout this entire time I never received one iota of performance feedback (good or bad) until they day they informed me that they were not going to pursue offering me a full time contract. I thought that everything was going great and I never had any chance to hear what I could have improved on (to this day they still haven't told me).They also set your starting salary low and give everybody in the company a large bonus once a year that corresponds with how well the company is doing to make up for the low base pay. However, if bonus time doesn't fall in during the 9 months you're there and your contract doesn't get renewed then you're out of luck.Also, there are numerous problems with the internal intranet/internet infrastructure - every couple weeks there's an outage of some sort that inhibits productivity. Likewise there are limited resources as far as test equipment goes, so you can end up spending a lot of time just trying to get equipment to do your work at all.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try managing your employees and providing them with feedback periodically so they can at least attempt to work on any shortcomings before simply letting them go.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Design Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good start up.”

</title><pros>Pros – There is a lot of freedom given to interns/coops to take time in completing assignments and spend time learning instead of doing. But don't spend too much time stuck at a given problem, and don't be afraid to ask (intelligent) questions. You're surrounded by talented engineers. It truly is a sink or swim environment, so be prepared to put in extra effort to learn new concepts and be thrown difficult tasks. The extremely flexible schedules are a blessing! Opportunity for bonus is there...with a caveat.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They continually cycle through "cheap labor" (aka interns).  Intern pay is so-so, and as a growing start-up, there is a lot of confusion about how things should be done, so things are changing often. Extremely difficult to earn trust of management. Must make a concerted effort to continually interact with management/higher-ups or you will be overlooked every step of the way. The payment model is simple, low salary with bonus if company does well...Bonus caveat: great bonus if you work 50-60 hours a week and are getting assigned high-priority tasks, otherwise the bonus isn't great.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide more feedback about the quality of work employees are doing and change payment model to a slightly higher base salary to encourage employees to have a life outside of work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-09-29</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok for an internship”

</title><pros>Pros – -Ok for internship (you will only learn what you teach yourself, though)-Flexible time-Mostly nice guys (both the full-timers and interns)</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Lousy pay-They basically abuse the interns: Demand a lot, pay lousy!-They are most likely to not gonna hire you after your complete your degreee</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – -Value and guide those interns.  You are likely to loose potential talent just because you don't have a competent mentor.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Electrical Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was a very good time working with them.”

</title><pros>Pros – They will help you.They will give you a chance to work on the field.They will respect your work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They give no pay to internee</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please pay some money to your internees...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>