<name>I-flex Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/I-flex-Reviews-E247606.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-11-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Programmer Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I was a pleasent experience working at i-flex onsite location”

</title><pros>Pros – The company mostly does large turn key projects extending over two to three years. The team sizes vary from 20 to 100 people onsite</pros>
<cons>Cons – They are limited to Banks as their clients. Hence once a project is over they send you back to your base location .</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You are doing a good job at exploring new clients in the bankng domain</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wokring at client site for implementing product”

</title><pros>Pros – Training and Learning, Travel, Job knowledge, Facilities, Peer Rapport</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work pressure, compensation, travel, politics, no ESOP/ESPS. Off late there is lot of attrition due to the above reasons. Management should make it a joy for employees to work here so that people give their 100 percent.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – To be fair to the employees would suggest put them at par with others/competitors else people migrate to better prospect</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“will fill in later”

</title><pros>Pros – lot of onsite oppurtinities compared to other indian companiesgood salary give at startgood exposure</pros>
<cons>Cons – onsite salary is not goodno increments latelyvery little bonus</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – need to take care of employees.lot of people have left the organization.client not happy because of the iteration.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“flexible timings, travel oppertunities, delays in yearly bonuses and yearly hike”

</title><pros>Pros – flexible timings, banking product industry , opportunity to travel</pros>
<cons>Cons – delays in yearly bonuses and yearly hike</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – salary should also be aligned according to oracle policies for i-flex employees along with other process changes being implemented</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Average Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Good learning experience... Good brand name</pros>
<cons>Cons – compensation is very low.... Its just ORACLE hype</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Principal Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Do not join OFSS/I-Flex just because it is Oracle now. Join it after knowing it well and if it suits you.”

</title><pros>Pros – Get to learn banking domain. Flexible timing allowed (at least in my project) - depends on the manager.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Oracle Financial Services Software Limited (OFSS) was formerly i-flex, which is acquired by Oracle. Flexcube is its corebanking product. AND I JOINED MAINLY BECAUSE IT IS ORACLE NOW.1) It takes lot of time to get hang of functional and technical aspects of the product. Too vast really. Hence it take lot of time to start being productive.2) Unreasonable customizations accepted. Why build such a huge, complex and generic product then?3) Poor program management. Employees will bear the brunt of this.4) Very tedious/lengthy process of doing product changes. Doing a small thing takes ages due to internal dependencies. You will learn nothing out of it. Process is constantly changing and no documentation.5) Very poor work-life balance in an active assignment.6) Onsites are mainly in developing countries and are poorly managed. Employees slog at onsite.7) The work has to be within product boundaries and according to its framework. No lateral ideas required nor entertained. Hence no learning or restricted learning only. Any additional skill-set you have is totally wasted. And existing skill sets would evaporate soon.8) Bonus is shown as part of CTC in the offer letter. And they hardly give 30% of it.9) No hikes nor increments. Forget about promotions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do they listen to my advice?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“salary policy is not good”

</title><pros>Pros – good opportunities to learn new things</pros>
<cons>Cons – increment and salary policy is not good</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Knowledge best !!!salary worst!!1”

</title><pros>Pros – High Coding StandardFlexible working hoursApprochable Managament</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay not at all good.Longggg working hoursSat workings</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Prime Sourcing - A Company once highly regarded, not anymore.”

</title><pros>Pros – Well, this review is about the Prime Sourcing division in Oracle Financial Services (formerly known as I-Flex Ltd.). I haven't worked on the Products division (Flexcube), so won't comment on that.1. Competitive salary in India and at Onsite, one of the best in the Industry.2. Peers are very good and knowledgeable. You really get to learn the domain (Banking - Payments) in-depth.3. Good work-life balance in some of the projects. You can say it's a laid back life.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Many - I am mentioning some of them.1. Once a highly regarded brand, now surviving by outsourcing resources. The brand value has deteriorated in past years.2. Very less number of projects in Pune location. Recently lost a big Client and that has worsened the situation. Huge number of resources sitting idle in the bench.3. Middle/Senior level Management seems to have lost the direction. The Organization is merely surviving by outsourcing its resources to its clients.4. Very much dependent on FundTech - GPP product.5. Appraisal and increments are not regular. No one knows when you get it (whether you will get it at all).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work on re-building the brand again. Instead of working as a placement agency, try to think out of the box and build solutions that will add value to the Clients.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Big Brand, Big Name, Big Satisfaction”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work cultureGood for Married people if you want to give time to family then join this placeSalary is Average and appreciation to deserving people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Service sector of company is dangerous to join</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Nothing</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Consultannt (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Work, great onsite exposure, average salaries”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexcube - their flagship product has a good name in market, you gain valuable banking domain experience working on it.Managers are focussed and honestNo or very less politics</pros>
<cons>Cons – Less salaryappraisals are toughUnlucky if you are in a team that provides no travel opportunities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay more</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Applications Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible company”

</title><pros>Pros – To start with they paid a good salary and mostly all of it comes in hand as i was from a premier college.Nothing good to talk about here much. Those onsites i donot know how are they satisfied so much. This company pays in actuals for onsite people thats what the policy says.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Well too many to count.Workculture- The worst i have heard. U donot even have to compare it to Google or FB. Infosys and TCS would do the job.Hike is average 10% - 2012 (2013 they said will be less)Management -Do not care simply - Give you training on something and tell you to work on smthing else no sync between managers also.Don't listen to you what ever u say. I had the personal experience of chasing 2 managers for 3-4 months for a team change and then finally had to resignDonot be fooled by the brand of Oracle. The benefits they have OFSS doesnot provide.HR - Always good with passing the buck. If u want relocation benefits written in your offer letter they wont give you and come up with some or the other excuse.Workculture - Dnt even get me started on that- no team meeting, no team outings, no lunch nothing nothing at all</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Well please change the way you operate and manage the teams. Let there be more transparency. Please treat the employees as assets you might have created the product but they are the ones who now develop it and support it. If they leave u might hire more but at the end of the day u have to train them and it will take time. U might think that Flexcube is a golden egg on which u can survive for generations . But face the facts u undersell it to 3rd world counties and no major presence in developed countries.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not so good”

</title><pros>Pros – Getting a chance to work on product is good.Good if get onsite</pros>
<cons>Cons – Less payRestricted access to net, computers etcLack of projects which causes critical situations during recession and causes lay offs</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to free up the people so that they can work effectivelyBring good project</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Associate Consultant”

</title><pros>Pros – We will be learning very good exposure on Corporate Banking</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pathetice HR policies and very less hike not upto industry standards. Hard work never appreciated.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Kindly  be employee friendly and provide good salary similar to industry standards.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Once good I-flex employer is now a horrible Oracle Financial Services Software employer”

</title><pros>Pros – Onsite (Few opportunities in good Europe, Aus, Middle East , lots in Africa region)Job SecurityWork mostly on client side.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most Product related support.Only Oracle Technology, no scope for products.Pays well for laterals during joining, 12% appraisal (2012)Some horrible managers.No scope of Project change.Hard to get promotions n recognition for hard work,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please treat your own employers with more respect & pay, rather than paying a lot for laterals.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good to enjoy life ...”

</title><pros>Pros – good work environment, senior management is strong and helpful,</pros>
<cons>Cons – be clear on salary increment on time of joining... company has some different policy which may work against you</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – please provide comp-off on one day base, provide every one fair chance based on one's capability</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was good with i-flex not so much since it OFSS”

</title><pros>Pros – Healthy work environmentFrequent travel opportunitiesVery good platform for grabbing domain knowledge</pros>
<cons>Cons – Technologies used are age old and no chance of moving on to the newer techs.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value the employees who have been with the firm for long instead of having them at the their sub par salaries while hiring new people with lesser experience at a much higher pay grade.If everything is being done the oracle way, like the billing to customer and the facilities( or lack of these) provide to employees, then why not the salary.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to start a career”

</title><pros>Pros – Great resources.  Lots of onsite work. Product Company</pros>
<cons>Cons – Does not pay well. To make money you HAVE TO go onsite.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-29</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work Culture”

</title><pros>Pros – learning options are available in the company</pros>
<cons>Cons – To  bad, Not at all employee friendly.They like to torture employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please get a good HR team where they handle the employees not their make up.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Oracle Database Administrator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not Bad Exp”

</title><pros>Pros – It was a Good time to spend, Good Learning</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management was not good- How to deploy resources at right Position</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Should take care</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company to work with. It is basically product based so there is always work to do. Spectrum of opportunities.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Salary. Easy work environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Learning is less in some of the departments. No facilities for shift persons.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My experience has been very satisfying”

</title><pros>Pros – quantum of work is what is humanely possible. If because of some reason it is not, you would be told so by the management that this particular project is estimated aggressively to eliminate competition etc. And when you are stretching to get the work done, leadership is aware of this.That typical attitude of software companies where they push managers to make people stay longer is quite less.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The people management during 2008 crisis was handled very badly. The company lost its human face and yet did not save substantially in terms of salaries.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The people management during 2008 crisis was handled very badly. The company lost its human face and yet did not save substantially in terms of salaries.Either company should have handled it in a way where company looks heartless and saves money or company looks kind even at cost of money. here company looked heartless and yet did not save money.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good experience and excellent exposure”

</title><pros>Pros – company provided great professional development</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company policy is not very employee friendly</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Good friendly work environmentGood set of technologies to work onFinancial domain vertical</pros>
<cons>Cons – not a good paymasternot open to employees</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tech Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Life changing experience -”

</title><pros>Pros – - Lots of opportunity to travel and long stays abroad .. if you are lucky it will NOT be AFRICA ... a personal advice here to youngsters - every  body has to travel :) so better travel before getting settled in life.- Good Pay- Early recognition for hard/smart workers provided you are in the RIGHT group.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Bias- Growth depends upon boss & team recognition (try to get into FCC or Retail)..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They won't heed to any advice</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fantastic..”

</title><pros>Pros – Good domain to work and having good exposure to Financial area... Training provided on Financial area are awesome... Managers are friendly in nature..</pros>
<cons>Cons – Will not get a chance to work on other domains... Issue with work locations.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall good and satisfying experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Talented team members and Good work culture</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation doesnt commensurate with the work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice company to begin your career with”

</title><pros>Pros – Employees get good exposure to BFSI domain.Good transparency across levels which instills a confidence among employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – Vertical growth in the team is bit limited as band movement is based mainly on experience.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Consultannt (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Small company. Obsessed with FlexCube product”

</title><pros>Pros – Small company, so you will get immediate attention, HR ppl are responsive and supportive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you join in flexcube division, then well and good. But if you join in consulting (primesourcing) division, then its not a good place to work. Not many projects, so you have to continue in same project even if you dont want to. Citi group only major client. People who are in onsite, they remain in onsite for ever and till they want. Very less onsite of others even if you perform above expectation in offshore.Last but not the least - its still not clear if this company is "Oracle Financial Services" or still "i-flex". Policies are not clear. Managers at high position do whatever they want(like sending onsite, promotion etc). Not a clear process oriented company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make policies and process better and transparent. Decide if this is "Oracle Financial Services" or still "i-flex". If its "Oracle Financial Services" then stop using i-flex name and intigrate into Oracle. Companies like Sun are already integrated in Oracle.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Associate consultant”

</title><pros>Pros – You will get Onsite if you stay for long time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – politics, You cant work any technology you preferred</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Enter @ your own risk”

</title><pros>Pros – Perceived brand NameLilttle BFSI exposure</pros>
<cons>Cons – No Transport FacilitiesWorst CompensationNo Technology beyond FLEXCUBE product;Same WorkNo promotion scopeOld Timers call the shotsWork on Saturdays</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to make i-flex as it was before Oracle's Takeover</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Exposure to new Tech.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good exposure to new tech, good exp for freshers.Free to incorporate new Tech, provided your lead is flexible too.Managers are fine , though it depends on your project and luck too.Flexible timing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is not at par and is avg.No work from home option in most of the projects.Helpdesk is not good at all.Not completely aligned with Oracle Corp till now.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Not as such as i didn't faced any prob with management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nightmare”

</title><pros>Pros – For freshers/trainees, i-flex provides the right environment for learning.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No respect for employees. Policies and processes are neanderthal, time consuming, tedious & barely serves any purpose. Be assured to be lost in the realm of dirty politics & paper work. Your growth is guaranteed only if you share a favourable personal equation with your immediate superior/supervisor. There is absolutely no work-life balance and there is no guarantee of any amount of recognition even after you have performed. Learning becomes skewed beyond a certain point.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – People are the asset of any organization. Understand them & treat them as humans first, than as factor of production.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Trainee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dissatisfied”

</title><pros>Pros – Brand name of OracleVery good pay package for IIT and BITS graduates.Minimal variable component.Consultants have on-site oppurtunities.Okay work-life balance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Peer group"Whatever has been, will be" attitude of employees.Lack of innovation.Bad work environment and almost no recreational facilities.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please give more freedom to employees. We can't even install an alternate browser. Also, there is no recreational facilities. The security desk is not ready to keep belongings, and don't allow them to be taken inside, too!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great work culture”

</title><pros>Pros – A great company to start your career with.Wonderful work culture</pros>
<cons>Cons – Repetitive workLimited avenues of growth</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good work great divivde in terms of salary”

</title><pros>Pros – good work compared to other similar organisationsless tension as managers are coolless pressure as it is a product company</pros>
<cons>Cons – great salary divide among equally experienced employeesless professionalism</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – maintain parity</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a gud payer”

</title><pros>Pros – Gud workWork Culture is Gud</pros>
<cons>Cons – Dont expect much of salary</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Boring, Frustrating,”

</title><pros>Pros – Since it was majorly a product company and has "proud" implementations all over the globe, good to learn the product. Else, not a great deal to work here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - No processes. You will encounter 10 + experienced ppl in the same company working for donkeys years but act as morons.- No documentation. They love re inventing the wheel all the time. Just because some "senior" did work in a way, (it could be full of flaws) others are also expected to follow the path. Totally snooty, arrogant.- Middle and Sr. Mgmt are simply clueless as to what is happening with respect to appraisals. They point to HR who turn out to be more clueless and make you hit your head against the wall.- The salaries are not at par and even when you get it, it will take ages to get one peanut.- The need passionate ppl at work who work 365 days, 24/7.Quite ridiculous.- One can name it i-toil instead of i-flex.- So many ex-bankers sitting there, with no idea of how an IT company works. They hardly know how to estimate a project.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Give way to proper processes and other youngsters down the line and let the 10+ seniors pave way to this.-  Seniors dont mean end of the world. It is really dumb to let "experience" take a bad shape just because it came for a senior, however flawy it can get!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Beware, they hire people from campus for different profile but move you to subsidiary at half salary.”

</title><pros>Pros – Has good work culture and is domain specific.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You can not trust this company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't spoil career of people whom you hire from campus.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly, nice, freedom to do things that we like to do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not much scope to grow professionally</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice place for functional people”

</title><pros>Pros – Functional people are considered a little above par when compared to technical people. They are always given additional roles but not to technical people.good infrastructureOracle's influence is more and helping the revenues grow</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary isn't on par with other companies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take care of technical resources and give them equal responsibilities as given to functional people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“freshers paid far more than experienced professionals of 4-5 y”

</title><pros>Pros – laid back lifeleaves on requestvery flexible work life balance (if there is work)good place to get bfsi domain knowledgeNo work at all</pros>
<cons>Cons – VVV poor salary - not joking at allno transperancySelfish mgtLack of new business especially at primesourcingno control in the hands of iflex management post oracle takeover</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – control the mass attrition levels by once and for all giving out good salaries to bring all at parity</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“review based on salary, job satisfaction,work culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Work culture is good , helpful people around to guide and help you out . disciplined life ..</pros>
<cons>Cons – The 10+ are overpaid and 10 years less are underpaid. Almost with 7 years exp one can expect not more then 6 lakhs with all benefits. Not at all competitive. Cannot survive at Bangalore with these peanuts if at all both husband and wife are not working !  Also no job satisfaction. You will end up patching the Pl/sql packages by reading thousands lines of debug log files day and night.. Need not use much of your brain !!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Worthless to say anything to them !!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Life at I-flex Turns me OFF”

</title><pros>Pros – Good in Banking domainOracle BrandNo standards to followNo process to follow</pros>
<cons>Cons – No hikes since many years.No promotions.We can't believe s.management. Every time false commitments by Sr.management.You wont get relieving letter. They wont even accept your resignation.After resignation,they will ask you to wait for 3-4 months, But company policy says, 1 month is the notice period.No powers to HR. HR will say, I cannot do anything about your resignation or relieving.Management is not good.No clarity about Hikes, Nobody knows when we will get action letters( after 2.5 years also , same situation).No Latest technologies.Overall horrible place to work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – When any employee resigns , please give them relieving letter after completing 30 days . . But don't threaten them, you do what ever you want.. we wont give you relieving letter.Give some powers to HR also.Employees are assets, so treat them as employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“working with i-flex”

</title><pros>Pros – working env was good and team mates were too good. a little bit of restriction on time but no so much of restriction.</pros>
<cons>Cons – team management is not so good as well as other management which handles the company is worst and after oracle has overtook i-flex its situation is completely worst. seniors having 3 years of exp still waiting for salary hike so we cant even hope so such kind of things.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – please don't behave like our polititians who always takes care to fill their pockets please have a look at the employees who do the main work over here.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Life at i-flex turns me off”

</title><pros>Pros – Good relaxing atmosphere.Political knowledge gained.Heart becomes stronger since it becomes hard.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Non-professional culture.Worst working conditions and infrastructure.World's worst logistics provided to employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Kindly consider employee's personal problems and don't make business on other's loss.Appraise with care.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>ASSOCIATE CoNSULTANT (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“gREAT PLACE TO WORK FOR”

</title><pros>Pros – domain expertisegrowth in terms of responsibility</pros>
<cons>Cons – no work and personal life balancepoor salary</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Thet should recognize talented people and there efforts</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Was Good”

</title><pros>Pros – Good ManagersCan be recommended for freshers to joinGood place to work, anyone looking for Financial domainBrand nameColleagues are more interactive again depends on team you get into</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor work like balance. Will be asked to work on weekends, even though they are officially declared  as holidayswhile Time Estimation  weekends too included. Not bothered about your family commitments.Poor technical career growthPoor pays</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give something to Associate consultants.Consider that employees got family, they have commitments with family tooDo not include weekends while estimating time, as they are dedicated to family</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dont fall for the brand name”

</title><pros>Pros – the compay gives you a Laid back life.Flexible timings on some projectsITs new complex in goregaon has good  infrastructure</pros>
<cons>Cons – Havent seen promotions in numerous yearsThey will hire you as business analyst and then will make you work as functional testers.Be-ware.. there is life beyong flexcube, you might land in the services division.. prime sourcing, and its not the same as flexcube in work profile and salary status</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The indian management has no powers and almost every thing is now controlled by Oracle USA. The liberty of top management has gone</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-02</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A bureaucratic company!”

</title><pros>Pros – Brand Name...and that's about it!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots!Incompetent, Rude and Arrigant ManagersOnly functional resources are valued and paid wellSalaries are way too lowLong working hoursLack of communicationUnfair for people working at low-mid levelUnstable</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire competent managers and get rid of those who throw their weight around without producing actual results</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Tech Lead (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Iflex”

</title><pros>Pros – V Good exposure to technologyclient interactions</pros>
<cons>Cons – poor middle management - only good enuf as billing clerks</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – need to shake up middle managerial layer . cannot keep postmen there.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>