<name>M Hayes Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/M-Hayes-Reviews-E250576.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent, professional company”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Benefits package.  Bonuses were great.   Company really cared when I had a family issue.  Loved my manager!</pros>
<cons>Cons – I'd never worked in the field before and wasn't used to working on this by myself most of the time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Schedule more time for employee interaction...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Nurse Case Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – to do well as a case manager in this company, you need to be organized in both administrative work and time management. the job can pay off hugely if you are a hard worker. Supervisors really care about your well being and will offer to help you in any way possible. The flexibility of the position is the biggest pro. all senior managers have worked files and know the challenges we face as case managers</pros>
<cons>Cons – some of the larger contracts require a high volume of assignments, some with short notice, If you love the work this ultimately should not be a problem. do not come aboard if you are tired and looking to coast.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I am glad you listen to us in the field! kepp this up as we need you to hear us!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Nurse Case Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unpaid overtime”

</title><pros>Pros – The company is professional and provided some training</pros>
<cons>Cons – The expectation for field nurses and vocational consultants is unrealistic.  The average case load is much higher than other rehabilation firms, and the QA expectations are impossible to obtain.  There are not enough hours in the day and most of us are salaried so we give much unpaid overtime.  Supervisors are micromanagers and documentation and Special Handling Instructions are out of control with too much detail.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The company execs should go out to seminars that us field counselors attend and talk with the other employees of your competition.  Your reputation as slave drivers is well deserved.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Nurse (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“DO NOT WORK HERE!!”

</title><pros>Pros – The money is great if you plan on working more than 60 hrs a week. That's about it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – VERY poor training/3 days orientation, most of which is HR information. After that the only training is online and if you ask questions. They start giving you files and expect you to know exactly what to do. I would not recommend working here unless you have done this exact work before. The WORSE training of all my nursing jobs. You have to work 60 plus hrs a week. Not worth the $.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need better training. More money for the amount you have to work. 60 hrs a week and no extra money for all the extra hours is wrong. You only get bonuses for the billable hours, not the hours you actually work. Job is not worth the money, unless you don't mind working all of the time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Field Case Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“okay”

</title><pros>Pros – Ability to work from home based office, some flexibiity</pros>
<cons>Cons – Increased out of pocket expenses and poor turn around time for expense reimbursement. Salary below average, low bonus rate</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>