<name>Achievers Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Achievers-Reviews-E250201.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My first 3 months have been amazing!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Product - Software that is just a bit ahead of the market allows us to drive vision and value.Great Leaders - Experience leadership demonstrates how to manage and grow a businessGreat People - I'm very impressed that as a start-up everyone has a role and does their job amazingly.Great Visionary - Razor, is the inspiration both internally with employees as well as externally  with clients.Amazing Culture - Everyone has everyone else's back.  All pulling on the same side of the rope.Income opportunity is there too..</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Achievers is still a relatively young company so there are operational issues that are still being addressed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Maintain the culture & continue to take care of the customers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“New leadership, great people undeniable future.”

</title><pros>Pros – I've been fortunate to have been apart of some great growth companies in the past.  This company and opportunity has me the most excited than I have been in the past 10 years.  The people are great.  Everyone is here to help. No politics. The new leadership team is fantastic and the moves have been brilliant.  They are technology pros, no question.  It's the only company I know of addressing an existing 46 billion dollar market that has not yet been addressed properly by a SaaS platform.  It's also backed by Sequoia, which brings the heat. The leadership team and the board are just flat out winners.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1) Old glassdoor reviews from people that were stuck in the awkward teenage phase of the company... all companies go through it in rapid growth, some employees handle it better than others to see it through to the other side.  2) I think everyone has seen enough success in the last 3 to 6 months with the new leadership team that any doubters have stopped doubting, but there still might be some people in the culture with a bit of a memory hangover from those awkward teenage days.  They need to get right quick.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing what you are doing. Believe in and invest in the folks that really want to see this company be something amazing, which you already are.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Place to Enjoy Going to Work Everyday”

</title><pros>Pros – I have been with the Company for 9 months now.  When I started it seemed like it was too good to be true, I assumed that once I was settled then reality would set in and the energy and work environment would become just like any other work place.  Nine months later this is not the case.  I still enjoy going to work everyday, Sunday's are no longer miserable because Monday is just around the corner.The Leadership truly cares about their employees.  They not only care about their employees today but also where their employees want to go and their career growth.  Another pro is the balance of work/personal life.  We work hard and things move extremely fast but we are always encouraged to maintain what is important to us in our personal lives.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Like the other reviews have said, there is the occasional craziness related to any start up.  This has significantly improved within the past month or so due to some key leaders joining the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great technology and team, lots of opportunity for growth”

</title><pros>Pros – Great culture, experienced leadership, the HR technology space is hot and being the #1 provider in the industry means Achievers is poised to take off.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This may or may not be a con, but things move fast around here and are changing everyday. You must be agile and adapt to meet the large opportunity Achievers is chasing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to work towards growing and training the talent you have so employees stay excited about advancement opportunities within the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Client Success Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast paced, customer and employee focused!”

</title><pros>Pros – At Achievers, we understand that it is our employees that make us so successful. We are constantly growing, and adapting to that growth, but through that what has remained constant is the value that is placed on making employees feel like their hard work is valued and will be acknowledged. When our employees meet targets and deliver on customer expectations there is a significant amount of public praise that is placed on those employees. On top of performance based recognition incentives, we have a generous benefit package, which includes fitness subsidies, in office lunch, 4 paid volunteer days per year. On top of that, our leaders are not elitist, everyone is given an opportunity to reach out to leaders to give feedback, ask questions, and ask for help.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is never a slow moment here, so if you are someone who prefers to coast along, this gig is not for you. as we strive to become more scalable, our processes our constantly changing, so you can never fully adapt before it is going to change again.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to give opportunities to existing employees to grow, rather than always going outside to hire.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing team-oriented company that knows their biggest asset is their employees.”

</title><pros>Pros – Young and vibrant company where people come to work excited, positive and ready to work. We celebrate our company's success as a team and everyone is encouraged to push the boundaries and grow into the career that they want. Transparency is a necessity and everyone in the company always knows what's going on and where we're going.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Any rapidly growing software company will say the same thing but we've recently had a large number of executives join recently who don't necessarily embrace the culture in the same way we have in the past. Not to say that they don't embrace it because they do but Achievers traditions are very special and important and sometimes higher executives don't necessarily see it as a priority.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company, great market, great leadership team”

</title><pros>Pros – First of all, the product and value proposition is awesome - our job is literally to create programs that make people happier about their job on a day to day basis. I've worked for plenty of software companies and never had such a great mission to work towards.Also, the overall energy and culture is great. People care about each other, work hard, have fun and communicate well. I haven't noticed any of the "cliques" that other reviews seem to talk about, maybe that's just based on my group and location but everything I see is pretty awesome.Our new leadership (CEO, CMO, SVP of Product, Chairman of Board, CRO) is world class, and is pushing us in a great overall direction. We've had good success to date in the market and we're just scratching the surface of the opportunity, so the upside right now feels pretty tremendous.Also, as a married person with a kid, it's refreshing to find a company with all the intensity of a start-up which doesn't somehow assume I'm going to be at work 12 hours a day. I put in a solid day, work really hard, answer a few emails when needed from home - and work life balance is very easy to attain without feeling I'm not "making the grade."Sure, there's typical "fast growing company" pains - sometimes things are a little hectic, communication is always evolving, etc. - but that's to be expected and everyone is earnestly trying to do the right thing so it's easy to do the same.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It being a fast growing company, there's always a new person or new initiative to accommodate. It's a fast paced environment, and if you don't like that or want something less exciting and less challenging, I would see that as a drawback.Sometimes communication between groups can be less than perfect as we navigation a two office structure (SF & Toronto), but that's improving every day.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep pushing to grow the company while keeping the culture, emphasize inclusiveness and merit-based rewards, and grow, grow, grow!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall a pretty disappointing experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great location, lots of potential for interesting work, free lunch daily.The corporate messaging around employee engagement that gets you in the door is also reflected in their marketing, which makes you feel good about coming onboard.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Remember that great messaging around employee engagement? It's all show, at least in some key departments. Like the one churning out all that messaging which has to be one of the least engaged and least empowered teams I've ever worked with.Senior leaders with poor people management skills somehow still advance up the corporate ladder, and are allowed to micromanage their often more experienced/competent staff. Isn't the point of hiring more experienced professionals that they can take ownership and drive results?Although San Francisco is the headquarters, and where they've added on a large number of leadership hires in a few short months (CEO, CMO, CRO, a departed CHRO), most of the employees are in Toronto. Expect frequent travel to/from Toronto if you want to stay in the loop.I came here thinking I'd have the opportunity to do some of the best work of my career. Instead, it has been incredibly disappointing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Either get training for your inexperienced managers who've been promoted beyond their abilities, or find them an independent contributor role before they drive out more capable employees.You've hired some amazing A-players -- don't squander their talents!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Be wary, unless your title starts with a "C"”

</title><pros>Pros – You will get to work with a lot of smart people. There are some nice benefits, including using their own product. Lots of branded swag, if you like that sort of thing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Favoritism and nepotism abound! Senior hires have brought along coworkers from previous organizations who don't go through the interview process, and end up as overpaid waste. More tenured leaders are too scared to stand up to the new hires & get walked all over. Culture is seriously failing, at a company about building culture!All those smart people I mentioned in my Pros -- they are smart, but unless they are someone's favorite, their ideas and suggestions will be ignored. So much amazing talent is going to waste at Achievers because not everyone is in the 'inner circle'.The employees are motivated by fear, and not by passion. (Hence all the good reviews on here are only from current employees who are scared to say otherwise. Same goes for me -- I was too scared to write my review until after I left.)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – To the tenured senior management -- stand up for yourselves, and your employees! The recent senior hires are bringing moral and productivity down.To the newer senior management -- check your ego at the door. If you need an executive assistant or first class flights, go work for a Fortune500 organization. Your ego is only making this company worse.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Been here about a month and a half and already love it. Everyone here wants to be here and there is no clock watchers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots of new upper management hires</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“6 weeks in and confirming the org is as advertised.”

</title><pros>Pros – high energy vibe in a proven business with great opportunity for growth ahead</pros>
<cons>Cons – typical start-up growing pains, lack of maturity in some processes but this is all expected.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – After 6 weeks, keep doing what you are doing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wish I'd trusted the bad feeling I had during the interview process.”

</title><pros>Pros – Free lunch, all-you-can-eat snacks and drinks, opportunities to choose your own rewards with points, a few great people, flexible schedule, amazing location.</pros>
<cons>Cons – For a company that specializes in engagement, I've rarely seen such a disengaged staff. Senior management hasn't the faintest clue what's going on, communication is dreadful, and the extreme emphasis on recognition leaves the unrecognized feeling awful. Few staff members are qualified for their jobs, although there are a few truly amazing standouts. You have to really drink the Kool-Aid to fit in here. When the in-crowd decides they don't like you, it's like Lord of the Flies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get rid of Razor and find an actual CEO.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor excuse for a company”

</title><pros>Pros – Free food like every other startup in SF.Colleagues are nice and friendly, but you definitely have to make an effort to fit in with the team which means drinking the "kool-aid."</pros>
<cons>Cons – This company is a complete oxymoron. All they do is pitch employee engagement and recognition, yet I have never worked at a company with worse morale or turnover. The management team is all about telling you how great the company is, yet their actions do not support that. In my career, I have learned that a strong company consists of a strong leadership team who has the experience and vision to lead a company in the right direction, a product that works, and employees who are smarter than you. This company has none of that. Also, it is run more like a fraternity than a company, where culture is forced down your throat. Their "culture" is defined by spending 24 hours a day together, partying on the weekends, and not the shared values of the employees. Those who hang out with Razor are given preferential treatment and growth is not based on talent.  Unfortunately, you don't realize how unhealthy the environment is until you leave.  Given how much hiring is going on in tech these days, I would strongly recommend avoiding this company at all costs.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't be fooled”

</title><pros>Pros – Free food, Some great people, cool workspace.</pros>
<cons>Cons – EGO city! You literally need to penetrate into one of the various cliques to have a chance at this company. The CEO thinks he running a fraternity and will literally say "YES" to anything potential customers ask. IPO will never happen here, best case they get bought, but senior management who claims to be well versed in IPO actually is not. Also, caution on any positive reviews as new hires are asked to fill out a glowing review in their first 30 days.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop lying to employees, they are adults. Stop lying to customers and sell what you can deliver.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>9</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Feel like I pledged the wrong frat and the pledge master is now hitting on my girlfriend”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a feel-good product.  Who doesn't like being recognized?  Clients (initially) like us and the idea of what we do for them.Free Food - lots of it.If you are "in" that week, management may be generous with points (our currency) so you can buy yourself something nice (if overpriced) from our limited catalogue.There are some very talented people here (caveat: they are not being utilized or recognized)Events and PR are outstanding. I bought into the hype, and some of our clients/prospects do too. Seriously, we should be overpaying these teams b/c they do the best things at the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Seriously wanted to love working here, but it just is NOT going to happen.  This company touts itself as a serious software company, but it is just a social cult.  If you don't like waking up on Monday wondering if management or the "cool" kids like you, then run.Everyone talks about going public all the time (speaks to the lack of real business experience and maturity). Really? an IPO? There are very few people here that understand what that means.We are not HQ'd in San Francisco. There is a presence in SF, but the leadership and direction come out of Toronto and those ideas are back in 1998 as far as how to compete and win in this space.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start over. Don't play favorites. Get a strategy to execute on what we commit to clients.Take the time to appreciate the talents of your employees and quit listening to the advice/gossip of the inside few - too many good people who are incredibly talented have left or been asked to leave without anyone really investing them - the revolving door is incredibly expensive.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Human Resource (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A professionally managed company”

</title><pros>Pros – I love working for Achievers because it is a professionally managed company that uses a professional approach to handle its blue chip customers HR and Financial consulting requests.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited availability of high end training.  Low to mid end training is provided</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep on doing what you do best.  Consulting in HR</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“one of the best achievers and well planned one”

</title><pros>Pros – ever increasing market revenue,very good job prospect</pros>
<cons>Cons – u have to work very hard</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – always ready for for work</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A fast-paced, high-growth company that provides great opportunities for employees.”

</title><pros>Pros – Achievers promotes from within. As such, the company helps true A-Players grow in their role and offer great career support and mentoring. The leadership team is approachable and allow employees' voices to be heard. The culture is upbeat, fast-paced, and high-energy.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working at Achievers can sometimes be exhausting - long hours, tight deadlines, and mountains of work - but the reward and outcome is worth it. Achievers has a sink-or-swim culture.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to help employees grow!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“One of the healthiest work environments I've witnessed, or been a part of.”

</title><pros>Pros – A company with great people and positive attitudes. It's easy to work in a place where everyone believes in the company's purpose. They work hard to really ensure they know how employees are feeling.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I worry about the scalability of the company culture as the company is growign so quickly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Positive Buzz”

</title><pros>Pros – Achievers is one of the best orgs I have ever worked for. Everyone at the company works together collaboratively, leadership entrusts their teams and provides them opportunity to innovate and make a real contribution to the company. Recent additions to leadership team seem to have done great things for employee morale (not that it was ever low - every company has peaks and lower points), however, seen and heard a lot of very positive buzz around the future outlook for the company. Growth is happening at a rapid pace, many new faces and clients joining the family. Have seen this company expand and evolve over the past year and half. Looking forward to what is still to come.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Cannot think of a con.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep growth going - continue providing support to employees to sustain growth.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Here for the long haul”

</title><pros>Pros – Where do I start?  I have been with this company for many years now.  I have seen it through all its success and growth and am excited about its future growth.The reasons I work here are the following:- the people!  We hire smart, driven, passionate, innovative, self aware individuals.  People who not only are passionate about their careers but passionate about how their careers impact our growth.  Its so energizing to work along side of these people daily.- I add an accomplishment bullet to my resume every quarter.  Career growth is here, and its here in spades.  If you know how to take your career into your own hands and deliver great work then its only a matter of time before a business need presents itself for further growth.- Impact: the work I do daily impacts the organization.  Big organizations have their own perks too like process and best practices but at Achievers we are building those as we go and everyone has the ability to leave their mark here.- culture: we find great ways to have fun at work.  Between First Round Fridays and awards ceremonies quarterly, company retreats two times a year and so much more, we genuinely have a great time here and often!</pros>
<cons>Cons – High growth companies are not for the faint of heart.  Its fast paced, constantly changing and constantly requires you to build while working vs just working.  Although I think this is the best part about joining a high growth business, I can appreciate that it isn't the environment for everyone to be successful in.The company is growing up daily.  As someone who saw it at its infancy stage, its incredible to see how much it has changed and shaped into this incredible business.  This really should be in the pros section but I think for some older employees they miss the "good'ol days".  Its an incredible opportunity to watch anything grow and transform, I think anyone who has the opportunity to get involved in this type of business is lucky.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do everything you can to keep the culture scaling as the business grows.  You're doing a great job and there is something great here to hold onto.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome company to work for!”

</title><pros>Pros – I have worked for this company for approximately one year and having just come off our annual company retreat this past weekend, I am even more convinced at how amazing this organization is. The vision, mission, and focus are unlike anything I have seen at any other company I have worked for.Achievers is a real thought leader and innovator in the HCM space. Getting a sneak peek at what Product is planning for the next year is incredible. Working with such brilliant minds on a daily basis is pretty fun, and working here has been equally rewarding and challenging (in a good way).Achievers has found a way to hold onto its corporate culture and the little things that matter, while going through crazy growth year after year. There is a very long list of things that make me love coming to work every day and these are just a few of them.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I can't think of any cons.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to support your employees, we are seeing many employee-focused programs delivered to help us benefit and grow.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-22</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>User Experience/UI Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An AMAZING company to work for, with a unique culture and the very best people.”

</title><pros>Pros – - Great company culture- Amazing employees- Great benefits- Great employee perks- Good location- Overall a fun place to work where every day feels like you are making a difference</pros>
<cons>Cons – - no cons to list</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing what you are doing</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Culture, Great Company”

</title><pros>Pros – This company is dedicated employee success, and that starts from within. The culture and morale within the company is always sky high and makes you want to work hard for each other. They have given me everything I need to help me succeed and continue down my personal career path.</pros>
<cons>Cons – None that I can think of</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make sure the culture and excitement don't get left behind as the company grows!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An Ideal Coop Opportunity”

</title><pros>Pros – Achievers offers everything a coop student could ask for. Amazing onboarding that teaches you about all aspects of the company, your department and its platform. Friendly, helpful and supportive fellow employees are everywhere you look. You receive consistent feedback from your mentor and leader, along with communication about what is going on in the company and how your work contributes to your departments success. Most importantly, you are given real work! there is no doing coffee runs or completing mindless tasks day-in and day-out. You are given real projects that will give you great experience to put on your resume (and that is what a coop is all about!). It you love a challenge and are adaptable to any situation, Achievers is a awesome place to work!</pros>
<cons>Cons – I have not encountered any cons</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An absolutely amazing journey”

</title><pros>Pros – I have worked at Achievers for a little over a year and have loved every moment here. Co-workers slowly became friends and have now become more like family. Achievers clearly states that 9 to 5ers need not apply - the important thing to note here is that this isn't because they're slave drivers making you stay late but that the work is so rewarding and the environment so fun and comfortable that you'll seldom want to leave.I am proud to tell people I work for such an innovative, inspiring and truly unique company. You're either a culture fit here or you're not. The people here are all from different backgrounds, different cultures, different walks of life but one thing unites them: they want to change the way the world works. They're all passionate about what they do, they love sharing thoughts and ideas, they inspire each other and learn from their peers. My colleges here demonstrate the term "work hard, play hard" every single day.At Achievers I have come across some of the most brilliant people who have taught me the true meaning of loving your work and sharing your success. Everyone here is eager to help each other accomplish their goals and reach the epitome of their potential. Your peers will guide you, lead you, inspire you and motivate you. You won't have a dull moment here. Everyone has a whacky sense of humor and is not afraid of bringing their personalities to the forefront.Every single person is friendly and outgoing in their own way, everyone here genuinely cares for your success and well being - like I mentioned before, this place becomes like a second family. I could not be happier.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The salary isn't on par with industry standards (but the daily free breakfasts, tri-weekly free lunches and Friday drinks help ease that pain a little)There's been lots of additions to senior management and that's leading to a little uncertainty in terms of goals and the future of the company - having said that, this is a welcome change because that's one thing this company was previously criticized on (lack of senior management)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I don't have much to offer in terms of advice, I am currently very happy with the management team and wouldn't change a thing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A solid opportunity with a connected company.”

</title><pros>Pros – It is professionally stimulating. You're given responsibilities here that you can grow into and develop with. In a normal company, I would have had to work for 2 more years to get the opportunities of growth that I'm getting right now. The whole working philosophy is to own what you do, and make it better. The way we work is challenging and stimulating - the only way I can work actually. There is an energy and connection to how the business is evolving and growing that keeps everyone motivated to do what they do.Culturally, we are genuinely valued. Truly. We are taken care of with all of the perks and benefits the company literally foots the bill on. We feel comfortable in our work space, and constantly are asked for feedback on how we are feeling, what isn't working and how we can improve things based on how WE as an employee base feel. You just don't see that kind of practice in other companies.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No sugar-coating here: it can get overwhelming. The company works at a fast pace and we love our goals and metrics. This type of work is not for everybody (the job descriptions say "9 to 5ers need not apply").</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome Culture, Innovative & Fast-paced”

</title><pros>Pros – This company truly fosters innovation by having a culture of diverse individuals working together to grow the company and themselves.  The environment is full of A-Players full of dedication and passion towards their work.  People live by the work hard play hard philosophy, so its as much fun as is it hard work.  There is definitely good transparency throughout the company, building a more positive environment for staff than I've seen in other bureaucratic companies I've worked with in the past.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working here often requires long[er] hours, although I do find that when staff work late they do so with pleasure.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The best company I have ever worked for!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great CultureFantastic PeopleIncredible ProductsWonderful BenefitsExciting future</pros>
<cons>Cons – None that I can find yet!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the culture intact</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – They really take excellent care of their employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Don't have any that come to mind.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Toronto (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company to work for, in a very exciting stage!”

</title><pros>Pros – - Company has done a lot to focus on their employees in the past six months, really listening to what we want (performance management, career development, feedback)- Great perks (catered lunches, breakfast daily, First round Fridays)- Product is revolutionary- Company culture and spirit is strong, hope this will continue</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not for those who want a stagnant or "inside the box" workplace, not a con, but not for everyone</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep focusing on your employees, they are what drives the business!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good nd co-operative staff”

</title><pros>Pros – superiors nd co-workers are very kind in nature nd supportive</pros>
<cons>Cons – n a to this company to work in very good culture</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – lead followup is not strong</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing company to work for. Fantastic work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Great culture. As an intern, they gave me the opportunity to prove myself in some relatively high profile opportunities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Like all web dev, lots of bug fixes. But so is the life of an intern</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Program Implementation Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Slight Chaos”

</title><pros>Pros – Relaxed atmosphere, smart intelligent people, highly successful in their industry and innovative company looking at how the world works and functions and what the next generation of employees want and need to be successful</pros>
<cons>Cons – They continue to loose their great employees because there is no career path or goals for them to benchmark themselves against; therefore they need to address this immediately or they will continue to loose more top notch employees. In order to be more successful more process needs to be put in place in order to ensure our clients understand what is going on and how we are changing as a business. Clear vision needs to be put in place and clearly articulated out to employees so they see the future path for this growing company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees and understand what they are requesting to make them more successful in their position.  In the end, with being more open to suggestions and helping carve out a career path for specific individuals, Management will be successful also. Plus you need to start charging for your implementation services, you are loosing money on this transaction and you are no longer a 1 year old company it has been 10 years and you are an industry leader; therefore get a move on changing the costing model.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sycophants rejoice!”

</title><pros>Pros – Free food and casual dress are nice, as are the perks along the way.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This is the place where all standard modes of operation you've previously experienced mean nothing.  If you've passed the screening and intense interview cycles and they make you an offer, think long and hard before accepting.If your intent is to work hard at playing politics, then accept the offer.However, if your intent is to work hard and focus on output instead of playing 'the game', then take a pass.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Clear out the self-serving 'leaders' and practice what you preach.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>9</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This company is nothing like what they pretend to be - does not practice what they preach”

</title><pros>Pros – There are benefits at this place like laptops for everyone, great work spaces/offices, a great dress code, food and drinks supplied, a drinks celebration every Friday and other things that are perks indeed but these are superficial and hide the huge cons below sadly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – To be honest the list of cons is insanely long. The biggest con which sums it all up is that working at this company is nothing like what appearances make it to be. Management says they are transparent but they are not forthcoming with much information - most times they tell people when they are forced due to rumors, issues or no other choice. Management presents themselves like they have a strategy and plan for growing and focusing the company - but reality is that it changes so frequently, randomly and without true research and strategic thinking (makes it impossible to keep your role focused in the right direction). The company claims to be inclusive and accepting diversity but unless you are in a clique, drink the koolaid you will be an outsider and anyone not in a favourites circle, good luck being properly recognized or rewarded, regardless of performance. Lastly, they claim they put everything on the table and speak honestly with everyone - nothing could be further from the truth - most discussions with management or senior leadership are lies right to your face. Lastly in terms of execution, whether operations, marketing, strategy, or product development, they claim to have hired people with experience and great qualifications (A Players) when in reality none of these people in such high regard have actually worked for decent sized companies and actually know what they are doing - they fly by the seat of the pants - and as a result the company is managed by people in way over their heads. As a result, while the company concept is great, it falls apart in every aspect of execution from strategy, operations, development, client relations and overall management. Oh and most of the hiring is done based on culture fit - yes that is important to get along - but it usually WAY overshadows a persons qualifications so many people are hired as long as they have minimal qualifications as long as the hiring people think they could be FRIENDS with them - seriously!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management need to take a huge step back and do some self reflection on every aspect of the business and ask themselves why so many employees are constantly leaving, even ones who have worked in startups, people with great qualifications and experience. Take a read and think about the points above because many people seem to be saying the same thing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>7</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company is just a showoff”

</title><pros>Pros – Well you get free lunch, a laptop, free breakfast but as mentioned in other reviews the lunch is awful and breakfast is sometimes well past its expiry.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No direction at team levelYour position is dependent on amount of cash in the bank for this startupPeople here watch and surf internet in the name of workNo incentives except for the stock options which you dont know if its going to materialiseWaste of time in company wide meetings which most people dont seem to be interested in</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Needs to quickly realise that people make the company and not vice versa.There needs to be some sort of performance reviewStop worrying about competitors and concentrate on what you make - which will make the company go forward</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Forward Thinking Employer”

</title><pros>Pros – Everyone here is incredibly talented at what they do. It's refreshing to work with incredibly talented individuals in a fast-paced company. Everyone has the same goal in mind and all work hard together to achieve it.Even though the company is growing at such a fast pace, everyone still knows everyone else and it keeps coming to work enjoyable.Having access to the stock options is amazing. We can see our company keep improving and succeeding in our space and know that we will all be rewarded even more down the road for our continued success.</pros>
<cons>Cons – With a fast-paced environment, comes lots of changes and extremely hard work. New deals means lots of new changes to the software and it's implementations. Not really a con, more a fact of business but it keeps us busy that's for sure.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>7</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An honest review from a past employee (no biterness) who saw a lot of change”

</title><pros>Pros – - They hire a diverse set of people (experience-wise)- Employees work really hard which I respect- Free breakfast, interesting events- Flexible work hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Before working there, if you've ever had any kind of social circle, you will find it bizarre how farternity-like it is- They say they want real feedback from employees, but they actually heavily encourage puppetry- Management has no idea what they're doing in terms of practicing what they preach- Unashamed of the fact that there are 'favourite' employees - and those employees are the ones who are willing to suck up- Inhibits the unique and soulful attributes out of employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management needs to stop patting themselves on the back and realize that this company is not all that matters in the world. There is very high turnover for a reason.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company with lots of benefits”

</title><pros>Pros – lots of benefits - free lunch, gift cards and a flexible workplace, 4 weeks of holidays</pros>
<cons>Cons – Basic pay doesnt match the standards for the position</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management needs to standardise pay's as per industry standards</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-25</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“its great”

</title><pros>Pros – fif i can do this job dn i vl fill great</pros>
<cons>Cons – the downsides workers have to work more</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – try 2 find more peoples</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The best career choice I have made so far.”

</title><pros>Pros – Achievers has provided me with endless growth opportunity, chances to be involved in areas of businss that I never would have thought I could be at the level in my career.  They truly value my opinion and I feel like I add value to the business and its culture on a daily basis.  It has a really grea fun loving and driven approach to business and it is incredibly motivating to work along side of some of teh most brilliant people in the GTA.</pros>
<cons>Cons – All companies have frustrating moments.  I think its fair to say that the entrepreneural businesses are not for everyone.  The amount of autonomy, change and rapid growth is 90% of what I love, but can also be the 10% of my frustrations as it is hard to flex 100% all the time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The business is brilliant!!!  You have a very talented workforce who are completely dedicated and passionate about the business.  My only advice would but that as you grow, do not loose sight of those dedicated people.  They are the busy worker bees willing to do anything.  I would also suggestion to ensure that all those amazing traditions, group get togethers and such continue to occur as we grow.  Its a great feeling to know that you are truly freinds with yoru colleagues!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A-mazing!”

</title><pros>Pros – Free breakfast, social responsibility committee, 4 weeks vacation, venture-backed, great benefits plan, and most importantly - passionate & driven people!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Because Achievers is such a young company and has a scrupulous recruiting process, we have a small senior leadership team.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on recruiting senior level executives who can provide opportunities for learning and growth, as well as instil better processes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I really enjoy working for a company that you are never alone, we are a team in working together towards our goal.”

</title><pros>Pros – It's an amazing feeling to not have to drag yourself each morning to work because Achievers has built a CULTure fill with great people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Achievers is a really fast growing company with many project happening which leads to overtime. It would be great if we get over time pays but they compensate with trips, celebrations, ipads during mini retreat.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – i would love if they can hire someone more senior in our field to mentor us, it's hard to grow.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Member Experience Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lovely People!”

</title><pros>Pros – Achievers does a great job of practicing what it preaches! People here take being a good worker and being a good person at work very seriously.The recognitions system also really works!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes my position is a little repetitive, but the more interesting cases that come in more than make up for it!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Junior Member Experience Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Energetic office that makes me happy to be at work”

</title><pros>Pros – There are so many opportunities to grow your professional career within the organization. You can tell that they really take pride in and care a lot about their employees. There is so much transparency at this office, you are never held in the dark about anything. There is real life team work going on here as everyone is all about making things happen together. The best part is, I look forward to coming to work everyday!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes I stay at the office for too long because I love it so much. We need a bigger lunch room. Thats about it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing what you are doing. I have only been here for about a month and not only have I been welcomed with open arms by my colleagues, but my senior leadership team as well. Hang on to this as much as you can and fight through those growing pains!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Achievers is a truly democratic workplace where what the people want actually matters.”

</title><pros>Pros – - great culture- hardworking people- fast paced- flexible work environment- accelerated growth- career progression- work hard, play hard mentality</pros>
<cons>Cons – - lots of changes (not suited to everyone)- trying to maintain the small business culture as they grow- everyone who works there is very hardworking, making it sometimes a competitive environment</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Leadership is really great at Achievers, but it would be great to see more of it.  Having more leaders at the top will help employees further with their career growth plans.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Recruiter (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My experience through the interview process and now being an employee has been incredible.”

</title><pros>Pros – Achievers is an incredible place to work, it is full of very hard working and driven individuals who are all passionate about what they do. We believe in our product and practice what we preach. Achievers and its employees understand and believe in the importance of recognizing each other for the great work that we do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Achievers is in a state of aggressive growth which means that we are always changing and improving our processes to make us even better. This is a wonderful state to be in as long as you are comfortable with constant change.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Achievers has an outstanding management team who truly believe in and live the open door policy. Our management team is very open to feedback and suggestions and they have done an outstanding job in growing our business to what it is today.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Inside-Sales Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fantastic Place to Work”

</title><pros>Pros – - Amazing Culture- Work with great people who are engaged and intelligent- Inspiring Leaders- Great perks- Huge growth opportunity for both myself and the company- Fantastic product offering</pros>
<cons>Cons – - A lot of change, you must be flexible and agile- Fast growth (if you aren't into that it could be a con)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – As we grow at such a fast rate, having a more structured onboarding and training process per role would help</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great culture, amazing people, awesome place to work...”

</title><pros>Pros – I Love Rewards is like no other employer I've ever had.  Every day is an adventure, the people that work here are excited to come to work every day, and the culture and perks are top notch.  You will work hard, but you will play hard too.  The team spirit of I Love Rewards is infectious, and the job satisfaction of employees is a top priority.  Employees never feel as if their hard work goes unrecognized.  Free meals and snacks, great travel perks, social responsibility days off, 4 weeks vacation, etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I Love Rewards only hires people at the top of their game.  If you are not an A Player, you will not survive and there is nowhere to hide.  For this reason, the interview process is extremely difficult and you will be asked things during the interview that you have never been asked before.  If you are a person who likes the 9 to 5, I Love Rewards is not the place for you.  Employees are expected to always be available including nights and weekends.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Inside Sales Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You will never work harder, develop deeper relationships with co-workers or have more fun. No other workplace is like it”

</title><pros>Pros – - Incredible benefits plan and comparable salaries - Great people - Constant change and innovation - Lots of autonomy - Very transparent - Exciting and fun environment to work in</pros>
<cons>Cons – - 9 to 5ers need not apply - Time will not promote you - Results always beat effort - The flip side of transparency is that you will be exposed to the downsides, poor performances and missed goals of your colleagues, and vice versa.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>SEO/SEM Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I love rewards is a place where people are passionate about what they do, and  get recognized for what they've done.”

</title><pros>Pros – The CULTure is the best I've ever been a part apart of, everyone is encouraging, helpful and fun to work with. Since you get to "own" your work - you really feel like you are a part of something big and you're doing your part to change the world.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everything is moving fast so it's a bit intimidating at first - but you feel awesome being a part of it!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Development (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tough recruitment process but an amazing place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – After a grueling recruitment process (they only hire the best) I was happy to accept an offer at I Love Rewards.  The culture is overwhelming but it is a lot of fun once you embrace it.  They definitely play hard at I Love Rewards and they expect you to work even harder.  The salary and benefits were very comparable to other jobs in my field and they can be flexible in order to get the best talent.  I have been here for a few months and I love working at I Love Rewards.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There can be a lot of travel required depending on your position which you may want to take into consideration.  Do not expect to work 8 hour days.  You're expected to do whatever it takes to be successful.  Whether that is working 12 hours one day and only 6 the next... the expectation is that you get quality work done no matter what it takes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I Love Rewards is the ideal place to work as it offers a fantastic environment with an amazing opportunity for growth.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great environment, great people, amazing product!</pros>
<cons>Cons – The culture is something we take very seriously and some people are not able to fit in with our culture.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – All of the leaders at I Love Rewards are great people and managers. They offer every employee great benefits, great feedback, and a great place to work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place for students”

</title><pros>Pros – The culture is amazing.  You get to work on different projects across different departments.  The people are super fun, friendly, and hard working.  If you're right out of school, the culture is perfect.  If you're more professional, not so much.  Having an MBA doesn't matter here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The CEO has his hands in a lot or almost all initiatives.  There have been cases where employees have been fired for challenging the CEO.  The salary levels were brutal.  The amount of hours put in were brutal.  Some promotions felt very arbitrary.  Extremely high expectations from senior management without any form of reciprocity.  Decisions made too quickly without thinking about the long run.  Turnover is high.  Little loyalty to employees.  Always looking for the next best thing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Put trust in the people you hire.  Hire people with experience and pay them for what they are worth.  Sometimes there's something to be said about traditional approaches that work.  Grow a small team and keep them on board!  Practice what you preach.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-10</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great work environment with challenging work”

</title><pros>Pros – Challenging work, and engaging work environment with a lot of transparency, excellent rewards and recognition program offered to all employees, constant feedback.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A lot, a lot of work to do. Often will require overtime to complete work and to keep up with co-workers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management does a great job at keeping the staff informed on their performance, also does an excellent job and recognizing employees when great work is accomplished.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>