<name>I state truck center Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/I-state-truck-center-Reviews-E251466.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2009-11-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“be warned”

</title><pros>Pros – i state is a good place to get training in major engine types and the newest technology. The techs working at this location are very up to date and helpful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – high demands place on techs which are impossible to achieve. Advancement is not likely for anyone working here. advancement is determined by percentage of  time on jobs compared to time quoted by service writers. Most service writers have not worked on a truck or have not for years. with that in mind times are quoted from an outdated book. only the times for job are quoted and not the additional time it may take to get to that item. Even when service writers are informed.  Most only get a raise when they put in there notice. Starting wage changed two years ago. some who have worked here longer than two years are making less than the current starting wage. procedures change daily as far as how things in the shop operate. Some people don't have to follow them at all at the cost of the techs time.on the other side customer bills get marked up further, customers are getting wise to this and are not coming back. Some of them i know personally. billing is a huge issue. It looks poor when customers are billed for shop supplies as a percentage of the bill. Then on the same bill get charged for brake clean. something that should be a shop supply. It is only a few dollars but the impression is made right away that they are getting double billed. What else is getting over billed.Since customers are not coming back there is not enough work. Techs are getting sent home early all the time. management blames it on a bad economy. Not true, other area shops are busy.very high labor rate. With a high labor rate people will not come to our shop for basic work when three doors down from us they can get it done for half the price.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – leadership must change there policy, this a recipe for disaster. management talks around these issues and do not fix them. Customers are not satisfied are not coming back. we have lost accounts that could have kept us busy due to cost.  Techs run out of work, not making money and being unfairly judged by a system that does not work causing good techs to leave.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>