<name>U, Inc Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/U-Inc-Reviews-E252756.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2009-11-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Administrator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Promises of leadership, quality, intelligence and growth fall flat.”

</title><pros>Pros – The individuals, the knowledge workers of U, Inc are among some of the most friendly and hard working I've had the opportunity to associate with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Objectively speaking, this U, Inc. is an organization lead by ego and hubris. As a company that happened into web development in 2008, having a small amount of success, they forged on into full-time web development, adding to their e-learning line of business.Their model, using an outsourced team from Chennai, India is an excellent model and one that could work very well if not for the lack of knowledge in the areas of software/web development, architecture, development lifecycle, change management and project management. In these areas, they are functionally incompetent and despite an excellent support team that has the experience to provide improvement, the leadership constantly looks the other way, following a flawed path.The result has become a strained, and sweat-shop like environment for the overseas employees, and an envrionment without a work-life balance. Projects are continually behind, and the quality of their product is that of a website from 2001.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – To succeed in their industry, the leadership at U, Inc needs to learn to listen to their knowledge workers who are experienced within the industry, and to also go out and learn the industry - what are other organizations doing? What are their processes? How do they manage change? With these things, it's a start but not the whole puzzle, but it will go a long way to improving quality and the relationship with your employees, and your customers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>