<name>The John G. Shedd Institute for the Arts Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/The-John-G-Shedd-Institute-for-the-Arts-Reviews-E253811.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-01-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This place looks like a dream, can be a nightmare.”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity to work with national artists and get experience running events and festivals. Learn how to operate an organization on a very tight budget and in some positions solicit donations. Many positions are actually many jobs rolled into one.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Explosive, inconsistant management. Many of the staff are starting at their first job or inexperienced in the arts. Upper management will step in and micromanage at any time, running over anyone's authority. Be prepared to be thrown under the bus. Some years most of the staff quits after their first summer festival. High turnover.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The Board of Directors should replace the Artistic Director and hire someone with proven people skills who respects artists, then hire a graphic designer and subcontract a webmaster.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Venue Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you enjoy feeling demeaned, feel free to work here”

</title><pros>Pros – Hearing the music through the doors...sometimes. There were two staff members that kept my sanity alive.  I got an olcc license out of it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – EVERYTHING ELSE.  I second everything that has already been said on here. For a non-profit, they treat their employees like scum and the building is infested with God knows what that would always make my allergies flare up.  The Executive Director is well known for yelling at staff and saying racist comments, homophobic comments, and you name it.  You also get told how to do things by staff over and over again as if you don't know how to do simple tasks like putting stickers on envelopes (to be fair though, plenty of the staff telling you what to do are afraid of the Director too so they are too meticulous).  The director also takes on responsibilities that shouldn't be his and he doesn't do well (programs often have simple grammatical/spelling errors).  They also like moving you around to different tasks so you are never good at one particular task.  My own explanation for this is a. the director is paranoid that his staff are out to get him and b. he enjoys yelling at them when they screw up.  The list of madness goes on...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Quit and replace yourselves with people that have compassion and respect for others</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A decent venue for the arts, but a terrible employer.”

</title><pros>Pros – The John G. Shedd Institute for the Arts offers a very flexible schedule for most of its employees, especially its VA (Venue Assistants).  If you are fortunate enough to work there for a while you may even get to encounter some of the more famous musicians that pass through to perform (though this is heavily discouraged by the management).  The venue provides learning environments for musicians taking lessons and provides them with resources needed to  improve.  Working in this environment would make most employees feel satisfied that they were contributing to the community at large if it weren't for the many, many cons to working there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management, while existent, is poor and often incompetent.  Employees are often given little or no training.  Employees are often reprimanded by management for not knowing how to complete tasks that require training that they have not been given.  These reprimands can range from unfriendly, petty behavior to subtle threats of possible termination to full-blown cussing.  Management will also find it necessary to interrupt training of an employ in order to facilitate the completion of a mundane or unnecessary task.Employee input is not valued.  Ever.  Management often will ignore the good, hard-working employee and reward the employee who shows up late and is incompetent. Paychecks are often late and overtime is often not paid to employees who have earned it.  Employee breaks are often ignored or discouraged by management.  This means that during busier times of the year an employee (especially VAs) may end up working a ten hour long shift without a break to eat.  This amounts to a blatant violation of Oregon law and it happens repeatedly.   All of this results in an enormous employee turnover.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There is no way to fix the problems of this workplace without a complete "restructuring" of all management.  This could only be done by the board of directors, but it won't be.  They are not ignorant to the failings of this establishment but have seen fit to turn a blind eye to these problems.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The John G. Shedd Institute for the Arts- An Amazing Concept, an Unfortunate Reality”

</title><pros>Pros – Full time salaried employees are eligible for decent health and dental insurance after 3 month waiting time, good resume builder as you're expected to perform an enormous amount of responsibility without proper direction, fairly flexible with hours depending on your position</pros>
<cons>Cons – Leadership is non existent. Management is inconsistent and lacks in providing the necessary tools and support for being a successful employee, rule by fear, very little room for advancement, employee input not valued and often punished, pay checks not often distributed when promised</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Leadership is non existent. Management is inconsistent and lacks in providing the necessary tools and support for being a successful organization. The Shedd would be better managed in different hands. Management needs to delegate more so as to have enough time to do the things only management can do. Don't be so controlling.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>