<name>e-Builder Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/e-Builder-Reviews-E253464.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hard work, real people”

</title><pros>Pros – Company culture - work hard but have fun.  Clients come first - this is nothing but lip service at a lot of other tech companies but e-Builder really lives this day to day - the company's growth and happy customer base prove this.  Overall, everyone gets along with very little "politics", as you'd probably expect in a 100-person firm.  People are pretty direct - if you are not an "open" person you might not fit in here.  You have to be self-confident enough to take criticism from time to time, y'know?Upper management knows what they're doing and tries to model the company on other successful SaaS firms.  Company direction is clear and growth targets have been reached consistently year after year.  It's a meritocracy - if you do well, you will be rewarded.  If you do OK but not spectacular, you'll get to keep your job at least!If you believe in the company's vision, then you're helping customers save real dollars on their construction programs so that they can buy more school books, pay more teachers, build better roads etc.  You're working at a tech firm servicing the least productive and least tech-savvy industry on the planet so it's a challenge right from the get go.Things tend to differ a little from department to department, but if you're in Services or Development, be prepared for hard work and probably long hours - this is a small, growing tech company.  Yes, this is not a 9 - 5 job, but chances are you were told that in your interview.People who complain about being micromanaged are the people who need to be micromanaged because they don't get their work done otherwise.  End of. I've always felt very supported here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Like any small tech company, it's a "dynamic environment".  That is, it will get hectic and you will get frazzled but as long as you're honest about where you're at and ask for help, you will be helped.  We are always growing and so always behind in terms of our personnel - it's not the environment for everyone.  If you like a slow-paced, do the same thing every day kinda job, this is probably not the place for you.It's also a "no frills" company - the new office space looks great but if you're expecting a Google or Facebook work space you will be disappointed.  We live within our means e.g., no VC funding.I can see how the company would not be everyone's cup of tea but there's a core of about 30 people who've been here 5 years+ and we're not all a$$h0les, believe me.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay, benefits and "extras" will probably need to be improved to compete for top, top talent as the company grows.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working with e-Builder”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly people and good culture.  Culture supports work / life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work is often very simple and not intellectually challenging. More of the function of the work itself and nature of the role than culture or management. Lots of background noise in new office</cons>
<advice-to-management> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Do Not Work Here”

</title><pros>Pros – Near some good shopping malls (Sawgrass)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Micromanaged. Pressure cooker environment because owners want things out really quick. No adequate training yet you are expected to do things 100% perfect the first time. People scream and yell a lot - Managers constantly under a lot of pressure. In general, childish management. You must account for every second of every day and if you deviate you are in trouble. Turnover is astronomical. they fire many people - at the drop of a hat. they don't treat people fairly at all. the new building is better but not by much. the positive reviews on here are so obviously written by one of the VPs it is almost laughable. Half the company has left because of him - and he knows it. No real thinking; software all laid out by the powers that be. The programmers just do what they are told - they are not allowed to really design things - use their own brains. The pay is abysmal.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you are going to put that card all around about how you treat people with integrity, then live up to that. To date I don't see it. Stop being so greedy to underhire and overwork and insist that everything be so FAST. Learn some integrity.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exciting place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – e-Builder is a fast growing company with lots of opportunities for growth if you put in the effort. I have been able to change positions with growing responsibility multiple times. Brand new larger office space is very nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There can sometimes be more work than people to do it and that can be a lot of pressure sometimes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to keep hiring as a top priority, but don't compromise on the quality of people we hire - that keeps the team strong.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company - on the surface!”

</title><pros>Pros – The product is good and most of the employees are thoughtful, smart, helpful, hard working and really do care about their jobs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Leadership likes to toot their own horn and go to great links getting positive press (See reviews dated between 3/2013 and 8/2013). Why the sudden attention? So the CEO would get his prestigious honorable mention in the local Business Journal. They are the epitome of micro-management and lead by fear, not motivation. No room for advancement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I don't care to offer any.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I love working for e-Builder”

</title><pros>Pros – The Management team works hard to create career paths for the employees.  The new office space is a great work environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I wish it was growing faster so I could have more friends work there.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep using the referral bonus program for hiring new staff</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – I really feel like the work I do directly impacts the company.  My co-workers are smart, supportive and committed.  Management does a good job of hiring great people and helping them grow.</pros>
<cons>Cons – We need to hire more people.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stay the course.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Current (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overly micromanaged environment - stuck inside a box”

</title><pros>Pros – Health benefits start quickly,  nice coworkers, new office space is a great improvement</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company has aggressive goals for the next few years yet lacks strong leadership and infrastructure to execute.  If you want to have a voice for change, you'll need work elsewhere to be heard.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get out of your own limited, metric driven, and in the box thinking to take this company to a higher level.   The current model is broken and needs to be fixed.  Follow other SaaS company successes as a benchmark.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Current (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Do not work here!”

</title><pros>Pros – health benefits start quickly, close to home</pros>
<cons>Cons – new office setting looks like a call center, poorly managed, unreasonable work demands, promotions and demotions galore, morale decreasing, a lot of attrition.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The company is going to have a tough time retaining employees as the economy gets better.  CEO needs to clean house in Customer Success, HR and Finance and hire leaders who will take this company to the next level.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A dead end job”

</title><pros>Pros – Not much experience in management so you can do pretty much what you want.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hire based on needing a person, not based on the quality of the person. Very profit driven, not very customer centric (though they think they are).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't pretend there is room for growth. There isn't any.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fantastic. Owners of company and VP of Services mentored me to help me grow professionally.”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. The people. Hard working.2. Accountability - everyone is held accountable for work to complete making it a fair playing field.3. Knowledge sharing. It's done in so many ways. At the "water cooler" while getting coffee with the VP of services. Or a formal on board training with a senior analyst.4. My boss - VP of Services - supports me and doesn't micro manage me. I've been at e-Builder for over 7 years. His SUPPORT produces results. He wants to know what he can do to help. We meet weekly to discuss goals and next steps to help me prioritize.5. Fun - we make a point to build bond with our team. The internal team that puts events together make them happen throughout the year. Be it pool, bowling, corporate runs, whatever.6. Reward for good performance. Every year here I've received a raise. Bottom line - you do your job you will grow professionally and monetarily.7. Culture - it's transparent here. Everyone on the team needs to step up and OWN it. If they don't then there will be consequences. No dead weight here. This is the thriving environment I have grown to enjoy and prosper in.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Work load. We are under the gun these days. Thankfully we are hiring to compensate for what I call a serious sales engine.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep making it real. Hold us to a HIGH standard and make sure we keep continuing to uphold a strong level of integrity. It is what keeps the pride so strong at e-Builder!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great community”

</title><pros>Pros – - e-Builder is growing by leaps and bounds. The opportunities to advance are numerous and based solely on merit and ability to do the job.- e-Builder promotes from within the ranks.- Management encourages employees to challenge themselves and has a culture that supports and nourishes success. - It is a small company, so the work that you do has a direct impact on the company's bottom line, you don't do work just to do it.- Decisions and hiring driven by the company’s core values: Integrity, Teamwork, Innovation, and Responsiveness.-Smart people in key positions. My boss is far and away the best I’ve ever had.- Management really does care about the employee and employee’s family. You are part of a great community at e-Builder- Open door policy with easy access to all levels of management, up to and including CEO and President.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - LOTS of travel. Often for extended periods which can be difficult on families.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – As we grow, the challenge will be to keep the small town charm. Don’t lose sight of what really makes this a great place to work: the community that you’ve all worked so hard to build.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“e-Builder is a great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – - e-Builder took a chance on me and allowed me to move my career in the direction I always wanted it to go. Prior to working at e-Builder I was working just to work, now I actually feel fulfilled.- It is a small company, so the work that you do has a direct impact on the company's bottom line, you don't do work just to do it.- The day to day routine is very variable which keeps me from getting bored- The culture is one of accountability and caring so people do what they are supposed to do, and the company seems to care about how you are doing as a person.- Benefits package is very generous,  health care is free if you are single with no kids</pros>
<cons>Cons – - As with most jobs today, it would be nice to have more vacation time. A more European approach to time off would be my preference- The work load is sometimes very demanding because the needs of the customer are seen as paramount and some customers are very demanding</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't let the company move away from its roots of hard work and innovation. Don't get too comfortable with the current run of success and start coasting.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Staff (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not recommended”

</title><pros>Pros – They give benefits to you from your very first day (medical benefits) and the benefit is a PPO health plan.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The office is cold like a freezer.They have not short term disability so if you get pregnant you have no money coming to you for three months and you have to pay them for your medical care insurance.they let people go all the time and at the tiniest pretext. They have a reputation for that. A few people told that to me when I first started. they said this company lets people go if you just look at someone wrong. It turned out to be the truth.Many people have left and many more are on their way out because of that and many other things and because of the director who seems to be out of control.They do not pay well unless you are one of their favorites but there are no many that way.It smells in there like some kind of paint i think it comes from a factory that is downstairs from their office or next door and it makes your eyes get tears.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay betterGet rid of that director who the owners seem to think is so great but he is out of control. That is why my boss left from HR because she could to stand him any more and she was a good person who could not support the things he did.Treat people like you would like to be treated. Learn to be fair and not have favorites people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Employee - Staff Member (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Very Micromanaged company”

</title><pros>Pros – the people are really nice (non-mgt)good equipment to work withgood with diversity</pros>
<cons>Cons – Ultra micromanagement - all the managersNo autonomy in your job - even professional levelFavoritismReactive, volatility among management (yelling etc)Fire very easily - and oftenCompany physical location is extremely cold, everyone ewaring heavy jackets - in Florida. Ltos of junk etc outside doors - Cleaning crew only comes 2 x a week. You cant' get supplies.Managers are under very high pressure to account for every second so that they pass that on to you - it is very "sweatshop" ish because of that.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give professionals more autonomy in their jobsBe less reactive/volatileLearn/brush up on some basic rules of management/good employee relationsNot so much micromanaging</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Energetic and exciting.”

</title><pros>Pros – My boss (VP) is the best I ever had.  Extremely smart as it relates to implementing complex software projects and knows how to lead teams.Just bought the entire team ipads as a thank you for putting in the extra effort.The company is growing by leaps and bounds.Management team is very open with strategic directions and seeks feedback early and often.Results are expected and latitude is given to obtain them.Learning from mistakes is encouraged and not criticized.Close knit team who travels together on projects.  Makes it fun.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Growth rate results in a lot of work and a lot of overtime.Needs to hire quicker.Too slow to fire weak links.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The main thing that needs to be improved upon is to hire people quicker.  Always being behind the hiring curve is a risk.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Staff Member (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“"Poor Experience"”

</title><pros>Pros – Starter job.Hours of operation.Diversed group of employees.Functional equipment.Office location is close to various restaurants for lunch.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Web-based software is not user friendly.Constant issues with the software.Micromanaged environment.Every minute of the day must be accounted for.No training. On the job training for a web-based software with many imperfections.Stressful.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Implement a 1-2 week training class which covers the software.Less micromanaging.Say what you mean and mean what you say (management).</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>