<name>J. Jill Group Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/J-Jill-Group-Reviews-E2557.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>P/T Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice way to experience retail on a more personal level."”

</title><pros>Pros – Beautiful clothing, fit, mostly easy to sell for the clientele that it caters to.Management is very supportive (at my store), sales associates are warm, supportive, and friendly.Interesting clothing throughout different seasons.Your clients are mainly repeat customers, which is a lot of fun. You get to know them on a personal level, its an easy sell, and you really enjoy spending time together.</pros>
<cons>Cons – J. Jill wants its associates to project the company's image, but sales associates barely make enough to buy the clothing, even with the discount. Its a constant battle between wanting to please management by buying something or paying bills, or feeding yourself.For part time associates, there are no breaks. Buy good shoes!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upper management should take into account the locations of their stores - the customers vary by region, and sometimes the stores are cornered into a spot no one knows about, so they pass it by without a thought.Also, don't hire more people when there aren't enough hours to go around for current employees!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Customer Service”

</title><pros>Pros – great people, fun atmosphere, room for growth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – not enough hours. varied schedule.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great”

</title><pros>Pros – good pay and good hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – not that i know of at the moment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>P/T Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice P/T job”

</title><pros>Pros – Good co-workers (makes for a pleasant work experience), great employee discount</pros>
<cons>Cons – during slower months often sent home without notice to save on weekly payroll expense.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – listen to feedback and ideas from employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun staff and nice atmosphere”

</title><pros>Pros – No commission, so no extra pressureNice, quality clothing</pros>
<cons>Cons – Steadily decreased employee discounts and focused too much on getting customers to sign up for the J Jill card</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't force employees to jump on customers with canned sales pitches as soon as they enter the store.  It's embarrassing and off putting to the clientele.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Brand-less”

</title><pros>Pros – The company has potential for lots of growth in the future & near future.Most people seem generally happy with there jobs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor or no sideways communication. Run extremely top down. It's never what's right for the brand, it's what the CEO wants. Corporate bonus is for management only, but feel free to work extra hours (salary only). Slow to adapt new technologies, they'd rather spend less on almost-outdated-systems, which just cost more in the long run. No corporate culture & the company lacks a soul. Senior management revolving door. Management is extremely miss aligned with each other and there lots of conflicting information with no clear direction. Direction from management is never black & white, but always conflicting.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Share the successes with the people who actually do the work. Real incentives are needed motivate people and help move the company forward & become "a great place to work". Figure out what the J.Jill brand is & stick to it! The brand needs to come first. And the brand needs to understand that it's most important resource, it's soul, is it's people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Leadership Vision not aligned”

</title><pros>Pros – work/life balance is fair, great working space and environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – constant revisions to strategy creates too many re-dos to assortments.leadership not alignedno career movement opportunities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Align your visionLeadership in Merch vs Design are not aligned, creates re-dos and extra work for teams, as well as uncomfortable meetings watching disagreements play out.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Easy laid back job if you never want to move forwad in your career.”

</title><pros>Pros – It is Decent pay.The job is easy and gives a great work/life balance considering most retail management jobs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Would rather hire outside than promote internal. Had to fight to get interview for open SM position due to being on necessary medical leave. Decided to hire external because i didnt fit the "35 and up" profile of the typical clients. Although I opened the store from ground up had the largest client list in the store, ran floorsets , most credit accounts in district ,and did weekly reporting for entire distict I wasnt qualified... They also failed to notify me of this because they claimed they could not have contact with me during my medical leave. Constant fear of store closing. Closed 75 stores all without notice and quality of product was consistantly getting worse with high prices. You are required to wear their clothing and gets expensive to buy a new wardrobe every season.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Recognize internal talent. Not everyone needs to meet a profile to be successful. I am currently a Store Manager of high volume, large corporation retail store and have been very successful. Top 1% of conpany last year.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I enjoyed my job there because I helped a lot of customers with there purchases”

</title><pros>Pros – CustomersTeam OrientedOrganizedManagement are Leaders and understandingA lot of positive energy</pros>
<cons>Cons – Honestly, there were no down falls when I was working there.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please consider me for this job opportunity for your company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Talk about being a great place to work but don't walk the talk”

</title><pros>Pros – Most of the people were good to work with and most had the best intentions</pros>
<cons>Cons – Revolving door...constant churn in leadership and company goals. Some senior management are bullies and could care less about their employees as people. Corporate bonus is for management only.  I believe that all add to the bottom line and if there is a bonus program, it should be shared amongst all employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat your hard working employees with respect</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Job started out great; micromanagement by senior management beyond ridiculous”

</title><pros>Pros – Customers are pleasant and enjoy the clothingStore employees are a fun group of women</pros>
<cons>Cons – Constant changes to the visual leave customers confusedUnrealistic sales plans that take all the pleasure out of the jobNot enough hours allotted for floorset prep or installation</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try spending some time in the trenches and see what really goes on day to day. Store management needs to see that the senior level is at least interested in what happens on the store level; try showing some positive reinforcement occasionally and not all negativity.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't expect to get a lot of hours”

</title><pros>Pros – All staff at my store are smart & nice, and were patient with me as I was learning the ropes.  I like J. Jill's accessories and some of the clothes, and the associate discount is generous (40% off full-price, 25% off sale items).  The stores are an attractive, pleasant environment to work in & most customers are pretty nice.  The schedule for each week is pretty fixed, so you won't get suddenly called in on short notice to fill in, or sent home early if things are slow.  When I am actually granted a shift to work, I really enjoy my time there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I was hired at what was supposed to be a "super-busy time" for the store.  During my first couple of months, I worked on average about 8 hrs. a week.  I thought if I did well, I'd get more hours later.  Well, then we went into "slow season" and everyone's hours were cut, supposedly because Corporate had cut payroll.  I was cut to 4 hrs./wk most weeks.  I kept hearing, "Sorry, no payroll" -- but they kept hiring more people!   I found out later that at my particular store, if you don't prove yourself to be a super-pushy saleswoman right from Day One, you're history.  It's not enough just to be friendly, warm,knowledgeable and helpful.  No matter how much a customer's buying, you must try to "add on" more items, to the point of irritating the heck out of them.  If you're not doing this, then rather than sit you down and "coach" you about your shortcomings, management acts like you're doing fine -- then quietly cuts your hours and hopes you'll simply get fed up and quit.  I have met many women who say they "used to work at J. Jill" -- the same store where I am -- and now I understand the high turnover.  (In fairness, I don't think this situation is necessarily typical of ALL J. Jill stores.  Based on my shopping experience, the staff at other stores seem more laid-back.)   I can't even take much advantage of my nice 40% discount because I'm not making any f-ing money.   If you love J. Jill products and just want to get the discount, feel free to apply here as a sideline or hobby.  Just don't expect them to keep you busy or even pay you enough to cover the cost of their clothes.  You should have at least one other job, or else a rich husband!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – (Does "Management" ever actually read this stuff?)If you want associates to push the J. Jill credit card, then make it a desirable card with worthwhile discounts and a reasonable interest rate!  Most of our customers are not so stupid as to think a 5% discount and a 27% APR is a good deal.Give the store managers more reasonable sales goals and adequate payroll.Don't expect associates to overdo the "up-selling."  Many customers will simply be driven away.Stop making wacky, unflattering designs that won't sell.  Skirts and dresses with weird, exposed asymmetrical seaming, or uneven elliptical hems, aren't "fashiony" or "cool" -- they just look silly, and women with taste avoid them.   Those same garments would sell much better without these weird design features.  Same goes for the huge amount of 100% linen that J. Jill rams down the customer's throat every spring and summer.  Many customers won't even look at linen, and a lot of stock is unsold at summer's end, despite big markdowns.  And how about some pants that are NOT low-waisted?  Many mature women are hippy and cannot wear ANY of J. Jill's pants.Finally, store managers should be very clear with new associates about how many hours they'll get and what their performance expectations are.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor Upper Management”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice employee discount. Management bonus program in place. Hours not horrible for retail.</pros>
<cons>Cons – NO accountability for the DM. Sales plans are unattainable most of the time. Allocated hours to achieve sales plan are a joke. Support from DM is non existent. Work/life balance can be a challenge at times due to the workload all coming at once instead of being spaced out.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't take everything your DM's tell you to heart. Listen to what the store level has to say since they work with the public everyday. Hold your DM's accountable for their time. Look at each store as individuals instead of grouping them all together in relation to metric goals.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Store Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice store enviroment. Customers were great. Nice discount on clothing. As far as retail goes the hours were not bad.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sales Plans for new stores are out of reach no matter what you are told in the interview yet you are held acountable to those plans. Most interacton between you and your Dm will be by email where you will be told how you are not meeting sales plan and asked for an action plan. Retail is not rocket science. The Dm needed to be in the store more than 3 hours on a week day observing the store traffic like on a Saturday. The Dm made assumptions about the sales staff without observing their skills personally. When there was a unhappy ssociate who I was holding accountable, who went to the DM, the Dm took her opinion and never asked my point on the subject. you are given very little direction on the adaptations you need to make to a floorset however; you are bereted for not doing the correct thing. Tthe DM came in on one day and move fixtures and on the next visit bereted me for the same set up she had set telling me I did  not learn anything because she was the one who was not following the company direction.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upper management has no idea what the DM's are doing or how often they are actually in the stores vs working from home. They bliss 2 to 3 stores a day for one maybe two weeks a month and then spend their time who knows where.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Positive work environment, great co-workers, nice discount. Pretty much stress free.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of organization on all levels. Antiquated POS software. Clothing quality has wavered in the past few years.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire new designers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Co-Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unprofessional treatment from upper management.  Encountered a lot of intimidation and fear tactics to motivate...”

</title><pros>Pros – The clothes are nice and easy to fit.  Very unstructured and comfortable.  Color palette is easy to coordinate.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible upper management.  Very ego driven and not appreciative of working staff.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>St Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great clothes. Great customers. Great home office support.”

</title><pros>Pros – A  generous discount allows buying the awesome clothes affordable.  Management bonus program in place. A positive work environment with home office support.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A crazy workload at times with unattainable goals. Limited amount of hours to work with causing a huge workload on employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make DM' s accountable for their time and follow up. Listen to and take heart to the info from feed back from the field.   Space out the projects over time instead of requiring unrealistic deadlines with limited hours.  Analyze scheduling scorecard when projecting sellable hours.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits and great people to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited career growth from my experience.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An unexciting outdated place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Work load is mamageable. Competitive salary and benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poorly designed product with zero fashion sense.  Leadership not interested in and do not value their people. Culture is toxic. Emplyee turnover was very high and leadership turned a blind eye to it.This company lost it's identity years ago and continues to flounder -if the company closed it's stores it would not make a ripple in the retail world.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – People work for people. Treat your emplyees with respect. Dig in to the root cause for high turnover. It's right there.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Multi Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“this place is heading in the right direction!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – The CEO has spent 2 years cultivating a strong leadership team. And the same for the field organization. After a prosperous year, enough teams have gained credibility, and the enthusiasm and belief in the brand is spreading. this is a great place to be if you want to be part of the growth and evolution of an established brand.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Still in the midst of change; some processes are slow to evolve. Not a con, every company has this upon them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to get out to the field, understand the reality of now and how it does or does not align with the vision. Good things are happening and the answers are always in the stores.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Call Center Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall positive, but there are issues in the past yr particularly”

</title><pros>Pros – I've seen the company start to turn around with MUCH better product in the past 6 months, sales are up. I really enjoy the people I work with and have had a usually positive rapport  with immediate management. The mgmnt on the ground at Tilton tries to keep morale up with contests, potlucks, etc which are often employee driven- however this doesn't happen as much as when I first came on board. For this area I feel it's one of the better jobs available. The facility is very nice, with a little gym available, and a very good outsourced cafeteria. The discount for employees is fabulous, as are the product. We are VERY WELL trained.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours are strange, not well planned, we are flexed down constantly and then xtra hours signups are posted. We are constantly understaffed and our customers have to wait on hold for too long. As earlier posted, we have a very short lead time to know our schedule and that makes personal life very hard, very few of us have the same days off. The hours seem to be computer-set so we come in and leave at very odd times- the constantly changing schedule is VERY stressful. Getting time off, as stated earlier, for family events or emergencies is very difficult. Mgmnt seems to be penny saving by turning off lights and leaving the bldg very cold on weekends which is an unwelcoming atmosphere for night and weekend staff. Poor communication from upper mgmnt, and the pay is very poor even for this area- as stated earlier, even with bonuses many employees are eligible for public assistance- the company should be ashamed! Seasonal employees are hired while permanent emplyoyees are given less hours- it creates resentment. New credit card contract places unreal demands on employees to push the J Jill credit card, with constant annoying contests to try to stimulate the card, it annoys the employees, makes us feel we aren't producing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value the excellent training you give your employees and UTILIZE IT!  Standardize schedules, it's really affecting morale. If you want to sell the credit card, give an incentive that customers really want like free shipping. Give long term well trained employees fuller hours instead of hiring well meaning but inexperienced people temporarily.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Straightforward, average work.”

</title><pros>Pros – The work environment is friendly, and the company brand is evident in almost every aspect of the store. It's not stressful at all.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As with most retail jobs, a consistent schedule isn't always guaranteed.Also, if you're not into the merchandise they offer, the sales incentives won't interest you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“worked there ten great years, new manager came in and it was six months of hell”

</title><pros>Pros – no pros with new management</pros>
<cons>Cons – manager only cares about sales. the store was always a wreck..manager had favorites.manager pressured guests into buying way more than they wanted so had huge returnsmanager was allowed to belittle employees, made only certain employees do the physical work.district supervisor was aware of manager's leadership style and allowed it because sales were good.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – take a look at the way the manager dressed and acted.what happened to the jjill image</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Clerk (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I am a Sales Associate”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun place to work everyday</pros>
<cons>Cons – No movement within the company</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Height of dysfunction”

</title><pros>Pros – There are some great people who work for the company and try to keep the motors running.  If it wasn't for people below the Director level the company would crumble.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I have never seen a company run so poorly.  One woman, Paula Bennett the President, makes all decisions. Everyone else is given the illusion of decision making ability, but then Paula swoops in and casts her decision without considering the hours of work and discussions that have already taken place.  Working here is completely frustrating.  The bonuses that are worked into the Sr. level and above's contracts would infuriate the other 95% of the company if they ever knew.  Company does poorly, gets sold and the executive team takes home a years salary as a bonus.  What did everyone else get?  Nothing.Upper management has been completely replaced as they started growing their legs and questioning the actions of Paula.  Once they started being a squeaky wheel, they were fired.All in all, an utterly awful place to work and I caution EVERYONE to stay away from here.  It will affect your personal life, your confidence and you will hate coming to the office everyday.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your people....you hired them for a reason.  Stop doing things just to do them.  Busy work is not productive.  Grow a spine and tell Paula that a request is not important nor can it be turned around in an hour.  Paula....time to step aside and let someone in that will be able to take this company where it deserves to be.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Health & Dental insurance and 401K</pros>
<cons>Cons – *Welcome to kindergarden (company supplies the crayons,paste, and construction paper)*Company mission statement does not apply to employees as employees are not considered to be human and are treated accordingly* Employees are never right. Team leaders,Monitors,Supervisors, and Managers are never wrong*Forget about  having a family or life outside of work as you will only know your days off for this week and next week and you will not work the same hours or have the same day off two weeks in a row. You are completely at the company mercy and have no say. This includes .needing time off for your kid's graduation or wedding or other important family function.*company regularly flexes employees down from 40 to 32 hrs per week. This happens so often many call center employees qualify for and receive public assistance to make ends meet.*Team leaders and supervisors use employee recognition program to give cash awards to other team leaders and supervisors.*lack of open honest communication between management and workers.They either lie or tell their employees just what they want them to hear irregardless of the facts.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employees who are treated as important team members and as human beings instead of as expendable minions are more productive and do a better job.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Initially a dream to work for, eventually a nightmare..”

</title><pros>Pros – At the time, fabulous compensation.  Good bonus package and constant morale boosting by upper management.Beautiful, unique clothing that was completely different.Associates as models.  In the beginning, no mannequins were used in the stores so the associates could be living models, in all sizes.Beautiful aesthetic.  The stores were gorgeous to work in.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Clueless DMs that allowed managers to get away with murder.A sense of disorder about operations.In the beginning, mandatory JJill dress code.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Better communication in upper management.  Hire more professional DMs.  Implement consistent direction for each store, streamline operations.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Key Holder (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Run the other way.”

</title><pros>Pros – Discount if you like the clothes.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You have to sell credit cards that are now 30% interest.You have to get customers e-mail and address and phone numbers.You are placed on call in.  If they need you you work if not you don't.You get sent home early if they don't need you.No benifits for part-time work.District Managers are unsocial and could careless about the employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You are going to loose some great employees if you don't treat your employees with a little respect.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-09-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK Place in a tough market”

</title><pros>Pros – Discount on clothing is pretty good</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can be very boring when not enough customers. Have to do  work like cleaning the bathroom, and washing windows.  No discount on sale items and at times customers fare better with there coupons and promos than we do as employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give employee discount on sale items, we would buy more, hence more money for you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“was great before Talbot's took over”

</title><pros>Pros – J.Jill has a great training program for associates and managers. They are very service oriented, and it can be a fun environment to work in.</pros>
<cons>Cons – J.Jill lost some of its unique qualities after being purchased by Talbots. Too much obsession over making comp numbers and not facing up to economic realities...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Bring back the unique qualities that made J.jill a special place to work and shop. The catered events were great, and brought in business</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-07-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“not a lot of news....”

</title><pros>Pros – When I started to work here, everthing was great. The staff was very helpful and understanding. I have a new position there and I have to say, it is very stressful being in this environment. Only because a lot of people here are trying to pull the wool over our eyes.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Communication is not the best. We get a lot of "looking down" at us a lot of the time. It's like High School all over again. -I know you get it everywhere you go, but c'mon.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay attention to what is going on , and let us know what is happening!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>C/s Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Scrutinized, fearful employees that just want respect”

</title><pros>Pros – There are some good call center associatesbenefits are decent</pros>
<cons>Cons – No matter how well you do, you'll get minimal if no praise.  This is because your callcenter team leader if fearful of (the head) callcenter manager, and or managementCliques in managementSome depressed supervisors bring down everyone elseLiterally treated like an elementary school student, (if you get up to go to the bathroom, you are watched all the way to the bathroom, and back to your seat, it's kind of comical.)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Converse with all of your employees, even if it's a "smile" or "hello".When you come out of your call center back office, make eye contact with the callcenter employees.Think if what your about to complain about is actually important or not before you speak.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-07-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Sales/service (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not worth working for”

</title><pros>Pros – One of the best health/dental packages in the area. Overtime available on a regular basis.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This place is a pressure cooker waiting to blow. Micromanaged employees are threatened and terrorized by a middle management that hands out verbal and written warnings as a way to control employees. If you dare to disagree or question you disappear and become one of the ex employees that has "left to pursue other interests".  If they can't find anything to get rid of you with, and they want you out, they will manufacture something. Promotions are based on how willing the person is to do anything, not necessarily moral, and not ask questions, rather than on competancy. Employees are critisized on a daily basis and are treated as though they are still in kindergarden.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Time to take a good, unbiased look at call center management and do some major housecleaning and restructuring. Get someone in there who knows how to manage and respect employees and inspire confidence. Recognize competence and potential and use it as a basis for awards and promotions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lot's of Job Bulling Job lookers beware !!!!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – There are no good reasons to work for J.Jill  1 they have unfairly secret shoppers that rate you terrible , also the District Manager thinks that she all that, never become her friend she will chew you up and spit you out. There is no trust.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Talbots has taken over and J.Jill is not doing very good they promise you the world and you get the boot. There has been several turnovers in the co. I believe that there is a District #15 that is not doing very well.  If they got rid of the devil wears prada things would be much better. I'm sure corp. does not know what she is up to. She is like a black widow spider attacks at any time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Senior management DM's  don't want to hear anything they just want to know why your not making your numbers  they are not very helpful theirs lots of bullying going on in some locations by the District Manager and they permit it. This should be banned. When she wants something then shes nice . Overall out look it is one of the worst nightmares in my life I would not recommend this place to the animal rescue.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Little to no corporate support”

</title><pros>Pros – It is fun to work with guests; they are loyal and enjoyable.  The store level team can become a close knit group.  Employee discount is good and the clothing is quite wearable, although quality is not as goods it used to be.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Corporate management is reactive rather than proactive, there appears to be little pre-planning with store level changes last minute and little to no concern with the pressures put on the store staff.  There is no reward for hard work and success, but stores are blamed for missing sales goals.  There is no incentive to retain good employees and there is a large turn-over in both full and part-time store employees, most moving to other retailers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Realize that without the sales staff at the store level, you would not have a job, not the other way around.  The part time sales staff is generally very hard-working for very little pay and just a little appreciation of them goes a long way.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“J Jill...”

</title><pros>Pros – company is based in mass</pros>
<cons>Cons – no bonuses for management other than store manager? as if the store manager runs the store by themselves.  it's a slap to the face to co manager and assistant managers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – acknowledgement of work, it's a group effort not just one person to pull off the success of a store, get real</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“stressful”

</title><pros>Pros – great peers and others to commiserate with. there are some really smart people who work there but they become burnt out and uninspired very quickly</pros>
<cons>Cons – no forward thinking, lots of people throw you under the bus, everything is reactive, very unprofessional. really long hours and decisions are constantly changing</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – listen to your employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Call Center/Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“grade school all over again”

</title><pros>Pros – health insurance, dental and eyeglass</pros>
<cons>Cons – Insurance offerings are great, but you don't make enough to purchase any of them. Schedules are tough,  start times and days off are never the same, difficult to have personal life and who sets a schedule start at 10:10 or 10:20?  Breaks are ridiculous, if you work 7-1/2 hours a day you get one 20 minute break, barely enough time to eat.  Huge turnover in staffing, hardly see anyone smiling/</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None-management obviously knows what going on and don't care to make changes that would make it a decent place to work</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was a pleasure to be around a friendly and calm environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Everyone seemed very amicable and it made for a positive work environment to be in. There was definitely a sense of synergy and appreciation for your work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Departments seemed to be so separated and it perhaps added to a sense of divide at certain times. The company was larger than it is now, so perhaps things are different.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't Be Fooled!”

</title><pros>Pros – Sharing the love of the product with the customer is like being with a good friend.Many of my co-workers are great to be with.Salary  competitive</pros>
<cons>Cons – Like a "Sweat Shop" - if you are salaried you are expected to spend your life there.  A pitch is made about the life/work balance, but there is none, it is all work because you have no payroll.You are expected to hire great people who can advance, but in my district, no one advances, new managers are hired from the outside.Every thing is last minute - there is always scrambling to change promos because business is not up to expectations.  Yet the promos are poorly planned and the customer is disappointed in the offering.  Then we are to blame because the product didn't move.Too many metrics - they compete.  If you don't sell at least 3 items to everyone who comes through the door, open a J. Jill charge and get an email, you hear about it.  No accounting for the mothers with children, the husband and wives or the busloads of senior citizens just out to "look" and have lunch.  None of it is figured into the conversion expectations.No positive reinforcement.  But, you will always hear what you didn't do good enough.  My DM's mood swings depend on your performance.  She really does not care about anything except the numbers.  Too bad in our present economy. But no doubt there is someone on her back too.The floorsets occur once a month and you do not get any extra hours - in fact, sometimes the hours alloted for that week are less than other weeks? It usually takes about 32 hours.  Corporate really has no touch with what is going on in the stores.  The quicker you get it done the more the expectations increase for the next time - but if you don't get it done you are in trouble.  Managers lie about how quickly they finish and just hope the DM doesn't pop in unannounced.Micromanagement is oppressive.  They hire bright, experienced people and do not let them make any decisions.  It is an environment of "do as you are told - you do not know anything", but we will ask for your input and do nothing about it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Maybe hire some upper management at the corporate level who have come through the ranks of field employees.  Understand that the employees in the stores are the ones with their finger on the pulse of the customer.  Recognize who your customer is (the 40 to 70  year old woman - mostly the50-70 group) and design to fit them.  Give them what they "want" to wear not what you want them to wear.Value your employees and treat them with a little respect.  Most of them really want to succeed and that spells success for the company.  Maybe give up a bonus or 2 and throw the money back into payroll so that we can give the customer the world class service that is expected.  You guys just don't get it that no matter how you configure the scheduling that it is unpredictable and we will always fall short of having the people needed to get the metrics that you demand.  Try running the business in real time rather than using excel worksheets and formulas - you know - you might even trim down employee expenses up there in Quincy at the exec level it you cut out some of the formula analyizers - just think, you could use it to advertise!!!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Key Holder (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Difficult”

</title><pros>Pros – The customers and fellow employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not fair in salary, ruder upper management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Fix it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very negative upper management, old fashioned thinking, stifling”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits if you're full time, otherwise, none.  Good discount on clothes.  Local team (in-store) is really supportive, proactive, fun.  Customers are great -- very loyal, very friendly, just genuinely good people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company is stuck in the 80's in many ways.  They have a very top-down management style and don't listen to employees in the field.  They give a lot of lip service to the notion that our input is important (we even fill out nightly feedback forms) but the reality is that no one is listening.  From the district level on up, they seem to think they are royalty, they know what's best for the little people and their words/thoughts/decrees shouldn't be questioned.Our DM is extremely rigid and doesn't allow the tiniest bit of creativity or resourcefulness when it comes to merchandising or marketing or growing the business.  DM micromanages to the nth degree but misses the big picture.  Example: we beat last year's comp and beat this year's plan for the month but DM criticizes us for having low conversion on a couple days out of the month.  The negativity is very discouraging.  Never praised for anything but always criticized for every tiny little nitpicky thing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Step into the 21st century with your technology, your communications and your marketing - ever heard of social networking?   Unclench a bit and give your local teams some leeway with merchandising -- allow them to put their individual store's best-sellers in prime spots rather than only the company best-sellers.  Climb out of your ivory tower and work in the stores once in a while.  Not as a grand gesture of the king/queen bestowing their presence on the peasants in the field but as equals genuinely interested in the people doing the day to day work that keeps the company functioning.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Key Holder (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Disappointing...Mislead”

</title><pros>Pros – You may meet a couple of very nice people, as this writer did.You may get lucky and find a bargain on some clothing.You will have the opportunity to see the new collections and various trends in colors and styles.You will meet some very nice people—your customers—treat them well.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In the store where this key holder works, the assistant manager is the 'teacher's pet', and can do absolutely no wrong. Lucy break for her, as customers complain about her frequently, but, that is acceptable in this particular store. It is very obvious that she is being groomed for bigger and better things. The remaining staff are her 'ladies in waiting'. Multiple phone calls are made by this assistant manager to the manager (if the manager is not in the store), as she cannot make decisions or actually operate the store when left 'in charge'.The name of the game is do your job correctly, with no room for human error, whatsoever, and at break-neck speed, regardless of whether or not you have been properly trained to perform a particular task or duty. Any slip up and—fear the wrath of the auditor! Period! Big Brother must be over-seeing this particular store! One can easily feel bullied.This old retail maven can easily translate those sorts of remarks, and posturing. The better the paper work, the better control over shrinkage, and the meeting of set goals, translates into management  bonuses. It's all about getting the bonus—and yes, on the backs of 'the little people'. This is not unique...most retail stores operate this way.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The hiring practices of this store (in which this key holder works) are questionable, at the very least. During this key holder's hiring interview, she was told that she would be given approximately so many hours weekly. This writer accepted this job, based on those comments and promises made during the interview( with the manager and the above mentioned  assistant manager ) to be truthful and accurate. After a week or two of never receiving hours remotely NEAR what was discussed, this key holder felt duped and strung on, and still does. Strangely, one evening , this key holder was working with another associate, and the key holder mentioned to the associate that the new schedules for the following week were prepared. After reviewing her schedule, the associate began to tell the key holder how she was told she would receive far more hours then she has ever received, and how she had to pick up another job, to cover the lack of hours promised and never delivered. After the key holder recovered from the deja vu wave, she shared with her co-worker that she too, had that very experience.Is there any wonder why morale is low and the want ads are so closely followed? The practice of luring people under false pretenses has this key holder on alert, and constantly watching her back. Under such conditions, how can anyone in management expect to be respected (no less trusted)? This key holder has the ability to be a great asset to the J.Jill company,  at a much higher management level, as she is intelligent, and educated—and is astounded by the petty way in which hours and the hiring of personnel is practiced. Although there are no extra hours in which the store can provide its' current staff, more people are being hired!!One very troubling practice which occurs regularly, is the working off of the clock. By doing this, this key holder believes the numbers are thwarted, and greatly inflated—the taste of bonus money really is sweet.>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>Attention!!Anyone in the J.Jill Executive Departments!!Be advised that The Peter Principle of Business is strongly practiced where this key holder works!! It is alive and well...and irregularly obvious to this key holder. Please, do take note.Everyone is an important part of your team, and this key holder would suggest that attempts to utilize the particular talents possessed by each associate could benefit all. You will have a stand out stores, and you will have very happy associates. Nothing can top that combination...With some fine tuning—this key holder feels J.Jill could become a shark, instead of being a cute goldfish, in the world of fashion retail. It appears to this writer that J.Jill does know who their clients are. This key holder sees great potential.>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>>PS: Remember too, your servant really is your master!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No Vision, Lack of Leadership.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great, talented team of seasoned pro's.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Directionless, consistent pattern of second guessing every decision. Very seasoned team is not empowered.  Energies misguided.  Lack of basic systems that would save time and reduce costs long term.  Extemely poor internal communications.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Immediate need to articulate a vision for the Brand and guiding the team toward that goal.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>PT Keyholder (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you can ignore incompetence, you can get through the day.”

</title><pros>Pros – I enjoy the company discount which allows me to purchase some great clothes and accessories.Being able to directly order from the catalogue through the store is convenient .</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much paperwork. Too many forms to process and e-mails to read..Timelines on floor sets and marketing schedules never fit in payroll budgets.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – When corporate visits the stores, they need to really listen to the employees. Listen to the negatives and offer solutions. We work hard and corporate sits behind a computer and sends out e-mails. Paula? Are you listening?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok”

</title><pros>Pros – Salary rate is pretty fair.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is inflexible about schedule</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A way to get retail experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible hours, good customer service</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor district management, low pay, no appreciation, unfair favoritism</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't unfairly single people out and try to get them to leave by making their jobs miserable</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“positive”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible, good benefits, great discount.</pros>
<cons>Cons – on call shift, merchandising direction.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A typical retail job except pay and bonus structure were not competitive.”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice discounts, always changing environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay, no benefits, few challenges for part timers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would suggest a better compensation level hourly and bonus programs with team incentives. Show more appreciation for part time staff since most of the staff is part time/hourly and not salaried.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company”

</title><pros>Pros – was a good company to work for. The company is very professional. Organization and structure and friendly people. Good job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The downsides were the pay. The base pay was lower than I'd like.  You can easily find a similar job somewhere else.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The downsides were the pay. The base pay was lower than I'd like.  You can easily find a similar job somewhere else.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I have never been happier (even though I have the worst district manager on the face of the planet).”

</title><pros>Pros – After working for the Limited Inc for 10 years this place is a cakewalk; you need to be organized though, to make it here because no one else is. You need to be self sufficient and patient, you need to like to spend time talking to your customers and you'd better be packing a good sense of humor. All in all I have a much, much better work life balance now than I have had over the last 10 years. I see my family more, I know what a weekend is, the most I'm working is maybe, maybe 45 hours a week, not the 65 to 80 I was working. I NEVER take work home anymore. Seriously sometimes I look around and I try to figure out what to do with my free time. The dress code is filled with words like "suggest" and "prefer" they do not insist that you wear their clothes, but I'm so happy and comfortable now I do anyway. You can wear stuff from past seasons or the Gap or Target and no one will look at you funny. The other posters that were complaining about management infighting and poor scheduling, that's the fault of your local store manager, not the company as a whole.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are some downsides to J. Jill the first is that I happen to have one of the worst district managers I have ever come into contact with. She's disorganized and mean, she doesn't so much play favorites as pick out favorite targets. I truly do not understand how this person got into upper management. I had worked for the company 4 weeks and she thought I'd been here 3 months, she cannot remember the store numbers for her district, there are only 14 of us and the numbers are only 3 digits long. Seriously? She cannot remember when I am working, the hours my center is operational, the time zone I am in, the times she schedules conference calls, etc. I am amazed they let her run a car much less a business.J. Jill itself is a little disorganized when it comes to its stores, but I think that the bulk of its business must come from the catalog and internet. They didn't get us our plans for the year until mid April, they are sometimes slow to replenish to the stores, but we do have the option of ordering for our customers off the internet. There are ways to get the product to your customers, it just takes a little longer.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I wish you guys in home office would do an anonymous survey at the meetings when there is unusually high turnover in a district. I've only been here a few months and she's already run off 2 store managers... I'm personally not going anywhere I'm also not planning on rocking the boat or painting on a target because, this district manager is nutty; not only is she nutty she's a liability to your HR department.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>PT Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's just OK, nothing too exciting happening here”

</title><pros>Pros – Great discount on clothesEasy job for a sales positionEasy to get days off I need</pros>
<cons>Cons – Quality of clothes not the same as what they are known forSerious sizing issues makes clothing harder to sellHaven't been scheduled a shift in two weeks because of payroll cuts</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't hire new sales people when you can't give the existing ones any hours</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“just ok”

</title><pros>Pros – discount on clothes make s it worthwhile to work here for 6 months</pros>
<cons>Cons – hours were insane due to high turnover</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – see above for all</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“run away as fast as your little legs can carry you!”

</title><pros>Pros – hourly pay is not bad,time off when needed</pros>
<cons>Cons – harassing employees to buy jjill clothing, managers throwing each other under the bus to make themselves look better, sucky place</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – get back onto planet earth, revamp your return policy, you are losing money hand over foot, treat employees better!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No room for growth.”

</title><pros>Pros – staff down to earth.comfy clothes, if the clothes fitpay is okay</pros>
<cons>Cons – visual team is full of themselves. They get paid a lot but spend many hours to do a small project.The corporate staff often want nothing to do with the sales people and often the management, except for the head manager.lack of encouragement. no room for growth.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take advantage of your staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“best retail job I ever had”

</title><pros>Pros – My Dms have always been great and supportive and gives recognition. We are able to run our stores as we see fit. Corporate does seem to listen to the field to some extent which is nice. There is a great work -life balance. I hardly ever work over my 40 hours and if I want to take a personal day I take it. If you know what you are doing they leave you alone to run your store, no drama, no politics.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Corporate likes to visit at Christmastime... really? Like it's not streesful enough we have to put on a dog and pony show to impress someone who'll be in your store for maybe 15 minutes? They cut payroll til you are by yourself til noon or one and you are supposed to give this great one on one personal service when you are the only one there answering the phone ,placing internet orders, ringing up guests, and running go backs and in the fitting room... No raises or bonuses in almost two years.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't go visiting at Christmastime. Don't be so re-active to business trends.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best retail company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – great collaberative environment. fosters great customer service.</pros>
<cons>Cons – none to speak of. a very positive experience</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – keep valuing the contributions of your employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-09-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“In shock - I leave everyday shaking my head in disbelief.”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible schedule to some degree.  The customers seem to be loyal to the clothing line and they are often fun to work with.  The Employee Discount is pretty decent which is nice IF you like the clothes.</pros>
<cons>Cons – J Jill offers a credit card that provides the customer with a discount of 5-10%, how nice---right?  Be prepared to cram it down the customers throat over and over and over again.  I have been in the retail world for a little while now and have worked for a few companies in varying roles and I have never seen anything like it.  There is a store manager and a few assistant managers, generally one of the assistant managers is responsible for overseeing the credit card sales quota.  Believe me, if you do not shove the card down the throat of the client be prepared to be pulled aside and "coached" as they call it, which amounts to being questioned, bullied, & belittled for not closing the deal!I have no problem selling credit cards in a retail situation I have done it in the past very well.  This company is overboard about it, very disappointing and makes for an unpleasant work environment.Overall from what I gather it seems that there is a tremendous amount of pressure from upper managers (regional and district managers) the more you do the more they want.  I had an opportunity to join the management team upon my initial employment - I thank my lucky stars everyday that I didn't.  I am not a fan of job hopping but I think I am going move on as soon as another opportunity presents itself....it's toxic.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take a break from the numbers long enough to catch a breath of fresh air, it can only help.  Meeting numbers and being successful is vital to surviving but there is a humane way and an inhumane way to go about it.  Create a positive team oriented environment instead of  a toxic, negative one.  After all its just shoes, clothing, jewelry, handbags, etc.  that we are selling, there is nothing that involves life or death....have fun, smile, enjoy it, and your associates might too!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>