<name>Wayne J. Griffin Electric Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Wayne-J-Griffin-Electric-Reviews-E25776.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-04-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A results driven company where employees are rewarded based on merit.”

</title><pros>Pros – Griffin Electric is a company where you will be challenged to be your best.  The workplace is the very definition of a fast paced environment.  Many senior employees are talented and considered the best in their respective fields.  You can expect to learn a great deal working alongside a staff with many years of proven success.  Those who succeed in this type of environment can expect to be rewarded for their efforts and sacrifice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The culture is not for everyone, especially those who prefer a laid back environment.  You'll be expected to work hard.  The drive of the employee's is the reason the company has succeeded over the years in a very competitive industry, especially in today's construction economy.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Office”

</title><pros>Pros – Exposure to many different types of construction, knowledgeable senior department leaders from which to learn</pros>
<cons>Cons – Insane workload, mandatory 9 hour work day minimum (and I stress minimum), poor treatment and verbal abuse is an everyday occurrence.  Senior project managers & senior estimators paid 20-30% more than industry standard. Competitors can't compete with salary ranges.  Then works you 5x more than he pays</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Title of "Manager" is only a formality at this company... this company is the epitome of micromanaged.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Over Worked with little pay”

</title><pros>Pros – To be 100% honest here, it was a ok place to work, but there was little pay with alot amount of hours worked and no growth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There was no growth within the company, the pay is more than 20% lower than the industry average with little or no respect as a company. Entry level employees start with zero days of vacation, not to mention you have to attend school on Saturdays (unpaid) and grades are part of your employment, you fail the class, you lose your job. You have 6 days of work with only 5 days of pay at 20% less than your counter parts. My recommendation is find a different company. This company has an extremely high turnover rate.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You treat your employees with little respect and under pay them for the amount of work, you wonder why you have such a high turn over rate.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>