<name>J Smith Lanier Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/J-Smith-Lanier-Reviews-E258886.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2011-05-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A traditional company that is getting lost in the new age of broker/consultants”

</title><pros>Pros – Good environment. Good Job security. Good People.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow to adjust to market trends. Not much opportunity for young people. Poor salary for same jobs in the area.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you are not going to be progressive - just sell already. Embrace the EB side of the insurance world and embrace technology.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Benefits Account Management (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company for a white male who graduated from UGA or Auburn”

</title><pros>Pros – Great employees. Been in business for many years.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is no employee diversity, mostly white males. You fit into the "in" crowd or frowned upon, if not. Welcome to the 1960's...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I think they are blind.  As long as the company is making money they don't care.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager  (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Ol Boy Network... (set your watch back 20 years if you work here...)”

</title><pros>Pros – There were some very nice people working at Lanier when I was there.  It was also very close to my home, and with Atlanta traffic the way it is, that is a big plus.</pros>
<cons>Cons – JSL is an "old boy" network.  Basically, if you're a white male and have a degree from either UGA or Auburn, congrats, you're in the club!  If you're female (no matter how intelligent, experienced or well-educated) you are considered the "hired help".   Salaries were embarrassingly low.  Bonuses were tiny to non existent, and totally based on the discretion of your producer.  There was no advancement potential whatsoever.  I couldn't get out of there fast enough.  Easily the worst job of my entire career.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Advice to management?  Realize it's not the 1970s.  Women are just as capable, intelligent, hard-working and driven to succeed as men are (sometimes MORE SO!)  Treating your support staff like the "hired help" and bending over backwards to cater to the whims of the Boys Club is simply unaccceptable.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>