<name>M-Tek Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/M-Tek-Reviews-E25851.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2011-08-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Place to work and to get foot in the door.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefit and pay.  Well established company that provide room to grow for any new graduate.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A good old boy company.  Glass ceiling is hard to break for minority.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to have a true Annual Review and stop the practice of reserved certain performance credits are for management position only.  It is a joke when pay raise already set and that the review scores has to be adjusted down to meet given pay raise.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineering Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unfair working environment for Non-Japanese”

</title><pros>Pros – Reluctant to firing non performers</pros>
<cons>Cons – Outdated software,  inflexible management,  doing it "like" in Japan.  Boarding on slavery</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give real authority to Western managers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Parts Assembly (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Management review”

</title><pros>Pros – Steady hours and plenty available</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management especially grop leaders are very reactive and are not situational. Most of the workers are temps. The Temp agencies do  basic background check. Temps for most of the time are not motivated due to the immature behavior of group leaders. There is a lack of professionalism. The assembly area folks are very vulgar and use a lot of offensive language, there is no respect for others. The group leader seldom corrects the problems. A horrible work experience</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need surveys from employees to improve performance of group leaders. Clean house. HR is a joke</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Not Sure (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“excellent”

</title><pros>Pros – Great ppl & excellent work atmosphere, great shift with weekends off perfect for me and my children as a single father.</pros>
<cons>Cons – being a new facility in chattanooga the communication and standard opperating procedures should be clearly specified, should get better as time goes on.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – listen to employee suggestions, they do the job and can always improve on current processes. company meetings on how things are headed for the future would be nice.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>