<name>Kids R Kids Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Kids-R-Kids-Reviews-E258033.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Teacher (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dream Job!!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Kids 'R' Kids gave me training and a fresh start to a new career.  The people are fantastic!  I loved working with the children and getting to know the families.  The Director was incredibly supportive and gave me lots of encouragement.  I was treated like a professional and not a babysitter.  I would still be working there if I had not relocated.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can't think of anything negative to say other than I miss Kids R Kids.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-31</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Am Float (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I love where I work, it feels more like a second home”

</title><pros>Pros – flexible, friendly management, employees are valued and treated with respect, competitive wages. friendly teachers, always happy and smiling. beautiful building.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some teachers hired are not "quality" and have been let go. Some are still working, and need to be either let go or fired. ASAP.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – VALUE the good employees, the teachers who go above and beyond for the school and the class. See the good that they put into making Kids R Kids a terrific place. Don't let good teachers slip away..a school is only as good as the staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hug first, then teach”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of support and training opportunities, Children learning through play, Hug first, then teach motto, experienced teachers make teamwork happen effortlessly. Properly maintained media and technology equipment for teachers and children.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is a high focus on the appearance of the center, less on employee satisfaction. Franchise is too involved in day to day operations with restrictive policies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Happy employees make happy children, Happy children make happy parents, Happy families equals high enrollment.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Daycare Worker (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Daycare worler”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with children and taking care of them</pros>
<cons>Cons – Dealing with the parents and listening to them</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Teacher (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awful, awful, awful”

</title><pros>Pros – The kids.  I felt so sorry for them while I worked there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unfortunately, there really is nothing good to say about this employer.  Put it this way--I would never put my kids with Kids R Kids.  Ever.  Management is beyond terrible.  Staff, or "teachers" (what a joke that term is) are tired and for the most part awful.  There are not enough teachers per child, so the rooms are full of chaos and teachers can't even leave to go to the bathroom for hours sometimes.  Some so-called teachers regularly use foul language in front of the kids if they think the kids are too young to notice, and management does nothing about it.  Management will try to squeeze kids into the classroom when they are already at the limit.  If a parent is unhappy, management will try to find a way to blame it on the teacher and will try to talk the parent into thinking it was the teacher's fault.  Employees are not treated with much respect from management and are disrespectful to other employees as well.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management needs to treat teachers with respect and not as though the teachers are the enemies of the institution.  You have to sometimes refuse the potential profit from potential parents in order to maintain a structured, well-run environment.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Teacher (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I love my classroom and kids!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great curriculun for the kids. Easy  lesson plans to run a fool proof class room even if you have no idea how to write lesson plans. Effective curriculum. Great perks depending on management. Benefits such as dental and medical offered. Management will listen to ideas you have to improve school.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not the type of company to stay with if your looking for upward mobility or good raises. My center has great perks throughout the year, but raises are not that great of a change maybe 25 to 50 cents. Not alot if your starting at $8 or $9. Definitely negotiate pay if offered position. Benefits package is expensive compared to actual salary gross.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Teacher (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun, fast-paced environment!”

</title><pros>Pros – Pros include that you get to play with kids all day, you can create your on creative lesson plans, great bosses, hours reasonable, weekends off!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some of the kids parents can be annoying and at times children can be overwhelming.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Teacher (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Kids are NOT Just Kids”

</title><pros>Pros – It's clean. Teachers don't have to create their own lesson plans, so every Kids R Kids has the same curriculum/ lessons. The teachers are very good at their jobs, but when you look at them, you can see how unhappy and worn out they are from the children.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I was extremely dissatisfied with the quality of learning at Kids R Kids for several reasons:1. The school is run like an absolute circus. At Kids R Kids, the motto is, "hug first, then teach" which means, "Oh well, kids are kids." Instead of disciplining the children when they have done something wrong, they redirect/ distract them. The children do not learn consequences for their actions, but instead are just guided to do something else when they are misbehaving. On paper, it sounds like a wonderful place for children to learn and grow, because they are encouraged to play nicely together and creatively together, but it doesn't work when there are 20 children in a classroom with no discipline.At Kids R Kids, the teachers are not allowed to give any sort of punishment to the children, which means there are never any negative consequences for their actions. You are only supposed to use positive re-enforcement and when you reward one child, you are supposed to reward all of them. You cannot use time-out or taking away privileges as a form of punishment. You can't even tell a child, "no, don't do that" when they are doing something wrong, and instead are supposed to ask, "are you doing what you're supposed to be doing?" or "is that nice behavior?"In the short while I was at Kids R Kids, I was kicked, hit, spat on, and had toys thrown at me by children. I was also cursed at and yelled at by 3-year old's and according to the rules, I was not allowed to do anything in the form of discipline when I was treated that way. I was supposed to rationalize with them and use only positive words to get them to calm down. But in doing that, the children do not respect the teachers at all. They are basically free to roam around and do whatever they feel like, with absolutely no consequence at all and you are just there to suggest/ try to get them to do what they are supposed to be doing.Every single classroom was run in this fashion and the children's behavior was some of the worst I have ever seen in my 5 years of child care experience. This style of teaching probably works really well when there are only a few students who are already well behaved children. But when there are 20 children in a classroom and half of them are already not well behaved, then it is extremely difficult to teach a lesson or get anything done in the classroom.2. At the school where I worked, they fired the custodial company that was in charge of the cleaning of all the classrooms. All of the teachers were told that it was now their responsibility to do all of the cleaning of the facility, which included cleaning toilets and mopping floors. I believe the teachers are already are not paid enough for their incredibly difficult jobs of managing unruly children, but especially not when you add in custodial duties as well. Teachers are not trained in cleaning the school and should not be expected to mop and vacuum and do other cleaning duties when most of them are making less than 10 dollars an hour.3. When children (have a fever) are sick at Kids R Kids, they are supposed to be removed from the classroom and put in the "boo boo room" until their parents come to pick them up. Twice while I was working at Kids R Kids, there were students with fevers who were not removed from the classroom and put in the sick room to wait for their parents. We had one child who was screaming and crying in the classroom because she felt so sick and had a high fever, and when I asked the director to put her in the sick room she said no because SHE didn't want to get sick and she didn't want to hear her crying at the front desk. So instead, we had to keep her in the classroom, with 15 other children, trying to teach a lesson plan. It was impossible to get anything done at all because the children already were unruly and misbehaving, and then we had to deal with a sick child crying and screaming.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They really need to adopt a different style of teaching at Kids R Kids because they are not teaching kids to be responsible for their actions. I think the teachers, the children, and the parents would benefit from there being some sort of discipline.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was a great experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly staff and Nice Environment and a Great place</pros>
<cons>Cons – No benefits and no pay for overtime</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>