<name>X-Ray Optical Systems Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/X-Ray-Optical-Systems-Reviews-E260325.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Mechanical/Industrial Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work with nice people and direct involvement on important company projects”

</title><pros>Pros – Hands-on experience. Small place with small manufacturing floor so you get to know everyone. Broad range of tasks and assignments working with a number of different experienced individuals. As an engineer you get to work in the machine shop, with design engineers, and out on the floor in manufacturing. Company is very flexible with work schedule. Everyone that works there is extremely nice and friendly and company treats employees well. Get to interact directly with upper management, including President, on a daily basis.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Periods of being idle or having to go to people to get work to do. Sometimes you get small tasks that make you feel as if you should be spending your time working on something more valuable or meaningful. Occasionally tasks or assignments lead to no closure and remain open-ended leaving you a bit confused as to what its purpose was.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Company is young and continuing to grow quickly. Continue hiring a number of interns of different majors for various aspects of company. Keep up the good work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Executive Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Executive Assistant”

</title><pros>Pros – - appeared to be a generally positive atmosphere</pros>
<cons>Cons – - at the time the company was going through a transition which left my position almost unnecessary and I prefer to be busy. All intentions were good it just turned out not to be a fit for me.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>