<name>92nd Street Y Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/92nd-Street-Y-Reviews-E260703.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Usher”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy, interesting, lots of famous people come through</pros>
<cons>Cons – Evening hours, almost every night</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place unnecessary stresses but overall good experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent benefits met a lot of wonderful people made a few friends. Opportunities for advancement although quite difficult.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible hours, worked throughout holidays and late nights. A lot of annoying internal quarrels and bickering within the department. Everyone needs to focus on their job and being professionals.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take control the entire department is a circus. Management does not know how to manage.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A solid, respectable nonprofit”

</title><pros>Pros – • comfortable environment where good work is appreciated and valued• amazing colleagues who are smart and take pride in their jobs• community focused institution that sponsors top tier programs</pros>
<cons>Cons – • there are many layers of management that sometimes conflict and create multiple hoops to jump through on a project, sometimes wasting human resources to do so• full time non-manager positions are unionized, which might prohibit the incentive to excel or the ability to advance in one's career. turnover is low, which is fantastic, but promotions seem rare.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great institution, challenging work envionment”

</title><pros>Pros – You will undoubtedly learn a great deal, as many staff members wear multiple hats.  You will also have an opportunity to experience some top-notch cultural programming.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Because many staff members wear multiple hats, the workload can often be burdensome and overwhelming.  There also appears to be some disparity in recognizing staff achievements and awarding promotions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Reviews are an essential part of the growth process and should be conducted annually, if not bi-annually.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great People to Work With”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people to work with, many organized staff members.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of communication between departments</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Camp Counselor, Fantastic Gymnastics”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy Work with generally nice young girls looking to improve their gymnastic skills</pros>
<cons>Cons – Administration tough on summer hires</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Grant some more freedom to staff</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“fun summer”

</title><pros>Pros – The staff at the 92nd Y are great people. Once you work for them, there are alot of babysitting opportunities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The work days are extremely long. Private camps pay much more. They are a bit disorganized and tend to waste time in meetings.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The management should be more aware of peoples' personal lives. Do not assume people want to spend extra hours with coworkers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>