<name>Saatchi & Saatchi X Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Saatchi-and-Saatchi-X-Reviews-E261136.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-05-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“One of a kind”

</title><pros>Pros – LOVE the people I work with and the company I work for. I've been here for a while now and have seen some great changes. I get to work for the most awarded shopper marketing company on huge brands that go in the world's largest retailer! Yeah, sometimes I work past 5, but it's not all the time like many ad agencies. When you sign up to work at an agency you should know that it's not always a 9-5 job. I guess it doesn't bother me as much as some because I enjoy my job and believe in loyalty when you find a place that's right.S&SX has maintained the culture that originated from the former Thompson Murray, but have been able to grow the company exponentially. When I first came here from an above the line agency in a big city I didn't think I would grow much. But, I stuck with it and have grown tremendously both professionally and personally.Like anything in life, it's up to you to make what you want of it. If you show passion and craft your talent they will be there for you no matter what...like family. Even the top leaders are the kind of people that will stop what they're doing to tell me hello and give me a hug. You can't find that many places.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not always a 9-5 job. NOT for the faint of heart. If you don't love what you do, this isn't the place for you. We work hard and play hard. If you're not at the top of your game and always seeking the next big thing, you could get stuck in a rut.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue investing in talent and hiring only the best. And know that you are loved by the people you take care of.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice, but clueless”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice people to work side by side withPleasant environmentMost people know their job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most of the real talent has left or is planning to.Never ending work. A slow day is very rare. A grind.No growth opportunity what so ever.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Ignoring opportunity for growth will keep people leaving. A title change isn't growth.No recognition is given to exceptional talent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Clueless”

</title><pros>Pros – Generous salary when hired, but then you are out of luck for either a raise or promotion unless you are from the Arkansas office.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Still trying to figure out what upper management does, other than worry about the frequent financial conference calls.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Worry more about advertising, less about the revenue goals.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Saatchi & Saatchi X, Chicago”

</title><pros>Pros – Some smart people. Some nice people to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Needs much stronger account leadership. Who really knows how to motivate client.Needs more creative opportunities.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Place is a sweatshop. Creatives don't have much support and production help.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-01</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Incredibly talented and dedicated people”

</title><pros>Pros – Variety of campaigns to work onDifferent size and formats of retail outletsStrong digital commitmentCreative and execution drive the business</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work comes in waves - so busy you can't catch up and then will slow down.  Good thing is that the global network moves work around</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Marketing always has a lot of transitions in leadership - leadership needs to be more visible and not stay in their offices</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Executive Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Arkansas Razorback Good Ol' Boy's Club”

</title><pros>Pros – Building itself is fun and innovative; Saatchi & Saatchi (parent company) is also an innovative company. Name is well-known and has good reputation.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Immature and Unprofessional Management - cussing, yelling and slamming doors are common.  Many staff on a "need to know" basis and treated as though they are expendable.  HIGH turnover rate.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – SSX (formerly Thompson Murray in Arkansas) was put together by a group of good ol' boys (and 1 female)  who happened to land a contract with P&G.  Their growth story is amazing.  Unfortunately, the senior staff's management skills did not grow with the company.  While I was there I saw a lot of yelling, cussing slamming doors and throwing of items by VP's, CEO, COO.  The term "born in a barn" seems to apply to them.  It was the most unreal /unprofessional situation I've ever witnessed. Dina was not yet in charge when I left.  I hope this has changed since she's come onboard.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not great, slow moving place, no innovation and no clear business direction”

</title><pros>Pros – Working on P&G as a client, shopper marketing experience, nice family environment, great people overall but low on IQ and ambition</pros>
<cons>Cons – No clear career path and progression. Management doesn't know what's going on. Bad new business development. Clients are dissatisfied. work is average and no creativity</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management needs to reinvent the business model. Having headquarters in Arkansas for a creative agency also is not too good. Invest in talent and nurture your top performers</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Outstanding leadership, everyone is focused on doing Great Work. You can feel the positive energy in the building on a daily basis.  People are approachable and always willing to answer questions.  It's a work hard, play hard environment.  It's a fun place to work!</pros>
<cons>Cons – The work is very fast paced, if you don't enjoy working in that kind of environment it could be a negative.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“High-Growth for the Type A Personality”

</title><pros>Pros – Saatchi & Saatchi X is a driven organization, with inspired people who truly are some of the world's best at the hot discipline of shopper marketing.  For an employee, that means:Thought leadership and learningAbility to gain high-profile experience with leading client companiesPersonal career advancement as you and the company both growCompetitive salary and benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not for the faint of heart; fast paced and demanding beyond traditional 9-5 boundariesGlass ceiling; limited advancement at the top or if you're perceived as "home grown" internal talent</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart and talented people (not senior managment) who do the work daily.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Senior managment is horrible and gives no direction (boys club) which if you're not a part of you're outta luck.- No advancement opportunites- NEGATIVE REINFORCEMENT on everything- Agency doesn't value it's employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get some better senior leadership who care about the agenc not about their own careers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Planner (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A lot of Work, Not a lot of Direction”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are smart, the businesses are interesting, and the atmosphere is fun and light-hearted. Everyone is good at what they do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – At least in the Account Planning department, there is no constructive feedback, and no idea if you are doing the job right. You are expected to hit the ground running. The work is way too much for the number of people in the department, and unreasonable deadlines are issued regularly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You really need to re-assess the effectiveness and leadership of the senior management in every department.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fantastic place to dig in to Shopper Marketing.”

</title><pros>Pros – You can't beat the culture at SSX. The people there are special.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Advancing and growing in your role can be tough.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – New management has a great open-door policy.  Employees are encouraged to find roles that fit them and pursue opportunities for advancement.  They really focus on keeping a culture of fun while producing great work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours can be long at times but management is quick to make sure your efforts are recognized and that you can take off time when needed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the monthly town hall meetings.  They are great way to keep up with what's going on with the agency.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Planner (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“horrible place to work!  senor management was clueless and not capable of giving the right directions.”

</title><pros>Pros – it was acquired by Saatchi & Saatchi. The  Saatchi name is good on resume and might help you get interviews.</pros>
<cons>Cons – poor management and  leadershipno growth opportunity if you don't have the connectionpeople with poor performance were hired or promoted just because they are the relative or friends to the founders or senor management.It is the worst company i have ever worked with</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – need restructure of the leadership. Hire people based on their talent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Vice President (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Focused only on P&G and Walmart”

</title><pros>Pros – Work with great brands and learn from global companies.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's an Ad Agency, not a shopper marketing agency.  Only loyal to P&G, any other work with other clients will be pitched to competitors.  Arkansas vision is limited and international business has struggled since conception due to poor managers for international and abusive pricing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus only on Walmart and P&G and forget about growing other accounts or regions.  Close international, it only loses money.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>