<name>Merchant e-Solutions Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Merchant-e-Solutions-Reviews-E261510.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2011-01-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work environment is ok if you like selling.”

</title><pros>Pros – Potential huge salary boost based on great sales. Offers base salary. Able to work from home and create own schedule. You are your own boss.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nowhere to grow within company. Extremely strict monthly sales quotas. Benefits are some of the worst of any company I've ever seen.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Offer better benefits. Offer better incentives. Ease up on the monthly sales quotas. They should be counted quarterly not monthly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Person (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“RWC location : It really was a very cool place”

</title><pros>Pros – Under the previous administration I had a lot of freedom and was the most productive I have ever been.No Pros anymore, taken over by Brazilian 9-5'ers  that have no idea how to interact with technical people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Open plan office, and I don't mean low cubes I mean flat rows of tables. Radically, offensively open plan. Your work space is the width of your monitor and only 10' deep. Total conformity expected. No customization of the work space is allowed or Brazilian HR will freak out. Incompetent employees are kept on forever. Treated like an idiot by Brazilians who are insistent that their way is best, even when their way is some sort of cross between Mexico and 1976 America.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Why buy a company in silicon valley if you have no intentions at all of learning how and why we do things the way that we do.  Don't make radical changes to the office environment, that are clearly intended to be oppressive, without interview stakeholders. If people say they'll hate it, don't do it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Help Desk Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor Management Direction”

</title><pros>Pros – Co-Workers are great, and the benefits are good as long as you only want them for yourself and not a spouse/child</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management makes decisions that cause a great deal of abuse to the employees by customers and they literally will tell you they do not care. They do not treat employees with the respect they deserve for the work they do and do not reward good behavior beyond an occasional pat on the back IF one of your co-workers notices it and reports it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat your employees like humans who have needs instead of cattle who can be replaced at the drop of the hat.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>