<name>Tech-X Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Tech-X-Reviews-E263120.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Research scientist”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity to work on great projects with high visibility.</pros>
<cons>Cons – not much thing to say.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Scientist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tech-X works on great problems and is a good place to work if you are a PhD”

</title><pros>Pros – Tech-X gives most of its employees many opportunities to grow learn new skills. The company is filled with bright, helpful people and good problems to solve.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you are not a PhD and you cross the boss, you could be out the door in minutes. If you are a PhD, you need to bring in money through grants or contracts in order to get any sort of positive review.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I know you guys are not professional managers, however, following some best practices would really help. Give employees feedback so they know where they stand. Spend a little money and build some offices -- cubes are lousy for productivity. In lieu of that, encourage employees to move conversations to closed spaces.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting and laid back but too academic to be successful beyond the SBIR”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of projects to work on.  It's possible to learn a lot of areas of physics / numerical modeling / programming in a few years here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Tech-X is SBIR driven.  If something needs to be done on a project, you first need to find government funding for it.  There is very little investment back into the company and this has lead to stagnation and a company that may never get beyond the SBIR.  Very little commercial income.  Not a good place to be (in the long term) if you don't have a PhD.  At Tech-X  you may ultimately come to the realization that the company is too academic making it difficult for the company to be successful.</cons>
<advice-to-management> – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>