<name>James G. Davis Construction Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/James-G-Davis-Construction-Reviews-E26597.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-03-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Family-Oriented Company with Great Benefits”

</title><pros>Pros – - rich benefits plan- small company feel with large company opportunities- great reputation- high profile jobs- good office location</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are no cons.  DAVIS is a great place to work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My honest opinion about Davis”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly people, very pleasant atmosphere. Great health benefits. A lot of projects so employees have enough responsibilities.Great leader in Jim Davis, he make an effort to get to know everybody and you can see how invested he is in the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Maybe because the company hires so many people, but I was never really trained, which makes it frustrating for me and for PMs who expect me to know. There are no standard operating procedures and it seems like some individuals protect what knowledge they have so it will take longer than normal to be up to speed. There is a lot of secrecy for some reason, so be careful they might stab you in the back. Work hours tend to be long at times with out overtime.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take time to train new employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Davis is a good company because of hard working people.”

</title><pros>Pros – Wide variety of construction project sizes and types within the Washington DC region.  On the cutting edge of technology relative to industry competitors.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As a fast growing company, Davis hires many new people every year, often burdening current staff with mentoring / teaching new hires (with already limited resources).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Information Technology Support (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company, but IT staff somewhat cliquish”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits package, strong company culture, some free gear, diverse learning environment, friendly PM's and assistant PM's, down to earth owner, well built IT infrastructure.Most everyone is very friendly and pleasant to deal with.HR dept. is greatThere are 2-3 true, good IT people there.Laptop to use/take homeGreat working space</pros>
<cons>Cons – Specifically the IT group is a bit cliquish, if you don’t play Call of Duty you’re not in with them (somewhat of a joke, but it is also somewhat true). There are a few people that have been there a long time and have put themselves in positions that they have made almost impossible to leave.Only the core IT group knows the inner workings of the company's IT infrastructure and environment. Any other IT employee is left a bit in the dark and DON'T try to document any of the procedures, troubleshooting, or inside knowledge as it would black list you.Sucks that there isn't room for advancement unless you’re IN.Word of advice, keep your resume on the street after you start there, they will weed out the threats/undesirables eventually.I really wonder how productive it is to have the one guy telecommuting a few states away, you know. How much can he actually do from there?</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Great overall management, IT management in particuliar could stand to shed some light on their covert operations.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work here!”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits, people, projects, gym, opportunities, morale, co-workers, IT, sincerity, ability to set your own pace and management style, advancement strides</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours, construction burn out, subcontractor baby sitting, management of subcontractors, change order disagreements, red tape with contracts and negotiations.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work, stay positive in times of a bleak economy, keep up the great benefits, thank you</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Client's Contractor”

</title><pros>Pros – James G. Davis Construction Corporation (DAVIS) was voted one of the Best Places to Work by the Washington Business Journal (2008 & 2007) and The Washingtonian (2007). In addition, DAVIS received the FastTrack Best Practices Award for Motivating and Retaining Employees. We are extremely proud of these awards as they acknowledge our excellent employment benefits, good management practices, and the dedication of our employees. A company can establish an atmosphere for success but it takes the personal commitment of each individual to make the work environment pleasant, challenging, and rewarding. DAVIS’ goal is to constantly nourish this atmosphere so that our employees may grow.Employees at DAVIS are given complete responsibility for their projects. While upper level guidance is always available, the project management staff is given the latitude to own and run projects resulting in high levels of job satisfaction. This trust encourages DAVIS employees to make confident and well-informed decisions for their departments and for the company. DAVIS is an equal opportunity employer.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unfortunately, they are all market driven and not the fault of the firm.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to work on teh grow of teh next generation.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best place I've ever worked!”

</title><pros>Pros – DAVIS has one of the most wonderful, supporting cultures I have ever worked in.  The company really takes care of you.  We have superior benefits (like 100% paid health insurance).  Top management regularly communicates with employees and really knows what goes on the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There really are not any cons.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Avg to Good Mid-Sized General Contractor”

</title><pros>Pros – Jim Davis is a fantastic company president, with an unusual combination of salesmanship/charisma and technical knowledge.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Besides Jim, the supporting cast is average on a good day.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Strive to stand out from the voluminous capita of small to middle GCs (in the Washington DC market) by stressing and valuing builder knowledge and quality planning/coordination/execution as a part of their culture (i.e. endeavor to know as much or more than their sub's, particularly how they interface with each other).</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fulfilling”

</title><pros>Pros – Progressive and open to new suggestionsReceptiveIntegrityTechnical experience offered - and ability to work within multiple market sectors</pros>
<cons>Cons – Still elements of fear based decision making at mid-level</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – better communication</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Family atmosphere.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great company to begin your career. Opportunity for growth and supprt of entire team, from supervisor to executive management team.</pros>
<cons>Cons – SLighty behind competitors in advancement of technology.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>