<name>James W Buckley Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/James-W-Buckley-Reviews-E265368.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-02-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A fair place to bide your time so long as your passing through, or if you like your niche”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are nice, the office is in a great area downtown (savannah), fairly steady work - educational type and institutional type.  The office manager is a great person and treats people well. Several of the VPs are a pleasure to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you don't consistently assert yourself or demand extra responsibility, you can become pigeon-holed, for your career.  Pay is terrible, and "loyalty" is lip service. The perception is that they're not giving raises or bonuses because people will stay for low pay since employment opportunities are limited elsewhere.  The owner micromanages projects, makes numerous last minute changes, and treats clients discourteously.  Doing innovative or modern type work is pretty much a no-go.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you want to keep your staff, you have to be willing to pay them. You also have to be willing to bring them into the process, at the early end, when schematics and the overall design is being developed.  If design skills aren't used, they atrophy, so provide opportunities for staff to develop their own skills.  Delegate more, trust more, appreciate more.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“boring”

</title><pros>Pros – They have work and the Associate who runs the office is a good guy</pros>
<cons>Cons – The salaries are as if you live in Swainsboro.  Savannah has a much higher cost of living</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>