<name>SK+G Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/SK-G-Reviews-E26818.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-02-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The agency has provided a good environment for my professional growth and allowed me to work with many talented people.”

</title><pros>Pros – We work with some of the leading brands in their respective categories and have had the chance to work on a number of high-profile initiatives.  We have a talented group of employees who make the tough days easier. We are hungry and persistent, which is one of the reasons we've survived The Great Recession and are growing again. But the best aspect of SK+G is without the people who work here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The downsides of working at SK+G are similar to the challenges any ad agency employee faces no matter where they work - difficult and sometimes unappreciative clients as well unrealistic deadlines.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to communicate in an open and candid manner with all employees, offer opportunities for educational/career advancement, and smell the roses more often.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Art Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Quality Scam Agency”

</title><pros>Pros – I have to say, they work with pretty cool clients.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I've been contacted by the MD himself telling me they were looking for a new art director and he would've liked to give me a test project to see the way I work and if a visa was worth it (i'm not from the US). I worked hard for two weeks and in the end the client went for my visual treatment. After that, the MD sent me an email saying the meeting went well and to let him know, in case I managed to find a way to get a Visa myself as they would be interested in having an interview with me. So in the end, they had quality work, for free. Well done. Very professional. NOT.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I've always been working with the big players in the industry and I was shocked to see how cheap and unprofessional these people are. Absolutely disgusting.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great coworkers, insane expectations”

</title><pros>Pros – Coworkers are great and the brands are interesting.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No raises. Ridiculous client expectations are always met. The turn around times are insane.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok for 1st career.”

</title><pros>Pros – There were some really great, dedicated professionals employed at SK+G while I was an AE. A lot of employees would really band together to get projects done (even if that meant all night work). Great Design Team and great Design Team leadership. Group Creative Directors are great and easy to work with.Most of the Account Supervisors are great, easy to work with and really want to help their team grow and learn.The environment was open and loose which was a great change from a "buttoned down" environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No ECD meant the owner would make ECD decisions, kill presentations, pitches, concepts before client presentations (sometimes hours before a pitch). It seemed as though the Group Creative Directors were left powerless to really execute and act as Creative Directors because of the ownership (they often seemed beat down under this leadership).Employees were often treated as "children" from the Office Manager and it seemed as the norm around the office was "you should be lucky to have this job."Some of the departments operated with little or no leadership (i.e Interactive and Broadcast Departments routinely failed to meet internal and external deadlines which meant working alongside these employees was VERY difficult) and very frustrating). No consequences for departments not delivering on time to clients (AM team routinely had to apologize and ask for forgiveness). I would be hard pressed to say I knew of anyone that really enjoyed their position or really wanted to be employed by SK+G (toward the end of my employment) due to many internal management "issues."</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Talk to employees and keep them in the loop regarding possible new business. Allow everyone a chance to work on new business pitches (sometimes the best ideas come from the fresh people).Evaluate what's going on within the agency. Find out why the Interactive Department routinely does not meet deadlines and why does the Broadcast Department seemingly operate as if they were more important then the rest of the agency.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-05-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Art Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work at Starbucks. You'll have better pay, respect and benefits.”

</title><pros>Pros – The group of low level employees - mostly entry level - are eager, enthusiastic and really talented.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Gross incompetence at the very top. The success of the company was based on personal relationships of the owner turned into professional relationships, but when that well dried up, there were no clients and because the owners know nothing about this business or industry, they can't rebuild the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't start businesses in industries you know nothing about. Seriously. Stop doing it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Junior Graphic Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“live everyday to the fullest.”

</title><pros>Pros – the work enviornment was the best thing about sk+g. the office is fabulous and the people on the working level cared about your well-being. the type of work was also another plus, being in the advertising industry with a heavy slant towards casinos and luxury hotels, it game a freedom that most designers don't get to experience in corporate america.</pros>
<cons>Cons – each day could be your last.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-11-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Management (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“How not to run an agency.”

</title><pros>Pros – For many, simply a salary that barely sustains. Some good people and many diamonds in the rough, talent wise.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The fall of SK+G came when the product became second to everything else. This happened with the hire of Eric Stein the Executive Creative Director, who we now know falsified his resume. Under his tutelage, we have not managed to win a single new account, whether through a pitch or where we are the only agency involved. This has been ongoing for over 3 years. As a whole, we have seen more money spent on furniture than on securing talent for all departments. We currently do not have a traffic department, interactive department and are functioning with very little to get by. The abuse of the agency towards its clients, especially where retainers are concerned, was criminal. Overall, an agency is to make a difference for their clients and we are sowing the seeds not doing this.Our employees are treated like dogs and because of the market we are in, talent has to be secured from outside therefore the agency punishes those who want to leave within the year they sign up.Strategically the agency has no footing and is unable to guide a client and the work. While we position ourselves as full service, it is just a phrase, we do not offer proper guidance to our clients in almost every area from media to creative.The turnover rate has been high, going as high as 70% in each of the past few quarters. Constantly overburdening every department for periods of time have cost the agency.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – In some ways I would say to look at the agency study done a few years back. Nothing from that study was ever implemented or acted upon and I believe it is too late for the agency to turn around, especially in the current climate. Overburdened with 2 buildings purchased and unable to ascertain new business, SK+G is not positioned well for this climate, let alone to turn it around.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Still a young company and needs improvement on communications.”

</title><pros>Pros – SK+G in it's prime was a great place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Still a young company and needs improvement on communications. The HR department lacks understand of the creative department.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work smarter not harder. Just because you have a person that's salary is cheaper, doesn't mean that the company will succeed. You need to figure out who your strongest team players our to make it thur a hard economy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“PERSONAL TRUTH”

</title><pros>Pros – During my time at SK+G the employees made the company. Some of the most down to earth, talented, hard working group of people I have ever met. SK+G was truly amazing the first year I was there, and slowly just started downhill. Friday Lounge was a great bonus working there. Christmas parties were always lots of fun. Awesome people to work with. Learning to deal with seriously 1 day turns on huge jobs. Lost weight. Grew a great deal with the company. Cool phone system. Parties. And did I mention how awesome the employees are?</pros>
<cons>Cons – So many loyal employees there that just aren't appreciated nearly enough. Upper management doesn't get what its like to work hard in advertising. They never give it to us straight which in turns they loose all credibility. SK+G became a slave to their clients instead of standing ground that this was our specialty. Never getting to take vacations. Not getting enough sick time. Getting rid of Friday Lounge was a huge mistake. Letting people leave that are bringing so much to the agency as well as letting go of the wrong ones. They make promises to people moving from all over and never follow through. Dead end for some careers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees and take action! Grow a back bone. Get involved. Be honest. Mentor, teach and train those that are qualified and those that want to grow.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fail now, get a new job later.”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy to get hired. You will be more competent than your boss.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most of management are idiots. The clients walk all over Account Services, and the partners let them. Many clients are leaving.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees, they know more than some of the senior staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous - They Blacklist You If You Talk Bad (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The current management team has ruined SK+G in just a few short years”

</title><pros>Pros – It was a very fun place to work in 2004 and 2005. It was the envy of all ad agencies in Las Vegas back then. Everyone worked 10-12 hour days and loved it because we all felt like we were a part of something.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Completely incompetent management team, they are absolutely horrible. Management has literally ruined this company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Replace yourselves.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>