<name>W Industries Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/W-Industries-Reviews-E269480.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-04-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people”

</title><pros>Pros – Small company with flexible hours where one person can make a big impact.  Very friendly work environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible benefits, different business units have difficultly working together causing mass duplication of efforts.  Small company, so there is not much room to rise.  Owned by a foreign company who sometimes makes weird management decisions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More competitive salaries, fix the interdepartmental issues, improve employee benefits.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Control Systems Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unique and educational”

</title><pros>Pros – Relaxed atmosphere.  Managment is conversational.</pros>
<cons>Cons – working in a field type atmosphere.  I prefer working downtown.  Administrative duties were not delegated to the correct people.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create a new benefit package.  Have the corporate office act like one, and not like a field office.  Analyst should not have to clean the kitchens and change out lightbulbs.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Past working experience”

</title><pros>Pros – no work politic to worry about. small company so it's very easy going.flexible schedule when working in officefriendly co-worker.</pros>
<cons>Cons – one position in a department. not much area for advance.poor salary improvement.depends on the postion, some require a lot of traveling</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The company itself is very friendly and nice to their employees.However, salary is often lower than other company while expected to know everything.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>