<name>Pay-O-Matic Corp Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Pay-O-Matic-Corp-Reviews-E269496.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Teller (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Preparation for the real world.”

</title><pros>Pros – I learned how to provide customer service with patience and decorum.</pros>
<cons>Cons – District Managers use offensive speech when conversing with employees. I couldn't deriveconstructive criticism to make my performance better because it was so negative.Customers were unreasonable. They didn't understand that they needed to pay a fee for thecheck cashing and wire transfer services we provided for them.The supplies needed to do the job didn't work properly, if at all. When you brought this tothe suppliers attention they responded poorly.A prepaid debit card that they pressured employees to sell wouldn't work properly. Customerswould always have complaints or issues with this item that we couldn't always fix.The scheduling was so rigid an employee was perceived as irrational if they needed aspecific day off.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – My advice to management would be that the prepaid debit card shouldalways work for the customer and if it doesn't  , they should be able to contact someonewho can fix the  problem.District Managers and managers  should make more of aneffort to give constructive criticism to employees. It is easier to correct behavior if they aretold specifically what they are doing wrong, and ways to make it better.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Teller (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Teller in New York City - Payomatic Corp”

</title><pros>Pros – - With the experience you gain it helps you get into the banking industry.- You learn a lot about checks, money orders, US currency and different forms of ID.- You learn to identify legit and fraudulent checks, money orders, US currency and IDs.- Above minimum wage pay for State of New York: Part-time - $10, full-time - $11.- They provide medical (co-payment) benefits, 401k, sick days, vacations, etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Terrible management at least in the store I work.- Terrible co-workers. They call out or come in late with no punishment from management.- Pay is very low, and raises are determined on merit (which is entirely dependent on management).- Poor working hours, you can be placed in a 24-hour store and work more than 8 hours a day.- Poor commission, $5 for debit card registrations, $10 for SSI direct deposits (which are ending soon).- Lot of the stores are 24-hours and are located in dangerous neighborhoods such as Harlem. Risk of store theft or even personal theft. Unruly customers and use of very colorful language.- Low growth opportunities.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Fix the cons.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>An Abused Teller (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is an eye opener.”

</title><pros>Pros – Interacting with many different personalities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – lack of professional communicationno respect from upper management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management need to go to school for ethical classes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Overnight Teller (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“overnight teller”

</title><pros>Pros – i dont know really any good ones i have good coworkers and a good dm rumors is the other dms are worst</pros>
<cons>Cons – you really cant see no growth here</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – how are you guys suppose to know who are the good workers when you too busy putting pressure on everyone an staying all day in the office</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>