<name>C Span Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/C-Span-Reviews-E26903.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Intern Experience!”

</title><pros>Pros – People are wonderfulYou can ask lots of questionsFun activities</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes long hours if you are dedicated</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Great job on intern program</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Information Systems Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very good environment to Intern with!”

</title><pros>Pros – I got to work with some very knowledgeable people and was able to learn a lot that would help me later in both my classes and my future employment opportunities.Very Flexible around school schedule.</pros>
<cons>Cons – At times it can be very slow at times in terms of things that need to be done but this doesn't happen often.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Only gripe I have is how outdated some of the systems employees use are.  I understand that compatibility is an issue when moving from Windows XP, but there comes a time when you need to stop thinking about how cold the water is and just jump in and try it out.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“C-SPAN Intern -Education Relations”

</title><pros>Pros – Great, friendly and comfortable work environment with many positive attitudes.Many opportunities to connect with inspiring senior staff members and other industry professionals.Extremely rewarding - all work is a public service. Giving instead of getting.Not to mention... some great meals are provided :)</pros>
<cons>Cons – No cons- It's what you make of it! Endless opportunities for experience...but only if you go after it.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great internship.”

</title><pros>Pros – + Kind employees+ Good learning experience+ Normal work hours+ Good chance to meet other young people if you're in intern alley</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Unpaid- Took about a week before I was trained to do any meaningful work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It would be nice if you paid your interns and had a little bit more of a plan when they start out for how they can contribute.  Nevertheless, you are doing a great job overall and I really appreciated everyone's kindness in the office.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Fantastic benefits package, competitive salary, CEO knows employees by name. Company is loyal to its employees. Management is generally promoted from within.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes the work is a bit boring. Working on Capitol Hill means driving in busy Washington DC traffic. Very strict dress code.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Brian Lamb does not need to change. He has treated his employees right, and it seems has positioned the company well for a possible retirement.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I interned for four years, during the summer breaks in different departments, and my experience was great.”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a comfortable environment, and the people are really nice. Senior management tends to be understanding. The employer and the HR team really do care about the employees, which is GREAT. They treat you with respect and decency and try to find the best ways to solve your problems. The CEO knows almost everyones' names by hear, and the company culture is awesome. The benefits are also out of the roof great There are about 9 weeks in vacation each year.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay isn't too great and as with any other job, there are a few weirdos in the mix, who have some issues.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“TV News, But Slower”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work/life balance.  Generous time off.  Minimal stress.  Pleasant work environment. Relatively consistent hours. Good salaries and benefits compared to others.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very set in its ways.  Resistant to change. Resents new ideas, especially if you get tagged as trying to be like CNN.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Time to shuffle management. Same people in senior positions for 15-30 years means no room for advancement and no new ideas.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Okay Place to Work”

</title><pros>Pros – Pays well, generally nice environment with good people</pros>
<cons>Cons – No real growth (people have been in their positions for uears and are not budging)Can get kind of boringNot really for a creative person</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Allow more upward mobility</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“With positive, down-to-earth and friendly staff, C-SPAN is a great place to learn about Capitol Hill coverage”

</title><pros>Pros – C-SPAN provides unbiased media coverage, a friendly work environment for journalists and gives viewers an opportunity to think for themselves.  Human Resources staff is very engaged in the intern program and is readily available to address intern concerns. Brian Lamb, the CEO, also interacts with interns.  On more than one occasion, he has engaged interns in discussion about C-SPAN's future development.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Office culture varies depending on one's department</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the great coverage!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“C-SPAN”

</title><pros>Pros – Very good pay, nice working environment, people know their stuff here, Bryan Lamb is a VERY wonderful person and knows nearly ALL his employees and interns by name</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's easy to settle and get comfortable. A lot of people have been working there for years and though their happy it may not be the most....exciting place to work. Great place to intern if you're a proactive person.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't overlook new ideas or the ideas of your interns!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>