<name>Z Gallerie Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Z-Gallerie-Reviews-E27076.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Visual Merchandiser (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“eh, good enough”

</title><pros>Pros – respect. fair towards employees. opportunity for growth</pros>
<cons>Cons – part time hours not flexible. low pay.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – higher hourly pay opportunity</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“There's so much potential, but it's disappointing that the company doesn't want to embrace it"”

</title><pros>Pros – - At the corporate level, the small environment allows working directly with upper-management and quick-turnaround for acceptance/approval on projects.- Direct ownership of projects.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Lack of technology resources ranging from an outdated POS and no CRM tools available.- Poor company culture, both from corporate and store-level.- There is a sense of fear in the company that makes it difficult to grow the company at scale or try innovative marketing campaigns.- No opportunity for career growth.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Need to shift the company for today's work environments by identifying a mission and core values.- Need to invest in technology resources to grow company further and truly compete with competitors.- There is so many opportunities for this company to grow and succeed. Need to make smart decisions and adopt new strategies for digital age commerce.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fantastic place to work for first 3-6 months”

</title><pros>Pros – Different tasks everyday within job descriptionLearn alot of new thingsDecent pay for managementGreat retail experience</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes job gets a little monotonousNot a whole lot of room for advancementHard POS sales system to learn for newbies and takes a bout 2 months to truly master</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work on getting furniture delivered in one piece, start offering commission for sales</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“HIGH PRESSURE + LOW WAGES + POOR MANAGEMENT = GREAT DISAPPOINTMENT”

</title><pros>Pros – ~ Interesting merchandise~ Employee discount</pros>
<cons>Cons – With over 10 years of retail experience, I was shocked at the way this store was run.Although, it's family-owned (beginning as a humble poster shop in the 70s by three siblings) it's one of the most rigid and exploitative corporate environments I have ever worked in.They demand that you meet daily sales quotas (without providing a commission incentive). The manager mentioned some vague bonus that I never saw anyone receive.Workers are restricted to wearing a limited color palette (white, beige, brown, black).No prints.Before being hired, they check your people-skills by stationing you at the entrance for approximately 30 minutes. The store manager stays in the back of the store, and if she can hear you welcoming customers, you've passed the greeter-test and are on your way to getting hired.After that initial step, you fill-out a massive amount of documents and liability releases that consume half of the day. Once you've passed a basic background check, you're "thrown to the wolves" (the manager's words, not mine).So out on the sales floor you go, untrained.I'm computer savvy and a quick study, but it was very stressful having to constantly interruptmy associates and/or the manager (when she was available) to ask for help. And what type of a message does that convey to customers?People are always complaining about the lack of service. As the old saying goes, "A fish rots from the head down." It is the responsibility of management to train their staff, so they can properly service their clientèle.The cumbersome POS technology was a big problem. The user-unfriendly system drastically slowed down every transaction and many salespeople lost credit for their sales because the cash register is programmed to automatically default sales to the store.Unless salespeople remember to take the additional time to manually delete the store number and replace it with their own employee number, they lose the sale. Is that how corporate avoids paying bonuses?Most customers complain about the inability to return sales items, and I noticed that the Z marks-down nearly everything (seemingly to avoid returns).Other problems that customers call on is furniture arriving damaged and they become livid when the customer service center does not resolve issues in a timely manner.Everything is sent via Fed-Ex; no other less expensive options are provided.Unfortunately, the store had a nearly paranoid vibe about meeting upper-management's quotas which creates a great deal of tension and hostile competition on the sales floor.Penny wise and pound foolish: I was admonished for wrapping several fragile and very expensive crystal perfume bottles in bubble-wrap because I was told, "The cost of those materials are deducted from the store's bottom-line." I was then instructed to use stiff (cheap) butcher-block paper (completely inappropriate).One last consideration: Truck-Delivery-Thursdays are rough.Salespeople are expected to unload big heavy boxes which is a painstaking task. If you'renot a physically fit individual with strength and endurance to spare, I would advise seeking another work option. Most retailers do not demand this level of hard labor from salespersons; it wiped me out and I refused to return.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Train the staff, delegate properly, use proper wrapping materials to protect items from damage, and upgrade the POS system.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lowered my hours to make me quit”

</title><pros>Pros – Relatively flexible regarding my school schedule. Initial management was positive and inspiring to be good at your job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The environment eventually became hostile due to the nature of sales. Pay was very poor for sales associates, and bonuses based on sales were a complete joke. Eventually the management became a mess and they couldn't keep a single person. People with no management skills were getting promoted only because they "wanted" the position. District manager only cared about numbers, sure, that's her job, but she didn't care at all for sales associates unless they were the top performers. Management overlooked all the hard work that people did aside from selling.Overall, the store was full of too much drama and gossip. This specific location had the privilege of working with the buying office so things were constantly being done and re-done and the merchandisers seemed to have more control and say over the actual management. I lost respect for them because none of them ever appreciated what you did for them and were too uptight and fake for my taste.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“it was okay”

</title><pros>Pros – great products to sell. Everyone loves Z Gallerie!!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not commission yet they want you to meet sale goals and generate leads</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – make sure you know who you are hiring as store managers. It may be the reason why so many employees left or found another full time job</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun Yet Frustrating”

</title><pros>Pros – The product is very interesting. The fact that it is a family owed company is nice. We have opportunities as management to interact with corporate daily. Which is nice to see all sides of the company. Getting to know your customers is also great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unloading the truck full of merchandise. Customer service is not always helpful to the store or customers. As well as everyone has to take on more than expected for no more money.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There needs to be a better training program for new hires especially managers. As well as the hiring process possibly needs to be more intense to know how serious the candidate is.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Job culture was awesome!”

</title><pros>Pros – Beautiful environment, beautiful merchandise and upbeat music.  Colleagues were upbeat and personable.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sales quotas were high and wages were low.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pressure to achieve and surpass sales quotas pitted employees against each other making working together uncomfortable at times.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a family owned company and you get to meet the owners.  Working with great product</pros>
<cons>Cons – When they went through chapter 11 they cut down or out completely stock associates, sales associates were asked to take on much more responsibility</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Room for improvement”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting merchandise and visually-stimulating atmosphere</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low wages, hard work, and minimum training.Cheap imports, that often arrive damaged.Rigid return policies.High Shipping Costs (Fed-Ex Only). Customers are not provided any other choices.Inefficient, Slow, and Unfair Point-of-Sale Software that slows down transaction time and can deprive employees out of their sales.In order to open the cash register / point-of-sale the salesperson must enter their 7-digit employee number (twice). After that, the salesperson must input the store's 8-digit code. (Meanwhile you haven't even scanned the merchandise and the customer is asking you what all the typing is about.)Next step: Scanning the merchandise bar-codes. However mid-transaction, another menu pops up showing that the sale has just defaulted to the store. At that point, you have to manually delete the defaulted store number and re-type your salesperson number (again) to get credit for the sale. This is not only tedious and time-consuming, it is unfair.Although, Z Gallerie employees are not paid on a commission basis, they are given daily sales goals. If they meet or exceed their numbers, then they are often given bonuses. But the way the POS system is currently set-up, it's very easy to lose sales to "the house" and to not get credit, especially when you're multi-tasking and working fast as retail often demands.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please read comments above.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Quality and Service, Instead of Quotas”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting, Unusual Merchandise and a Decent Employee Discount</pros>
<cons>Cons – Physically demanding work. If you are not strong physically, with high levels of energy and endurance, it would be better to seek employment at a less taxing retail environment.The staff is expected to unload weekly Fed-Ex shipments; move furniture; climb tall ladders to retrieve stockroom merchandise (often in heavy cardboard cartons), fetch weighty glass-framed prints and posters from the showroom walls (and then replace them), haul heavy packages to customers' cars, and so on.Inadequate training. Store managers are stressed and scattered. This prevailing issue affects everyone and the store's bottom line. With constant pressure from corporate to meet sales quotas (which increase daily), managers are often unloading cartons, and working behind the cash register, instead of using their time to organize, delegate and support staff as needed.Questionable owner/upper management decisions, and stressed-out store managers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more open-minded and encourage staff to share their thoughts about finding solutions to existing problems.When corporate's emphasis is placed solely on a store's "daily numbers", instead of a progressive work environment, efficiency, and top-notch customer service, problems follow.Allow store managers more time and latitude to properly train new employees, and compensate managers fairly so that the best ones remain with the company.Upgrade the cumbersome POS system to expedite transactions and efficiently maintain inventory data.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Visual Merchandiser (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun, but Ultimately Very Disappointing”

</title><pros>Pros – - Product is so fun to merchandise, since my store was kind of off the corporate radar it was easy to tweak bland corporate directives and make the collections look compelling, streamlined, and more suitable for our customers.- Most of my co-workers and managers were really kind and supportive.- I got a lot of great feedback and consulting opportunities which felt really rewarding.- pretty good compensation for retail.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Exhausting. Eat your wheaties, because you'll be moving furniture, heavy glass shelves, running product all over the place, etc. all in a huge showroom and all by yourself. The physical aspect of visual merchandising is often the most exciting, but here it's almost too much. I was injured in some capacity pretty much the entire time I worked there, and had to do some completely ridiculous things that OSHA would have had a field day with. I ended up with a slipped disc which caused a lot of problems.- Corporate favoritism is pretty obvious -- my store kept getting trucks filled with stuff we didn't need, and my store manager was usually ignored when she asked for stuff we did need.- truck day is absolutely a disaster. This kind of shipment should be processed overnight, people! During store hours it makes the back half of the store unshoppable for 2 days and is a hazard for customers who insist on walking through debris.- In my last week I was extremely disappointed with management's ability to assess a problem and deal with it effectively. Their passive-agressive, baffling decisions were detrimental to the store, to me, and to the efficiency of the fall floorset installation.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Seasonal Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was a great company to work for, even as a seasonal cashier. Wish I'd had a chance to prove my merchandising skills.”

</title><pros>Pros – Beautiful products and merchandising. The managers and other employees were really nice and helpful. Great music playing all day long!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Standing on your feet all day, rude customers, and the fact that I never had a chance to prove myself as a decorator/merchandiser.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The management was great! No complaints.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Frustrating and little room for professional growth”

</title><pros>Pros – Design discount for employees, somewhat flexible scheduling, interesting clientele and product line</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low hourly rate for management position, even for those with college degrees; lower level employees were young and dramatic; corporate knew they were going to shut down store but kept telling employees they were not going to- came as a surprise to everyone.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Place To Work”

</title><pros>Pros – Great, positive co-workers.  Fun merchandise. Room for promotions if that's the career choice for you. Good discounts and heads up on sale merchandise.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Truck days are not easy. Short staffed often to maintain sales per hour. Customers can be super needy and thankless.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Offer some resolution to the short staffing and keep reasonable sales per hour goals. Staff doesn't mind working, but wants to spend more time with customers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“exciting”

</title><pros>Pros – Good training and follow up. You "owned" your store and could make deceisions on prices for customers if need be.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Never seeing home office employees so you could put a face to a voice or top management.  Familyowned company and would have a least talked to someone.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Easy hourly gig...truck is the worst part about it”

</title><pros>Pros – Hourly pay is decent (if you negotiate)Employee discount is really good (depending on region)Hours are flexible depending on work availability</pros>
<cons>Cons – Truck days are the worst thing about coming on board.  They make you come in around 4am to unload a semi trailer.  After that everything must be unpacked as upper management just stands there and watches you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Over a better pay rate for those who have to do 'truck'.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“sales”

</title><pros>Pros – Aetna PPOWork very good thats all..</pros>
<cons>Cons – management  doesn't work since long time ago and they know about....</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-31</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a great work environment and corporate makes it an even worse environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Fairly easy job. They are more interested in you doing day to day operations and they don't expect much more.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Corporate employees make store employee's job much more difficult than necessary.  They do not help out and have no idea what the stores need to succeed.  IF you need anything from corporate, don't bother wasting your time.  While I was there, they fired numerous great employees and kept many of the incompetent ones.  Also managers are not allowed to have a single holiday off...so plan on working Memorial Day, July 4, Labor Day and all the others.  Not much of a work/life balance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Corporate employees need to help the store employees do their job.  That means supporting the ones who are dealing with customers every single day.  Listening would also benefit the company, unless the plan is to keep running the business into the ground and keep closing stores.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great temporary job”

</title><pros>Pros – My store was flexible with schedules, good discounts, great vibe and atmosphere, and fun place to work. It was a good seasonal job. Products were great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It gets boring and seems like there is little room for growth. My other co-workers did not respect the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More supervision. More exciting promotions and incentives. Make it more fun and interesting to work there! It got really boring quick.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Love/Hate relationship”

</title><pros>Pros – decent discountnice merchandisedecent hours (when i was there)great staff (when i was there)Great inventory look-up system!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad management decisionssome cheap quality merchandiseOutdated register systemsnot easy to move up within companytreated associates like poorlyupper management was very incompetent</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Gut your management style and start over from scratch. what you're doing right now is not working...and thats why the company is dying.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-10-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Had high hopes...”

</title><pros>Pros – Family owned atmosphere.  You are known as a person, rather than an employee by the owners.  This, however, has changed over the past 1-2 years.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company does not have a clear goal, and are constantly reversing decisions and changing directions, no matter the consequence to either the store teams or their customers.  New direction is to over-work and under-pay every member of the store teams.  No BOH support, even when processing shipments and floor changes.  Communication from upper management and corporate is disconnected and cold.  You'll be told how horrible your performance is, but won't be recognized for any positive or outstanding performance.Be prepared to not only do your job, but also the job of your DM (or who ever is above you) and/or take on additional roles and responsibilities without recognition or compensation.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Remember to relax and remind yourself how it was when you worked in the store.  Stand by your sales support and give them the tools to not only succeed in their own position, but the opportunity to be promotable.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-09-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stressful and Unrewarding Place to Work”

</title><pros>Pros – Loved working with customers: Hourly pay rate is decent, helping them pick out accessories, picking out furniture selections, fun environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management in store is horrible. Management plays favorites. All they care about is that you make your store goal. Period! Company cut bonuses out. No commission, You don't get rewarded anymore for making or passing your sales.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get out of the office more often and come out to the floor and work. Be more involved, train, and be morally supportive. Stop tearing down your employees. Lead by example: If you get on your employess for being late, dont go out to lunch and take more time than your allowed. Just because you are a member of management shouldn't mean you don't have to play by the rules.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-06-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Visual Merchandiser (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Was A Great Job Until They Shut Down A Third of the Company”

</title><pros>Pros – The position gave me the great opportunity to be creative and really expand my capabilities.  My boss was incredibly supportive, helpful, encouraging... basically the best boss I've ever had.  I had a great M-F, 8-4 work schedule... can't beat that in retail.  The atmosphere was relaxed and fun, even during the holidays.  From a visual merch standpoint I got the chance to combine my own style with corporate directives, making for fun displays.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Where do I even begin?  This is a poorly run company, end of story.  They expanded far quicker than their budget would allow and when the economy hit a slump, they were forced to shut down nearly a third of the company (including one of their two distribution centers) and file for Chapter 11.  Although I worked in one of the stores that they closed, I would have left the company by now anyway; I truly believe more stores will end up being closed.  We got very little warning (the store closed in under three weeks) and there were no severance packages.  Also, someone needs to tell the accessories buyer to back off on some of the ugly crap they call merchandise.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't let this company die, please.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Room for improvement”

</title><pros>Pros – Unique merchandise, pleasant work environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Rigid return policies.-  High sales goals emphasizing selling over-priced imported furniture which takes 6-8 weeks to receive.- High shipping costs (exclusively Fed-Ex). Customers are not provided less costly delivery options.The owners should look into the following issues and resolve them to increase employee efficiency, morale and loyalty.- User unfriendly cash register software. Excessively laborious and biasedIn order to use the cash register, the salesperson must first input 7 to 8-digit codes 3 TIMES CONSECUTIVELY -- inputting the salesperson's employee number (twice) followed by the long store number (once)This time-consuming process must be repeated every time a transaction is executed.Most troublesome is the fact that halfway through the transaction, another menu pops-up, showing that credit for the sale has DEFAULTED to the store. (Isn't that interesting?)After all your hard work, the store wants and will receive credit for your sale unless the store's code is manually removed, and changed back to your 7-digit sales code.No salesperson should have to type and re-type nearly 30 digits before hitting "Total Amount Due".Although Z Gallerie employees are not paid on a commission basis, they are given daily sales goals, and they are paid bonuses if they meet or exceed their numbers.However, as it stands, the computerized cash register software is programmed to make it easy to lose credit for earned sales -- especially when one is working quickly and multi-tasking, as retail often requires.The current defaulting software, makes it appear as if the deck is stacked in favor of the house, so that the salesperson unwittingly loses credit for their hard-earned sales. Very unfair.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please read above.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Experience  is Great”

</title><pros>Pros – Customers,  discount, few employees, many hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – lack of communication and training</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Training and communication is key to any successful business</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Needs Imrovement”

</title><pros>Pros – Z galerie can change from store to store.. i was positioned in the salt lake city utah store and it was managed well trained well and you were treated as family and a coworker.  Appreciated and thanked for your heard work and going above and beyond. i would sugest this company in slc area not california.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In california where you are located alot closer to head quarters it becomes alot more family oriented and promotions are not given out based on who has earned them or who deserves them they are given and taken away based off how much you are known by the owners.  My store manager passed me up for associate manager and assistant manager for a kid that his father was best friends with owner promoted with in 1 month of being there and promoted to assistant manager one step under store manager within a few months... over looking me someone that had surassed my sales goal every month and brought moral to the store..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep in mind that we are people, people with brains not cows.  we know how much you are paying us and there are many many jobs out there that will pay us that much and appreciate us.  Im not going to work for a company that does not appreciate me and get paid a low income.  SLC z gallerie i love you managemet should strive to be more like that.. its not all about if you make your goal each day it is also about customer service which slc had.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Attractive surroundings to work in. But  overall going in wrong direction.”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting and active work environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor corporate and senior management ethics.  Not trustworthy.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be nice, humble, and more appreciative. Be higher quality,  not so generic.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Over worked...under paid!”

</title><pros>Pros – Unique and creative store concept. Great visual appeal. Cool products at reasonable prices.The store has good energy with the music and environment. Never a dull moment. Everyday is an adventure!Good employee discount and management tries to be flexible with the schedule.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too few employess to support sales and various daily tasks. It could be a simple solution of just plain hiring more people! Duh. Truck day is a nightmare, lots of physical labor demands. Also, very little concern for safety isuues. Not very structured or organized either. Pay for managers is very low considering the demands. Always short staffed because the turnover is so darn high. Most days I leave just laughing and saying to myself, "It will be a better day tomorrow."</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get with it people! Listen to the feedback you claim is so valuable to you. Pay your employees what they deserve or at least offer some incentives or bonus or commission to people who are contributing to the sales numbers and success of your business! Duh.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“So much potential to be big, but product selection keeps the company afloat and not the leadership”

</title><pros>Pros – -Stores are beautiful if there are strong visual merchandisers on the team-Employee discount is better than most competitors-Upper level managment receives a decent quarterly/yearly bonus incentive</pros>
<cons>Cons – -"Truck Day" methods are absurd, the company has reduced payroll to the point that associate managers and upper level management have to assume an all encompassing responsibility of unloading trucks early in the morning, processing stock and merchandising while maintaining required sales per hour quotas.-No enought support staff to handle laborious parts so sales people can maximize on sales opportunities.-Not enough support from corporate and District Managers; my district is so far spread apart that I haven't seen my DM in 7 months!-DMs need to supervise remote stores more closely, my store manager takes advantage of my lack of DM supervision to take extra time off, work less and exploit his/her associate managers and assistant to do more than what is in their responsibility and pay range.-Remote stores are neglected by District Visual Merchandisers-Payraises are virtual unheard of, especially if you work for a store that is not in Texas, California and Florida where District Managers hide-There is not enough emphasis placed on merit promotions--District Managers should look for outstanding employees in the store and encourage growth and promotion!-Customer service creates as much undue stress as they help-Elimination of key roles such as Gallery Specialists and Visual Merchandisers make operating medium-volume stores difficult-Corporate does not listen enough to individual store input regarding product, start listening to local management about what sells so stores can customize to suit clientele to boost sales</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It's time to consider hiring someone who is experienced in operating a company with 50+ stores. The current VP of Sales is weak. Her spam mail of forwarded daily inspirational quotes from a website does not drive business. She operates by placing fear in DMs by firing them for under performing districts, when she should be looking at performance results and creating short-term and long-term objectives to increase revenue. Owners, find corporate employees who are not yes-people. All is not well-throughout the company, but everyone smiles in front of you for fear that the whip will come down. The buying office needs to run consistent and cohesive sales, during Thanksgiving have textile and dining furniture sales, during the summer, have seating sales, etc. Develop a better sales campaign, focus on American-made furniture and get the word out as a competitor about the ability to create custom-order furniture. Keep furniture and product in stock! It's unacceptable to try to sell a bed on back order for three month to a customer. And look for honest employees to give you vital feedback (for example, many store managers were afraid to be honest on the holiday feedback forms, especially in the sections about district and corporate leadership. The forms went directly to the DMs, would you send a letter to your DM saying they forgot your store and didn't extend enough leadership strength to create a clear objective or sales plan district wide? I think not.)</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good”

</title><pros>Pros – easy to work with other people</pros>
<cons>Cons – some parts of the job can be demanding</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – good</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome staff, incompetent company”

</title><pros>Pros – -beautiful environment-great staff-good benefits-good discount-supportive district manager</pros>
<cons>Cons – -corporate management plays favorites-mediocre quality products-minimal training-a lot of expectations-poor communication from the corporate offices</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get to know your staff before criticizing their work, particularly upper management and owners. Keep consistent with communicating objectives to the stores and stop changing your minds with store policies. That's the biggest complaint from customers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A decent time at the Z”

</title><pros>Pros – The energy of the space was very up beat. The team was close, and the hours of operation were great. Not to mention, closing at night took 20 min and then you were out. The visuals were always amazing. The discount is great and the prices are already so low you can get some great stuff!</pros>
<cons>Cons – You take the shipment through the front doors. Truck day looks like you are closing down. The furniture ordering system is very difficult. The amount of communication from senior management was very little. The company is very strict with letting you develop your community outreach.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Host more store specific sales to help drive the business in the store so the team can have more payroll.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not your average Mom and Pop furniture company”

</title><pros>Pros – Good discount and  nice merchandise</pros>
<cons>Cons – False sense of "family" environment, back stabbing politics run rampage ate the higher level.  You are asked to do your job plus the work of 2-4 others with out clear goals be told to you and then told you failed when you do not make those goals.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – clean house of those managers who have been there so long that they do not grasp what its like to run a business.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>