<name>Paul C Rizzo Associates Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Paul-C-Rizzo-Associates-Reviews-E272635.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very Helpful Colleagues”

</title><pros>Pros – Very helpful colleagues, you can ask them any questions; You need to work overtime depending on the project, but you get more paid</pros>
<cons>Cons – People are getting laid off in some groups</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“3 years full time in a technical capacity”

</title><pros>Pros – There used to be great people working here. Now only a few are left.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is incompetent. Family run business where Rizzos get all the perks without doing any work. Zero appreciation for the people who do work. Abusive managers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Challenging position for a firm that is doing challenging work around the world.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Work.  Good work environment.  good benefits.  Globally diverse work force of international experts.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Firing/ layoff decisions taken from technical managers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give the tech managers a break and let them have a say.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Project Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Employees undervalued.”

</title><pros>Pros – When I started this company was welcoming and the work was fulfilling.</pros>
<cons>Cons – After the CEO left his daughter in charge of the entire office it became a disorganized mess. Managers are completely lost and have no clue what they are doing. Most of the managers are friends of family. The people running things are rarely qualified to do so.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Quit and hire someone who has experience and education.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Civil Engineer Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very good!”

</title><pros>Pros – very friendly and hard working environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – some problem in project management and time lines!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineering Consulting Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company for people serious about engineering consulting.  Small, though.”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunities around the world, in select countries.  Pays well, considering the size of the company.  Opportunities for technical training.  Meritocratic environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Small company.  Not a lot of training.  Must be a sufficient self-starter to thrive.  Not the best company if you're not sure that engineering consulting is what you want to do.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Allow employees that demonstrate interest to have a say in the strategy and the direction of the company to have an opportunity to do so.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>