<name>Bird-X Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Bird-X-Reviews-E274888.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The most challenging and rewarding experience of my career.”

</title><pros>Pros – My opinion actually counts. Open door policies and lack of red tape makes getting things accomplished easier and provides a more fulfilling experience. Employees are given the freedom to get involved in other areas of the company. Incentive based commissions can be lucrative. Profit sharing and great insurance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not everyone is comfortable with commissions for sales people. Not everyone likes the job variety and freedom to explore creative ways to do the job more efficiently and effectively.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Based upon the results they don't need my advice, but are certainly open to listening to everyone's input.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Treat it with respect, and you get the same in return.”

</title><pros>Pros – Casual yet focused working environment.  Greater responsibility, raises and promotions are granted to those that show determination and strong capability.  Fair and honest management.  Due to the company's smaller size, things can get done, or fixed, very swiftly.  Great benefits, especially for a small company.  First-rate healthcare, dental, vacation time, and profit sharing.  At Bird-X you are a person, not a number.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This is not a glitzy/trendy marketplace or company.  If that's what you're looking for, this isn't the company for you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to show respect to the workforce.  Listen to, and understand, concerns.  Communicate the annual agenda.  Reward team players that demonstrate the very best intentions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“SDVSVSLKVNSVLWW  orst WworW”

</title><pros>Pros – it office are in Chicago, but in a really bad area. You will cross paths with drug dealers and homeless if you exit the company doors.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The whole company sucks lack of any business understanding or idea what it real core business is at all.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“How are they still in business?”

</title><pros>Pros – I was in sales and was given a decent pipeline to start withSome departments and people were greatUncapped comission</pros>
<cons>Cons – i took public trans but others had their cars broken into and were muggedPeople seemed to isolate themselves by raceManagers played favoritesPeople were lazyNot near any EL linesWeird business practices</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get tough on people</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Happy Employee”

</title><pros>Pros – Company provides a high level of comfort, stability and job security.  Allows potential for personal growth and income improvement.  Positive team/family atmosphere which contributes to long-term success of the company.  Central location makes it accessible for commuters throughout the Chicagoland area.  Attractive and comfortable interior work space.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not located in a glamorous or cosmetically appealing neighborhood such as the Loop or Gold Coast (although not far away from either) if that is an important feature for you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This company's been good to me!”

</title><pros>Pros – Wow, I just read a not-so-great review and I’m shaking my head.  This is so not the company I know!  I guess you can’t please everybody, and people leave for a lot of reasons -- but don’t always see their own contribution to an unsatisfactory situation.Lots of us feel lucky to work here!   As a 15-year Bird-X employee, I work alongside many people who’ve been with the company five, ten, fifteen and even twenty-plus years.  Among a small staff, this level of loyalty says a lot.  Many have grown in responsibility – currently, five of our department managers plus several assistant managers gained promotion having started in non-managerial roles within the company.   Not everyone wants or seeks increased accountability – but for those who do, with our growing sales, there’s certainly opportunity.I’ve seen initiative rewarded over and over again during my years at Bird-X – my own and my co-workers.  The company gives incredibly generous benefits for its size – first-rate medical that’s heavily subsidized for employees and dependents -- a profit sharing plan – plus we enjoy an upbeat, informal atmosphere and an extremely positive, stable work environment.   PTO is generous and we have company lunches and twice-yearly parties on company time.I'm happy here, and I plan to stay!</pros>
<cons>Cons – I wish there were more ethnic restaurants close by.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You're doing a lot of things right.  Always keep improving.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent pay, bad management”

</title><pros>Pros – Laid-back, casual officeNice officeLots of parking so it's easy to drive to</pros>
<cons>Cons – Promotions and salary are based on if management likes you or notNo room for advancement</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Promote people with legitimate experience</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>