<name>Triple C Designs Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Triple-C-Designs-Reviews-E275611.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast growing company with motivated team.”

</title><pros>Pros – Company is growing fast due to its amazing product, good management and motivated team.Each of the employees can raise their voice and be a part of decision making in almost every area such as sales strategy, product design, marketing and customer service.We are all (including the owner) bonded well as a team with a family feel. The team is motivated and feels a part of the overall growth. Frequent outings and drinks at the office are keeping us all up.Good compensation and adjustments with performance shows recognition and helps me growing individually.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Small growing business requires hard work, initiative and responsibility. If you are not the right one, this will be a con for you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Bring more people asap and good hardworking people to help all of us to fulfill the demand.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“On paper, it looks like a cool place to work.  But in reality...beware.”

</title><pros>Pros – Products are cool.  That's about it.  There isn't anything groundbreaking or revolutionary about the products they offer, but they're good-looking, mostly useful, and trendy.  But then again, many other companies offer similar products.  Phone and tablet cases and portable chargers?  They're a dime a dozen.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I worked here for an extremely short period of time and it was enough time for me to realize that if I continued to work here, I would probably lose friends and my personal life would crumble.  The hours are long and the compensation is not reflective of that.  Every one who worked here put in the hours and didn't seem like interesting people outside of work because, well, they didn't do anything else but work.The owners started this business from the ground up, which is very admirable, but they have a long way to go in terms of management and people skills in general.  You can ask questions and ask for help, but to an extent.  This is not a good work environment if you thrive off collaboration and teamwork (the other reviewer is spot on when they wrote that everyone was out for themselves) or like to ask for feedback.  You will only get feedback if you make a mistake.The benefits are pretty awful.  While I was here, I kept worrying about what would happen if I were to get very sick or get into an accident because given the horrible health insurance and not-so-great pay, if such a catastrophe were to befall me, I'd be completely broke.And like the other reviewer wrote, yes, it seems like all they care about is looking cool.I'm glad I left.  I would have not advanced my career as a whole if I had stayed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Your customers notice the high turnover rate and it does not reflect positively on you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company That Allows Employees To Grow Professionally”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with this company has not only allowed me to grow professional but helped me gain knowledge and experience in sales, fashion, production, logistics and overall business management. Starting as an intern allowed me to learn the basic goals of the company along with learning the ins and outs of each department. I enjoyed interning for Triple C so much that, I've decided to go apply for a full time position after college. Now I am an account manager handling hundreds of accounts within my territory, traveling to various trade shows around the US, and growing every day as young professional!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working for a small business, you must take initiative, have the drive and motivation to be able to adjust, work in a fast pace environment and be able to multitask in various areas.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the great work!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sample and Show Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Small Business with Unlimited Potential”

</title><pros>Pros – This company offers a fast-paced environment with hard-working, dedicated employees and managers. The incredible, innovative products account for the continuous growth and unlimited potential. I am actually surprised by the previous review as management makes an effort to address any issues brought to their attention and offers incentives for hard work. I have learned and grown so much while working alongside Triple C.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As a small business, you must be willing to make an effort and treat the company as your own.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst Place EVER to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Nothing positive to say about this employer.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you like being treated without respect, speaking in Hebrew in front of your staff is complete disrespect! if you do not want them in on the conversation...close a door, leave the office!If you have a life outside the office you are treated like a step child...oh and if you have leave right at 6:00...look out you will get the hairy eye ball. They say they want structure and you can grow with the company, maybe if you are willing to sell your soul! Oh and don't look for assistance or any kind of help. Everyone here is out for themselves! Training and  time to prove yourself are nonexistent...Michelle just "doesn't have the time".  YOU WILL BE JUDGED.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create and allow the time that is needed to train the staff, allow and encourage the staff  to have a life outside of the business. If you want them to treat the business like they own it...treat them better and they will. Be okay if someone needs to leave at the end of the day at 6:00 when the day is suppose to be done. A 9 -10 hour day should be acceptable.Allow someone real time to get to know the business, processes, etc. Here is an idea...maybe you should get to know your staff, not just the people who have been with you for years. Allow your staff to take a REAL lunch break, offer real benefits. Act like you care just a tiny bit, other than making money and trying to look cool. Last bit of advice, the phone interview, then 3 hour interview process for such a small company is a bit much.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>