<name>X-Tra Light Manufacturing Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/X-Tra-Light-Manufacturing-Reviews-E276515.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-03-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I learned a lot...and I'm glad it's over.”

</title><pros>Pros – Work here only you absolutely have to have a job and no one else is hiring. If you want to work hard you'll be better of building pyramids or working on the Burma Road. This company is, for the most part, a business case study of how not to do things.  Oddly enough, though, they did pay for the workers, that wanted to, to go get their GED or H.S.diplomas (which is totally inconsistant with their general treatment of employees).</pros>
<cons>Cons – This place has a great product that is marketed reasonably well, but internally the environment is very toxic. Hourly employees are used up like they're expendable and blamed for everything, even for things that happen when they're not there or had no control over. There is only a set start time and you work till you drop. This company does just about everything the hard way (from product development to building to packaging to shipping.) "Salary, exempt" is just code for lots of unpaid overtime. There is no root cause analysis taking place at any time, only blame-storming to identify a scapegoat. There is no such thing as work-life balance. You work and that is your life.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – X-tralight makes one of the most inovative products that should sell itself. Hire some managers who are dedicated to product and process imporovement before profit improvement. The task-master style of leadership will only make folks work hard enough not to get fired. The safety person should be qualified and actually work in the building, not just visit the airconditioned offices once every six weeks. It really is okay to take the time to get something right and not just jam it through the process just to meet a number and send somethiing out that is below standard.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>