<name>U-Line Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/U-Line-Reviews-E276395.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Mechanical Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Beware”

</title><pros>Pros – A few good managers, purchasing and marketing department to clarify.Don't have to work overtime, usually are out by 3:30</pros>
<cons>Cons – High turn over rate.No thinking outside of the box, basically do what ever you are told and all will be good.A lot of favoritism going on in the higher management.Horrible planning and schedulingLittle to no communication between departments.Always playing the blame game</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Remove some of the higher up managers that think they are untouchable and it might be a bare able place.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“DO NOT WORK HERE!!!  THIS PLACE IS SCARY.”

</title><pros>Pros – You can gain a lot of experience here that will look good on your resume... but you won't want to stay here very long.</pros>
<cons>Cons – To list a few:- Very unorganized- Little to no communication between departments and management- Just about every department here is severly mismanaged- Unethical behavior demonstrated by members of management- Extremely low employee morale- High turnover throughout the organization</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If the company truly wants to improve its business operations, they should probably look at removing their inexperienced members of management. (ex. director of operations, plant manager)These guys are clearly out to meet their own personal objectives and can care less for the company suffering.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>