<name>E-Technologies Group Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/E-Technologies-Group-Reviews-E276409.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-02-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A cutting edge industrial automation company with plenty of opportunity for those who seek a challenge.”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Multi-disciplined: Process Automation, Machine Process Automation, Business Intelligence, IT, Regulated Industries, Engineering and Design2. Multiple clients: Consumer Products, Manufacturing, Life Sciences, Food & Beverage, SI to Large EPCs3. Cutting edge technical development4. Work with excellent technical resources5. Opportunities to cross over into other technologies6. Flexible work schedule7. Management truly appreciates the company employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. The company has a family feel. Its a challenge to hold that feeling as the company grows.2. The office is becoming crowded and space is becoming an issue. Your workspace is functional.3. Huddle rooms are needed</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 1. Continue to press on with the new organization model and growth model.2. Maintain the communications / keep the employees informed3. Consider moving to a larger office facility</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Treated as contractor but paid as employee with few benefits”

</title><pros>Pros – Some interesting technologies, Could be a great company, lots of potential with product and smart young staff. need a few more grey hairs. Good clients but not many of them - very risky</pros>
<cons>Cons – Out of site - out  of mind. Little management  Infrastructure to support employees particularly those offsite. Probably a great 30 person company. A poor place to work with 100 employees. Two owners often do not appear aligned.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Delegate & Listen - Build structure, Led Leaders lead. Owners Own. Decide to be 120 person company making 15% Margin or 30 person company making 40% margin.  Talk to employees and take heed of what they say even if they earn less or are younger than you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>