<name>Earle M. Jorgensen Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Earle-M-Jorgensen-Reviews-E2779.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2010-07-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“EMJ”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Company with a good reputation in the Metals Distribution market.</pros>
<cons>Cons – More effective communication in certain areas could improve.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management has been doing a great job steering this company during the tough economic time this industry faced.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“dissatisfied former employee....downsized by company”

</title><pros>Pros – had a great boss but he was let go</pros>
<cons>Cons – not caring about employees as a whole divided employees by job class</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Stainless and Aluminum Products Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My compensation rose only when the competition tried to hire me away.”

</title><pros>Pros – Overall, it was a very satisfying experience with the one exception when corporate management ram-rodded through a new computer system in 1994 that tests proved wasn't ready. Compensation could have been better. Yes there were small increases but nothing out of the ordinary for exceptional work. The really big increases only came when the competion made an offer for one of Jorgy's superstars. After 3 runs down that road in 21 years, I finally took a competing offer.</pros>
<cons>Cons – See the pros, I made a full statement in that section.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you value those that are making marked contributions to the bottom line, don't wait until they are walking out the door to reward them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If they like you, you will be treated differently.”

</title><pros>Pros – If you are inside sales it is laid back as long as you get your work done.  Rarely do you have to stay late.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The bonus structure is impossible to figure out.  They tell you what you made each quarter and there is no way to track your progress or success.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value your employees, give them the opportunity to learn and grow, ask for input before changing the systems we use.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>