<name>J Knipper and Co Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/J-Knipper-and-Co-Reviews-E281716.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great starting point”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice, small company.  Not a very stressful environment (workload wise).  Benefits are not too bad.  The company gives free flu shots every year and they do a nice amount of get togethers throughout the year.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hard to move up, not many positions available.  Pay rate is low.  Poor communication between its internal locations.  High turnover, except at the top of the ladder.  Poor communication among team members makes it stressful.  The people in charge of accounts often do not know how things below their level work.  When asked for help, there have been many times people have been chastised for asking too much.  Hard to determine whether they want work done correctly the first time, or after mistakes are made.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stress positive communication among all levels of the company.  Too much finger pointing goes on.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Director/Vice President (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Potential to thrive, but bureaucracy pulls the company down.”

</title><pros>Pros – While the talented folks were still in the employment of J. Knipper and Company, this firm was an exciting place to work with great career paths.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation is less than competitors, too many politics and hidden agendas have caused the company to spiral down into a dark abyss, with no hope for the future. As a result, most of the talented FTE's have been gradually resigning from the firm to work elsewhere. CHART (Caring Honesty Accountability Respect Trust) only exists on paper and seems to be more propaganda than anything else - if CHART really did exist at Knipper, the high quality of talent that left the firm would still remain there today.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't ignore your hidden talent before it's all gone...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Val Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Over all good experience as Val Analyst”

</title><pros>Pros – Many giant pharma clients' project in Sampling App helps to grow in multi function.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Validation is not facilitated by Automation testing</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Be wary of applying at J. Knipper”

</title><pros>Pros – -Competitive benefits package-Very fair and flexible with personal & vacation days-Easy commute if you live in the central New Jersey area</pros>
<cons>Cons – As of the writing of this review (6/22/2011), J Knipper is experiencing a mass exodus of any talented employees across a variety of departments within the company.  Many of which who have been employed here for more than 10 years.  Over the past 2 years, Senior management has ignored the advice of its employees, and in several cases, punished those who were more vocal about their concerns.I'm not writing this to dissuade you from applying here, as I believe this company can become a great organization once again some day, but if you're reading this near the time this review was written, I warn you, you may be in for more than you bargained for.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Place to work if you want to work hard”

</title><pros>Pros – Best in class company, nice working enviroment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Communication with employees is limited at times</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make certain goals are attainable before making promises to clients</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>