<name>School District U-46 Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/School-District-U-46-Reviews-E290911.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Teacher (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I enjoyed working there for the most part”

</title><pros>Pros – The people were very nice. Many were willing to help if needed.  The students were okay. The benefits were pretty good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The technology was extremely lacking.  The equipment was ancient.  The  supervisors were not very effective.  It was hard to find the answers to questions, because there were so many people in a department, and nobody knew who would know the answers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The administration is very top heavy, and there seems to be quite a bit of unnecessary bureaucracy in the top echelon of the administration.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you like working for a narcissist, this is the company for you”

</title><pros>Pros – Many of the staff are very dedicated and committed to providing a great educational experience for the students in U-46.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The superintendent is very narcissistic and is very much of a micro manager.  He is all about himself and advancing his opportunities in Washington DC.  He does not have the best interest of the district in mind, only his advancement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get rid of the current superintendent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Bilingual Special Ed Teacher Gr 9-12 (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Challenging, exciting, rewarding-loved working w/t kids and staff.”

</title><pros>Pros – Staff to staff support is incredible! Mentoring program was excellent.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too many grade levels to teach in  a self contained environment 9-12, and all subjects for each level.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Lack of communication between Dean and teacher of consequences given out. Follow thru from Dean's Dept. slow to response. More Deans' needed at the high school level.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very disorganized in the management of the district”

</title><pros>Pros – Many good teachers and instructional staff working there</pros>
<cons>Cons – Senior management is very disorganized and run the district in a very selfish manner</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get Out!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Teacher (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A decent district that has a loooong way to go to become successful”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of people work there.  They are trying to improve.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is very little technology to use in classrooms.  They are a little behind the times as far as modern education.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Teacher (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“hard district to work in”

</title><pros>Pros – Had a great dept. chair (who eventually became principal) who cared a lot and had my back!  She was extremely supportive... always!!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – The district is so resource poor.  We needed to use both sides of the paper in the printer, shake the ink cartridge before throwing it away. ..  Our budget was so tight!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unsatisfactory”

</title><pros>Pros – The Benefits were good.Pay was based on seniority</pros>
<cons>Cons – NEVER providing trainingPut you in any position just to fill gaps, it did not matter if you never did the job beforePut people in positions and set them up to failDid not take student discipline seriouslyPut its workers in harms way</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your workersTake student discipline seriouslyTake a look at what goes on in classroomsDon't hire HR directors who have never been in a school system before</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Teacher (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Discouraging as they treat their employees with little respect.”

</title><pros>Pros – The work day ends at 3:30, you get weekends and national holidays off, and there is a minimal health plan</pros>
<cons>Cons – The teacher retention program is in the hands of poorly trained administrators who display favoritism and bias in assignments, the pay is not comparable to other districts.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire new principals and ask the residents of the district to financially support the school system with higher taxes.  Stop giving away free lunches.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Special Education Teacher (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“1 Year Contract”

</title><pros>Pros – They try when it comes to planning and team work. They attempt to think outside the box and everyone does their part or helps make up for those who don't. Like I said, I appreciated the teamwork effort. Professional.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Morale of some classes was very low, usually depending on the teacher's attitude and presence, how they molded the class.. . or didn't. Was given a one year contract but told after the fact. This shouldn't normally happen. From my experience, teaching is not a dependable occupation anymore - most likely due to the economy. Make sure you ask if the contract is a one year minimal. If you are teaching, I suggest going ahead and aquiring a masters in something while your working. Whether it be School Psychology, Speech Pathologist, Counselor, Asst. Prin. Three years of teaching are needed for the School Psychology position but going to school during those first three years of teaching is doable and districts, in my experience, are linked with colleges in the area and have set it up where teachers get nice tuition discounts. A master's in something related to the field supports job security - have always seen positons open for School Psychologist and Speech Pathologist - have seen good counselors get the shaft.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Expound on the fact that it is a one year contract. I was told by an administrator of a different district that the position that I was applying for was a 2 year opportunity only. I understood that, but was fine with it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“School District Facilities and Maintenance”

</title><pros>Pros – Personal satisfaction in the improvement of School District.</pros>
<cons>Cons – District politics and unwarranted union criticism.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Negotiate with unions for the betterment of the district not the union members</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Teacher (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“From alumnus & former teacher perspective”

</title><pros>Pros – Many of the school-level administrators are former U-46 teachers that have gotten their type-75s.  So, they're invested in their school district, and they have tested educational know-how.  I am proud to have graduated and gone back to teach along side of many teachers I respected.The union is very supportive of its teachers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unfortunately, top-level district administrators lately have been a revolving door of people who mean well but end up trying different latest & greatest strategies to both balance the budget and improve student achievement.  However, since no one stays around long enough to see the impact of their plans, the students end up being guinea pigs for these strategies and teachers end up blamed for botched top-level district instructional mandates.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try not to do so much with so little.  Give more time for strategies to work before moving onto the next "greatest" thing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Psychologist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor salary; stressful work; nice people”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice people; great hours; summers off</pros>
<cons>Cons – No growth opportunities; poor salary</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Enrichment Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fair”

</title><pros>Pros – The family of staff make it a pleasant working invironment</pros>
<cons>Cons – our voices are not hear when conflict arises</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was bad.”

</title><pros>Pros – my children go to this school district</pros>
<cons>Cons – no room for  growth or pay</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – they need more educsation</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Teacher (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Satisfactory”

</title><pros>Pros – Safe school.  Good teacher student interactions for the most part.  Teachers have a lot of autonomy.  Other staff are supportive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This is a small district so everybody knows your business.  Parents of many students blame the schools for their student's troubles.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You need to be more aware of what the staff are doing.  Strengths need to be recognized.  Weaknesses need to be addressed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good”

</title><pros>Pros – good schedule for family life</pros>
<cons>Cons – incompetent managers at all levels</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – hire people who are competent in the area they are managing, instead of giving retired teachers jobs meant for people with the skills to do the job.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Educator review for a Kansas City elementary school”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity for professional growth and challenge.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A specific school had poor management and employee roles were constantly being confused. For example, paras were given lead teacher roles over certified teachers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve upon leadership roles and more employee interaction.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>