<name>Law Offices of Marshall C Watson Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Law-Offices-of-Marshall-C-Watson-Reviews-E290850.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-10-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Legal Fees Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good company”

</title><pros>Pros – MCW is a pretty good company to work for. The salaries are somewhat good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – hours are not flexible. It is a straight 8:30-5:30 job.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve your management and people skills. Not everyone can just completely be on board with everything you say to them just because you're a manager. Figure out how to motivate people more.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Foreclosure Paralegal (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Choice Legal/Marshall Watson....”

</title><pros>Pros – They don't micromanage.  They let you do your job.  Good benefits as well.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Don't expect to get a review.  I was there for 2 years before I got a raise (after months of asking).  I was laid off a month later.  They are not concerned with what kind of job you do, just hiring/retaining the cheapest employees.They are constantly laying people off (about 100 people since August 2013).  You cant feel safe there.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be loyal to the employees who are loyal to you and that do a good job.  Don't hire people and then get rid of them after 2 years just because you think you pay them too much.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Paralegal (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Needs Improvement”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly atmosphere and great benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – High turn over rateMandatory overtime - including weekendsLack of pay equity.  some employees were paid up to $10.00 per hour more for doing the same job as their colleague. Pay was not based on experience or education.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Develop current staff and promote from within</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Attorney (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“challenging”

</title><pros>Pros – Does not micro manage.  Ability to learn all aspects of the legal field, transactional and litigation</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too many changes on a daily basis</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be consistent.  Choose a formula and stick with it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Opportunity to learn”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity to learn about legal processes and to prepare guidance documents for these processes.  Variety in the jobs that are available.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not all of the employees are very professional and many lack basic understanding of how a corporation should operate.  Many of the employees are not competent to execute their jobs effectively.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The Firm should establish a Quality Assurance Program and regularly engage in process improvement.  Clear and metrics should be established and monitored for compliance.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>