<name>JFK University Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/JFK-University-Reviews-E29087.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sinking Ship”

</title><pros>Pros – considered to be a "green business"</pros>
<cons>Cons – The morale is very low here. The culture has completely changed to a corporate environment. They are consistently taking from employees (salary reductions, eliminating refrigerators, microwaves, and holiday pay).</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst Company Culture Ive Ever Experienced- The President/CEO is Powell not Steven Stargardter”

</title><pros>Pros – Students, faculty, staff are wonderful. Very committed. Or they were at one time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – New President Powell is very demeaning and has a cruel streak. There is something not quite right about this man. His only concern is how things look on the outside. He will use the time to clean things up at the expense of students, faculty, staff and then he will move on to the next pace and do the same. He has no regard for what works for employees, only what makes him look good to the corporate office. He listens in on conversations, says his door is open for people to share but when you do he gets angry. He only wants to hear things that stroke his ego. The corporate office hopefully has no idea the damage he is causing to the reputation of this university. Students are upset and feel taken in. Employees are jumping ship on a daily basis. Not because of the changes, but because of how he institutes the changes and how he demeans employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get rid of this horrible man before he completely ruins what little goodwill this university has left. Some of the things he is doing warrants lawsuits being filed. It is just a matter of time. Something is not right about Powell.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>