<name>Otis R Bowen Center For Human Services Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Otis-R-Bowen-Center-For-Human-Services-Reviews-E291424.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Case Mgt (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“DIversity for certain.”

</title><pros>Pros – Somewhat autonomous position, however gov't intervention is decreasing autonomy and making maximizing billing penultimate priority.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low compensation; work hours do not match 40 hr. work week. Usually give away 6 - 7 hours a week in free work due to restrictions on billing vs. hours of hourly pay allowed per week.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do not over react when you have a glut of clients who haven't yet received due to receiving many request for services at same time for many clients. You tend to over hire, then perhaps 20% of clients do not work out, leaving you with staff fighting for remaining clients and administration having to make perhaps some unrealistic requests from staff to cover services for remaining 'valid clients'.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Rehabilitation Services Provider (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent Entry level job”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible schedule, pretty good support from management, can be fun</pros>
<cons>Cons – Productivity matters more than quality.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide more training on ADLs and activities to do with clients</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>RSP (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good way to start out”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with people who really need helpVery flexible hoursThey can decide to give bounces</pros>
<cons>Cons – A productivity system that rewards quantity over quality.Being forced to lie about working over due to productivity requirements but lack of clientsPaperwork is more important than actual care.NO PAY INCREASEThe office is such that only the people who are terrible, lazy, or wanting to become management only stay.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stay behind your people, and trust them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>