<name>H Mart Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/H-Mart-Reviews-E292561.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“W.Grocery Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Work Ethic, Controlling the Section that was to be responsible!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary, Co wokers and the hours of work provided.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's ok to work with no expectation”

</title><pros>Pros – no overtime working, few good peoples</pros>
<cons>Cons – working on every other saturdays, no insurance</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Demonstrator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast-paced and”

</title><pros>Pros – The H-Mart that I worked at (Edison, NJ) was a relatively new store and as a result it was very clean, organized, and had very little clutter.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not as much recognition between employees and upper management</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Easy to hire, easy to fire”

</title><pros>Pros – free lunch. hiring process is quite easy because they are almost always under-manned. They are always willing to train you, so it's good for people fresh out of college.</pros>
<cons>Cons – non-existent benefits, high turnover rate, promotion/pay based on how many years you've spent in the company instead of merit. Senior managers should stop slacking and need to do WORK.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Many employees are VERY dissatisfied with the management. reduce the work hours, give us with better benefits (insurance, 401k, etc.), and more vacation days!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“umm.. depends how u think”

</title><pros>Pros – If you are a entry level professional, you will learn a lot from big work loads, tight deadline and smart people. Free breakfast and lunch will save you some money. Provides H1B visas to many ppl.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Literally, 0 benefits. (no insurance, no 401k no everything) 50working hours plus you have work on Sat twice a month. No overtime payment. If you have a family, you won't have lots to time to spend with your family!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I want the company to know that without hard working workers, Hmart couldn't have made this far. I think it's time for Hmart to step back and give back all the efforts and sacrifice of workers in the last 30 years.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>managger (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“work work and work”

</title><pros>Pros – friendly people, free lunch and snacksmany young talented people will help in many waysNo evaluation to your outputAbout $100 bonus per yearyou can try something new because there are lack of working process in many parts.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You will work  50 hr per week + by week Sat work 6 hr Some managers keep monitor the  workers, it is very stressful sometimes. Poor salary range and increasing rate No overtime payment No insurance, No vacation on first yr, and 4 days for 2nd yr. promotion is not related your output, it is based on continuous service.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A lot of work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Probably one of the best reasons to work at Hmart is that they give you plenty of hours if you are willing to work them. Applying for the job was relatively quick and I got started a week later. It was also nice building relationships with regular customers and I found that the customer service aspect was quite enjoyable at times. The workers there are nice also and are one of the few reasons why I found it tolerable to work at Hmart.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The job itself ranges from very exhausting to very boring. It can get very busy during upcoming holidays and weekends but can die down pretty quickly near closing. Breaks are very short as you are allowed one 30 minute break during a shift. Work standards are pretty strict and regimental as well. The worst is the amount of pay you earn in proportion to the number of hours you work there. Though you can receive quite a bit of income from a college student's perspective, the number of hours and sometimes overtime hours you must work does not offset the low pay. Also the customers can be extremely rude and difficult to deal with at times. Mishaps do not go unnoticed by supervisors and management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay the workers more and reduce their hours. Better pay equals happier workers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Human Resources Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Growing company”

</title><pros>Pros – able to meet many different athnicity.It's still growing company, you can build your carrier with your own ways.offer lunch!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working 10 hours a day.Working every other saturday.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>