<name>Michael C. Fina Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Michael-C-Fina-Reviews-E29315.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2010-12-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>28</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Quite a ride”

</title><pros>Pros – Able to speak to all levels of management if needed. Family environment with your coworkers, not everything is straight business all the time. The Finas will help you out if your in a tough bind. There's never a dull moment, there's always something going on to keep the job exciting.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay isn't competitive. A lot of managers who don't belong managing but have been able to keep their jobs because of personality. Very gossipy environment. Vacation/days off aren't competitive. No one ever does their job, always have something new thrown at you on a regular basis. Not praised/compensated justly when you do take on extra work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Praise, promote and/or compensate your best team players and people who have been loyal throughout the years. Don't always respond to just the problematic people, look into the crowd and see who are the ones who consistently deliver and don't make a fuss about things and foster those members of your team. Fire all the toxic team members and create a better overall morale.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>25</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Slavery environment, waste of time while work here”

</title><pros>Pros – There is nothing to be pros except friendly nice co-workers</pros>
<cons>Cons – No room for growth(not in my department), as mention on another review many people favorable by senior management because of personality not skill., Very very low compensation on this economic situation totally unfair</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please survey another great company and follow their way to make employee happy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-31</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>25</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“"All work and no pay makes for a unproductive employee"”

</title><pros>Pros – For a rewards company they do practice what they preach by offering annual service awards. But I'd rather get a raise every year than a certificate.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No annual salary increases! Promises of increases which never come, yet the work keeps piling on. Salary is low to begin with and the location is nothing to smile about. Totally inconvenient place to work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – This company should learn to treat their employees with respect when it comes to offering a decent wage.  Rewarding an annual certificate is not going to sustain ones ability to pay rent!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>27</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not too Happy”

</title><pros>Pros – Company has interesting products for a Corporate Recognition Company. The Magic Box, and Gift Brochures and presentation when an employee reaches a milestone are very original.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Communication disconnects between owners and managers. Managers are not given the freedom or support to implement changes or new policies without extensive round and round meetings. Solutions are not enforced or encouraged. There is a very high employee turnover at this company which may be due to a large amount of employee dissatisfaction.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Owners need to move into the 21st century and take a good hard look at how to run a company and retain employees. Micromanaging and ruling by fear and intimidation only breeds bad results.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>29</upvote>
<employee-type>Drone (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Big Mistake”

</title><pros>Pros – Coworkers are very nice people. Company has many off site social events such as Holiday Party and Company Picnic, as well as onsite events such as Pizza Fridays.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I joined this company a few months ago and I am very sorry I did. It seemed like a nice company when I joined but very quickly I began to see I was wrong. Terrible morale, constant employee turnover, very expensive health insurance, no raises, Managment does not communicate to workers, no vacation for one year, employees are unhappy and they are losing business every day. It's only a matter of time before the layoffs begin. Rampant favoritism among owners friends. Managers who hire only their friends . The offices are dirty and the HR people are very cold and aloof. Managment says they have an open door policy but they are never in the office. There are a lot of people who are looking for a way out of this company as job descriptions are not defined, a lot of people are shuffled around from department to department and do not know what there job is. The place comes across initially as a corporate environment but once inside becomes anything but.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Cut the phoney Town Hall meetings and be honest with your employees. Improve morale by creating better working conditions and effective communication. Create better policies that will encourage employees to want to work here.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-09-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>28</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Corporate Offices - Slavery and no Pay Raises”

</title><pros>Pros – Family owned, loyal, with an open door policy.  You refer everyone by their first name for all levels of management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Forget raises in 2009 and 2010.  Low moral.  Departmental restructuring.  Our pay raises is construction for new building across street.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more straight forward to the employees who make this company a success.  Reward us for our very stressful life.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>28</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Kingdom With Many Kingdoms”

</title><pros>Pros – As the company is privately owned, with relatively few employees, the structure lends itself to be nimble and agile. I find the ownership to be incredibly loyal and they do a tremendous amount to empower their employees by giving them a lot of responsibility without looking over their shoulder. While new ideas aren't always incorporated, they are welcome.The people, for the most part, are enjoyable to work with. The frontline staff are very courtesy and cordial. Frienships are easily forged and nurtured.Despite the fact that companies in this industry have been in business for a considerable period, the industry remains relatively immature. There still exists a wild-west mentality. Because of this fact, those who competent and possess a high degree of business acumen can not only enjoy a long career, but create business opportunities for themselves if they are willing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – One of the major drawbacks is the culture. It is extremely toxic, as are most companies that fit our profile. Because the ownership is extremely loyal and empowering, some employees in mid and senior level management have been able to create silos that have enabled them to conceal their professional shortcomings and gaps in competency. Interdepartmental information-sharing is completely non-existent and suggestions or feedback, intended to help, are met with a certain measure of hostility.Further, among some managers, there seems to be an imbalance between responsibility and authority. This makes achieving performance benchmarks unnecessarily challenging.Finally, although the company's structure is built for agility, we are not as agile as I would like. Ideas seemed to be evaluated based, in large part, by who has the idea, as opposed to judging the idea on its own merit.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Senior Management simply needs to be more engaged in the day-to-day operations of their respective departments. There seems to be too much of disconnect between Senior Management and their employees and functions. Some Senior Managers also need to spend more time being more proficient at their jobs than scoring political points when and where-ever they could do so.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>29</upvote>
<employee-type>Slave (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“For The Love of God, Work Somewhere Else!”

</title><pros>Pros – There are no good reasons, never mind best.Job descriptions do not live up to the actual job you will be doing.Collecting a paycheck but at what cost? There is so much dissension at this company nobody stays for very long. Very little room for growth, and terrible morale. Pay is unfair, Holidays are practically non existent; policies are back from the stone age, I'm sorry there are just no pros to this company unless you consider getting a paycheck, but going home exhausted, drained, sick and nearly a nervous wreck from a day in this place is just not worth it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everything about this company is terrible. This is not a great place to work. Here are some of the existing policies in this company.1) Health Insurance: at the Fina company everyone is charged the same rates, regardless of whether the employee earns minimum wage or six figures. There is no salary banding where an employee’s premiums are adjusted to their salary. There are only two plans here, PPO and EPO and only individual or family. The lowest plan available charges each employee 100.00 per week for family coverage and the PPO family coverage charges each employee 150.00 per week.2) Vacation: at the Fina company, no one receives any vacation at all for the entirety of the first year of employment.3)Sick Time: The salaried workers get 10 paid sick days per year, the hourly workers only 5 paid sick days per year. A lot of employees are berated for using all of their allotted sick time even if they have doctor’s notes.4) The working environment here is unclean. In offices employees have to tolerate flies, roaches, and mice. Whenever it rains some of the offices get flooded which creates a mold problem as the carpets get soaked.5)The working environment here is unsafe. There is constant mopping of public areas such as lunchrooms and staircases during occupied business hours. This is a safety concern as employees can slip and fall and sustain possible injury.6) There is a serious rift in the rules and regulations company wide between salaried and hourly employees. The employee manual does not address the different needs of each group and there is no one set of standard rules for all employees.7)The Fina company is not a psychologically or emotionally healthy place to work. The Fina company has an extremely high employee turnover, as people come onboard with good attitudes only to find that this company is so unlike most other companies. Morale here is at an all time low, with many employees unhappy, depressed, and searching for new jobs. Many employees are stressed, as this company does not give breaks as required by law.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Retire already</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>24</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor management, Low pay”

</title><pros>Pros – A job that pays a little better than minimum wage.</pros>
<cons>Cons – For a company prides itself in helping other companies recognize and retain talents, it did not do a good job in keeping its own employee happy.  The pay is below average.  Employee turnover is high.  Management is out of touch with reality.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The company has great ideas but applies them inconsistently.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great location.  Great product.  The management is constantly thinking of new ideas that can make a difference. The management is sensitive to employee needs in tough situations.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is inconsistent.  I witnessed many examples of favoritism.  The employees don't always know what is expected.  Implementation and follow through of new ideas is lacking.  The management is not always aware of employeed needs on a daily basis.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat everyone the same way and try to get a more 360 on the day to day.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>26</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“reviews”

</title><pros>Pros – co workers and the fina family</pros>
<cons>Cons – managers have double standards, they need to be more fair and understanding</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – management needs to be judge like employees,  stop spending so much on directors and pay the employees who actually worked</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great family oriented place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – They are a family owned company and it feels very family oriented.  Senior Management is very fair, and all of the managers give great direction to their teams.  There are great company events like the holiday party and summer bbq.  They have a great social conscience which supports numerous charities including the Leukemia and Lymphoma Society, and a great charitable match contribution. They communicate extremely well with us through town hall meetings, newsletters and Senior Management has an open door policy that I have never experienced before.  There is a real commitment to the employees and a constant effort to make Michael C. Fina a great place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The only issue I have is that the corporate offices are in LIC and there is not much around here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to empower the employees and stay on track for the future.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>29</upvote>
<employee-type>PO Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ANTIQUATED”

</title><pros>Pros – close to grand central, good 401k, free breakfast once a week. salary was camparable but not worth it to work here for too long. this is a family run company so room to advanced is somewhat limited. also lack of physical work space means theres is a cap on how many employees they can have in each department. offices have no windows and can get very depressing especially since the furniture is old and the offices are messy. nothing fundamentally wrong with this company but just not a happy place to go to everyday.</pros>
<cons>Cons – no room for growth, salary is not good, high turnover, information in system is never updated,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – if you care about your employees, your employees will care about you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>