<name>Law Offices of Daniel C. Consuegra Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Law-Offices-of-Daniel-C-Consuegra-Reviews-E296957.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-05-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Legal Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great opportunity to work in a law office and work with a great group of people.”

</title><pros>Pros – The hours, benefits, compensation, and opportunity to advance are some of the best reasons. I also enjoy working with people who are respectfully and take their job seriously. Even though we have our own work, we are all willing to help each other.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The biggest downside, if you want to call it that is the office is running out of space. The office is continuously expanding and really needs a bigger office space.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – My only advice is to keep doing what you are doing. Keep everyone informed when a policy or procedure changes so that everyone knows. It's all about staying informed and the management at Daniel C. Consuegra has that under control.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant? (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If Unprofessional, Crazy and Ghetto is for you...go for it”

</title><pros>Pros – None. Absolutely Zip! Nada! None!</pros>
<cons>Cons – The experience I had walking in the door was bananas! I thought...law firm? Professional, partnership, respect... NOT at this place. Think Ghetto, rampant and unprofessional.For starters the person ( I don't think its human) who "trained" me had no clear objective, goal and/or set up. They just flew by the seat of their pants. This person had 0 credibility to me as they could only churn out their workflow which was troubling to say the least. The lack of respect shown to the few "trainees" there was left me with the the taste of vile on my tongue.The rampant bullying, disrespect and unprofessionalism of the "workers" ie monkeys will make you want to run screaming from the building.  On every given day you see these monkeys patrolling the aisles (this place IS a call center environment...the best Tampa has to offer) and hurling disgusting insults at anyone they please.  (I am waiting for this one woman to turn into the Hulk with the grief they give her... I guess because she is not a monkey as well. )The crux of the ghetto monkeys days are to be promoted to "team leader" even though they do not know how to spell leader let alone read up on or endow the Principles of Leaderships.If you wish to work with vile, under achieving, un-educated wastes of skin this is the place for you!On the actual "professional" side, the attorneys DO NOT read the documents submitted their way, neither do they take into account the client, defendant or the legal process as they are expected to churn out a record number of foreclosures as that is what this "firm" is built on.The founder Daniel Consuegra has a birds eye view as to the entire firm, thanks to a glass wall and cameras but he has no idea from the bottom to the top his hard works and efforts are being destroyed. i saw from the bottom to the top as a firms foundation starts at the grassroots and works its way up.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – RESTRUCTURE. RESTRUCTURE. RESTRUCTURE! Take note of whats going on! Although most in management are not qualified, you still have the power to ensure that the work, professional conduct and culture of the firm be turned around.Unfortunately, this means relieving yourself of the guilt to be affirmative action go-getters and releasing a bunch of ghetto and a whole lot of monkeys...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Paralegal (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Modern-day Sweatshop”

</title><pros>Pros – Since the departure of Jennifer Sesta, morale has improved tremendously! The "Gemini-style" of management is being slowly replaced by a more stabile "Sagitarian-style." The following could be construed as a positive: Shift work, each person has a PC.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is, unfortunately, a lot to report here - employee exploitation is the thrust of the business model. They will hire people, who no one else will hire and pay barely above minimum wage. You will find here people who are pierced all over, wear whatever, reek, and have bfs/gfs serving prison sentences. They claim they perform bakground checks but I seriously doubt it.  A former computer tech is rumored to have once hacked into their system and disrupt business for several days after being fired for porking a co-worker in the HR office.Bullying is rampant, theft (of food from the refrigrator) is frequent, and incompetence is everywhere. Attorneys are casually dating each other and dating the staff - one attorney recently slapped another attorney   during an outing. The place resembles a call center and is constantly running out of space. There are cameras all over the place. The restrooms are positioned within earshot of people working at cubes (they can hear toilets flushing). The head-guy is full of fluff with little professional substance. The second honcho is, at best, one notch better; but, nothing to brag about.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – This model will eventually implode - look what happened to Nazi Germany.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Paralegal (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

““Bad apple tree infects all apples””

</title><pros>Pros – No drugs, alcohol , or background check; benefitial for some people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very unfair working place. You can learn here how bad apple tree can infect all apples causing very low employees morale and bullying.Destructive behavioral pattern occur when the group made decision like firing a poor performer. Co-workers routinely treated one another with disdain and disrespect.Scowls, insults, back-stabbing, teasing, and widespreaded meaness; completely infected working environment. One nasty person brings down the whole team. Anger and hostility are contigues in this firm and the whole team becams infected.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take long look in the mirror if you lead a jerk-infested team. Learn about anti-bullying. Managers weaknessess are damaging workers morale and performance.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Have to be in the "IN" crowd to advance”

</title><pros>Pros – Casual dress environment, that is it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is all over the place.  Change of procedures in a blink of an eye.  If you are not friends with management then your potential for growth is nil.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be professional, stop the gossip, and recognize the workers.  Stop flaunting authority and use your authority when it is needed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Legal Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Comfortable and Fun”

</title><pros>Pros – The work environment is relaxed and fun.  I really like the people I work with.  There have been a lot of positive changes in the way the firm is being managed which are making the firm a better place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The level of training has improved, but I would like to see more and more training.  There is a lot of work to do, which is both good and bad.  For someone that cannot live with not getting everything done same day, it may be a con.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to introduce more training.  Better communicate changes being made in the firm so you make sure everyone gets the information timely.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work and learn the legal process”

</title><pros>Pros – Relaxed dress code and casual work environment, nice people to work with, lots of opportunities to learn new things, different work schedules, willing to train, the attorneys are available and nice to work with, have seen lots of good changes in the last 6 months - like rewarding good employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Open cubicle environment (can be a con to those who want offices), more on the job training than training classes, lots of work (can be a con to those who can't get organized), lots of people (con to those who like smaller more private workplaces).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work on more training for everyone, keep trying to find ways to reward good employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good entry level job with no advancement”

</title><pros>Pros – good entry level legal job</pros>
<cons>Cons – no decent chance for advancement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more consideration of personal issues for staff.  more chance for advancement.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work if you have few options.”

</title><pros>Pros – There was exposure to the foreclosure process and simple hearings to get your feet wet.  With enough time spent there it would be possible to get more litigation experience.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Required to perform unethically for low pay and extremely large amount of work.  Was required to sign so many pleadings and other correspondence that it was almost impossible to read anything.  Was expected and encouraged to sign faster and get the documents out as fast as possible.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I have no advice for management.  There business model includes paying low pay for large volumes of work and walking the gray line and they expect high turnover.  The management has succeeded at their business model.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Starter Job”

</title><pros>Pros – Casual Dress code is allowed.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No recognition for job done well - only repercussion</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More recognition towards the workers when they steadily produce quality work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Legal Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Legal Assistant”

</title><pros>Pros – The office is pretty flexible if you are attending or planning on attending university or grad school.  They have different shifts because the firm is so busy due to the industry it is in.  There is no dress code, so you can wear sweat pants to work if you wanted to since the clients rarely visit.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I think now the 8am05pm shift is gone and you have to choose between a morning or night shift (5am-1:30pm or 1:30pm-10pm) and that means sharing a desk with someone.  They also pay significantly less than competing firms that do the same type of work around the Tampa Bay area.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would suggest recognizing the good people you end up hiring.  A lot of college kids come in because of flexibility, but their efforts are not recognized.  Also, I wished management was more open to suggestions for morale boosting.  Morale was the biggest problem around the office.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Need to start over”

</title><pros>Pros – no dress code..Cameras all around not to watch the property but to watch the people. No trust.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This company has a very high employment turn over. They are not loyal to anyone. They treat you like you are in high school. I wouldnt trust them with any of my business. Its ashame that the managment team is the one that is running the place into the ground. I have never seen a company hire and fire over 100 employees within 6 months. Its like a revolving door. The pay is about the amount you wil recieve at McDonalds. You have to get permission to have a pot luck.  wow.....Kindergarten program.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The worst career move of my life!”

</title><pros>Pros – Casual work environment and nice co-workers</pros>
<cons>Cons – This office resembles a call center more than a law firm.  Management is completely disrespectful to staff.  There are no ethical guidelines whatsoever.  Paralegals are expected to churn out tons of pleadings and attorneys just sign everything without reading anything.  There are no good attorneys there as all of the good ones seem to leave within a few months.  Attorneys are not encouraged to properly review work.  Managers, not attorneys, run the firm and tell both the paralegals and attorneys what to do.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management should all be fired and people with a decent work ethic and respect for the law should be hired.  If not, the firm will continue to have such a high turn around.  After the first two months, everyone cannot wait to find a new job.  Clearly management is awful!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>