<name>Sistema Universitario Ana G Mendez Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Sistema-Universitario-Ana-G-Mendez-Reviews-E297373.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-03-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Any advice for the interview”

</title><pros>Pros – A friend of mine has an interview with them at Orlando Campus. They want a teaching demo; do you have any advice!!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – I think it is for Biology Department but I'm not sure</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – ..</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Development (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great job experience that promotes creativity but lacks greatly organisation.”

</title><pros>Pros – They promote creativity and innovationListen to the lower workers for ideas</pros>
<cons>Cons – Payment by contract can be delayed up to 6 monthsCommunication is done only by phone</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Use other methods of communication.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“They will screw students for money and they have a poor sense of management - Wheaton, MD”

</title><pros>Pros – bilingual education, good salary and opportunity to get your degree with them</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of management from corporate and from campus leaders. You learn while making mistakes and they have a very toxic culture. Memos come an go with no resolution, instead telling you that you will lose your job. Intimidation is they way they operate and either they let you go or people leave because they do not want to be subject to that kind of treatment. Personnel is like a revolving door, many of the original employees have been let go or they quit. Most of the employees in the current positions do not have the qualifications to have those positions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Salaries are extremely conservative. No compensation and no opportunity to grow.”

</title><pros>Pros – Many days off because of the holidays. Fair schedule (Monday - Friday).</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salaries are extremely conservative. No compensation. Poor management skills. Lack of professionalism from management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Educational Facilitator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working as part-time facilitator”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to work with experienced professionals and very helpful administration staff.  Faculty members are very accessible to sharing educational experiences.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Improve planning and scheduling of class offerings for the whole year.  Opportunity for full time facilitators with benefits.  Adoption of new technologies to enhance educational experience and productivity, such as social and digital media.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More acceptance of newer technologies to enhance teaching methodology, such as social media tools and paperless class documentation.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>IT Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Only to learn not to stay.”

</title><pros>Pros – Holidays, time to study and more!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor culture and little objectivity!!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A lot of bureocracies...”

</title><pros>Pros – Being in a learning environment...</pros>
<cons>Cons – The managers I had did not meet the neccesary competencies for their job. Lots of competition  and jealousy, and gossiping.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take in consideration employees feedback, monitor their managers...</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Job Review at SUAGM”

</title><pros>Pros – University environment, Diversity, academic competence, good benefits, decent salary, localities around PR, committed professors, good academic programs, friendly people</pros>
<cons>Cons – limited opportunity for advancement, supervisors hired without minimum requirements, lack of supervision,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be attentive to employees complaints, supervised directly branches throughout PR, promote from within, tuition payment outside SUAGM</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>