<name>SK+G Advertising Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/SK-G-Advertising-Reviews-E297943.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-02-28</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great atmosphere. Fast paced.”

</title><pros>Pros – Love the work and the people. Great support and benefits. Great agency atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work load can be challenge, but worth it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Interactive (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not the best for sure.”

</title><pros>Pros – Met a few hard working people that made it possible to keep working there. Free snacks and alcohol on Fridays. Clean refrigerators.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Met too many unpleasant and mean people. Too much politics. Sweat shop. Do not need to be talented to get ahead, as long as one knows whose back to scratch.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management would not know what to do with any good advice. They don't seem able to learn new tricks.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A modern, laid-back but engaging place to work. Standard amount of politics to deal with.”

</title><pros>Pros – It's very laid-back. Employees are trusted to get their work done without being micromanaged. Very modern environment, employees are taken care of very well on a general scale.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long nights are sometimes a necessity to get big projects done on time. There is some level of politics to deal with, depending on department.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stay on top of feedback with employees, try to be as open as possible with communications on a general scale.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Advertising is Hard Enough, Don't Make it Harder.”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of smart and talented people are attracted to SK+G because of its client roster, few places have this much experience in Hospitality and Gaming. Contrary to some of the reviews posted here, I would say that there are intelligent people in every department, giving their all to do the best job they know how. Caution: If you are looking for a real agency, let me just say, SK+G is a great place to get some serious customer service work experience. For Creatives, if you like it when you sweat bullets to find the sweet spot on a idea, it gets really fun when you are required to present something less compelling and even safe, just to be sure all bases are covered.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The managing partners make sweeping decisions from the gut, with little patience for background information, based on their forecasting of the personal whims of the client; rather than what might be good for the client's brand. At random the managing partners over-rule any and all staff, regardless of that person's level of experience or expertise. This creates a stressful and chaotic environment where information and ideation is not shared, but plans are made behind closed doors and shared only moments before they are shown to the client. An integrated shop it is not; without collaboration opportunities are missed, only to be called out by the client.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – A. Keep doing what you are doing. As long as you have clients, you must be doing something right.B. Trust the experts you have hired to be experts.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Account Coordinator Review”

</title><pros>Pros – Great colleagues to work with and great benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low salaries, very political, account management is treated horribly compared to creatives- we were known as the "dark side."</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest more time and effort into your employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>