<name>J Sainsbury Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/J-Sainsbury-Reviews-E2978.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“General Assistant”

</title><pros>Pros – Great atmosphere, top salary. Make sure you leave a good impression on your manager/supervisor because that is key in this company. To do that, work hard from day one.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can get repetitive so you have to be prepared for that. Also, you may encounter some unfriendly customers so you have to be able to take stuff like that on the chin.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop showing favoritism.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-28</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good PayBonusesCareer prospectsGreat TeamEmpathetic managers</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bonus isn't great compared to other companies within this sector (e.g Waitrose)Due to high number of staff, overtime isn't always available</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company but work needs to be done”

</title><pros>Pros – great company to work for and the pay is really good if you are in one of their local stores. Really easy to transfer to other stores and even easier to move up within the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The uniform is awful - polo shirts and black trousers; nice if we were in shirt and ties like every other supermarket name. the workload is too much because some stores are so under staffed and some employees will not partake in all aspects of the supermarket (In a local store every person including managers are expected to work on the shop floor and put out stock etc.)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – hire more staff, get a better uniform and train staff more</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Varied”

</title><pros>Pros – National organistion which should mean better career prospects for growth.Quick with customer queries.Good working hours which is goo for balancing a social life.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Do not see the the full abilities of all staff.Should improve recruitment process to change for different service areas.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Change online recruitment process</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Department Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not bad”

</title><pros>Pros – Only the Salary and the possibility to make friends</pros>
<cons>Cons – Almost thing in tre word</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“BA”

</title><pros>Pros – Looks after employees very well</pros>
<cons>Cons – Headquarters can seem distant from stores</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to develop through from all levels of experience and expertise”

</title><pros>Pros – Can do culture, great community feel across organisation, everyone is working towards serving our customers from HR to IT to Finance ect.....meeting celebrities in the office and free products.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Normal politics across most places, often people are moved around to departments without experience...for example a Beers manager moving to IT role.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Is what it is.”

</title><pros>Pros – You are treated relatively well and have to try really hard to be fired. Sainsbury's is pretty ethically sound.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The work is not mentally engaging at all. The environment is not a very nice place to be after a while. You will have to take a lot abuse from customers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start realising and utilising the resources you have at your finger-tips: very capable and skilled people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Code Checker (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Brilliant company who understand staff are the key to success.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great prospect of progression and training. Key to success is staff and the company understands this quite clearly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Improve pay to a living standard. Store management could adopt a flexible management style to improve operations. Having to work a few departments at the same time during busy periods with minimal staff is a struggle.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hard work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good bunch of people that you work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management are quick to judge and point fingers so don't encourage.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Remember your only as good as your staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great First Job”

</title><pros>Pros – Discount CardGreat Team to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor managementPoor wagePoor shift management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Respect colleagues that work hard at their job and don't undermine them</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overworked and under-appreciated”

</title><pros>Pros – There's a decent pension scheme and adequate discount which is increased at holiday times throughout the year. There are plenty of opportunities to attend Food Colleges in some departments, which can lead to NVQs in subjects relevant to your current role, which can then be transferred on. There are also some genuinely delightful customers who make it all (briefly) seem worthwhile.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I have never worked for a company with such blatant disregard and disrespect for the well-being of its staff. On food service departments, scheduled hours are slashed to the bone meaning colleagues receive a bare minimum of breaks and sometimes go hours without even a drink of water, as it's apparently prohibited to consume anything behind the counter, and are often expected to assist other departments even though their counter is single-staffed and this means leaving it empty. Company rules state strict hygiene and apparel rules,which are flagrantly flouted by management, as it doesn't apply to them, apparently. There is a group who are 'in' with management and therefore get away with floating about and doing as little as they can manage, while the rest of us work like dogs to keep standards up. If you work over your shift time, you won't get paid - this is expected of team leaders who get treated like the scum of the earth by management and sometimes by colleagues, with no comeback whatsoever. It is an absolute joke that one of this company's mission statements is 'respect for the individual'. No consideration is given to colleagues who have families outwith the "2.5 children" scenario leading to terrible work-life balance for colleagues who may also have demanding personal schedules albeit without any child-rearing duties. Rules very strict on absence with no consideration given to those with chronic conditions or hidden disabilities, even after meeting with management to resolve issues, they are told that the "needs of the business" outweigh their own personal considerations.From a business standpoint, the focus is very clearly on customer service, and yet colleagues who spend too much time with a customer (helping an elderly customer with their shopping, for example, or advising a customer on a recipe for the product they are buying) will receive a tongue-lashing. Much is made of their "legal documentation to prove due diligence" and yet colleagues are advised to falsify these or "just sign it" and even when arguing their case are told that they are in the wrong for following the correct procedure they were explicitly trained to follow. Lip service is paid to being safe and legal but to all intents and purposes it is only lip service and management clearly don't care if they endanger their staff and customers, as long as they can say "oh, we're compliant" and keep raking in the profits.Lack of organisation: may be unique to my store, doubtful though that is. HR constantly and consistently "lose" papers submitted to them - expenses receipts, schedules, and worst of all training booklets. Some colleagues have been repeatedly trained and signed off on the same modules, the paperwork submitted, only to have it mysteriously go missing and the colleague being dressed down for non-completion. I myself am on my fourth copy of a certain module. Repeat training must cost a fortune in paper and colleague hours and certainly engenders a lot of ill-will towards the idling HR colleagues.All in all the store would not be unpleasant to work in if it were not for the constant procedure 180 turns, appalling disorganization and mis-communication, or the daily microagressions and complaints of management leveled at colleagues who are already working near flat-out just to complete their daily tasks.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please start treating colleagues respectfully and as people, not as brain-dead automatons without any spark of creative thought or knowledge. Start listening to local knowledge and stop treating every store as if it were a big city superstore. Recognize the strengths you have in your colleagues instead of insisting they all perform in exactly the same way, and then criticizing them when they cannot perform at superhuman levels for extended periods of time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I've been here a long time so it can't be that bad”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of opportunities if you want to reach out and get them. Company has great corporate values and place high importance on making the world a better place even though it strives for profits</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow in some respects to get things done</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Checkout Operator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A friendly environment that made an effort to make a boring job a little less boring”

</title><pros>Pros – - You get to meet amazing people.- There's a light and non-corporate feel (for example dressing up on red nose day).- There's a real active effort to make the colleagues matter. The company's policy is that if the employees are happy, so will the customers.- Good, mostly worthwhile, training.- Lots of opportunities for extra work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Breaks were often late or supervisors didn't reply to reply to requests very quickly sometimes.- The till systems were quite old.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Spend some money upgrading the tills and making them modern - it'll look better as well as being easier and quicker to use.- Make sure employees get breaks on time.- Allow anyone over 18 to approve an under 18 to sell alcohol; it's the person who's under 18's job to  ID the customer.- Ask employees before making big changes - for example a load of tills were removed when we really needed them.- When a colleague quits, allow the store to hire someone new if they need them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Feels just like school and that is not a good thing”

</title><pros>Pros – Meet great people and build's up your confidence as you will meet very strange and rude people in-store - thicker skin.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is not the best, managers ask but never give, managers never take your side even when the customer is wrong. managers can be extremely rude (lack of people skills), Sainsbury's customers can be quite rude to staff for absolutely no reason and the discount is how may I say this politely la crap.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Enhance pay, improve or recruit better mangers, better holiday allocations and up the percentage on the discount cards.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent”

</title><pros>Pros – Great managment teamExcellent training</pros>
<cons>Cons – I loved my time at Sainsburys</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There needs to be better opportunites for development within the comapny</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“J Sainsbury”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work-life balance and not strenuous work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Tedious, not very rewarding work</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for part time work while at university.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good managements, work balance, central area to live in, competent senior management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Rigid career movement opportunities, repertitive work, lack of training.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Project Management”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible, ability to move cross functionally</pros>
<cons>Cons – Quite stuck in its ways, lots of old timers making progression quite hard in certain areas...</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“General Assistant”

</title><pros>Pros – Job security, lots of staff</pros>
<cons>Cons – Boring repetitive work, customers are a pain</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good no frills”

</title><pros>Pros – paid holiday even on part time contracts no matter how long you have been there. good starter job</pros>
<cons>Cons – not very flexible and can be very repetitive. but overall you get what you expect from the job</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Human Resources Planning & Development (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best Employee Oriented Retail Industry in GB”

</title><pros>Pros – Employees get the utmost respect.</pros>
<cons>Cons – a employee oriented mostly dont have cons.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Checkout Operator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Friendly & helpful people, would reccomend if looking for a job!”

</title><pros>Pros – Most of the people I've worked with in my time there have been very friendly. The processes are straight forward. It's a great company to work for!</pros>
<cons>Cons – They're fine with given you overtime, but not when you ask for more permanent hours! They'd rather hire temps for Christmas than offer extra hours to current staff first!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Some of the managers don't have a clue how to manage!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“very good”

</title><pros>Pros – joyful,accountable,worthy, credible and good atmosphere</pros>
<cons>Cons – If they got talented people who are already working and willing to work and stay in uk but the company doesn't support for  visa.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to talk with the government and try to make a way for the working employers to stay and continue their work .</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Expect too much from an ever shrinking work force”

</title><pros>Pros – Good team morale, good opportunities to progress and further your career.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Size of workforce is decreasing to almost inhumane levels, expected to do the job of 3 people now.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employ more staff at all levels! Would improve the completion of daily processes to ensure a better customer experience.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Code Controller (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Controller”

</title><pros>Pros – Learn Management skills, work under pressure, solving analytical problems</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not specifically relates to my filed that I am actually looking for</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent career progression at lower levels”

</title><pros>Pros – Incredible CEO and leadership team developing market leading strategy and then implementing impecably</pros>
<cons>Cons – Still some residual 'bullying' management behviour tolerated. It is dying out, but is still rewarded too much.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Insist on those is the top 200 managers displaying the desired behaviours at all time. Never turn a blind eye to proactices which deliver results but don't align with the behaviours.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Challenging and not great communication to trainees”

</title><pros>Pros – The people culture is amongst some of the best i have worked for</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours, very tight budgets, challenging stores</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>CSA (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Nice place to work  very nice”

</title><pros>Pros – very Flexiable, good with families  Friendly</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing that i could think of for here</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Counter Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Terrible for Deli Staff, especially students”

</title><pros>Pros – You used to get more time to socialise with other staff</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you book a holiday. Middle management will probably forget and call you in anyway.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Middle management make it hard for students to take time off to study for exams</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“typical Supermarket”

</title><pros>Pros – Discount card, Pension Scheme, Save as you Earn, Staff all friendly</pros>
<cons>Cons – Staff have to stick to policies, have to fight for Management/ Team Leaders to stick to there Policies</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stick to the Policies and do the jobs all the staff do to pick up the moral of the work place</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good,interesting,funny, dangerous,fabulous!”

</title><pros>Pros – quick , good, cashier, checkouts fine!</pros>
<cons>Cons – insults, name -calling, bad customers, horrible bosses.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – have a heart. listen. be good.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Counter Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good employer”

</title><pros>Pros – They are good too there employees, the wages are reasonable and if you are ambitious there is always opportunities to further yourself</pros>
<cons>Cons – Wages are lower than other employees in the same sector, some methods by dept. managers and team leaders are not good</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – listen to employees more to save money as wastage is excessive</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Checkouts, Produce and Dual Storing...”

</title><pros>Pros – I've worked on pretty much every department in JS. There's always good oppotunites to move along, and very good connections to "those in the know".Being a University student, I have been able to spilt my term time and holiday's working between two stores.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working between the stores does have difficulties in switching and moving holidays, and organising training and refreshers can be challenging.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Code Controller (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good”

</title><pros>Pros – if you want to get on then its there if you want</pros>
<cons>Cons – you say its best to know all the ins and out but some times it feels like we were doing the managers job .when all you want to do is your job you were trained to  do</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – talk to the staff see if they like the job they are doing</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Basic wages, boring repeated work..”

</title><pros>Pros – They pay our Holiday but nothing else.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Boring. No respect for staffs. Customer are always right. No place for career development opportunities.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay decent wages, support ur staffs. Delegate jobs. Give opportunities to handle responsibility to bright staffs.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Assistant (Night Shift) (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A fun and enthusiastic place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Progression opportunities within the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work/life balance not reviewed as strongly as could be.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work/life balance not reviewed as strongly as could be.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good colleagues, bellow par management.”

</title><pros>Pros – Depending on the location of the store, the employees are all really nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most of the management are only in their positions because the competent people have left, as a result, they remain and get promoted because they are the most experienced, not because they are the most competent.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Realise that some of the part-time student employees are very talented and deserve more respect than they are given.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good”

</title><pros>Pros – nice company with good prospects. it is a growing business that has managed to weather the downturn in the economy</pros>
<cons>Cons – there are not much downsides. It depends on the role and how you progress but you have to meet their conditions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – the leadership is going in the right direction and needs to adopt better strategies to compete in the global environment.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not too bad”

</title><pros>Pros – The job is an easy one, you meet some cool people, management is professional, you get a decent discount after working for a while, tend to be flexible with the working hours to suit everyone.</pros>
<cons>Cons – HR tends to be pathetic at dealing with some issues such as payment, sometimes the shifts you get are too long, breaks are too short</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Train up your HR department and allow your staff some longer breaks! I also suggest getting a designer to sort out that horrible maroon uniform.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good way to keep me funded during my student years”

</title><pros>Pros – The job was ok, I had varied tasks and was trained to work on many deparments. Plenty of overtime on offer also.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There was NO recognition from management when a job was well done but they were soon to come down on you when something isn't done correctly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Recognise a job well done, and constantly communicate expectations to employees. Also make sure employees get the opportunity for feedback more than once a year.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great”

</title><pros>Pros – great place to work , nice company</pros>
<cons>Cons – pay is not reflective of the hours worked</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – great</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Job that will always be there, but stagnating”

</title><pros>Pros – The work is solid and as long as you don't make a gross obvious mistake you will always have that job. Discount is ok. It's fairly easy to get promoted to the Team Leader position. They are excellent towards students and I've never had a problem getting emergency time off or had any issues or complaints with my holidays. Store managers treat you as humans. Solid development system. Training readily available if you want it. Job responsibilities clearly laid out.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work weekends and holidays for no premium. Pay is very low, even with London Weighting. Customers will abuse you for their own amusement/stress relief. Bonus is slim. Labour budgets too tight (in Convenience) leading to massive stress and failure to hit other targets. Store CCTV and security procedures focus on staff being criminals, rather than on actual criminals. There is serious risk of assault on weekends, especially in Convenience. Physical toll on your body. Quality of working environment depends on the specific store you are in, some of the Convenience stores are catastrophically bad.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increase labour budgets in Convenience stores. Start treating each Convenience store as it's own local entity with it's own sales direction and daily routine, rather than standardising ranges and policies across a whole diverse area.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ok”

</title><pros>Pros – good for part time student</pros>
<cons>Cons – work will not appriciate that's why</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good”

</title><pros>Pros – the pay was good , and also the benefits , uniform looked nice</pros>
<cons>Cons – work load was too much ,  the costumers can be rude . not good place to work if want to work in calm enivironment .</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – hire more people</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Alright”

</title><pros>Pros – Good as an inbetween job but very difficult to consider as a serious career option. You move up quickly at first and then things stagnate after the second year.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's a grocery store. And no matter how hard you work you will always be working at a groery store. Employee motivation is low.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“it was fantastic, energetic and little bit stressful”

</title><pros>Pros – enjoy to work with different people and to have a good unity in diversity among all.And delivering excellent customer service.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Little bit pressure is given for the job to be done</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-31</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Shelf Stacker (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sainsbury's Could Be Great Again If....”

</title><pros>Pros – Holiday time is about the best thing to say about Sainsbury's....although the staff discount isn't bad at certain times of the year....</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of respect from some of the departmental managers towards other members of staff. Constant procedure changes by the management on the basis that you're supposed to be able to read their minds!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You need to retrain some of your department managers in the art of of to treat other members of staff with respect in order to get the best out of them. The phrase "to many chiefs and not enough indians" springs to mind. The night shift are a law unto themselves causing a great deal of problems for the day shift....And i think the term "to many kingdom builders" also springs to mind along with bullying by departmental manager who seem to think that is how they are going to gain respect by making people cry and belittling them in front of others. So, Senior managers do your self a favour and take care of the staff that help you get your big bonuses at the end of the day.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Grocery Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sainsburys Staff”

</title><pros>Pros – 10 % Discount on shopping, 15% at peak times of year eg. Christmas, Easter etc.No problems arranging time off.Paid holidays, which increase when you do more over timeExcellent staff facilities, pool table, canteen etcExcellent staff parties</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working weekendsManagers who think they're better than you at timesBoring routine at timesPlenty of training, good and bad i suppose</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't make such a big gap between employees and duty managers. Store managers definetely shouldn't get the money their on and especially bonuses. Iv worked under 5, and all but 1 does nothing!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Counter Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Okay place for a student, but dead end for anyone else!”

</title><pros>Pros – Good job while you're studying you're A-levels.Makes you realise the value in going to University and getting a decent job!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very boring and monotanous. Customers treat you like you are dirt even though they know nothing about you! Little or no respect from managers. But who can blame them, eh?</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – To be honest you do a good job for the most part; just make sure managers treat people as individuals and bother to get to know new staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Assistant (Shelf Stacker), Fresh Foods (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you have to work in a supermarket, you could do a lot worse”

</title><pros>Pros – The trouble with reviewing retail firms is that it's impossible to say whether my experience is representative of other stores.Nonetheless, I was fairly impressed by the senior colleagues at the store I worked at though - they got things done with the minimum of slave driving, and treated you as a person. Not a lot to ask for I guess, but probably shouldn't be taken for granted in this sector.Sainsburys does seem to be genuinely trying to invest in the development of shop floor colleagues - via both promotion and job rotation. While I wouldn't expect to go from checkout to boardroom, competent (and inevitably incompetent) staff who stick around seem to get promoted, eventually. Don't get me wrong - it's still a dead end job, but by the standards of retail Sainsburys isn't probably a bad place to be a till monkey.Benefits (paid holidays, discount, pension, ect) seem pretty good - if your plan to to supermarket work for the long haul, god help you then Sainsburys probably isn't a bad place to be.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay, obviously: though £6.44/hour basic [that's with London weighting] is pretty average for retail work. Your bonus for hitting sales/mystery customer targets is a mere 1% though. Compare that to 15% at a Tesco I worked at a few years back (again, not sure how representative these figures are for other stores).As you can probably guess, the work ranges from bearable to soul-destroying. Obviously a lot depends on your actual role, colleagues, and temperament, but there's no getting away from the fact that shelf stacking/till work is about as menial as it gets. if you can hack doing the same thing every day with very little development or variety then you'll be fine.A small minority of customers seem to get kicks from talking down to you. Again, probably par for the course for retail.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop messing about giving 1% bonuses to shop floor colleagues. Up it to double digits, or just don't bother.Other than that JS seems to be in a good place at the moment. Keep up the good work, and don't take your eye off the ball.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Shelf Stacker (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Low wages”

</title><pros>Pros – Best reason for working ast Sainsbury's is the company of other staff. They come from all over the world and I made many friends there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The work I was doing was boring. But that wasn't the fault of management. Shelf stacking would be dull in any supermarket.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increase the wages and incentives offered.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type> Department Manager  (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Start”

</title><pros>Pros – Best UK Retailer 2009. Great team. Friendly colleagues, & good training regime. Staff discount raises to 15% twice per year - combined with offers mean some great deals on things you need every day.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long Hours. Lack of resource puts all teams under great pressure to deliver, but the money saved is being pumped into the expansion plan which should be great for Sainsbury's who will then take on the likes of Tesco in more areas of the country.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“only just over minimum wage after 10 years service”

</title><pros>Pros – yearly bonus scheme, after you have completed a number of years service you get a say in the hours you want to do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the pay is dredful for the amount of work you have to do.really busy and no praise or even a thankyou after a shift.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – please tell your managers to treat staff with respect,we are not rubbish.how do they pick their shining stars?should also include people with a clean absence record who are proven to be honest and reliable.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Warehouse (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Never work here...”

</title><pros>Pros – None, absolutely awful place to work. The only upside is how mind numbing it is. This is a plus if you are brain dead. However some employees are the salt of the earth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Useless employee's. In fighting between managers. Food hygiene standards were non existent. Management tried to use me as a bodyguard when they caught a drunk stealing alcohol.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Your doing everything bacward, treat your staff better and with more respect, hire some honest nice people rather than anyone that walks in off the street. Communicate better between each other.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Stock Control and Warehouse Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Making Life taste Better????”

</title><pros>Pros – The discount scheme is not the best in comparison with other retailers, but it is increased at holiday times and during the summer and you can get some excellent bargains amongst the sale items and the seasonal offers;As the store is open long hours it is possible to arrange hours around outside commitments such as child care and medical appointments which means that holiday s do not need to be used; there is a fairly generous holiday allowance given plus the bank holidays, you can opt to work the bank holidays and have an alternative day off providing it fits in with the needs of the business. some stores have a very good atmosphere and friendly staff</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are constant changes to processes and procedures that sometimes hard to implement and sell to the staff and just as everyone adjusts it changes. It would appear that some decisions are made by people at the top who have never worked in a store or it has not been trialled properly. Information is given out on a need to know basis with the idea that no one needs to know. communication has improved but it is still not good enough. The stores get the blame for most things and have to take the cost of any losses. The depots cause problems at times, but have improved greatly. System information is not available at store level that would help resolve problems and provide proof that deliveries are not accurate. Staff employed on night shift are a law unto themselves, are often not able to read english sufficiently to do a good job and this causes problems for day staff. If you have no family life then this is an ideal job as it can take over your life if you let it. Power hungry kingdom builders are often allowed to get away with their appalling behaviour</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value your good staff  - don't burn them  - or they will leave</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-12-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“1 000 000 Reasons to not join sainsburys in any way.”

</title><pros>Pros – There are not many good reasons for working in sainsburys apart from the fact that its easy to get a job in there even people like david beckham would get a job at the snap of two fingers. The other reason why it is kinda reasonable is because if you work on the deli you can eat as much as you want, your not suppose to, but what the hell who cares if sainsburys losed 50p evertime you eat a slice of ham. Oh and maybe one more thing everyone that you work with in their hates the whole management tier.</pros>
<cons>Cons – When you actually get given a discount card its 10%, oh wait that aint that good. Every manager is stuck up their own arse, except the normal department managers and sometimes even they act as though their god.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would advise managment to not talk to their employees like they are dogs and to get their head out of their arse otherwise one day they may have a brown face when they come up against someone that isnt going to let themselves be spoken down to.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type> Administrative - Price Controller  (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“favouritism leads the way”

</title><pros>Pros – If you get in with the right group you can work your way around the departments quite easily. Being on checkouts it is quite easy to avoid serving customers if you are pally with the supervisor, instead being put to do left behinds - walking around the store for however long you decide to take, or baskets/trolleys.Having an office job is another way of saying you're lazy. Most office workers spend a lot of time sat at their desk getting the bare minimum done and delegating to others on their department.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The managers seem incapable of encouraging the members of staff, HR treats staff with contempt. If you go to them too often with queries or complaints they will do very little to help you and during a recent reshuffle of hours they acted with favouritism when it came to being forced to do unfavourable hours over favourable ones. Career opportunities are unfairly given out with the same favoured few being tossed from department to department when they get bored of whichever role they are playing at this week.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The senior management need to actively try to motivate the people at store level who are the face of the company they are trying to change. They give us all these targets we should be meeting but instead of motivating us they are telling us it's the way things are. If they want the company to improve they have to have better delegation down the line</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Department Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sainsbury's no worse than any other retail group”

</title><pros>Pros – Good progression for career, company is more interested in your experience than what qualifications you have.  Always improving and wanting to succeed even more so through the bad times.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work life balance is very poor.  Work over your hours on a daily basis.  Shift times change on a weekly basis, sometimes daily, unable to plan anything outside of work, unless booking as holiday.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Remember that we can't do impossable.  We all want to succeed, but allow us to be able to interact with customers and colleagues, without feeling that we havn't got the time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Personnel Administration Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Variety great, pay disappointing”

</title><pros>Pros – The role had lots of variety and could involve anything from conducting disciplinary hearings with employees to stacking freezers on the shop floor.   All roles customer facing and if you enjoy working and dealing with people then this role is for you.  There is a lot of scope for "on the job training" as the approach is very much "get stuck in" so if you like a challenge and picking things up as you go along this role will suit you</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay was certainly on the low side and sometimes the hours can be unsociable as operations are 24 hours seven days a week.  The lack of career progression opportunties was certainly a drawback as was the support available for more formalised personal development and training</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Paying people slightly above minimum wage is no good for staff retention</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Counter Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“could do better in staff relations”

</title><pros>Pros – job security staff discount pension plan</pros>
<cons>Cons – the hours are sometimes insociable, but this is I suppose to be expected in a retail environment. customers are I find much ruder than they used to be, and I think this is partly because we pander to their every whim. Whilst I agree that sometimes the customer is right, not always so and this reflects in their attitude to the staff. A more positive attitude towards staff would result in a happier working atmosphere</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – to be more receptive and friendly towards staff and to realise that it is us who are dealing face to face with the public and thus providing THEM with their bonuses!! We are also human and a Good morning or acknowledgment would do wonders for morale, praise as well as criticism would go a long way to making it 'GREAT' again!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“sounds great but then reality bites!”

</title><pros>Pros – The concept of the values is great and the board seem to display these.</pros>
<cons>Cons – managersdo not live the values or behaviours</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – For the board to have 1 2 1 s with middle to lower management to understand how life really is.Not group discussions where colleaguesfear to speak.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-07-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Checkout Operator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for part time work, not so good for full time”

</title><pros>Pros – To meet new people and interact with customers. If you like knowing what goes on behind the scenes of companies, then Sainsburys is a good place to work. The staff discount is also a bonus and the feeling that you have helped customers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay isn't very enticing, and management can be awkward when trying to book time off.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The store manager needs to interact with employees more and give them praise for doing jobs well. He also needs to spend more time on the shop floor, taking part in jobs there, to see how the store is operating.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>