<name>ATCO I-Tek Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/ATCO-I-Tek-Reviews-E29890.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-02-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The team i worked with were great, I learned a lot from them.”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun collaborative environment. Nice office space.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not much room for advancement. Never received a bonus. Vacation weeks weren't negotiable.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More advancement opportunities and bonuses. Be more flexible on vacation weeks so that you include years of experience in industry outside of ATCO.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“To much favouritism.”

</title><pros>Pros – The company benefits were very good and the pay was above average for most customer service centres.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is very little advancement to no advancement at all. An employee would have to be "buddy buddy" with management to get anywhere in the company. I wouldn't advise anyone to work for this company</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start caring more about the employees and not about the contract with the client. Treat every employee equally.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people, Weak Leadership and Unhappy Clients.”

</title><pros>Pros – Staff for the most part is very skilled. Benefits are great. Good place to gain experience in Enterprise IT. Compensation is decent. Do not overwork employee's.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No opportunity for growth. Managers and Information Office staff are all business savvy but lack knowledge of *new IT industry. No quality assurance testing. No proven software development methods are used (within my team and a few others anyways). Great deal of clients are generally unhappy due to past experiences which lead to negative stigma for company and difficult interactions with clients.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in a QA staff! Clients might not want to pay for it, but the company and client will benefit in the long run. Get rid of the in house "anonymous" employee survey and point staff to a service like this for honest feedback.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Systems Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Been with them for a loong time”

</title><pros>Pros – For me, part time arrangement</pros>
<cons>Cons – Stuck in time, provincial, top heavy. Change of policies every couple of years with no follow through or assessment of the previous policy</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continuity, less PR, better straightfwd communication please</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Systems Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not bad, gained allot of experience, good place to learn about technology.”

</title><pros>Pros – Have good support systems in place, redundancy is well thought of, good for students comming out of school to learn about technology.  Salary is not the best but its not the worst.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes over worked, some people are just dead wood, pay scale is not the best but its not the worst either. Hard to move up in the company, allot of lifers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get rid of dead wood and reward your work horse.  Overall not a bad place to work at they have allot of really good people that need to be recognized or you could lose them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent benefits, limited opportunities for growth, below industry average pay scales”

</title><pros>Pros – People take pride in working at ATCO. Great benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Growth opportunities are limited. Salaries are below industry average.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-11-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to put your career on autopilot.”

</title><pros>Pros – Work life balance is excellent</pros>
<cons>Cons – Stagnant work environment, low upside potential</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Look at peer companies for process improvement and motivation.  Be competitive.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>