<name>CNBC TV18 Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/CNBC-TV18-Reviews-E303827.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Producer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Competitive and intellectually stimulating work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Fair managementGood growth potentialSmart people to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – StrenuousCan improve work life balance</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Video Editor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“As a video editor i am doing my best”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Work envorment in the organastion</pros>
<cons>Cons – i don,t feel like that</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – work envorment make flaxisible in office</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Art Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent Environment for career Growth”

</title><pros>Pros – I worked with TV 18 in the initial days. The environment was very conducive, lively with ample scope to grow in the organisation. There was freedom to learn new skills/ explore avenues in the organisation as long as your job was done as per expectations. Raghav Behl is a great visionary and a very encouraging Leader/Boss. Fondly remember my stint at TV18.</pros>
<cons>Cons – None as such. There were periods of uncertainty Job-wise in the growing phase, but I feel the same is a thing of the past as the Organisation has grown exponentially in all spheres</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Management Trainee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was great experience to work in challenging enviornment”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work opportunities you can prove yourself</pros>
<cons>Cons – lot of cometition because of that collegues are not helping</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – pemper employees more they will pay your more in returne</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Director”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Brand, strong programming and good talent</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much politics and favoritism</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Transparency and open communication needed</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Graphics Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work environment, Experienced professionals</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not enough facilities for employees compared to other media companies</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Producer, Features (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“working on the features team at CNBC-TV18”

</title><pros>Pros – Exposure to some of the best names in the industry</pros>
<cons>Cons – no real disadvantages as such</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Editor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The best newsroom in India is at CNBC-TV18”

</title><pros>Pros – Peer to Peer relationships are healthy and competitive. Superiors are very easy to apraoch and the HR department of CNBC-TV18 is absolutely the most employee friendly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you are a laid back, easy going person then it may not be the place for you as the energy levels of the whole place are very high. You would be expected to deliver like the rest.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Producer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Associate Producer”

</title><pros>Pros – Majorly expanding media organisation, Good learning ground, Best in business coverage, Associated with a global brand and a big brand in itself,</pros>
<cons>Cons – Believes in cheap labour, Had a mass laying off in 2009, Extremely face ( personality ) driven organisation, Fifedom of seniors who've started their career here, Overtly concious of competition , Too technical and can restrict creative skills</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Must get over the emotional trauma over its former employees leaving and going to the competition. It does not let focus on other issues such as growth of those who want to be loyal to you</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Learning”

</title><pros>Pros – Respect at workplaceInvolvement in decision making neutral of hierarchy</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work Life BalanceEmotional place to work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work and the 'spirit of start-up' without compromising on the professional set up</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Correspondent (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“High pressure, high rewards Russian Roulette”

</title><pros>Pros – As a culture, CNBC TV18's managers just ask their sub ordinates to get the job done. There is absolutely no interference thereafter in how you execute the task on hand. Flexible working hours on the condition that the job gets done within the deadline. A high degree of freedom to branch out and do different work but only on the condition that your current responsibilities are fulfilled.</pros>
<cons>Cons – An extremely insecure and competitive environment ensures one is constantly on their toes and watches their back. Zero work life balance. You are given a short period of time to prove yourself and sidelined if you falter later. High pressure has lead to an average 3 year burn out period.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Use a more metric and data driven approach to rewarding employees than the current word-of-mouth method used by managers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>