<name>J. Mclaughlin Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/J-Mclaughlin-Reviews-E304445.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Preppy heaven”

</title><pros>Pros – Clothing quota and  flexible hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – Absentee upper management made it easy for a dishonest store manager, not located in NYC, to keep limited hours or not show up. Sales associates gets little or no respect from upper management. I've heard they now have a sign in timeclock on the computer, hopefully, this helped the situation. I would imagine its still easy for a manager to give sales person her code to sign them in.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep better tabs on your store managers. Respect your sales people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Womens Merchandising (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Disorganized, unprofessional and dirty office”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent environment to work in when I was there however I heard that changed. Summer Fridays</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very disorganized,  the people that work there are not friendly. Bad pay, terrible benefits. The toilets weren’t working for an entire day there and they still had us come into work and had buckets of water by the toilet to flush it… was pretty gross. There was also a rat problem in the office. When we would come into work we have to wipe our desks down to get the rat droppings off of it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get better managers that don't have open affairs in the office. Clean the place up and treat your employees better.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Another Retail Job”

</title><pros>Pros – You earn a decent amount of free clothing each month</pros>
<cons>Cons – hours and pay is minimal</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – open stores later in major cities and start employees with at least 10/hr</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Merchandising (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience but a disorganized company”

</title><pros>Pros – Wonderful atmosphere, very aesthetically pleasing environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – A long commute for most people (Green Point, Brooklyn) and rather disorganized as a whole</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work load is too distributed could work with other departments more and create a stronger base</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great team”

</title><pros>Pros – great team of people, great work hours, great management, great opportunities, great place to start a career, and great opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – slow career progression and not too ideal location</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – you are doing great!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sales Associate”

</title><pros>Pros – the clothing quota. Hours are usually regular- expect to work a 7.5 hour day. They are stingy on o/t, but the pay isn't too bad. Expect to start at $12-$15 an hour depending on experience, need, and store location.</pros>
<cons>Cons – So much of it comes down to the manager you have and your store location. If you're in a city store- be prepared to work long/busy days with other employees, if you're in a suburban area- you'll be busy in waves, however the best J.Mac's to work are in the rural locations. Slow pace, easy going, often work by yourself.Mostly female employees throughout the company, i've out lasted two managers- both have had their pro's & con's. Be prepared to work MOST HOLIDAYS.... half the time its worthless if your store has a history of having $0 days on those particular holidays- they no longer care. corporate is cracking down on any say individual stores used to have.Poor if any health insurance. Almost no opportunity to work your way up.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – With their new investor buyout- they are currently undergoing a huge changes in their corporate structure. They are still quite patronizing, but now are micromanaging daily store operations more then ever.  To store managers- be please easy going, respectful, kind, patient, NICE, and approachable.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“J. McLaughlin Doesn't Care About It's Store Managers”

</title><pros>Pros – Job description and running events are nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Where do I begin:1. Terrible internal communication. Expect to be told to do something by 3 different people, 3 different ways. LOL!2. Horrible benefits. I couldn't afford their benefits. I had to buy insurance outside of the company. This certianly is hard on me and my family.Only 1 week vacation...even for tenured Managers- non-negotiable!       Expect to work all holidays, even if other  stores around you are closed.3. Managers are treated poorly, certainly not respected.4. You have no voice and they patronize instead of coaching.5. If you have experience you report to management that has a lot less experience, and who aren't business savy. Example: your store must be open on holidays even if you have sold $0 past years AND your the only store open in the neighborhood.6. Expect to be open on religious holidays....Easter.  I still can't believe it, even as I'm typing it.7. Sales goals are unrealistic.8. Hard to make goal when you receive 1 dress in 1 size. Ordering doesn't make sense.Easy to see how at the end of the day, you won't like the company. Too bad!  If they would have invested in their employees they could have achieved so much more.It's my opinion the J. McLaughlin brothers beleive that the majority of women working for them don't need benefits, they'll get it from their spouses.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 1.You would be more successful if you cared for your Store Managers i.e. benefits and time-off2. Improve communication.3. Stop patronizing</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Management review”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a positive store environment. Lots of downtime to get tasks accomplished. You can develop a relationship with other stores to get the product needed for your clients.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No structure, poor communication with corporate. They have very little concern for the balance between life and work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Great company, but very hard to get your voice heard. I really have a passion for fashion and clothes. I also enjoy a handbook and structure, which this company has neither.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>