<name>Richard J Bagan Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Richard-J-Bagan-Reviews-E305430.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-02-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Lab Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great working conditions, great working relationships”

</title><pros>Pros – Clean, comfortable environment. Top of the line instruments. Strong work ethics!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lot of eggs in Plastics industry.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Calibration Technician (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bagan, a small company with growing pains.”

</title><pros>Pros – Richard J. Bagan Company started with electronics calibration and repair, also building specialty cables used in the robotics industry. In recent years, they have added a mechanical lab, a new electronics lab, a temperature lab, and RF lab. Each lab has its own room, most recently Bagan has started on a lab specifically for the rubber industry.  Employees work in the labs and also at customer facilities. The company is A2LA accredited. At the back of the building is another company (PT Measure) that is operated by Jeff Gust, Bagan's Vice President of Metrology Services. The building and the labs are kept up to date, clean and brightly lit. Their sales department is very aggressive and continues to find new clients.</pros>
<cons>Cons – All new hires are required to sign an "employment contract" translated this means "non compete". If the employee leaves, is laid off, or fired the employee cannot work for any company that is in competition with Bagan or that is a Bagan customer, within a one hundred and fifty mile radius of the Bagan Company for a period of two years after leaving the company. To my knowledge, employees either quit or are fired. In my time with the company, only one person ever retired. The president appears to surround himself with people who completely agree with his ideas and decisions, in some instances this has been to his detriment.  Although Bagan Company has continued to find new clients, the company continues to increase prices. This has been a cause of a lot of customer complaints and the loss of some customers to Bagan competitors. There have also been losses because of long turnaround times.  This has translated into a lot of extra pressure, by the supervisors on the calibration technicians to get the jobs done quickly. In turn, getting the jobs done as quickly as possible has led to increased mistakes by the technicians. Working as an employee of the Bagan Company means working under constant pressure. The various requirements of what  customers want on their gage certifications are not made clear to the lab techs and this can cause mistakes and extra time rewriting the certification.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Customer requirements should be clear and concise, in one clearly defined section. When the Technician is expected to begin a calibration, the gage work sheets should be attached to the customer gage, in the computer, and also the procedure for that gage. Too many times the technician must remind their supervisor that they need a worksheet and procedure before they can begin. Gages that require uncertainty's should have them added in a timely manner, not after six months or a year later, which has happened in a number of cases. Management should employ supervisors  that are knowledgeable technicians themselves, and be able to train or give advice to junior technicians. Hiring from within the company would be a good start. The company should not, on a yearly basis, promise year end bonuses, and then not deliver. Calibration standards should always be given the highest priority.  When a Standard is out of calibration, the technician cannot  use it to calibrate customer gages, and then time is lost waiting for the standard to be calibrated.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>