<name>Paulette F. Balin & Associates Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Paulette-F-Balin-and-Associates-Reviews-E307836.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst, most dysfunctional firm in America.”

</title><pros>Pros – If you are starving and cannot get a job anywhere else, consider applying here. Keep looking though, because you WILL find better.</pros>
<cons>Cons – All problems flow from the firm owner. She is irrational in her decision making. She uses verbal and mental abuse to keep her staff in line. She micromanages EVERYTHING. She frequently complains about having no money for raises, but has plenty of money to hire family members and to take European vacations. Meanwhile she gives you 5 vacation days per year, PERIOD. Ever. She encourages employees to spy on one another and actively promotes drama.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take a class on leadership and management. HAPPY employees are productive employees. By talking down to everyone, micromanaging every decision, offering practically no vacation time and no raises, you will continue to employ a staff that loathes you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Case Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a good starting point.”

</title><pros>Pros – Probably best if you are looking to go into social work or Social Security Disability law as a career. You can say you worked at a law firm. You will be reviewing medical records most of the time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor compensation, stressful and unpleasant work environment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Reduce the amount of stress, it brings out the worst in people and makes it hard to focus on work. Probably will want to pay people more if you want professionalism from them and a cheerful attitude around the office. Senior case managers may have more time to train/coach their assistants if there was more focus on weeding out the bad cases at the intake level..</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>