<name>Ben E. Keith Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Ben-E-Keith-Reviews-E3088.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-02-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Driver (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great job”

</title><pros>Pros – Good pay and good benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – Its a lot of hard work</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Driver (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“not a good job”

</title><pros>Pros – good money if you kiss ass</pros>
<cons>Cons – if you don't do what they want you to do they will try to get you out there by drop all your hour down</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible!”

</title><pros>Pros – Fort Worth branch was wonderful......................best company I ever worked for and loved every minute.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Transferred to Houston Branch and was let go for no REASON other than my CM wanted a friend of his to have my position so he set it up to look like I was not doing my job................very POOR Management in Houston Branch!  I was cheated out of my job of 12+yrs and devastated!  Everyone in Ft. Worth knew me and that I was an awesome employee!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Look into this and get my job back...............................please!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hard work and pay less”

</title><pros>Pros – Nothing to share. Bad environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very stingy on salary. If you take day off or you ill.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – To be fair for salary, see low level have hard work but less pay than other!!! Some always play game on the phone. Pay attention on Accounting and sale department</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Territory Sales Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Ol Boy Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Family Owned, Texas Based Company, with a certain amount of freedom to develop your own territory and customer base. They have a vast selection of products to offer. Competitive pay and great benefits. Quality produce.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They are stuck in the shadow of Sysco. You will work 7 days a week and many nights. A CRONIC Lack of support from transportation and routing. The pricing on several key segments centered on Tex Mex and similar restaurant models makes it impossible to stay competitive on rice, beans, and cheese. If you are on the "good Side" of management. Then the goals set by management are far more attainable and you will be handed a lot of existing clients and leads.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give merit to what a DSR does in the field. Base the goals on the actual work they are doing. Not the personal relationship that you have with that individual. Adding a 100% sales increase for 3 straight months just so you can document an unsatisfactory job... Uncool.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review”

</title><pros>Pros – Good company to work for with solid core competencies. This company provides you with tools to suceed and grow your business.</pros>
<cons>Cons – From a sales perspective, the market is saturated with sales reps. Thus, you have to be willing to spread your territory out to really take advantage of growing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Order Selector (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Order selector”

</title><pros>Pros – mad money mad money mad money</pros>
<cons>Cons – alot of physical work yo</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – keep paing mad money</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Driver (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good training and exprience to move on to a better job.”

</title><pros>Pros – Stepping stone to get to where you wana go.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company still uses ramps to make deliveries</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Company need to upgrade to lift gates</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unless you are one of the top reps, you are forgotten and all on your own.”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a family atmosphere with many employees that have been with the company for 10+, 20+, and quite of few with 30+ years with the company. You don't see that much anymore.</pros>
<cons>Cons – On the sales side there is a lack of management. It starts with the President of Sales and goes all the way to the Sales Managers. They teach their managers to merely crunch numbers and deliver messages from up top.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat people other the top sellers as people. I don't understand how and why a company that preaches about family can distant themselves from new people and unexperienced sales reps.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience learning the beer distribution busines”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of good beer brands!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company relies heavily on uneducated work force.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increase beer knowledge among sales staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Surprised at the company it's becomming.”

</title><pros>Pros – The close group of people working together. The company at management level office recognition. The company parcipiates in community activities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I feel the company is losing sight of the voice of the people. Loyalty pay scale. Upword mobility in all locations.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I believe the company needs a new training program. The company has lost sight of the value of an experienced employee and  has begun replacing experience with newly educated simply because they can pay less salary dollars.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-08-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>District Sales Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sales Rep for Ben E Keith Foods”

</title><pros>Pros – Very laid back atmosphere, with lots of opportunity!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Transportation and Credit department issues!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Transportation and more specific Routing needs to coordinate better with sales reps.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hard”

</title><pros>Pros – Great pay, used to be great employee incentives but those seem to have gone along with budget cuts. Higher management knows employees by name.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours, lots of stress, people not recieving praise for work well done, in fact if you are a good sales man you seem to be pushed even harder instead of getting recognition for doing a great job in the first place to make up for the slackers who can't work hard. Long weekend work especially during special events. Not enough people to do the work, but if there are more people then less opportunity to win incentives. Work/home balance isnt great when you are on your route until 6 or 7 at night and working weekends.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do more to let employees know they are appreciated. Hours are long and hard, provide us with the tools we need to get the work done more efficiently. Provide training tools to help us advance. Not much room to move anywhere once you reach an area manager job because there are so few higher positions. Expecting the same number of employees to do 3x the work. The company business is growing, the number of people doing the work is not.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Route Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Young mans game”

</title><pros>Pros – Great pay out of gate. Late model trucks. 2 weeks vacation after 1year of service.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Demanding physically. Sleep is a luxury. Pay raises not passed on performance, but merely jut being a warm body with an employee id number. Management doesn't get the big picture and relays messages about certain issues to the wrong body of employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get with the times and update the equipment. Company still uses prehistoric ramps to move product off of trailer. Liftgates would be an all round help, yes they cost $$$$$ but they would save time and $$$$( employee injuries)Evaluate your employees for pay increases. The method of handing out raises to everyone for "just being there" is a waste of money. Take care of the ones taking care of you. Keep track of when an employee is due for a raise.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Driver (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“As a route driver decent job, but your body and your metal health cannot handle more than 5 years on average, no career.”

</title><pros>Pros – World class full body workout daily on the route, meet people and interact with them daily. 95% unsupervised work environment, most weekends off and some holidays. Paid Weekly. Benefits are unreal in the industry but do have to put in about 3 years to really start to see them.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Extremely early work schedule and longs days, 10-12 hours minimum. Pay is not hourly. Not a job for those with a family. Very hard on the body.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Could show a lot more face time to the little branches. Our satellite office is 4 hour from the division warehouse and have seen my big boss only 1 once in 18 months. Little things could be better property that is much better maintained. Better bonus. Stop spending dollars to save pennies and pay the little people more, they make you!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I've had a great time at this company,”

</title><pros>Pros – they really care about there employees, the pay is good, the benifits are good. they have functions for your family, upper management knows you by name and always talks to you and ask how your doing.they also have employee apprecation lunchs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the only down side is that we work alot of hours, exspecially if you work in the warehouse.but management gets out and helps so that's a plus.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – your doing a good job.on site child care would be great, and maybe an employee gym.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“They don't care about the sales rep.”

</title><pros>Pros – No terrtitory restrictions on your area.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They feel the rep is an inconvenience and care mostly about making money on the buy from the suppliers and not the on the sales end with the reps.  Pads are very high and the credit department is entirely and outrageously strict on terms with customers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Trust your reps more.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Desktop Support Specialist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ben E Keith”

</title><pros>Pros – Paid retirement but not very much is paid.  Lay ed back atmosphere.  Good people to work with.  Benefits of employee purchasing.  Profit sharing, once again not very much unless your a manager.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bad health insurance.  Managers do not care about employees.  Employees do all of the work while managers do nothing.  Sick days are a joke.  You can not use a sick day until you are out for 3 days.  Then you can use a sick day but you only receive 75% of your daily earnings.  If there are no company cars available to visit customers with.  Then you do not want to use your own vehicle.  You will only receive .15 cents a mile or they will pay for your gas.  Which ever one you want to pick but not both.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You call yourself a great company.  Prove it to your non management employees.  They do all the work for the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-10-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Support Specialist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“0”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a good company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – they have perfected their employee retention program.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The company is run well in it's key area. The company should effort improving their non-key areas as well.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>