<name>Big Y Foods Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Big-Y-Foods-Reviews-E3093.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent employee demographics, great people, and professional”

</title><pros>Pros – Writing this because I feel mostly only those with negative reviews post their views.  I just started working at Big Y.  I feel management has been MORE than friendly, More than generous and flexible.  My particular store has a fabulous mix of both mature adults and kids.  A very nice mix.  So far, I'm quite happy with my decision to work for this company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A fridge in the break room would be helpful, but other than that, things look great.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – ESR & management at Wilbraham is great.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You have do more than 1 job but get paid for only 1 job”

</title><pros>Pros – Very good in offering paid benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – Expected more than required of its workers. Jobs could not be completed in time allowed</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wasn't completely terrible.”

</title><pros>Pros – - A lot of amazing co-workers.- I liked all of the managers except the CSM.- 30 cent raise every 6 months if you perform well.- Easy job.- Good first job.- Scott Gardiner was a great Store Manager.- Easily make friends, 95% of the cashiers are friendly and welcoming to new employees.- The more you're available, the more hours you get.- They do give pretty good hours for part-time.- They ask you to stay late a lot (you don't have to) and if you want to then more $ for you.- Time and a half on Sundays.- They ask you to go home early sometimes (the best) (but you don't have to).- This isn't a pro but if you work there MAKE SURE you always look in the customers cart for packs of water/things at the bottom.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Everyone there is either dating or related LOL.- EVERY manager picks favorites.- Customers nickel and dime everything.- Customers watch you bag $400 worth of stuff and don't even help.- If you're a service clerk, the bottle room is hell.- Scan-It-Alls.- So cheap about bags.- They expect you to ring super fast, but if you miss items you get in trouble. (and if you miss things often you get taken off of the register.)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get rid of RUDE Customer Service Managers. The one at my store was so mean to all employees and was always in a bad mood. I heard complaints about her from customers almost everyday. I don't know how the hell she got hired. Also the 8-12 items per bag thing, ARE YOU SERIOUS? Most of the customers are 55+ in age.. They don't like heavy bags !!!! No one likes heavy bags.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tiresome.”

</title><pros>Pros – The pay is steady, and it's work you don't need to think to terribly hard about. The people tend to be pleasant, so long as you treat them kindly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay is terrible, the benefits are nonexistant, the anti-union bias is so strong, you risk your job by even thinking the dreaded u-word. Management never gets attached to any person because they're constantly being shuffled around from store to store. The amount of petty, personal politics and power-games being played at any given store are not only constant, but neverending and frustrating. Gossip culture runs rampant, the turnover rate on cashiers means that you constantly have people who barely know how the register works working up there.Use this job as a way to make money while searching for a better job digging ditches or banging your head against the wall.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take the entire management structure out of the chain and start over. The advertising executives don't know how to do their job, the store-focused managers haven't spent any time working in a store in the past ten years. That last point is extremely obvious what with all the little "productivity improvements" that are put into place and do nothing more than increase workload while doing nothing that is actually productive or relevant.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Seafood Clerk (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent”

</title><pros>Pros – Structure, professionalism, cleanliness of the store. Good location, so there is a lot of business</pros>
<cons>Cons – poor accountability processes as far as I could tell. Double standard for some employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Damned if you do, damned if you don't.”

</title><pros>Pros – - Good time off if requested in time- Good co-workers- Always something to eat on a break- Free Silver Card with Employment</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Overall morale of management at times is low- ALOT of favoritism, the better you suck up, the more hours you get- Gossip with everyone in your department- No modified dress code for summer, yes in 90 degree weather, you wear long pants and long sleeves- Managers have very high demands, so you work later than your scheduled shift (if closing), and they complain because you were there too long, but if you leave on time, they always complain things weren't completed. Management at times is never happy.- Want to move up or get cross-trained? Your ESR does nothing but ask "How are you?" .. all the time, and never follows up on everything.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make it so that I don't want to walk out the door and never come back; pay is good, but the morale sucks. Already looking for another job, I lost faith in my department manager, but not so much our store director.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Like high school all over again”

</title><pros>Pros – Unbelievably flexible vacation and time-off policies- Solid pay for a first job- Room for advancement (to a point)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Incompetent managers- High school-like atmosphere at store level - more gossip than a tabloid, cliques everywhere you look, and any new hires who don't fit in immediately can expect to be treated unfairly- Favoritism runs rampant - raises, promotions and bonuses seem to go more often toward the managers' friends rather than those who perform best- Ridiculous uniforms for store-level employees in messy jobs - dress shoes, slacks, pressed white dress shirt and tie. I don't know who came up with that policy, but have THEY ever tried pushing carriages with dress shoes on? It's a grocery store, not a law firm!- No uniform allowance, even though a uniform like this could run you close to $100.- HR reps seem more symbolic than functional at times - senior management often has them under their thumbs</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Just because an employee is different than you doesn't mean you can treat them like dirt, especially if said employee has special needs. Treat ALL your employees the same, and reward their achievements just as you would for your favorites. Just because you're miserable being stuck working in retail for the rest of your life doesn't give you the right to drag others down with you. It takes a very low form of human being to pick on those who can't defend themselves.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Deli Sales Clerk (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great first job!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great flexibility for hours, and plenty of room for advancement. The variety provided allows for constant progress and excitement for those who seek it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Benefits are NOT extended to minors, even those working within the part time hour boundaries, and full time positions are hard to secure even for award winning employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Seafood Clerk (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great benefits but not a great company”

</title><pros>Pros – - Benefits are great, even at part time they give you paid vacation and paid medical ins- There are some really great people to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Management is often switched around so its not fun to have to change routines, but not a huge deal.- Some of the management can be impossible to work with.- Its like any other company, where the managers don't work smart and expect the underdog to work more than they should have to.- I see many other managers doing nothing like for long periods of time even when the departments get busy they let customers wait while they just watch. Then they yell at the workers for not getting to them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work! While I know you have management tasks to do and I'm sure you do them but don't just watch your workers get hit with customers and do nothing. You will lose those customers if they have to stand around and wait.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great”

</title><pros>Pros – very nice people always bases on my schedule</pros>
<cons>Cons – everyone is so nice and you get time and a hald on sundays</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Place to Work”

</title><pros>Pros – Not a bad place to work.  The people are nice for the most part and the work is easy.  They let you go on leave for things like school so it's great for college students.</pros>
<cons>Cons – People can get a little wierd about their groceries... to put it nicely.  If you're a guy you'll have to do stuff like empty the bottle machines and push carts in nasty weather.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier/Service Clerk (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working at Big Y is fine”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are very friendly</pros>
<cons>Cons – I dont have any cons.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They can be rude sometimes</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Fresh Foods Clerk (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Okay but unfair”

</title><pros>Pros – decent pay, flexible hours, interesting work, some cool co-workers</pros>
<cons>Cons – The management is terrible.  After working for the company for four and a half years and being one of the top employees in my store I was targeted because the store manager didn't like me. I had a huge target on my back and couldn't even transfer stores because they just wanted me gone, so I had no other option but to quit or to continue being treated in this manner. The ESR's are not on the employees side either making matters worse. I've never been in a job where the management acted like high school bullies before, they are just horrible! Also you will never get a promotion unless you suck up, your work ethic hardly matters.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop all the high school gossip and cliques! I was with the company for so long that I saw in three different locations I worked in how the management communicated with each other and would run people out just because of personal opinions and not because of the work an individual did!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Service Clerk (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An okay place so far.”

</title><pros>Pros – *Some Nice people to work with at the front end as well as customers if you know them.*Pay is good*Fast-paced environment means they're a lot to do in departments.</pros>
<cons>Cons – *Management can get a little unethical and, at times, incompetent*Exempt from benefits if certain requirements aren't met regardless of how long you were employed*Employees and some managers can initially seem closed-minded and rude towards those they are unfamiliar with. Managers can also get a bit sour if an employee gives simple criticism.*Rude customers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Drop the favoritism and treat all employees equally, that'll create a more comfortable environment for everyone. Also, constructive criticism from both employees and customers alike is intended to help both you and the store's integrity, and not belittle you as an manager.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Clerk (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not horrible, but room for lots if improvement”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits for full-time employeesFlexible scheduling for studentsClean stores</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nepotism, cliques and favoritismLow pay for certain jobs AND certain peopleKey personnel transferred without explanation or noticeMandatory weekends and holidays (no family time)Advancement is extremely political</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Encourage fairness and equity. Observe first hand rather than continually surveying staff and customers. Staff fears recriminations so they aren't honest. Customers usually only participate when dissatisfied or a reward is offered. Truly appreciate staff, not because it's on the calendar to do so. Most of the corporate employees have only worked at this company so very little changes. New or different is ignored or patronizingly acknowledged then dismissed.  Let new ideas in for real.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“unfair un pleasent aweful and terrible”

</title><pros>Pros – free silver saving card and good people</pros>
<cons>Cons – cant be in contests and the pay is terriblde</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – be more fair</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Dairy Clerk (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's been a learning experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – Steady hours with decent pay</pros>
<cons>Cons – the long night shift hours</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Bakery Clerk (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great for a college student, or temporary/”

</title><pros>Pros – The pay isnt too bad to start.. most of the people are easy to work with, and there isnt a union, which is great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's hard to see Big Y as a career when you've been there 6 or more years and you're making the same amount per hour as a cart pusher who was hired last week. It's difficult to advance in Big Y because you're not allowed to unless your direct manager, and the store director OK it. So if they aren't huge fans of yours, you're a janitor for life. This company is going downhill fast when it comes to who is managing it. They seem way less picky. And they don't care if their managers follow policy. There's too many exceptions to rules for the special ones, and they are losing alot of money because of it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You need to keep a better eye on who you leave in charge. They set bad examples, they disobey important rules and policies, and then you wonder why you're losing business. Meriden Big Y is slow because the customers don't WANT to come back to a store full of new employees who are uneducated on their products, and what Big Y stands for as a whole! Stop thinking of ways to cut costs and quality and invest time and money into EDUCATING your employees. They are your future!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Deli Sales Clerk (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“fun and a great learning experience”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are great to work with. The customers are great and after they keep coming back you know their order cause it never changes</pros>
<cons>Cons – I cant say much but some co workers are hard to work with because they want to be the boss knowing that they're not and want things done a certain way.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Terrible”

</title><pros>Pros – -Work for high school and college students.-Flexible hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Managers are disrespectful, unprofessionalism because of too much gossip.-Most of managers highest education are high school degrees.-Favoritism, cliques.-Managers are never usually in the departments unless they want to kiss up to district managers.-No opportunities to grow.-Dress code for pizza department is ridiculous especially when you're working with tomato sauce.-No seniority.-</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please review your managers. Focus on the big picture. Part timers help run the show. Without happy part timers there are no happy customers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good”

</title><pros>Pros – flexible for a young adult</pros>
<cons>Cons – Get rid of paper, drives up cost</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Help</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Front End Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This is a great job, not a great career.”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent benefitsFlexible scheduling, time off whenever you need itOpen to new ideas, and constantly implementing more efficient proceduresFree membership in the Silver Savings Club, along with employee discounts</pros>
<cons>Cons – Education does not guarantee success here.Constant evolution of procedures often results in back-tracking.It is clear that those "in charge" have not worked on store level for quite some time, especially when  they "script" certain customer interactions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please respect the education level of your employees, know and appreciate all of their resources, as they are yours as well. You do a great job at creating a community culture on both a store level and company-wide, take this into consideration when promoting from within.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-31</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Never felt so disrespected.”

</title><pros>Pros – They're great about requesting time off. If you request a day off, no matter what time of year, it will be approved. They do encourage and help you to cross train if you aren't happy in your department.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is so disrespectful towards employees, particularly on the front end. If an honest mistake is made, you'll never stop hearing about it. Nothing is ever said to your face, but you always hear about slander going on behind your back. The place is like a high school, cliques and drama and all. The pay is terrible. Managers play favorites. Not just department managers, store managers as well. I wouldn't recommend working here to anyone.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management needs to get to know employees better. Give hard-working employees a shot at advancement, even if they aren't one of the "favorites."</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Family Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Fair pay, good benefits, nice people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Difficult future asa medium size supermarket</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Too many people in charge.  need one voice</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An OK place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – There are many company activities and it is a fairly social place to work. The company picnic is held at Six Flags New England, and there are company trips every so often. Each month, they have birthday cakes in the break room to recognize all of the birthdays in that month. Every employee is sent both a Christmas card and a birthday card. There is a decent amount of available recognition for achievements, such as "world class performance" slips, which managers and supervisors can hand out, although they lose some of their meaning when they are overused. They are an active participant in community events.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low-level management lacks competence. The dress code for non-management employees is a bit much. Management focuses more on unimportant issues than on the big picture. Related to the dress code, I've seen cashiers, whose feet cannot be seen while they are working, be sent home for incorrectly colored shoes. The stores become like a clique. Don't expect it will be easy to get promotions without being in the in-crowd. Full-time employees are transferred to distant store locations unnecessarily, with very little notice. Don't expect to be able to keep a short commute to work, or keep the same co-workers, if you are full time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't transfer full-timers as much, and get upper/mid-level management to have some respect for workers and lower level management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-02-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – It may not be the highest paying job in terms of salary, but the benefits are GREAT. If you work in the support center, there is a health club and a very nice cafeteria.  There is tuition reimbursement.. They really try to recognize the employees w/ employee of the month in each location.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It seems as though it doesn't matter how well you perform (or don't!) through out the year, you always get the standard 4% pay raise! It is still a reletively small company in terms of career advancement.  They retain their employees so it makes it difficult to advance if you want to change positions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-11-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Job for a Young Person”

</title><pros>Pros – great location, reasonable hours, convenient</pros>
<cons>Cons – Tiresome, repetitive work, not for those who need mental stimulation, co-workers not so bright</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None, as a whole they do really well but can be a bit self involved</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Phenomenal work experience for a 16-year old with no prior working experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – - Working casual while in high school, a maximum shift consists of 6 hours- Time and a half pay every Sunday- Automatic discount items (silver coupon for every item)</pros>
<cons>Cons – - There really are no downsides to working at Big Y.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ehh its ok to work there”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible schedual, Starting wage higher then minimum wage</pros>
<cons>Cons – Difficult customers, not a lot of hours</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent part time job”

</title><pros>Pros – Good pay for what it is and they are very flexible with your availability for the most part. Good people work there</pros>
<cons>Cons – Managers don't really care about you, you are very replaceable. The employee discount is essentially non existent. Can be expected to do a lot with little help</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier/Service Clerk (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Big Y”

</title><pros>Pros – There are really no pros to working at Big Y, besides the fact that is a good job and stable as long as you are available to work. Will accept most time off requests</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hours tend to be all over the place and often not in your availabilityIf you request 30 hours a week you usually end up with 18 and if you ask for 18 hours a week you get 30.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more open to employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good pay, must be in good terms with superiors to get hours”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay on SundaysInteraction between EmployeesFriendly AtmosphereDress Code promotes professionalismRelatively easy job</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some employees get away with more than othersMust be in good favor with whoever is doing the scheduling</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“discouraging”

</title><pros>Pros – employee discountflexible schedules for students</pros>
<cons>Cons – you will never go anywhere in this company, unless you are part of the "incrowd or related to a manager" when i was hired 3 years i was promised all kinds of growth, i am trained in many areas of the store, but i keep seeing relatives of mangers being promoted or worse someone from outside you train, most jobs not posted for current employees to even apply and next thing you know someone from off the street is in, because of who they know. UNFAIR</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take care of your current employees, they are what make your company successful. there is alot great people that work for your company</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Front End (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hit or Miss”

</title><pros>Pros – If you are lucky, the people you work with can be great, very flexible schedule when it comes to availability and going to school, great first job for high school students.</pros>
<cons>Cons – FAVORITISM, if you don't get in with the "in crowd" you might as well quit, promotions are only given to those that the csm's like and shifts are only awarded to the ones that are considered there fellow clique. It's very difficult to achieve much from working there besides a head ache from the lack of knowledge from certain csm's and the different approaches everyone wants to take to handle situations. It's as though everyone wants to impress and prove themselves, but there is no one to impress because the management is too busy hiding in their offices or making you feel dumb for asking them a question. Very rarely are there compliments given out to the employees and there is a lack of cooperation when it comes to the different departments that make up Big Y. When new employees are hired they always seem to hire students instead of hiring those who actually need the jobs. When school comes around they find themselves understaffed "shooting themselves in the foot." Overall i would only recommend this job for students going through school or those that just want a hobby.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would highly recommend that the managers and different departments get on the same page as far as what it takes to run this company. Also the favoritism needs to end so that those who are working hard can get the compliments and promotions they deserve. Scheduling could be worked on as well.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Full Time (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I wish I never started working here”

</title><pros>Pros – employee discounts on foodvery sociable atmosphereno time clock to punch in or out-honor systemlet leave work early alot of times and you still get paid for the full 8 hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – Downsizing-hundreds got laid off;less help and more work for allManagers hide in their offices all day on a computerManagers  look down on employeesvery low once a year raise</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Review your managers  and just because they been there along time doesn't mean they are good at what they do</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Deli (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Meh”

</title><pros>Pros – Ok hours, decent pay raise</pros>
<cons>Cons – The dress code is freakin unnecessary. Why is a tie, black dress pants, or black dress shoes crucial when honestly the customer won't care about any of those things just as long as they get their order?</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try not to be such nazis with the dress code. Why should I wear a tie when 2/3 of it is covered by an apron?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Service Clerk (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“decent”

</title><pros>Pros – good first job, get treated very well. would recommend for anyone looking to get in the door at a good local company</pros>
<cons>Cons – lousy pay raises if you have to actually make a living. not a whole lot of cons to tell ya the truth</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Better raises, maybe not as much looking down on the front end employees and their competence as employees. not much to say tho.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a bad place to work....”

</title><pros>Pros – They will cross train, and they do have benefits for both part and full timers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Rotating schedules constantly and very reluctant to upgrade to full time, good for high school or college students.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Show appreciation for hard work and be clear on what is wanted/required.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good job”

</title><pros>Pros – benefits, non-union, co-workers, and employee perks</pros>
<cons>Cons – the salaries and some of the customers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – higher salaries</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier/Service Clerk (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Okay for a grocery store, I guess”

</title><pros>Pros – -Management is hit or miss. There were some really great managers and some terrible ones.-Silver coin employee discount.-They allow and encourage you to change departments if you're unsatisfied.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -No choice between cashier and service clerk. If you're at this level, you're both.-Some terrible management.-Mindless work.-Not enough promotion opportunities, even for the best cashiers. Seems like promotions are based heavily on favoritism.-Have to sell random items at checkout.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Cashiers asking customers if they'd like to buy a tub of sprinkles at checkout is annoying for both parties. Either increase the quality of the items pushed at checkout or do away with the program. Do a better job of recognizing talent and rewarding it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-08-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decentn”

</title><pros>Pros – You get to dress up and they handle customers with respoect</pros>
<cons>Cons – Overwork and nitpick the front end staff</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat employees better expsically cashiers they maek your buisness</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>