<name>Nfrastructure Technologies Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Nfrastructure-Technologies-Reviews-E311606.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-09-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a bad place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – There are some really great, smart people at nfrastructure.  Jobs can be challenging and fun if you like IT.  They try to work with their project management team to create an educational atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It can take a long time to get internal projects done, because people tend to be set in their way's.  This tend's to stifle innovation.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Clueless Management; Inbred Employees”

</title><pros>Pros – They direct deposit a paycheck every week.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Started small and keeps growing. However, the older employees have no idea how to grow with the company, and are hostile to new employees.  There is an incredible lack of communication and uncaring attitude from mid-Managers who are neither able to delegate nor handle the ever-increasing workload.  As they're hostile, there's an undercurrent of hoping for failure by new employees.There are lots of cliques that are impossible to enter.While there's a lot of drum beating about "working together' it's just the same old corporate line, except here it's more hypocritical with meaningless cruises on Lake George.  That's the owner's response - let's throw a party.  Big deal.  Pay me more!  And mostly those expensive parties underscore the divergence between the show-off, rich owners and the 99% working for them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There is none. The damage may just be too bad to repair.  The owners, while able to spin gold, are on a collision course with disaster as they're unable to manage the rapid growth of this company with Managers who are incapable of sharing that vision.  nfrastructure might be positioning itself to be sold.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stay Clear”

</title><pros>Pros – Eventually I'll find one good thing to say about nfrastructure.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Family owned business that caters to that family.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep your resumes up to date.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>