<name>C-Dot Alcatel-Lucent Research Centre Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/C-Dot-Alcatel-Lucent-Research-Centre-Reviews-E313037.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-11-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for Engineers”

</title><pros>Pros – Good learning opportunities for Engineer Trainees and Engineers</pros>
<cons>Cons – No proper managementNeed quality technical architects</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to improve the project management side</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Last resort for someone searching job in CHENNAI in telecom domain”

</title><pros>Pros – Life/Work Balance will be good. As there is no track of projects and deadlines.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Getting projects and executing same doesnt happen clearly. Dont have Customer base. Dont have idea on projects that should be taken</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Not applicable</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to work as lot of opportunity to explore new areas of work .Provides great satisfaction to see your hard work rewarded.Always a very learning experience.Lot of critical tasks giving good boost to your spirits</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are a lot of challenges and people should be ready to face the technical challenges and resolve them .I believe this is expected and is helpful for personal growth.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“not bad”

</title><pros>Pros – gud ooputunity to work in the new tech</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad package for all levels</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – hire good people</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Technically challenged .....nice management and nice colegues to work for ... In helps you learn a lot in short period of time</pros>
<cons>Cons – They have agressive deadlines in most projects especially in the project that i worked for , workplace location comunte is more.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – nothing...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This place was good to work, but now things have deteriorated.”

</title><pros>Pros – Till now Good,, but now no future here</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everything except work load and sometimes good pay.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to get new projects.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Need to be more aggressive in progressing.”

</title><pros>Pros – Compensation package is good. Work life balance is good. For learning new technology, this is a good place. For testing professionals very good opportunity.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No challenging work for developers. No career growth. Have to work any team and any language at any time, despite the experience acquired over years.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have to look for good opportunities rather than sticking to the same project. Employee recruitment has to be relevant for their experience level and the requirement.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>