<name>U Mobile Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/U-Mobile-Reviews-E313344.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-02-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Mundane”

</title><pros>Pros – u have ample of time to 1 project. Freedom. Work quality increased</pros>
<cons>Cons – Projects often get held up and delayed. Management cut budget and freeze recruitment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>RF Optimization Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast learning environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Working inside a shopping mall, can enjoy shopping after lunch. Multiple discount by showing employee's pass for Berjaya business including cutting your hair, Starbucks coffee, buying Berjaya property. Flexible working hours.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The open office is exactly like a library office, lack of privacy.Entry salary for freshie is low, better for senior level,  increment and bonus are not promising.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide more training to staffs</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of oppurtunity to learn if you have the initiative.”

</title><pros>Pros – When I was with the company they were int he midst of preparing to lauch their service and brand in the market. There was a need for employees to step-up and taken on additional responsibilities to oversee a successful launch. The right amount of initiaitive allowed me to participate in the startegic team overseeing the launch activities. The company is in need of employess that show impetus. If you do you will get to work in the more exiciting projects.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A lot of politicking within the management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Set the direction and the rest will follow.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Support Department (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Start Up Experience & Lots of friends Made”

</title><pros>Pros – - Staff have a high degree of flexibility to work on assignment taking into account it is a new project so timelines are available but not consistent due to management response- Lots of technology to try out, recommend, create as this is a new 3G project with the vision to include DVBH (mobile TV on the phone as application and service)-Work environment at Berjaya Times Square is suitable as sufficient resources available, great network coverage, team of newly hired and experienced staff to kick start and possibly roll out the product</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Management issue as to accountability, responsibility, superiors and sub oridinates-Job roles and functions vague as it was start up-Multiple roles in the start of project, confirmation and staff appraisal not being addressed appropriately by mgmt and HR-Staff benefits and responsibility vague, office management structure not clear</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be honest and more approachable to staff, have better communication channel, flexibility in job roles and who is managing the hires so that tehre is clear jo roles and work scope to meet time lines</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you love challenges,  work here...”

</title><pros>Pros – Company is still growing, there MIGHT be opportunity to grow with it too...</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unsettled, due to change of Management several times - it does impact employees as they have to start all over again adapting to changes etc. Old timers who are still there - most does not seem to embrace changes well but yet they are still there as they have no where else to go. High turnover, bad bosses (they will always win), weak HR (not pro employees).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Time to weed out bosses who cant bring the company to the next level, being different means its necessary to change everything inside out.  Its about getting the best out of staff, putting them in the right roles (create new ones if need be!) . HR is weak, no development plan. Manager reports to Manager - weird reporting line.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>