<name>TCS e-Serve International Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/TCS-e-Serve-International-Reviews-E314082.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall a good experience to work w”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work culture , Good friend and nice environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow growth bad transport and lesser growth oppourtunity</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – A good place to start for</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Process Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not Great Company, But Ok”

</title><pros>Pros – Extraordinary work life balance,  its a Govt company, No login and logout timings.... Most of the Managers are too good. Good company who wants to settle at the age of 35+</pros>
<cons>Cons – work environment is pathetic. Cost cuttings. No learning opportunities. Growth NIL. overall not a great company to work at early stage of your career</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Nothing</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Company to start a career”

</title><pros>Pros – Work Life Balance is good</pros>
<cons>Cons – Depends on project to project</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Good Job</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“From the day one itself I was not sure what was my job title till I left.”

</title><pros>Pros – Nothing except a brand name on CV</pros>
<cons>Cons – no proper job description. You will never no when your job ocjectives wil change.No proper training facility.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – better training facility needed and proper job objectives should be drawn for any new comer to understand his actual position in the company which will help to achieve whats is defined,</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Process Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its a good company to work in........work life balance is mentionable”

</title><pros>Pros – employee friendly,work life balance,less stress</pros>
<cons>Cons – no incentives and bonus schemes introduced</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Credit Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very satisfying. The profile had lot of growth potential and great work”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work; Business was diverse and had lot of learning potential; great colleagues</pros>
<cons>Cons – Senior Management had no path chartered for employees;  Bit of negativity and close reviews</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Chart good growth plan for senior people; rotate among teams; give ownership</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Citi was a wonderful client to work with.”

</title><pros>Pros – Salary and work life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – Citi is winding up its relationship because of the middle management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Average”

</title><pros>Pros – People, culture are nice and secured to work. Enjoy lots of movement during the tenure of employment. Proper transportation facility.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Environment is workaholic but at the same time if Management keep their employee satisfied, then it will be great. Management have to discuss issue with their employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Should take proper care of your ground employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-28</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“s/w engg”

</title><pros>Pros – brand, gud salary, satisfaction, growth</pros>
<cons>Cons – there is nothing wong with tcs</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor work ethics and lack of motivation & inspiration from higher management”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly co workers and nothing else</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of exciting projects, hardly any employee growth, too many do's and don'ts, strict work hours even when there is no work</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Foreclosure Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great to work and enthuaisatic”

</title><pros>Pros – Work life balance and safety</pros>
<cons>Cons – Transport must be provided for both pickups and drop</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Must be transparent and close enough to the employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader Band III (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“an extremely good learning experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Learning, Opportunities if you part of a growing team. Citigroup name helps</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long work hours, Night shifts</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to focus more on work life balance</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Process Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“slow paced journey to accomplishment”

</title><pros>Pros – good scope of learning  for those interested into banking</pros>
<cons>Cons – LONG WORKING HOURS,  Non efficient mangers</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No growth, and biased management”

</title><pros>Pros – Only good for people who can entertain the senior people</pros>
<cons>Cons – less scope, no growth opportunity</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give equal oppourtunity to all the employees,</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Clients”

</title><pros>Pros – Clients are great to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Promotions and Increments don't come to those who stay with them</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Tester (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Test Analyst TCS e-Serve”

</title><pros>Pros – Good CompanyRelaxed environmentModerate work load</pros>
<cons>Cons – Time TrackingNo Work From HomeOffice politics</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Remove Time TrackingStart Work From Home</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>WORKFLOW SPECIALIST (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“TCS is my first employer,as a fresher i'am satisfied to work in a renowned company like TCS”

</title><pros>Pros – Job security,Second largest BPO,Stress is comparatively less</pros>
<cons>Cons – Need  to give little more importance to value added learning for the employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – nil</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Back Office (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work experience at TCS”

</title><pros>Pros – TCS is one of the best bpo sector in technical support.It provides better growth opportunity,better envoirnment,It has good management.It has better transort facility,.It pays better package.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There were no downsides working at TCS. It was a great experience working with TCS. If I get chance I would like to join back TCS.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – All the best</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – TCS e-serve has friendly environment to work culture.</pros>
<cons>Cons – i am not wise to disclose ..................</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – i am not wise to disclose ..................</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible commpany”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people.can bulid communication and understandings with others.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No comments. Do not want to explore about the company and there is nothing to explore.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management is were bad and nothing much to share about it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dominated by Senior Management”

</title><pros>Pros – If you are lazy, if you know how to keep your boss happy and you do not maintain a good client relation</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you work hard, if you have good client relation, if you tell your boss you are wrong, if you complaint about your boss "Never think of getting into the company"</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 8 year long horrifying dream finally came to an end. Respect middle management, respect people who have given a significant time of there life. Do not blame others to hide what you are not capable of delivering</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Join if you want to stay for a long time....”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work/Clients and good exposure towards themFlexible timingsDrop facility</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bad ManagementBad AdministrationVintage employees running the organisationOrganisation not inclined towards the employee3 months notice periodno buy out optionpeople think that you are in TCS but actually you are working in their BPO Arm!!!At least they think so..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Retain People, Give good hikes and stay true to the brand. Its TCS eServe, not eServe.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Process Officer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was My second home”

</title><pros>Pros – always good not much pressure</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are certain handfull people where they make your life miserable</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please scrutinize and kick these people who make people life miserable and do not let other reach the ladder as well as to climb the success ladder.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No.1 BFSI BPO”

</title><pros>Pros – Salary is good comparatively yo other BFSI..</pros>
<cons>Cons – No growth,, culture.. structure and Indian corporate structure</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My working experience with this company is good and satisfactory”

</title><pros>Pros – My learning and working experience is really comfortable. The Management is good part through out my tenure with this company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The only thing is Unlikely shift timing</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to re-think about the abrupt shift timing</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“sorry for the first time got dis name”

</title><pros>Pros – an optimystic  company sector which gives an opportunity to the younger ones</pros>
<cons>Cons – sorry dont hav any idea</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – to provide best advice n proper guidence to the younger people</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work but as far as the salary is considered will not recommend”

</title><pros>Pros – Good place to work but as far as the salary is considered will not recommend</pros>
<cons>Cons – as far as the salary is considered will not recommend</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – relook in to the salaries.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“very bad”

</title><pros>Pros – Good atmospheregood foodgood transport facility</pros>
<cons>Cons – very bad work cultureno work life balancevery bad senior management</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Business Analyst”

</title><pros>Pros – Good career opportunities to look forward to</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation and Bonus should be looked into</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cool with proper work life balance”

</title><pros>Pros – Proper Work life balance during job</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary hikes should be more competitive</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Better and competitive salary as per the market condition</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Process Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I learned about capital market very well, its very good process and I have improved my carrer growth,”

</title><pros>Pros – we have the carrier growth .</pros>
<cons>Cons – no comments about the TCS</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – kindly improve the hr facilities and follow the new application for salary method</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Finance dept”

</title><pros>Pros – Great GoodwillGood premisesGood incentive schemes</pros>
<cons>Cons – More pressure - Management always expects over time work at free of costLess SalaryDominant ManagementPolitics</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Subordinates also humans like you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Name speaks everything”

</title><pros>Pros – True certainty of success comes from working with a partner you trust to provide the insight, support and expertise that will propel your business forward. Experiencing certainty with TCS means you can count on results, partnership and leadership.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are downsides of TCS e-service international ltd</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Survived”

</title><pros>Pros – If you get into right process there is lot of scope to improve</pros>
<cons>Cons – Timings are the worst thing and you don't get enough leaves</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There should be more transparency between the management and the employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Process Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Company offers  excellent pay for experienced candiddates”

</title><pros>Pros – It offers a lot of scope for learning and career growth.The company allows  career growth to mature candidates.It offers a work life  balance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Career growth is dependent on one's work as well as personal rapport with Supervisors.It makes Career reviews a one to one with Supervisor, and is not always an objective view of reality.It also offers opportunities to experienced candidates in the field.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would like to have performance review done in a mature way without bias.It would make work life more result oriented.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hated its Company Policies & the Managers+HR were rubbish”

</title><pros>Pros – TCS eServe portrays the Scope & Future of a booming ITES industry and manages to accommodate lots of human resources despite of any market down in economy. Fascinating, only because of the amalgamation of TCS being taken over but not completely!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Although TCS eServe maintains a good image on the outside! The employees suffer from the inside due to hasty decisions, Salary revisions & foolish cum Dumb Managers. The industry has a wide scope of employment opportunities but is not manipulated under the right hands for sustainable future!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please provide weekly Refresher trainings to HR personnel's of eServe as none of them know the Organization's policies & regulations! Also revoke all top managements decisions & initiate with a new Management which can make the employees feel that they are working under the actual TCS. Not like some 3rd class/low budgeted Domestic company! Please intake many amendments else shut down eServe!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A drop in an ocean”

</title><pros>Pros – Good policies, Flexibility in opportunities, Good infrastructure & amenities, Excellent brand name recognition & standing among peers. Mid level positions have it the easiest.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Easy to get lost in the bureaucracy, U're just a small drop in the large organisation, not easy to get oversights rectified, job satisfaction can be unsatisfactory at times. have a commoditized approach towards recruitment and retainment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Systems & Automation can replace hands on management and interaction only to a certain extent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Gives nice opportunities.... and good exposure....”

</title><pros>Pros – opportunities to show your talent, nice work environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – HR management is not so good....</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – can do much better</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Tester (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Leaves you wondering what's there to learn & earn...”

</title><pros>Pros – > Good for Freshers in terms of guarantee of Job & initial learning curve> Just OK work environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – > Policies change rapidly without any involvement or suggestions from employees.> Salary is extremely unstable at times, with surprise deductions. Not at all near the industry standard for experienced crowd.> Very less learning opportunity.> Management & HR play the blame game to each other in terms of solving employee queries.> No Clarity on challenges.> Client dissatisfaction is seen in some internal processes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – > Value an employee(s) suggestion and try to work on it.> Be clear, concise and better prepared in terms of  accepting challenges.> Don't give false promises.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Average, As any other company end of the day!”

</title><pros>Pros – Good place to work if looking for an employer to settle down for a long time again if u stick with the company initially.  gud compensation and pay scale compared to any other's in chennai, very competitive pay scale.</pros>
<cons>Cons – you will have to take care of ur own transport. Transport will be provided if you leave late evenings' say after 9.30 pm. advisable dont take the transport facility. pathetic :-(</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Process Trainer & Back-up Team Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It been good overall. Got to learn lot of things.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good fun at work activity overall during the year all around, Also sports facilities are provided. Good boost to Professional Career.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low Compensation benefits, No rewarding factor for high performance individuals, Mental stress due to long work hours.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to promote individuals with high potentials and performance.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“one of the reputed organisation in chennai”

</title><pros>Pros – Located at the heart of the city. Really a different environment to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – management should also concentrate on employee activities apart from getting new business.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – should also concentrate on employee activities apart from getting new business.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>BPO Information Processing Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its a big brand but not really a great company to work with”

</title><pros>Pros – You get to be associated with one of the biggest brand nameJob secutiry</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work pressureWork culture isn't very goodEven after spending years with the company you aren't sure of promotionBiased managementNo fun at workHR never has any answer or solution to your problems/queries</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to obtain feedback from associates and get to know their views, opinions & ideasThere should be work & fun balance. All work & no play makes you dull.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“BPO Workculture - how good for MBA's”

</title><pros>Pros – Brand name, policies, job security</pros>
<cons>Cons – BPO as a sector not very great opportunity for MBA's with mostly Team lead and project management profiles to do with not much flexibilityThe bureaucratic way of working might not gel well with people starting their career as managers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More tailor made profiles for management trainees, across various departmentsThis will give a better intake of people across colleges too</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Risk Mitigation Specialist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“was a very good BPO people really good even managers were friendly”

</title><pros>Pros – good managers,good salary,satisfactory perks</pros>
<cons>Cons – the transport and facilities management needs to be checked</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to look for better employees then just length of their work for promotion</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“career growth”

</title><pros>Pros – a place to upgrade oneself</pros>
<cons>Cons – internal communication can be improved (inside the team)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – could improve appraisal methods</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“About the company”

</title><pros>Pros – If you want to experience stability and security pls join.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you are oriented to internal growth then...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No advise as such to give.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-10</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Process Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great company to work with great satisfaction ..!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Operational Team and the available Projects ...</pros>
<cons>Cons – HR Policies - Promotions Cycle is not very satisfactory</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create opportunity for the interested employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Process Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Handling front end Underwritting, Mortgage.”

</title><pros>Pros – Environment and infrastructure is good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – TCS is not a good pay master.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat everyone as equal.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Process Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“its wonderful 2 b a part of tcs”

</title><pros>Pros – brand name & facilities being given.oppurtunity to seek a challenging position in industry & prove urself.good carrer oppurtunity.</pros>
<cons>Cons – growth is very low,notice period is too long</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good to start your career with”

</title><pros>Pros – Brand name of Tata consultancy services</pros>
<cons>Cons – although it has TCS brand name but most IT projects are maintanance projects which do not offfer to learn much...management was better when it was e-serve / CGSL</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – give better salaries...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>BPO Information Processing Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Job Security But not Satisfaction....”

</title><pros>Pros – If your are looking for a Co which gives you Job Security, Then I will say there is 100% Job security in TCS e-Serve International.</pros>
<cons>Cons – But will also be aware that this Co has a bad Policy's which keep on changing in favor of Management's Benefit. So ultimately they don't care about there Employee's welfare.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They need to understand that employee who is giving his hart and sole to achieve Co's Goal's, they should be respected and there job satisfaction should be taken in consideration as well. That will not only help Co to Grow, the employee will be with the Co for long period of time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Process Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I had good team members and a manager but we all were victims of cheap office politics”

</title><pros>Pros – An excellent work cultureSupportive team leaders and team membersThere are chances to grow if you are an extremely hardworking person who doesn't mind getting involved in some cheap politics</pros>
<cons>Cons – The salary packageHR is not that supportiveThere are less chances to grow if you are not involved in politics</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There are hardworking and deserving people, who goes out of the company because of the politics. Just because people cant play good in office politics doesn't mean they are not good performers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This company has given me enough opportunities to display and increase my talent.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good opporunities with good brand name in the market ...</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very miser in terms of compensation and benefits to their employees ..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Our management needs to be little vigilant on client side ... Upper management need to leave their internal politics and come together for companies growth ..</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best place to start career.”

</title><pros>Pros – The company follows the Citigroups principles well than Citigroup. Diversified domains in financial market is supported.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very less salary for the vintage resources and don't know how retain the SMEs. Need to tap the knowledge approrpriately.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The worst company i hae ever worked with, promotions, hike, ratings are not given equally or based on the work.”

</title><pros>Pros – No reasons, if some one asks me about this company i would tell not to join</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everything is downside for this company</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please give back the management to CGSL itself</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work more and take home less year by year”

</title><pros>Pros – Name and fame only reason.</pros>
<cons>Cons – All allowances are been grabbed from the employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employees satisfaction is also important like company's growth.So please keep the employees happy at least not by giving new benefits rather than cutting off.Many are affected.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Job security at the cost of compensation and diminishing standards of living.”

</title><pros>Pros – Your job is secure and it helps the bread winner of the family not be displaced.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay scales are not up to market bench marks and your standard of living diminishes, as a result. However, its like any form of investment. The risk of losing your job being lower, your returns (pay cheque) are also lower.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Perhaps, employees need to be treated with a little more attention. More so, the loyal ones like me who have stayed on for 6 years and earn half the pay of someone recruited from outside at the same level! Quite literally..</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Tester (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Knowledge Enhancing in the field of Banking and funds transfer.”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent place to grab knowledge in Banking and funds transfer as in my project.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not a very good salary package is being provided to employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Before implementing policies it should be discussed and communicated well to all the employees and should be applied when most of them are satisfied.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Little learning”

</title><pros>Pros – Salary, work life balance, flexibility</pros>
<cons>Cons – no learning, incapable senior management</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Process Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Top Management and Team leaders are blood sucking bugs”

</title><pros>Pros – TCS Brand NameKnowledge of Capital Market</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very low salary package (Fresher-Rs7500 to Rs.10000 including bonus and variable allowances)12-15hr informal working time.No proper on the job trainingRude behavior of ManagementNo proper transport facility.Brainless team leaders</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do not spoil the name of grate TATAs and TCS...Sack all top management employees to make all right. Blood Sucker Top Management</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Tester (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work but not for long term since it is a merger”

</title><pros>Pros – flexible sometimes, good location, some managers are good</pros>
<cons>Cons – Night shifts, transport is bad, food is also not good, company thinks more of cost cutting than the employees need</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – brand name and challenging opportunitygood salarybonus and other recognitionswork life balanceweekend fun activities</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad canteen and foodwork place will not be much comfortpolitics</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – no comments</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work at when compared with other BPOs but it lacks a sound and healthy corporate culture as an MNC.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good salary for employees at management level.Good prospects of learning various BFSI processes.Rich in domain expertise.Good Brand name of TCS.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Entry level employees do not get very good salary when compared with other BFSI MNCs.The culture at TCS is not like much of corporate, which is desirable for any MNCThere is lack of competitiveness among the employeesIn pursuit of cost cutting, they have stopped many facilities which were earlier available to the employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The processes and clients handled by company are really great and rich in terms of domain knowledge. Instead of turning it into an Indian "cost effective" BPO, we should try to improve the standard and culture of organization. Our competitors include JP Morgan, Barclays, BNP Paribas, Northern Trust, Deutsche Bank etc. We should be at par in terms of culture and employee satisfaction, as these companies and TCS E-Serve target same segment of talent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good to work”

</title><pros>Pros – More Chances to move upward</pros>
<cons>Cons – Promotional Cycle is too long.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Should be more employee friendly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Operations Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A place where you have to forget life...”

</title><pros>Pros – TCS Brand Name, Content of work for initial few years, Transport Facilities</pros>
<cons>Cons – No personal Life, extreme pressure and responsiblity without authority, Temporary Solutions to recurring problems, extremly negative atmosphere, Non transperant and only paper based assessment for company records, Too many changes in HR promotion policy, No job rotation, No growth after 2-2.5 years of service.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Quality Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Management sucks in TCS Eserve LTD (Mumbai and Chennai)”

</title><pros>Pros – No workload only if your in good process.Brand Name.Corporate discount.Well pay master if you have good experiance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management sucks,No cordination between HR and Financial Management Team.Senior Management are real dumb.TCS is a good company but TCS eServe sucks big time.No proepr communication between HR, Team Lead and Employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve communication with employees.Inform employees for any changes done by the management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a company for a core IT professionals.”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. TCS brand is a big plus.2. TCS compensation policies are fair as compared to most other small players.3. Company policies are good but their implementation is a big problem.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Shifts working is a big problem.2. IT professionals feel undervalued and are frustrated as most of the company is filled with BPO employees and helpdesk guys.3. Company does not think beyond its Citi Group Global client.4. Management has no clear planning for the future of the company.5. Execution and delivery of projects is a big issue.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat employees with respect. Give clear direction to the employees. Dont expect non technical BPO employees to fill up IT related positions and expect them to deliver quality.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not bad”

</title><pros>Pros – Pride when it was under the unbrella of Citi. Good amount of oppurtunity for transitions</pros>
<cons>Cons – Time spent in office is very bad so the work life balance you will not be able to match at any point.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Think every employee work life balance</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“no so bad, but no growth”

</title><pros>Pros – great salaray, good accomodation, no work on time</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad overall conditions,  work in time proceses</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – employ competitive people and let them work</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good work place”

</title><pros>Pros – good to be part of the company</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad to stay in the company for long time</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – give recognition to the vintage employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Working space for all freshers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Career growth is too low</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please take look at the employee growth</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“1”

</title><pros>Pros – Good salaryGood EnvironmentNice policyBrand name TCS</pros>
<cons>Cons – No career GrowthRatings are very poorNo recognition for good workNo justification in the ratingsTeam handling poor</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Senior manager should allow employee interest in the work, need to take better suggestion before implementing anything not for the sake of trying something. Senior level should involve in the team not just with managers data.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not for career oriented people”

</title><pros>Pros – Security,Brand name,No work pressure,Good work and life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – No growthNo quality workToo many processes</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Assign role and work according to competency and interest of associate</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a good place for people from premiere institutes... but average people can flourish..”

</title><pros>Pros – less workload.. you work for Citi...</pros>
<cons>Cons – nobody cares what you are working on... senior managers are too dumb...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – get better and more intellectual people for band6+</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Test Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst HR policies”

</title><pros>Pros – Perks, pick ups and drops</pros>
<cons>Cons – Stunted growth. You will get stale if u wait here long</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They can do good with some management for themselves : )No justice towards promotions. Incompetent work atmosphere.There is a huge attrition rate and the company chooses to hire inefficient people in their place of skilled experienced people. Experienced people leave for better salaries and growth.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Quality Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good organisation to work”

</title><pros>Pros – TATA values and integrity is the best</pros>
<cons>Cons – less salary & no transperancy and bossisum culture do not suit present employment condition.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to employees voice when they are badly need your support</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good work culture”

</title><pros>Pros – TCS eserve has a gr8 work life balance you dont usually land up with leave issues. All the appraisals happen on time each year.Good transport facility, home drop service.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The appraisals happen behind closed doors, there is no clarity as to what ratings you have received and why? there is no platform for discussions either.Getting access to any new system takes a decade!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The appraisals should be discussed with the employees and the ratings justified. there is no clarity on what feedback is received from the clients. the management should definitely work on that!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok compensation, work allocation through lottery system”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Good compensation, one of the best in industry2. Good work culture3. respect for individual4. TCS Brand name advantage</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Highly Improper work allocation - some over worked and some leaving company coz there is no work2. Very poor employee empowerment3. Not good talent recognition</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You just have to allocate work uniformly among the various offices. Mumbai is overworked while we in Gurgaon keep sitin idle waiting for work</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>