<name>M Fredric Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/M-Fredric-Reviews-E315199.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-03-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not the worst but would not return”

</title><pros>Pros – Ability to have independence in merchandising visuals (no plannograms), good employee discount, less micromanaging if you work further away from the HQ.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Crappy pay, unprofessional upper management, no room for growth.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Act professional and be an example of how you'd like your employees to behave.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Floor Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great job for starting in retail”

</title><pros>Pros – 20% off store merchandise from start of employment-6 months, 40% after 6 months.Great management</pros>
<cons>Cons – Commission based sales created hostile environment</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate/Key Holder (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“review of M Fredric”

</title><pros>Pros – as a sales associate you are always given the hours that you were hired to work. There is opportunity to work full time if you are willing to drive from one store location to the next. Also, one top of your base hourly you earn commission as well. These perks beat working long hours as a sales associate at a mall.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The work environment tends to be very competitive among other sales associates because you are competing for sales. Unfortunately, this makes for a cut throat environment. It is very difficult to push a sale upon someone who is just browsing especially when they have a set amount they are willing to spend.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Having a less critical store manager would be helpful. Someone who is more patient and fair with her employees would be much more beneficial for the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>