<name>Y of Central Maryland Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Y-of-Central-Maryland-Reviews-E317267.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-02-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great work place environment”

</title><pros>Pros – The people here are very nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Better integration more IT to daily work instead of manually.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Little room for Advancement, Heavy Politics”

</title><pros>Pros – The people who work there are generally very passionate about the cause they are working for, creating a very great environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Large disconnect from Association Office and the Branches, senior Management is not in tune with what is needed at the branch level. Promotions are only based on politics, not actual merit. Within the Organization, there is a resistance to outside training, even if it would be beneficial, they are only concerned with training done in-house. Pay is not great for the amount of work expected.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – One of the Goals is to be an employer of choice. If you are serious about that goal, you need to really sit down and look at the Organization and change things. Advancement needs to be based on merit and accomplishments, not politics, compensation needs to be in line with the amount of work expected.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great People, Confusing Work Environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Wonderful community of people working together for a common goodOkay work/life balanceGreat people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor payOverworkedNot recognized for your work even if you are doing the job of 6 people</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take care of your people. They are working hard with very little respect.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Community service oriented, but no clear sense of direction”

</title><pros>Pros – There's a strong sense of community among coworkers. The organization provides internal training resources for employees, including paying for state required licenses (child care services).</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is little to no room for growth within the organization and the pay is abysmal (under $30k for full-time white collar position after two years).  I've witnessed certain members of the management and executive team speak down to employees in condescending tones, or sit idly by as interpersonal conflict arises between coworkers within the office. The organization, while community service focus, lacked a clear sense of direction. They had great ideas on what they wanted to do for the community, but it wasn't clear to the employees what their steps were for getting there.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take recognition of your strongest employees and promote from within. Provide professional training and/or educational reimbursement opportunities for employees who wish to grow professionally within your organization. Clarify your organizational goals and steps for attaining this to all of your employees, not just the executive team and community board members.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>