<name>International Fund Services Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/International-Fund-Services-Reviews-E318799.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-03-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A stable job, whatever this implies”

</title><pros>Pros – This is a stable job with good work/life balance and flexible schedule, so it could be beneficial for family people or for someone working on their advanced degree. Overall, a friendly environment among employees, with few exceptions.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not much upward potential or motivation, not enough challenge either. If you are after fat bonuses to compensate for extra work - look somewhere else.Somewhat bureaucratic when comes to technology - unreasonably many websites are blocked and no rights to install anything on your computer or otherwise set up environment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Quality over quantity. Try to acquire hardworking talent and compensate it properly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company to work for if you want a relaxed environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Very friendly coworkers, easygoing, and job is not stressful</pros>
<cons>Cons – Minimal career growth opportunities for ambitious individuals</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Transfer Agent (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Boring”

</title><pros>Pros – At first it;s not bad but as you move up it gets a lot worse</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not enough people to do the job. Always stressful</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Show some appreciation for the associates</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“State Street PDP Review”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work/life balance. You rarely work more than 45 hours per week.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The job can be very pigeon-holed</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Was good at first then went downhill”

</title><pros>Pros – Good experience if you haven't worked in the hedge fund industry before.  Centrally located in Manhattan.  Most people are friendly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Morale is extremely low and management doesn't work to correct this.  Many people in management have left in the last few years, taking a lot of knowledge, staff, and experience with them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Fix the morale problems, if bonuses and raises can't be done, atleast communicate this better to managers and teams, and stop using a pre-set matrix to determine everything.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good”

</title><pros>Pros – Balance between work and home life is good. Ability to work remotely is nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Clients as well as management are very demanding.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Development Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Safe Place great work life balance”

</title><pros>Pros – The perks are great, work from home, 4 weeks vacation day 1, good health, etc</pros>
<cons>Cons – The work is not very interesting or challenging.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Off-shore is not always the best or the cheapest way to get the job done.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate I (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I needed a college degree for this?”

</title><pros>Pros – -Immediate coworkers were great people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Was the salary a joke?  $33k a year for a college degree living in Boston?  Seems a little low.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – In 2010 there was close to 70% employee turnover.  Spend less money on recruiting and more money on paychecks and I bet that % will decrease.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“IFS was a terrific place to work but since State Street changed the company culture it's not longer the place it was.”

</title><pros>Pros – Co-workers are generally friendly, many people are willing to help if you need assistance, it is am open environment where you can exchange ideas, management is pretty good about granting vacation time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A freeze in all raises and bonuses has been in place for approximately 3 years now, promotions have been few and far between, politics are usually involved if you do get a promotion, hours can be brutal with little recognition for your hard work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start compensating employees what they deserve otherwise you are going to find yourself with an under qualified workforce.  Since State Street took over the number one objective of the Company has been the bottom line.  IFS used to be the #1 administrator of hedge funds for a number of years. This was during a period of time when they valued their employees.  Since State Street shifted it's focus to the bottom line, IFS has fallen back and is no longer considered the premier hedge fund administrator.  I believe this is directly related to it's shift away from it's employees to it's obsession with driving the highest profit margins possible. In just the last 2 years there has been a number of managing directors who left the Company that have been there since day 1.  That should tell you all you need to know about how they have been treating their most valuable resource: the human resource.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>NAV Officer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“dont stay too long”

</title><pros>Pros – good place to learn, good work/life balance, generally nice people</pros>
<cons>Cons – zero development or training or career advice from management, unorganized and political atmosphere prevails.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“lacking anything good”

</title><pros>Pros – good benefits, ok place to start right out of school, great entry-level job to give you a taste of the entire industry-</pros>
<cons>Cons – after a while you feel stuck and your brain gets dumber each day you sit in your cube.management plays favorites, only advance if its on accident</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – great place to start - but long term growth isnt really attractive</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Operations Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“State Street Changed the firm but still strong overall”

</title><pros>Pros – Pros:Good learning environment and good people to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Cons:Too much influence from accounting firm State Street, ran off some of the best leaders the firm had for decades.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on the team and what they need to improve the process for you</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate I (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No Room For Growth!”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a nicely friendly work environment. Everyone is friendly and it's open here. Time off is always approved when requested.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is no room for growth. I been working here for several years and have been doing the same work. There is no challenge and it get's boring.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – In order to retain some good talent, you must provide your employees with the opportunity to grow within their positions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Derivatives Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review”

</title><pros>Pros – Learn a lot of new stuff about finance, programming. Good team work. Friendly helpful people. You can work normal hours.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not enough growth. Sometimes it is hard to take time off. sometimes need to work over time. a a a</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to work more to give ability for promotion an growth for people. Listen to the new ideas, support new ideas.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cons outweigh the pros”

</title><pros>Pros – Since IFS is a subsidiary company of State Street, you are able to benefit from the perks of a big company while getting the one-on-one personal time with management that you can only get from a small company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hiring and promotion process has been slow, with no end in sight.  Salary is not competitive with other companies and seems to be the number one concern of most employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Lately, upper management seems to have been listening to the employees and started taking the necessary steps towards better communication.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Financial Analyst”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice people to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not so many opportunities within department.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Fund Accountant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fund Accountant  Alternative Investments”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Looks good on resume2. Opportunity to work on large funds3. Company pays overtime</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Toxic team environment2. Unstable systems which is a cause of lot delays3. Systems could be more organized</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Supervisors and Seniors could use interpersonal skill training because they snap for the slightest things. This damages team dynamics. If they were just patient and respectful it would help a lot for one to perform well in this position.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Fund Accountant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice and suitable place to work and learn.”

</title><pros>Pros – Pilot batch of this company, it is a Joint venture between statestreet bank (IFS) and HCL technologies, get trained on this process for 6 weeks in Ireland and Stabilized the process in India.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Applications are not standard, the can improve the standard of the applications.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management also take part in the operations to know the difficulties of the process.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Shareholder Services Administrator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Shareholder Services”

</title><pros>Pros – Young friendly staff, central Dublin location</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poorly managed, nepotistic, male hires are fast tracked for promotion over and above female staff.AML procedures not followed. Shareholder services had a high turnover and managers seemed not to have a problem with this..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Investigate departments with high turnoverDo not allow managers to continually extend trial periods</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good and Bad Times”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Systems, good office locations.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Natural seepage of staff leading to increased pressure on the ones who stay.  You will work late in this job so be prepared.  Once you get to supervisory level you will actually earn less money than those below you due to the fact that you do not receive over time payments.  These factors all combined mean that the workforce is very demoralised.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start rewarding the Hard work that people are putting in with better pay.  Stop drumming on about work life balance when the vast majority of the teams can not implament it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A nice place to work if you are happy to "go through the motions" every day”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a place of diverse cultures.They are flexible on work hours.Good social environment (most of the time).It is a good place to work if all you want from a job is the standard 9-5 routine.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Progression appears very limited.Poor pay and poorer bonuses (for the money being made only a minute fraction appears to trickle down below AVP level).Variety of work is non existent.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest more in your employee. External training sessions for continued professional development would help the employee continue in understanding both the fundamental and evolutionary products within the market and subsequently provide a more efficient service to the client.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Fund Accountant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is not a decent job”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a good step to entry finance industry and international bank</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited career path and not very good paid</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Fund Accountant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok to start, but very boring”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly atmosphere, no pressure to perform</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited learning experience, job is usually not very demanding</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Prioritise training</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Shareholder Services Administrator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“International Fund Services”

</title><pros>Pros – Great opportunities to advance in terms of qualifications- ACCAs ACAs. Fully paid by the company. Diverse workforce. Highly regarded company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Boring place to work. Very monotonous work. Very little unity. Little knowledge of what was going on at corporate level.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Better communication with employees is required. More interesting work. Better compensation for overtime, ie pay us like the law states.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>