<name>Toby Keith's I Love This Bar and Grill Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Toby-Keith-s-I-Love-This-Bar-and-Grill-Reviews-E318412.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-02-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An ok place”

</title><pros>Pros – When there is a big concert the ant the Bar is at Capacity, it is an awesome place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Overstaffed and slow unless there is a major event.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“the best of the best”

</title><pros>Pros – they take good care of their employees and provide plenty of opportunity to advance and grow..great company!</pros>
<cons>Cons – sometimes it can be long hours and they keep you challenged and very busy..in the restaurant business its expected but they are more intense than the usual..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – try to provide better hours or more vacation time</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“general manager”

</title><pros>Pros – lots of good looking women</pros>
<cons>Cons – long hours, poor pay, lots of stress</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – give bonuses based on labor, COGS, sales, etc...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Server (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Never work here.”

</title><pros>Pros – Half off food, great kitchen staff, great kitchen management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible communication from management to servers, horrible leadership from front of house management and shift leads/headwaits, based on good ol buddy system to recieve promotions and who goes drinking with the managers after work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give consideration to servers that do the work and do it well to be put in leadership positions. Actually do background checks on management and hire accordingly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst Company Ever”

</title><pros>Pros – Meet and take care of high-profile national acts and celebrities one-two times a month, free meals</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are SO many, where to begin... This company is full of broken promises, labor law violations, and as cut-throat as it could ever be. Completely unorganized all the way into the corporate office. They will turn their back on you and treat you like the dirt on the bottom of your shoe. No matter how hard you work, the time and effort you put in, it is unappreciated and underpaid. You are just a number if you work here. They have over $7 million in law suits across all their locations as of Dec. 2012. Run away as fast as you can. Avoid the stress, anger, and disapointment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Problems need to be fixed all the way up the corporate ladder.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Server (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Favorites Game”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible ScheduleEasy to get time off</pros>
<cons>Cons – unfortunately the favorites game determines the schedule</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More organization and streamlined processes would help.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>