<name>T/DG Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/T-DG-Reviews-E320342.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-04-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's growing company”

</title><pros>Pros – work on new technologies, it's usa based company in pune</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lott of work load is going on, Leave probleam is their</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Team Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not so good”

</title><pros>Pros – 1) Good Salary2) You can grow if you are having dependency on project.3) Time flexibility (some extend)</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1) You have to always fight for your increment.2) Completely Client oriented.3) Believes on Managers not on employees.4) No transparency on increments.5) You have to pay for your trainings if you will leave company within one year of trainigi held.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There should be 360 degree of feedback policy to take any decision to fire someone.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Company to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Environment to work for</pros>
<cons>Cons – Increments not good, appraisal does not happen on time</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK company to work in.”

</title><pros>Pros – Work/Life Balance is good.Good for people who are not very ambitious.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No job satisfaction.3 months notice period</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>SSE (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good working culture and Salary structure”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunities to work on latest technologies.Performance based appraisals.Good working culture.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Policies needs to be more stable.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – A more stable policy structure needs to be framed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Lead (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nobody should even think of joining this Company”

</title><pros>Pros – There are only Cons with this company,</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper & middle management - NO mind ,No accountability, No Respect for Employee, will try to force their decision on you and if you dont agree then they will threaten you if you still dont agree with them then they will terminate you even if you have put your papers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Go and Open some vegetable shop</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very compensating career marred by nuisance middle management”

</title><pros>Pros – simpler process, friendly top management, good work, friendly clients, compensation - pay and appraisals every year.</pros>
<cons>Cons – work life imbalance, middle management, culture,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Old heads need to make way for the new ones</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Accountant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was a satisfying experience to work in Digital Group”

</title><pros>Pros – Salary is good and work pressure is not that much compare to other IT companies</pros>
<cons>Cons – Fickle minded upper management. They don't stick with their own decisions.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not what i expected about MNC.”

</title><pros>Pros – If you get good manager then you are too lucky @ T/DG.Have good traveling facility, too good for long distance employees.Perform good annual sports activity.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low Securities towards job stability, means unless and until their are project in streamline your job is till then secure.Too Less Salary Package offered than market value because its always compared to previous employer's package offered.No quarterly or half yearly parties.No stability in food quality offered in lunch.Cuts food coupons and traveling allowance from CTC.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please fulfill cons into pros which is considered as minimum pros in all MNC</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Bpo Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“awesome”

</title><pros>Pros – great working environmentnice co-workerslove my job</pros>
<cons>Cons – salary packagetoo far from my home</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – it was a great experience working in T/DG</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>SSE (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“type”

</title><pros>Pros – good for technical improvement and good for you if you are into developement.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Has Only one client, so sometimes you may expect to be on bench.....</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The Digital Group can assist your organization in the adoption of industry standard process methodologies. We believe our consulting responsibility goes beyond assessment and recommendation. Our consultants will assure that your objectives are translated into measurable performance improvement and bottom-line results. We have a team of highly qualified and experienced professionals with proven problem solving, consulting and analytical skills. Our Team consists of Domain Experts & Technical Experts so as to provide world class consulting solutions to our clients. The primary strength of our consultants is to work with the client organization to optimize resources & implement the improvement strategies successfully.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>