<name>Manipal Universal Learning Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Manipal-Universal-Learning-Reviews-E321284.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-01-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Facilitator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its challenging and there's room for innovation”

</title><pros>Pros – Its a upcoming org,therefore offers ample scope for vertical career growth</pros>
<cons>Cons – I hav'nt found any such drawbacks,as I consider the maxim:"No Risk No Gain"</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – May cut down the unnecessary frills to save cost and thereby enhance profitability</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Junior Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Innovative & Educative throughout the carrier”

</title><pros>Pros – Learning & Working atmosphere, Innovative & Educative throughout the carrier</pros>
<cons>Cons – Relaibilty,  unNotice employees who gives more than your expectations</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please Notice employees who gives more than your expectations</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>SLCM Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Learning Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Learning Experience and opportunity to work across different segments</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work culture and monetary benefits</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Approach</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Development (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not Great Employer”

</title><pros>Pros – Sufficient time is given for learning.Culture and values are given high importance.Efforts are counted when results are not there in terms of numbers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Except Head Quarter which is Bangalore other locations are not given that importance.Operation wise it runs at snail rate.Planning and execution never match.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Should be executing plans when ready to launch.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Technically very far with the current trends”

</title><pros>Pros – Many oppurtunities to workGood work life balance (if you are able to manage).Many functional opurtunities if you are willing to go in that direction.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No clarity in what needs to be done.No proper technical gudanceArchitects doesn't have clarity on what needs to be done.Design changes before day of release.Trying to build a product  is built on drupal, no architect knowns drupal.People were egoistic.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire some good full time architects.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>