<name>Vinsys IT Services Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Vinsys-IT-Services-Reviews-E323179.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-05-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Vinsys IT services”

</title><pros>Pros – You may grow with company considering size if the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Current Cost control measures can result in to d dissatisfaction.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Corporate Trainer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“hire and fire policy”

</title><pros>Pros – lots of time for your own study</pros>
<cons>Cons – no basic structure for process</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – follow some rule and do not follow hire and fire policy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I was an independent contractor. Payment was never on time...”

</title><pros>Pros – Some of them are friendly and easy to access.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Payment was never on time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Corporate Trainer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's ok if you just want to do time pass”

</title><pros>Pros – Company has good infrastructure and has nice work culture.All the people are helping and nice. If you want to learn something go and learn.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They do not have much business these days and job satisfaction is not there at all.You will never know what will happen to you on next day.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Executive Business Development (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Atmosphere!!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work atmosphere, supporting and motivating superiors.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not good pay master, need to concentrate more on the employee satisfaction.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – they need to concentrate more on the employee satisfaction and benefits.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>