<name>K-VA-T Food Stores Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/K-VA-T-Food-Stores-Reviews-E3246.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-27</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“got to become friends with other co workers and customer”

</title><pros>Pros – they are very good to work for and they will do everything that  they can to help co workers and customer</pros>
<cons>Cons – they give hours to their pick  if they don't like you you get no hours</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – treat co workers all the same and try to help them all you can</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall a wonderful, great experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – You always get a break no matter how many hoursIf you have six or more hours you get an hour long lunchGreat management</pros>
<cons>Cons – I do not have any cons</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I think there is wonderful management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“FoodCity”

</title><pros>Pros – nice co workersdifferent jobs to train onflexible schedule</pros>
<cons>Cons – low payvery few weekends off</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Courtesy Clerk (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Clerk”

</title><pros>Pros – Friends and family shop at these stores</pros>
<cons>Cons – No opportunities for future advancement</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Courtesy Clerk (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was a good first place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Your schedule is flexible for the most part.The store treats their employees decently.They promote from within the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They are way too serious about everything.Most of the managers are no older than 21 and/or have no education past high school.They put way too much work on their employees and don't pay nearly enough.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more relaxed in your approach. There is no reason for asking us to carry an umbrella out to the car and load the trunk of our customers for every customer.Pay more liberally.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Computer Room Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK. Great for students.”

</title><pros>Pros – Very flexible scheduling. Great for students.Possibility for advancement.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Possibility for advancement ? possibility of a raise. While you're given regular raises with performance reviews, you're not given raises when you are promoted to a new position.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Discipline employees fairly. If there is serious problem deal with it sooner rather than later.When doing performance reviews, do a salary review too.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Pharmacy Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Food City Pharmacy--a great and growing place to practice pharmacy.”

</title><pros>Pros – Food City Pharmacy offers good support overall for pharmacists and their staffs.  The pharmacy hours are excellent especially for family-oriented persons--Monday thru Friday 9:00am to 7:00pm, Saturday 9:00am to 3:00pm and closed on Sundays.  Food City is a family & employee owned company and this gives you a more "personal feel" and less of the feeling that you are just another number in a huge corporation.  There is an "open door" type atmosphere in the company and at any time you could call and talk with the companies president, if needed.  It is very nice to be known by name by senior management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pharmacy communication is challenged and inconsistent.  Supervisors are spread too thin therefore pharmacies don't get as much help, guidance and input as needed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more upper management help for pharmacy--more delegation needed--must have consistent and regular communication</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“family”

</title><pros>Pros – they are very family oreinted, and they want nothing but the best from the employee of the stores</pros>
<cons>Cons – no company benefits such as discount card for employee purchases</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Company but requires forbearance”

</title><pros>Pros – Food City offered me a chance to grow professionally and earn a good living. It is a growth company which means there is alot of opportunity for those who have the drive and stamina. The company has very strong and innovative corporate leadership that parleied strong sales growth into excellent profits which has translated into strong contributions to their ESOP program. From a compensation standpoint, it offers competitive wages, 401 company contributions, and has an excellent ESOP program company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you choose to work for Food City you should not expect to be treated has if you are a piece of china but more like a paper towel. You must have a thick skin, strong mind, and be forbearant.  It is an extremely competitive environment that demands strong work ethic from you and the staff you manage. You must demonstrate these skills with proficiently, consistently, and with authoritarian vigor. The demanding payroll requirements and other issues often created difficult, stressfull, and  demanding  working environment for hourly and salaried associates. This is why few retire from Food City and the turnover rate was high before the economy turned bad. Overall, my work life experience at Food City was stressfull and generally unpleasant. I worked there because they had the opportunties, so I did what I had to do.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The company must work to create practical ways to apply more effectly its goals to improve work life.  The corporate payroll increases (number of people employed) while % payroll demands cause staffing reductions at the store level placing stress and reducing customer service and productivlty. The stores are told to do more with less.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Day Stocker (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Place To Work”

</title><pros>Pros – Food City is a great place for anyone going to school or college because they work very well with your schedules so if you need a day off for something usually its not a problem. It was a pretty easy place to work and most of the people who worked there were really friendly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Food City is a busy place almost every holiday and weekend so expect to be working alot on weekends and every holday such as Easter, July 4th, Thanksgiving, and Christmas these are the main holidays you will be very busy around. Pay is also a downside of working here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – To management I would say that it is pretty good.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Meat Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Eh, Pays the bills, but...”

</title><pros>Pros – Good part time for studets,</pros>
<cons>Cons – It payed the bills, but that's it... Keep it at part time and try to keep very little responsibility if possible.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>