<name>The Egg and I Restaurants Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/The-Egg-and-I-Restaurants-Reviews-E324119.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-05-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Waitress (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Extremely negative environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with customers and regulars who would come in looking forward to being served by you.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the turn over rate and negativity behind the scenes. I was never given enough tables even though I could handle it. While everyone else was running around frantic with too many tables I had hardly any and would end up helping them out but only getting my own tips.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get new management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Corrupt management. Do not apply ladies...”

</title><pros>Pros – The hours are great even for managers</pros>
<cons>Cons – As a female manager you will consistently make less money then men doing the sane job even if your numbers are better. Upper management has actually told women that if they decide to get pregnant they need to plan on being induced so the restaurant can better plan for her absence. They routinely use under handed methods to remove women from management and the overall atmosphere is sexist. There is rampant sexual harassment at the store level that is consistently overlooked by the higher ups. In short keep shopping ladies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Easy money great hours but just another job leading nowhere”

</title><pros>Pros – Awesome hoursConsistent 60-100dollars a day tipsEasy</pros>
<cons>Cons – Its just another jobHard to advanceTo much work for servers compared to everyone else and they personally only pay servers 4 bucks an hour</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Usually pretty good</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>