<name>R Systems Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/R-Systems-Reviews-E32444.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-04-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Support Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Technical Support Analyst”

</title><pros>Pros – Good People - Knowledgeable about products serviced - good tiered models of support</pros>
<cons>Cons – Process/case handling needs severe improvement</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bad deal”

</title><pros>Pros – There really are none, they do not care about employees at all.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No raises for years at a time</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Work, Less Compensation, Lay Offs”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Work, Experience in Technology, Advanced Learning</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work hours, No security in job, too much pressure</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start thinking on employee benefits and loyalties the employees show to the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associated Technical Architect (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very Bad Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – when you go through a tough interview and they call you for final HR round. They made a excuse of availability of concerned person beside fix an appointment yesterday.Ridiculous company</pros>
<cons>Cons – Atleast reply to emails. very frustrating. unprofessional.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Atleast Reply to emails i</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“worst place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – can't think of anything positive</pros>
<cons>Cons – everything comes under cons only</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – throw away many  managers who don't posses even ok level managerial skills then only this company can grow.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager Technology Infrastructure (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Average company to work with”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Talented staffAverage work environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of Vision & decision making by the Senior ManagementLack of basic amenities in the work environmentImmense lack of process in the organizationPeople dependent organization rather than process driven organizationThe organization does not learn from past experiencePersonal relationship based reviews.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on business and process orientation</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer - QC (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very average place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – - Can learn technology if willing to- Good Salary negotiation possible if one possess skill in demand for a project- Few good professionals</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Did not have a good work-life balance and most of the employee had this issue- No major projects. most of the teams are small sized teams- Higher management not approachable</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - More transparency in processes- More approachable to junior members</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Big company with some good opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – Getting the kind of work you want to do is difficult</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Quality Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Midsize company with lots of potential but not the intention”

</title><pros>Pros – Helpful colleagues & ManagementFlexible timingsAppraisals are industry standard</pros>
<cons>Cons – Top management should think of new initiatives and horizonsCompany is able to identify critical resources but unable to retain themMore like semi government organization.Few senior management folks need some behavioral training specially towards female employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Kindly think of moving to some new horizons and identify the critical resources to fit them in a suitable role. Lots of resources are under utilized.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Network Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“R systems employment”

</title><pros>Pros – work culture is quite good..</pros>
<cons>Cons – salary is not enough types..and their is also a bond of 2 years..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ok”

</title><pros>Pros – flexible to employee needs (if you can get them to do it)</pros>
<cons>Cons – limited growth, lack of  vision and roadmap from senior management</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company is Good and work was also good”

</title><pros>Pros – Work is good for freshers and reasonable salary ...</pros>
<cons>Cons – For me everything was good......</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Programmer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Real Facts About R Systems”

</title><pros>Pros – - Can be in the company as a stop-gap arrangement before you find your dream job- Mediocre talent required- Ability to treat the job like timepass- you can buy time and look for better opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Worst HR department you will ever find in any IT company- Pathetic Principal Account Managers run their own 'gangs' who will give you no exposure- Only big talk and no action- No growth of the company or individuals. same turnover for the past 12 years.- You speak your mind and you are kicked out- typical family shop...racial, only punjabis are welcome :-(- If you are a serious professional your career will end dramatically. talk to existing employees before joining (i have left the company recently and God only knows what a mess i am in because of time wasted in R systems)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do something good for customers, employees and shareholders or else you will be wiped out from the industry. God only knows how you are cheating everyone and this is the reason why your customers are running away...no competency only big talk</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's a good company for IPTV domain work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly environmentTime flexibilityExcellent senior supportLocation advantage of Noida.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Loose HR policies.may be long wait time till the next opportunity or project.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Web Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bad Company - Never Join Even If you don't have job”

</title><pros>Pros – Brand Name only nothing else.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bad HR tricks and un-professional practiceBad managementNo Job securityHeavy shitty politicsImmediate termination of employeesNo personal lifeYou will put your career and your family on risk by joining this companyFake appraisal promisesNo future opportunity</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – you really need to work on bad politics going on. also need to offer employees permanent job and cut the crap of immediate termination of employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-10</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – - Flexibility- Great learning environment- Competent team members- Opportunity to innovate and face challenges- Excellent bosses</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Some people are negative who spoil the work environment- Canteen food can be improved</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up with your good work and support to all performers. Please ignore negative people and all that they say because incompetent people will always complain. I presume that is a typical Indian trait with IT professionals today.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“One of 5 PCMM level 5 company in India”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice people, more opportunities to grow...People are treated as assetTop mgt has people who are here from 15 yrs</pros>
<cons>Cons – At times teams have to do overtime to meet delivery deadlines</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Good workKeep it up</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-27</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager RMG (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good PCMM L5 Software Companay in Noida”

</title><pros>Pros – 1.Excellent Carrier Oppertunity.2.Good Onsite Exposure.3.Good Technical Enhancment.4.Good Carrier Growth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Every S\W company are working in their own limit.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-25</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent company, great learning environment”

</title><pros>Pros – - Learning environment- Challenging projects- Excellent colleagues- Some very intelligent leaders in the top management- Work Life Balance (never remember working on a Saturday)- Good management team across the world</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Some software engineers are very negative. Seems they bring their frustrations from home. Company should do something about them. They are irritating</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – We should lay more focus on innovation.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pretty OK if all you need is brand name tag, but keep your expectations low.”

</title><pros>Pros – - A brand Name- Good for freshers with no opportunities elsewhere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Growth prospects are quite low.- For attending a training session Open to all RSI employees you require your Manager's approval.- Low salaries. (Except rare cases wherein you are a urgently required.- No Criteria for Appraisals.- Depending upon your Projects requirements you might need to work for long hours and on Saturdays.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Politics seems to be a major issue in higher management.- Proper Criteria for Change in designation must be available.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Tech Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexi TimingGood Compensation if the requirement for the position is crucial otherwise average salaryGood domain to work one. Many projects are in core technologies/domain.Salary components are fixed</pros>
<cons>Cons – No Salary standard. Your salary depends on how much you  bargainNo party, no perks, no gifts. Do your work,Take your salary and go home.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – When HR is organising some events please encourage employees to participate in it instead of loading them with a lots of work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My overall experience was neutral”

</title><pros>Pros – Good onsight opportunities in r systems</pros>
<cons>Cons – Growth and pay limited pay package, small clients and projects.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Should think of developing some products for Indian Market to survive during recession time</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The worst Environment, at WORK place.”

</title><pros>Pros – Hardly any pros for this company other than Location preference for few. Onsite opportunities  for testing team.Good for those who are outwitted and cunning, as Head management recognizes and appreciates these people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Fire when they dont need with one or two days notice.Finance dept is not so cooperative (My PF transfer form is lost by them no acknowledgement for my 20 emails)Managers, Architects are totally useless. Even HR policies are worst. HR dept is worst with politics.Technical Architects pass most of time talking to females.  does not deserve to architect at allCivil Engineers become Tech Architects for Embedded division. Which obviously shows their management and its fairnessBad work life balance</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Mr Rekhi, Please shift to India and look at you management and its transparency. Please take 1:1 with engineers/staff and ask them for any issues you will come to know truly about the culture especially at Noida office.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was okay”

</title><pros>Pros – Great options for people with BE and MCA degrees right out of college.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Older culture. Very political. Not all project/account managers are good.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take care of employees. Easy to leave and go to other places.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“its an below average experience”

</title><pros>Pros – flexi hours to work at office</pros>
<cons>Cons – tough balancing work & personal life</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Architect (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't join even if you are jobless”

</title><pros>Pros – Only freshers should join this company not experienced.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Don't join even if you are jobless and having a senior profile. Rather, keep looking for some better company.They fire without any notice and compensation. There is no concept of bench here.Company does not bear even one day without billing. But in case you resign, you will have to serve full 2 months notice in any case.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If management start taking feedback seriously, then there will be a complete overhaul required. Every poicies in the company either unclear and/or not even available for employee view. HR avoid policy query over mail. They ask for in person meeting there you will not be having any proof for any confirmation later. In reality there is no HR exists. Its similar to a growcery shop job here.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associated Technical Architect (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very Bad, You may join for one year only.”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy selection criteria. If you have OK-OK knowledge about the subject, you may get through.Good parking space.Bit flexi timeAccounts dept is goodGood training started these days</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bad HR policies.Not at all employee friendly company.Long notice periodBad upper managementHire and fireBad salaryOnly designation changes, work and responsibilities do not</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do learn from good companies.Change your HR policiesThink about employees who earn money for you. They are not your servants as Mr. Baldev Singh says.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Test Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hire and Fire”

</title><pros>Pros – - nice environment - upper management is approachable</pros>
<cons>Cons – - hire and fire - very few onsite oppurtunities - bad work culture - Managers only listen to clients not concerned about off shore team</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide security and stability to the employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“awesome for freshers”

</title><pros>Pros – gud workenough to learn for fresher</pros>
<cons>Cons – nothing in terms of corporate culture</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Testing Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“it was wonderful experience”

</title><pros>Pros – provide good opportunities for mutual growth</pros>
<cons>Cons – very few offices across the india.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – company has potential for a vast growth .</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Engine Room for Creating Hell for its employees”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. I don't think I have any reasons to work at R Systems other than that I got peanuts for working long hours and getting company $$$$$$$'s.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Pathetic Management (Senior Management + Project Managers)2. Bad Culture of asking and making employee sit late3. Incompetent Project Managers. Company has promoted guys to PM and Sr.PM just on the basis of their service in company. Based on my 4 year experience in company, RSI PM are worst PM's I have seen in my 8 years experience.4. Apalling HR and its policies. Guess, all office got two mails from HR head for same subject.One with original content and second with corrections in previous mail.5. Apalling Notice period policies. RSI makes policies that benefit it. Just this year, RSI made 3 month notice period. It comes with a rider, if you leave comapny before 3 months, you pay 3 months basic salary. But, in between if company ask you to leave before 3 months, it pays nothing.6. Vindictive attitude of all senior management. Guess a principal account manager and now a Vice President of RSI shouting at an employee and using abusive language in hindi. No need to tell what common hindi abusive language is. Management comes with a vendetta if any one dares to point the short comings or oppose wrong doing.7. Pay package may be good but keep in mind, you will loose your personal life by spending almost 12-14 hours daily.8. My response to good reviews - these seem to be given by HR and resourcing guys to lure people looking to join RSI as an employer. BEWARE OF THE HELL GUYS!!!9. No transport - I remember few of employees being robbed when returning late after attending client calls and giving IPR to client. When a mail was circulated about one of employee, team meeting was called by the team PM and reprimanded the whole team. He(PM) also gave excuses on behalf of company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would suggest following action points to turnaround the image of RSI as an hell to work in/for:1. Get competent project managers who know how to make a team and get work out of it and not think only of getting revenue for company at the cost of employee life.2. DO turnaround things for HR policies. You have worst HR policies.3. Respect employee personal life. Give some breathing space to enjoy life rather than thinking of making profits.4. Don't ask for employee feedback ONLY in open house sessions. Get out in the mud and find what plagues the employees the most. Dear company president, being a former army officer it's not too hard for you to get to the root cause of people negative image of RSI.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review as a Project leader”

</title><pros>Pros – No Timing issuesCan do Work from HomeGood Parking areaAccount department is too goodGood locationGood seating space</pros>
<cons>Cons – Notice period issueBad HR policiesBad client relationshipVery less onsite chancesNo recogzination of workLess support from management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Must be employee friendlyApply employee first policyDo some recogzination to employeesprefer the employees rather than lateral hire</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good place to work but not very good”

</title><pros>Pros – good compensation empowerment salary as per market good work atmosphere employee friendly trust respect earned flexible work timings work timing as per requirement</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad employee behaviour, faulty hr and admin policies parking a big problem crowded canteen bad management bossism favored no group parties</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – listen to the employees boost the morale of the employees reduce attrition rate employee parties must be organized better work conditions are required</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bad work culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Not bad infrastructureSpacious, sometimes overcrowded cafeteriaGood locationNice support from accounts and other support departmentsFlexible timings, if you are able to make your manager happy anyhow</pros>
<cons>Cons – 2 months must serve notice periodBad managementPathetic admin and HR policiesNo job security, no notice period for firingNo recognitionPoor seat spacingFight in parking spaceLess cultured employeesNo motivation, no parties, very rare team outing - once in 2-3 years</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employees are assets for any company, respect them and recognise their opinion instead of shouting in open house as associates, and still making their life hell by thousand of reasons. Anyway, you already earned a very poor name for yourself.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>