<name>Thomas P. Gohagan and Company Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Thomas-P-Gohagan-and-Company-Reviews-E328979.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2010-06-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“TPG”

</title><pros>Pros – A pay check every two weekshealth and dental insurance401k non-matchingSet scheduleVacation daysPersonal DaysPaid Holidays</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of InnovationOut dated business practicesTop down management styleLack of confidence in making a final decision from managementMicro-Managed Company</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop using paper memos when there is emailGet rid of approach its cut into job performance when the system crashes two or more times a dayYour employees are not grateful to work for you, You should be grateful we know how to keep the company runningListen to ideas when expressedStop selling travel only to senior citizens (Nothing wrong with seniors its just you put the company at risk if you only cater to one demographic, also your employees truly lose out in not having competitive skills)</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Program Operation Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pure false demonstration resources, Stone Age”

</title><pros>Pros – Salarie -- a ck every two weeks, 401 non matching, Time set schedule. Fringe benefits. Health / Dental plan insurance. Vacation time. Personal time. Paid Holidays.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Only be marketed to the senior population. Little variety of excursions. Their lack of active interest tours Employees lack team building Management is deaf before better environment needs lack of respect for administrative management Not considered other markets or develop new markets Marked lack of variety Managerial conformism</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – find new markets within breed diversity. never rule out developing new destinations more tours for youth market be innovative</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working with the Dinosaurs...”

</title><pros>Pros – paychecktypically active social crew (turnover was so high, sometimes there were fun people to commiserate with for happy hour, sometimes not so much!)paycheck</pros>
<cons>Cons – archaic practices- computer system, constantly crashing, never updates operating systems & software.Absolutely no room for growth unless you've been there for 20 years and even then its not guaranteedTop down management style</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Bring your computer system to this era!Allow growth & new ideas from employees!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tour Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The worst job experience”

</title><pros>Pros – a pay checkholiday paysick days</pros>
<cons>Cons – a huge revolving doorlack of communicationgloomy work environment</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Innovation...employe empowerment...changing with the times...instilling a robust corporate culture..etc.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>