<name>J-PAL Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/J-PAL-Reviews-E329669.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Surprisingly entrepreneurial, need to have people/project management skills beforehand”

</title><pros>Pros – - Very interesting work in India. Due to the professors' stature and connections, you can get access to some top policymakers, and the project results have a better chance of being implemented than many other NGOs.- Work with top-notch professors, get stellar recommendations if you do well. Almost everyone gets into a top grad school in economics or policy (masters or PhD)- Work and lifestyle is fairly entrepreneurial -- you manage your own time, and often a team of staff. Should have some people management skills (and like managing people) to do well in JPAL, even though it attracts aspiring PhDs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Support and directions could be weak because professors are far away, but JPAL has beefed up its project management structure in the recent 2 years. Hence, there are now more senior managers than before to oversee the young RAs and help them deal with management problems.- Choose professor carefully, not necessarily project -- not all JPAL professors are equal in terms of the strength of recommendation at different schools and how willing they are to write great ones. I would focus on choosing the right professor (and do some groundwork and who's good to work with) instead of the most interesting project area.- Non-Indian origin RAs are no longer hired due to change in work visa policies -- very sad!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Intern”

</title><pros>Pros – Development projects and econometrics, grad school opps</pros>
<cons>Cons – Development projects take a long time to finish!</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pretty good for getting into grad school”

</title><pros>Pros – Strong network of professors and great group of RAs</pros>
<cons>Cons – Terrible disorganization, experience depends on PI</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Research Associate”

</title><pros>Pros – Work with phenomenal academic researchers/Experience to observe how randomized evaluations are done/Data Analysis/Great letters of recommendation for graduate schoolsIt really depends what you want to get out of the job position.  There is room for enough growth as a researcher. You end up learning how to handle pressure.  You get to enhance your management skills.  You also get an opportunity to decide whether you really want to devote the rest of your life doing randomized evaluations.  If you want to be in academia or want to pursue development as a major field of your study, I would strongly recommend gaining at least a year long experience with JPAL.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inadequate salary by global standards (if you work in a developing country)/ Stressful job - need to work even in the weekendsAlthough pros clearly outweigh cons, you should be mentally prepared that this is not going to be a standard 8:30-5 job.  Honestly, because you are surrounded my fellow JPAL employees (depending upon where are based out of), you get used to the culture of the organization. Plus, while socializing with your fellow colleagues, you end up learning a lot.  Be prepared that you will be working all the time, literally.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More structure needed. Lack of transparency on what the position actually entails.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The best social science research experience. But no place to move up.”

</title><pros>Pros – Direct contact with researhc community in the US.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is no place to grow within the institute.</cons>
<advice-to-management> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Low pay, high brand but above all great experience - for a time.”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Poverty concerns all of us. Understanding it is rewarding in an intellectual and moral sense.2. Great professors, brand. Useful for those who want a recommendation for PhD/MPP admission.3. Great managerial position with enough scope for on-the-spot thinking and learning.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Low pay. This is the flip-side of pro #2.2. Low focus on intellectual value-add - focus is to get the data for the profs. One can start feeling like an automaton soon.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More two-way feedback sessions - even if associates' suggestions are ignored - may lead to morale boost.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Career Launch-Pad, and much more.”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting projects, research opportunities, learning new stuff, academic environment, talented colleagues and superiors</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not anything serious in particular. People deciding to work for J-PAL are motivated enough to bother less about the traveling part, or relatively low compensation as compared to private sector companies.Work-life balance does take a hit, but as majority of researchers are bachelors looking for some experience before enrolling in a university, it doesn't really matter.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting research and management opportunities in the first 3 months, after that you feel under-paid and over-worked.”

</title><pros>Pros – Prestige of the organization and its MIT and Harvard connectionsRecommendations from top professorsWorking with the brightest minds in Economic DevelopmentInteresting work - at firstOpportunities to live abroad</pros>
<cons>Cons – Truly under-paid and over-over workedNo appreciation for any personal time you may want, thought taking vacations (if you find the money) don't seem to be a problemManagement is very poorTraining is horrendous and unhelpfulYou're pretty much expected to enter a PhD program after a year, max 2, and there is little other room for advancement</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Develop and prepare your training -- remember you're generally sending 21 year olds into very remote areas and they made need some guidance on that.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-02</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very difficult, demanding, and isolating.”

</title><pros>Pros – There will never be another time in most J-PAL employees' lives when they can live in the field, with nothing else in their lives except helping to impliment programs that could potentially make a difference in needy people's lives.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is a reason why people do not do this for their entire life.  The organization requires constant work, gives little feedback and largely leaves RA's alone to fend for themselves, except when in emergencies it sends more senior staff to babysit them.  There is no work life balance and very little contact with research.  It is a lot of busy work, and I feel that many new comers are not accustomed to this kind of work.  The salaries, benefits and balance aren't good enough to encourage more mature applicants.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would suggest that the ogranization move away from the model of trusting early 20-somethings with all of these evaluations in difficult cultural settings.  It is insensitive to the cultures and very hard on the RA's.  I would wish that they would be more upfront about the demands and what the job actually implied.  By and large, it is not economic research.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“J-PAL”

</title><pros>Pros – Great independent project management experience, opportunities to work for top development economists</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours/no weekends during busy periods, can be difficult to take vacation time, little support/feedback from supervisors</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Devote more time to proper planning of projects, work with RAs to identify and solve problems sooner rather than later, spend more time in the field understanding real field problems</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>