<name>Mr X Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Mr-X-Reviews-E332560.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2011-11-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Post Production (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A very mixed experience, good projects but an old school harsh management style.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good projects, variety of work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Harsh and critical management, little positive feedback, only negativeMr X has sometimes averaged almost a 50% per year employee turnover, excessive even in this industry.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Unless this studio changes it's work culture, it will remain on the B-team. Mr X could be a better studio and a bigger studio, but historically has not been able to hold on to core talent. To get to the next level, Mr X needs to reinvent itself.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Lead (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“MrX : Good... if you can stand the heat.”

</title><pros>Pros – - Good people trying their hardest made for a good team vibe.- Fun projects if you like horror movies.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - People crying in the studio on a weekly basis is not good for moral.- Despite constant growth, there is a very high turn around of employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take it easy on the artists! Everyone wants to help, it could be a really great studio with just some small tweaks.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Compositor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“the good the bad”

</title><pros>Pros – - you got paid- you got vacation days- you got sick days</pros>
<cons>Cons – - lots of politic involved- lots of backstabbing among employers- long hours + beyond (no after hours pay)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try appreciate and balance out what employers did. After all it's the artists that actually did the works.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>