<name>American Recovery Service Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/American-Recovery-Service-Reviews-E333013.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-07-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Frivolous, Tedious”

</title><pros>Pros – The company does make efforts to give back to its employees with dress-down periods each quarter, raffles for fairly large prizes, and recognition for great work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The typical position at this company is very monotonous, where one who loves to learn and develop new skills constantly would have a difficult time.  Most positions are also very sedentary.  To avoid getting migraines or severe headaches from staring at a computer for 8 hours per day, I would take brisk walks during my lunch time rather than eating lunch.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It seems that employees may find their work more rewarding if they weren't so regulated as to what they did and how they did it.  Not every employee will function exactly the same way, so some may struggle with some methods while others thrive on the same methods.  I suggest a little more variety in tasks overall for every employee.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-02</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>No Way (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working at Mcdonalds > working here.”

</title><pros>Pros – When they feel like it, management will rarely give out bonuses for our work even though we deserve them every month. They have activities sometimes to boost spirit.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management doesn't care about it's employees. As long as they're making money, they're happy. They constantly lie to the company about how we don't hit our goal, but then they tell us that we are doing really well and better than ever. They've also turned the place into a dictatorship where everyone is afraid to sneeze without getting in trouble with the COO. I could list cons all day but I'll stop here. Oh and the pay is terrible so plan on never getting a raise and making the same amount after years of working there.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay your employees. Respect your employees. Don't reward the bad employees and punish the good ones.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>