<name>eMeter Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/eMeter-Reviews-E33459.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-03-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Services Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Managed Chaos”

</title><pros>Pros – Good industry, highly technical, environmentally positive products</pros>
<cons>Cons – Rarely intellectually stimulating, lacking in community</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Better integration with customers and Siemens</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Spinning plates and watching your back”

</title><pros>Pros – Owned by Siemens.  Some well respected industry leaders (Larsh J and Chris King).</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inability to deliver product due to lack of foresight into development constraint and making unrealistic promises to customers.Senior executives ( excluding co founders) who are out for themselves only, and have no commitment to stay in the space or leadership drive for developing employees' careers.  This includes the current President, the former CEO, most anyone with a VP title.A culture if it can be called that of intrigue, favoritism, back stabbing, and every man for himself.MDM is not a platform with any huge growth prospects.Very high turnover in the engineering and development arena.Lack of product management expertise in Utility processes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Shuffle the legacy EMeter executive and sales team, and focus on product development and smart grid business processes consulting.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hectic, but for a good cause”

</title><pros>Pros – The industry is a little peculiar - heavily regulated utilities that move pretty slow - but reducing global electric/gas/water consumption is a great cause and it's global in scope.  The past year has been a good transition to a more focused development roadmap, allowing us to hit our objectives.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Team is overloaded with work and has been on overdrive for too long.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do a more realistic resource analysis</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“eMeter, and the Smart Grid: Now firing on all cylinders!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – The market is finally heating up for Smart Grid (rather than the mere talk by the government and analysts we've had to endure for years).  The execs at eMeter represent a crazy amount of experience/wisdom with respect to the energy industry.  The Board has rounded out that experience with the talents of some Engineering, Product, Sales and Marketing sharp-shooters, and I *really* feel we're poised for serious growth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 2009 was a year of transition for eMeter (and for the Smart Grid, in general).  If you've been in the Valley long enough, you've experienced the 'Year of Puberty' each young company must face: the somewhat challenging transition from a small group of heroes to a larger organization with more predictability.  We're on the tail end of that transition.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the spirit of the 'start-up' while making the necessary organizational improvements.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Emeter a start up with start up expectations.”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with new technology, knowing what you do contributes to less energy being used and therefore is helping the environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – No raises, bonuses for any overtime or hard work done.  I felt that the development team lived in the office at one point.I wore multiple hats when I worked here.  Even when I found ways to save money for the company I was never given a raise or title change to reflect new responsiblities I willing accepted.  Everyone was salaried when I worked there and overtime was required and expected without comp time.  This is typically of start-ups where as an employee you agree to no longer have a life outside of work.Management was similar to a teenage clique.  By far the worst management I have had in my 20 + years as an employee.  The managers had no problem gossiping about people in the office when they were not there to defend themselves.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try engaging with your employees.  Reward them when they do a job well done and help them do the job better when they don't preform well.  Being in the office is part of a manager's job.  Try being in the office 5 days a week like your employees do.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Prefer Not to State (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“tread with care”

</title><pros>Pros – promising technology and decent pay for a start-up.</pros>
<cons>Cons – overwork. dishonest accounting. gossip and back-biting. also, while I was there, I personally witnessed a manager lie to get rid of a new employee simply because the manager (who was otherwise very capable) felt threatened by the employee's ability. therefore I would not recommend working for e-Meter if you are extremely talented, unless you are adept at office politics and have good friends higher up in the company who can protect  you from this type of abuse.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – listen to everyone, not just your back-scratchers. make sure that everyone is treated fairly and rewarded accordingly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unique Management”

</title><pros>Pros – No work (for those who don't want to work), you can complete your daily work in just 2 hrs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor management, the management is highly biased. People are not good, poor culture, nobody is interested in sharing product information. Technical/Project manager are not technically sound and are not open to adopt/listen new ideas. Managers get special attention and HR get super attention. Tea and snacks are served into their rooms. No team building activities, never seen any thoughtful programs in the company on festivals.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat all employees equally, give all employee equal rights.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Diminishing and Marginal utility”

</title><pros>Pros – Insanely generous compensation and benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – Disconnected management ,  Most people seemed Bored , Laid back and Frustrated, Overstaffed teams and Over Engineered products</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't rest on past achievements, Concentrate on adding value for customers and shareholders, Do a reality check with employees ,Encourage and reward professionlism , Cultivate a culture of openness and excellence</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very good atmosphere”

</title><pros>Pros – Helpful teammates, Understanding boss, Nice Learning opportunity</pros>
<cons>Cons – Workload high, can't think of anything else</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Could offer better salary</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good compensation and benefits. Company has some good core employees with good domain and technical knowledge.Acquired by Siemens.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A high level of unsatisfaction in core employees.Management always promotes their Favorited candidates in every appreciation.A common reply from management that If you are not feeling good here then why you are here. which is demotivating employees here.Work assignment is highly biased.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please do a fair survey to know the reality of eMeter India without including  eMeter India management in it.Company is continuously loosing their core employees . This may be a huge loss for the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lead Software”

</title><pros>Pros – Technology oriented company and a lot to explore</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work life balance but Technology oriented company and a lot to explore</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Darwinian culture in an otherwise ok company”

</title><pros>Pros – - Utility domain is still "cool".- The technology is interesting, but not cutting edge. The functionality is pretty straight-forward and easy to learn.- Very dynamic, lots of different projects in parallel.- Some knowledgeable people.- If you are a young professional, tap your nose for the politics and learn as much as you can, then leave for something better.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Small company, thinks small, acts small. Short-sighted.- In general employees are seen as a liability to be disposed at the first chance, rather than an asset to be developed and kept long term. A good performance may not be enough, as one needs to be outstanding and watch out for the politics.  One day everything is good and the next day there is a termination letter in your inbox.- High management is a little boys club, that promotes politics, gossips, backstabbing, etc. If you are in, good for you, if not watch your back. Since its a small company they fire people on a snap  without a fair process and HR is mute for that matter. If they don't have a fair case against the employee, no big deal as they can and will make one up.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No advices as there is no desire to change or improve anything. The sick environment was designed to be that way. So keep up the good job!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Special treatment for Managers in Noida”

</title><pros>Pros – Integration with Siemens may bring in some vigilance by Siemens and it may expose the faces of the tyrants and their politics.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible culture. Never seen such a work environment.Managers have have the luxury - they have dedicated office boys to serve them tea coffee water. They have access to diet cokes kept in the refrigerator. Imagine you are sitting in a meeting and the office boy gets tea/coffee just for 1 person, who happens to be your Manager.While all the employees get chairs that are ordinary ones, the managers get special chairs that cost at least 10 times more. Why should only a few people get such special treatment. Are they from a different planet.Employees have started quitting the organisation at a rapid pace.People obey to the instructions of the manager not because that makes sense, but because either you don't have a choice or to keep the boss happy.Unfortunately , the higher management from US is also supporting this culture very strongly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The India management should themselves be ashamed of what they are doing and should correct themselves before they get a kicked out. Siemens management should start looking into why employees have started leaving . Blindly shifting work</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Over all good experience in Learning.”

</title><pros>Pros – Will get chance to work on good technologies and also get build Energy Utilities Domain knowledge. Will get good salary package, provided you are good at negotations.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much Politics inside companies. Senior employees will not allow the juniors one to grow.Even HR are not sometimes keen interest in employees suggestions/ problems.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Tries to see each employees with same eye.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Incapable, pathetic and highly dishonest management in India.”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart Grid Domain and related areas.Recently Siemens has acquired the company so it may have some positive impact.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The local management is pathetic and hopeless.They have absolutely no clue of how to manage technical people.Politics is their weapon to deal with any issue related to people.There is no one in the management who is accountable for anything.HR is being handled mostly by someone who is just out of college.The management feels that hiding truth and misguiding people is the best way to bury the issues.A clear lack of experience in doing any kind of management is highly visible in all aspects of work.Most of the decisions are taken by gut feeling or by how they were managed by their bosses in the past.The folks at Head Office have a blind trust on the local management or they don't care about anything related to India as long as work is getting done. The truth is that work is getting done just because of few key employees.The local management is under the illusion that they are good payers. Good pay is a relative term, unless you compete with all the companies around you in product space you cannot decide where you stand. But no one can prevent you from boasting what is not true.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Wake up !!! Hire the right set of people at the management and mid management level in India office.Fire the people who are a misfit.Do a background check before you hire employees.Get some honest surveys done to asses the actual state of affairs in India office.Pay is not the only thing that can keep the employee motivated. Educated people need respect and good work culture around themselves so that they can stick around in the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Technical Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good developers and bad Management”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Satisfactory Salary2. Good colleagues</pros>
<cons>Cons – Senior Management is not capable to take fair decisions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to review the decisions of senior india management.Due to some of their partial decisions, some good employees are planning to leave the company. This is very bad thing for a good company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>6</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible Management, Unprofessional Managers”

</title><pros>Pros – Work life balance, compensation, Office location, team members, new and upcoming domain of Meter data management and smart metering/smart grid</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unprofessional and incapable Senior Management, No growth prospects, No vision for the company and employees, biased feedback and reviews, no linkage between salary hike and performance, Flattery is promoted in the company, Lots of dirty politics. The management in India is doing all the wrong things. They are using unfair means to serve their personal interest with the company money.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Fire all the managers of India office and you can see increase in satisfaction and productivity from employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The local management  has destroyed the professional culture of the office to safeguard their selfish interests.”

</title><pros>Pros – The domain of the smart grid.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You would rarely find so much of unprofessional and incapable senior folks in any IT product company.The managers of India lacks communication skills.Instead of improving upon the mistakes, they take pride in taking wrong steps.They are very good at politics and hiding information, telling different stories about an issue to different employees.When the managers cannot automatically get respect from the rest of employees, what would they do ? Neither the management trusts the employees, nor the employees trust the management.Never seen so much of politics in such a small company.May be the company wants it's employees to quit hence they are just silent on this issue.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Replace the local management with good leaders who understand their job and are able to manage the teams working in the office. Identify the talented folks and not the folks who just do lip service.Get some better leadership from Siemen's pool of talent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>6</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A product company being run like a typical Indian IT Services Company.”

</title><pros>Pros – One of the few companies in Delhi region that work in MDM and smart grid space. If lucky you can a chance to work with some thought leaders from smart grid space.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is like a dictatorship between management and the employees. If you like working for a dictator, you will enjoy this place.The env. is that because you get a salary, you are expected not to question any decisions that are made by the management. You should just follow them.Promotions, designations and pay hikes are not at all related to the contributions of the employee.It is being run no different than a typical Indian services compnay and not like a MNC product company .</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stake holders should try to find the root cause of the issues and address them or else be prepared to loose the employees.In India , the 2 major factors that cause the employees to leave are  a) they are managed badly. b) they are not rewarded for their work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“eMeter's got great positive momentum!”

</title><pros>Pros – The leadership at eMeter has changed drastically recently.  The new CEO, Gary Bloom, is taking a very hands-on approach to making things better at the company.  Not only is he creating an environment of openness and fairness, he's also taking a active role in making sure that the culture within the company changes for the better.The industry is hot right now, and so is eMeter. The company and team have been getting an incredible amount of positive coverage in the news and our alliance partners are sending more and more business our way. It's definitely a great place to be working now!</pros>
<cons>Cons – As at any company in transition, there are the normal bumps in the road when it comes to things like "where do I find this..." or "do we have a...?" There are great opportunities for improvement and the upside is that there are people rolling up their sleeves all over the organization to make it happen.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the lines of communication open, and share more positive news with the whole company. Continue to work on getting more structured process in place, too.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Growing Company, Getting Better!”

</title><pros>Pros – The product is technically relevant and the industry that they address is growing rapidly!  Management is very competant and experienced.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sales seem to be difficult to come by.  No plan in place to stimulate sales.  I never felt that the HR group was committed or very concerned about employees and there seemed to be a great deal of weight placed on the opinions of the HR group even though that group did not have a substantial amt of utility interface or experience.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Communicate throughout the organization more.  Employees want to know what is going on!  This is on an upward trend at eMeter.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>