<name>Atkinson Construction Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Atkinson-Construction-Reviews-E340252.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tunnel Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tunnel Engineer”

</title><pros>Pros – Takes care of employees and cares for their future.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Back log is dwindling. Not a lot of variety in the project types.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wonderful”

</title><pros>Pros – The people there are so nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The people there can be boring</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Field Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lack of direct guidance leaves a lot of room for autonomy.”

</title><pros>Pros – I had a lot of room to tackle problems on my own.Sink or Swim atmosphere.Unique work environment (underground excavation)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of specific job descriptions.Geographically unstable - always moving around the country.Uncertain promotion opportunities.long, hard hours</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Subcontractor Administrator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great learning experience but poor management in the office.”

</title><pros>Pros – The department will train someone with little or no experience so it a great place to get exposed to the accounting side of construction. I don't have any experience working on the job site.  Flexible schedule.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor management in the business department.  You have to do a lot of over time just to barely keep up with the workload.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Seek the opinions and concerns of employees during yearly reviews, such as implementing a 360 degree review.  Change some people in management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineering Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Strong team environment with excellent opportunites to grow professionally”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly and energetic teamFast-paced, challenging work schedule</pros>
<cons>Cons – No set intern schedule of work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Excellent opportunities given to a young engineer in training! Thank you!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Safety Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“What you see it what you get”

</title><pros>Pros – Great field relationships and positives challenges.</pros>
<cons>Cons – lack of involvement from higher ups, long hours which equates to low pay.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't over promise and never follow through.  In addition, stop bringing in people and paying them substantially more than what you are paying people with more experience within the company.  The reason there is higher turnover is because they cut deals with some people and then deny perks to individuals that have earned them.  I left on good terms, and would be glad to cross paths again with a lot of the safety personnel, but when you don't provide the opportunities to better your life professionally and personally, then do not expect people to wreck their own life to keep a project level job where you work 12-15 hour days, and perform overhead work on the weekendsthat is delegated on you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>