<name>HeyMath! Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/HeyMath-Reviews-E341902.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-01-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Summer Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was full of insights and collaboration.”

</title><pros>Pros – Very affable environment, Transparency in the system, proper recognition to good work, good compensation, extremely good location of the office, very convenient and flexible working hours.</pros>
<cons>Cons – during my brief stay as a summer intern I couldn't find any cons at heymath! but if asked to put one I would say that there is a possibility that one may get tired of monotonous work pattern at times.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I believe right now the company is small in size but is growing at a phenomenal pace. I experienced a very  satisfactory level of transparency as well as well as conducive environment, it would be a real challenge to maintain it when the company grows in size.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You can learn the work but very less opportunities for growth”

</title><pros>Pros – The company structure is flat. You can easily reach to the top management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No promotions. Standard salary hikes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Salaries are not everything. But they are important.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager - Human Resources (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very enterprising product & good work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Potential of the product developed is huge & good mix of employee talent</pros>
<cons>Cons – Needs more streamlining of process & decision making</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>