<name>Neal R. Gross & Company Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Neal-R-Gross-and-Company-Reviews-E342221.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-01-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“conscientious employer with good benefits, excellent staff and great work environment/location”

</title><pros>Pros – The staff here is excellent.  Intelligent people with great attitude and hard working demeanor.  Compensation is good and there are opportunities for career advancement.  There are also retirement benefits and company matching as well as excellent health care coverage.  The main office HQ is located in a great and very accessible part of DC.  Certain positions offer opportunity for travel both in the US and abroad.  Hours are fair and most employees are not expected to work overtime (except for rare instances).  Upper management is understanding and accessible/available at all times (unlike at many other companies).  Employees are not micromanaged and given responsibility once they've proved their competence.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Expectations for work performance are high but in-line with other high-performing companies that I've worked at.  Work load is cyclical with the nature of the business so sometimes you are totally slammed and sometimes you have a lighter load.  Company culture could be stronger (i.e. more after-work events, team building exercises etc--though sometimes it's hard to get current employees to partake in events when they are happening).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to be accessible and available to the employees.  Continue to encourage employees to grow and take on more responsibility both within their position and within the company.  Continue to provide and add employee benefits.  Create a better review process both in regards to compensation and also actual work performance.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Court Reporter (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Long hours with little opportunity for advancement”

</title><pros>Pros – The work done as a court reporter is not very challenging at all - simply go to a location, record people saying things, and then deliver the results back to the company.  In addition, you will get the opportunity to visit a number of courts, government agencies, and private companies in the DC area.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The atmosphere at the company was unpleasant, verging sometimes on unprofessional.  Management didn't get along, shouted arguments were common, and employees rarely got the opportunity to interact with one another.Though you'll be around other people while you're visiting various agencies and courtrooms, they will view you strictly as a functionary who should be ignored and not interacted with.  Don't expect to form any personal or professional relationships with the people you'll see on a daily basis.There's essentially no room for advancement - once you start as a court reporter, that's your job.  There was a considerable amount of turnover given how displeased some of my colleagues were with their positions once they realized what it was like.Finally, the hours of the job are very unpredictable.  While you may be finished with one day by 3 p.m., another might take you until 11 p.m. - and the latter is much more common than the former.  You'll be hard-pressed to find any time to manage a personal life in this position.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Court Reporter (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you're flexible, don't need a lot of positive reinforcement, and like having intelligent coworkers, it's a good fit.”

</title><pros>Pros – Coworkers tend to be very intelligent, compensation is high for a job with so few entry requirements (need any undergrad degree and to pass a difficult verbal intelligence test), easy to get unpaid time off with little notice, workload tends to be cyclical with the rest of D.C., e.g. August and the holiday season have a light workload, employees are salaried rather than hourly, some work travel</pros>
<cons>Cons – Zero opportunity for advancement, no retirement matching, start with five paid vacation days a year, management varies between semi-benevolent disinterest and absurd demands of perfection varying with the moods of the managers, management by memo whenever someone makes a mistake, hours vary wildly with usually one day's notice and include evenings, overtime is uncompensated for employees (but employer charges clients for overtime anyway), pricing of services to clients is purposefully obscured so employees won't realize how little they are paid relative to company income, little to no praise for good work, as one coworker puts it, "if you don't hear anything from management, you are doing a fantastic job"</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't be afraid of telling your very intelligent employees more about how the business operates.  They already know they're getting soaked.  Own up to it and explain where the rest of money goes if it's a legit expense, or tell them you just want it all for yourself.  To retain employees, institute better benefits for employees or up their pay if it's too much of a hassle to set that up.  Compensate overtime, either with more pay or more vacation time.   Improve assignment notification by giving out information earlier when you have it and using e-mail for employees who have been around long enough that you don't need to check in with them all the time.  Try to remember that just because you're angry doesn't mean your employees deserve to be yelled at for errors that normally don't even get mentioned.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>