<name>Z Line Designs Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Z-Line-Designs-Reviews-E357621.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2010-11-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Big dollars, small heart.”

</title><pros>Pros – Small company with diverse, good people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company is not young it is over 10 years old.  Confidence and communication is lacking.  There are no corporate goals, mission statement. There are no cross functional meetings. No periodic staff meetings (Monthly, quarterly, or annual) This makes it hard for employees to see their contribution and therefore they lack motivation to strive for goals because there is no 'vision'.  Does not promote bottom up input/ideas.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get continued education.  Allow staff to take CE courses to gain confidence, professional knowledge and to broaden their professional experience since upward mobility is virtually impossible.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“One of the WORST places that I have ever worked!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – The hours are set so there is no work to take home and you know what time you will get off of work so if you have another job or family obligations you are sure to be on time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The management is simply terrible!!! They do not support their employees, back them up, or support them! They throw them under the bus every chance that they get with customers, other employees, higher level management, etc. They also cover up issues (i.e. harassment in the work place). There is also no availability for promotion in the company. If anything they demote their personnel. It is overall a very TOXIC environment to work in and I would not recommend it to anyone!!!! No one has that thick of skin!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be kinder to your employees! Listen to them and resolve issues when they arise! Be pro-active and not re-active when under fire. Take action when a problem arises and do not brush it under the rug or try to blow it off.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>