<name>Toys R Us (UK) Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Toys-R-Us-UK-Reviews-E36320.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-05-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun job”

</title><pros>Pros – It was fun helping everyone out, customers, children and all.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management could use a little help, they are not running a tight ship</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hard work with little reward and praise”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly staff, discount .Customer interaction.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Highly political culture, not much positive feedback.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to praise hard work and performance manage those who do not do a good job.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Culture & Environment”

</title><pros>Pros – New office, can see the culture changing to keep up with the times, people are friendly and a creation of family culture. New CEO or MD awesome, a real people's person.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Reactive (but slow) rather than pro active due to nature of American business. Poor rates of pay. Long and inflexible hours with little reward.Limited opportunity to develop career.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more generous in compensation from stores to office. Be more supportive in people development and change the way senior directors go about the business. Times have changed and so should those at the top sooner rather than later if the business is to turn around.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Advisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Alright overall”

</title><pros>Pros – As a company they are alright, lovely people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They arn't the same company i first started working for.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Being "Old school" sometimes doesn't work False Promises AVOID”

</title><pros>Pros – Leadership at regional and higher levels is generally good, friendly and approachable.Although minimum pay you have some real good staff shame you can't keep themPay for managers is dependent on experience but is good if you worked your contract only.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Where do i start. When you view the website you get a impression that Toys T Us is a very professional company with excellent career options including "fast track programs"So you were fooled by this and decided to go for a interview ? Like myself hahaThe interview i had was with a regional manager and a directer ( very easy ) here everything seemed genuine and i got a real sense that this was going to be a great company to work for, how wrong could i be.-Working hours vary between stores and vary between a minimum of 45 but often this is 50 plus(this does not include travel time to work )This changes in October till January or if ever a visit is to happen this increases to easily 70-80 hours don't be surprised on the rota. ( by the way no holidays between October and January are allowed. )Callouts every managers worst nightmare. ( no extra pay for your time which can sometimes exceed 3-4 hours waiting for a engineer to come and reset a alarm that has gone off )-Progression is pretty much non existent so forget that fast track option you saw on the website the reality is most stores have had the same GSM for years, promotion is based on how many hours you are prepared to give up and trust me lots do i knew some managers that had been working for the company for over 4 years and they are still waiting despite performing very well in there job.Working Conditions= Back in time i am sure the stores had that magic look now most stores are very dated around ( 60 - 70 percent ) technology is also back in the 80s if you have worked in other retail company's this will come as a shock at how basic and shocking it is.NO STAFF= This is possibly due to the recession but with so many cut backs in staff as a manager pretty much everyday it is just you and a supervisor. with one member of staff!!!! Expectations are always going to be high in retail but to deliver this you need staff !!Overall Avoid this company at all costs and look for a bigger more successful company where the job description actually lives up to the promise.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 1=Act on the above, look after your staff better and hire more. Maybe more will stay and turnover will surely decrease and will stop managers/staff looking for better options. You could be Great.2= This is just a review based on my opinion but for all those who disagree please take a look at Toys R us Facebook page for the UK so so many complaints as a previous manager i am ashamed to say i worked for the company.3= Undercover boss would be great for you give them a call</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>ECommerce Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Good team of people”

</title><pros>Pros – SizePeople/ColleaguesThis was the most balanced job i have had to date.  Resources to do things, if you can justify it, decent size of people to do the work but you don't get lost and can make a difference.</pros>
<cons>Cons – old fashioned cultureupward communication to board levelsupplier managementFriendly CEO but not being a direct report communication was something that can down from above and wasn't open to two way communication.  You may also suffer to get consistency and support from senior managers, who are personable but seem to respond to events and can cause uncertainty.  Their approach to developing supplier relationships, at least where i worked, was highly problematic.That said it was on balance a good company to work for.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was ok”

</title><pros>Pros – Discount on toys 10 % payed every two weeks. Clean nice staff. Managers were ok. Mostly some were very friendly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not enough hours. Very busy seasons. Not enough staff. Not payer enough. Sometimes I needed to go to the bathroom and I couldn't because of no toilet paper.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire more staff keep a more clean bathroom its disgusting. Accept sic so cu stomers wont complain. Make pay higher</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Department Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A company that does not treat junior management well”

</title><pros>Pros – -A big company-Good products to work with-'In it together' atmosphere-Running a toy shop for kids never gets old.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -No extra store management recruited at Christmas despite shop assistants tripled.-Poor staff discount.-Vastly excessive hours: 6 days a week 12 hour days from October to January.-No real recognition on good department sales.-Expects results to be the same whatever the resources when practically it isn't possible.-No store security: spent a lot of time dealing with shop leaders.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Look after your store managers better.  8 managers working 40 hours a week is better than 4 managers working 80 hours a week. It may cost you a bit more, but their performance and efficiency will be miles better. Working the same people long  is not efficient or effective.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Geoffrey Slave Trade”

</title><pros>Pros – You learn good professional discipline, hard working ethics, and because of their training you do get exposure to different areas of the business.The friendships you make are also great, you spend by far the majority of your life at Toys R Us so these people become your family.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Before important management visits it's not unusual for managers to work a 24 hour day.  Retail is long hours however in the 21st Century it is not acceptable to rota managers in for 80 hour weeks AND expect them to work extra to that!!The culture is one that area managers will come in and shout at store managers if the mood takes them.  The idea of motivation hasn't found it's way to this company yet.Do not work for these people, you are not valued, not paid enough, and you will be worked into the ground after a couple of years.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Other companies don't work like you because it what you do doesn't work.  Other retailers of your size and turnover of stores, have double the managers that you do.  They don't think it's acceptable to rota in managers for 80 hour weeks.  Your turnover of managers is massive, with the 'old time' managers only staying because you've given them no development, no one else will employ them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>