<name>I Love Bracelets Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/I-Love-Bracelets-Reviews-E363341.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2011-01-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It has been a learning experience”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are very nice, and are very willing to help you learn new things.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The upper management is very indecisive.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would work on listening to your employees more.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“"Unstable work environment"”

</title><pros>Pros – There were multiple employees with whom you could commiserate with, allowing for a small family-feel. Casual-dress; snacks provided.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Minimal pay and little to no benefits for the work that is expected- Incredibly unstable upper management style- often condescending and degrading in front of other employees; micromanaging- No opportunity for advancement, or the ability to work full-time; hours were reduced "indefinitely"</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat every member of staff as if they're valuable and can contribute something to the work environment. Do not blame your own in competencies on others; and expect cheerful results.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work & learn!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to learn the wholesale business of fashion jewelry.  Company lets you be creative when given the opportunity.  Great discount off merchandise.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No bonus, only given jewelry as bonus.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Owner of the company is a good mentor and leader of the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>