<name>C-DOT Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/C-DOT-Reviews-E364096.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent opportunity to work and learn”

</title><pros>Pros – CDOT is the best place to start one's career as it provides immense opportunities to learn while contributing to his/her job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor remuneration with respect to similar organizations in the private sector.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – C-DOT should come up with competetive remuneration to retain its workforce.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice working environment”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Flexible timings2. Wide varieties of project to work on.3. Both research oriented and application oriented projects undertaken.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. The work environment is not very enthusiastic.2. Lack of discipline among the employees.Rest everything is good.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Educative and research oriented work”

</title><pros>Pros – Research oriented, Good pay, Pressure free work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Monotonous work, Look for greater challenges</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More scope to engineers to work on different projects</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“slow- can be a good thing or bad”

</title><pros>Pros – good place to learn at a leisurely place</pros>
<cons>Cons – can feel pretty out-dated very soon.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“it is a decent place to work and learn”

</title><pros>Pros – The nature of wokr can get challenging sometiems</pros>
<cons>Cons – work culture ougth to be improved</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Student Trainee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exp as Student Trainee summer 2012”

</title><pros>Pros – Govt. funded organization. No limitation, no hurry.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Govt. organization. Laid back approach</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Avg Company: Good for lazy souls”

</title><pros>Pros – Government organisation, hence job securityNot much work pressureGood work culture - homely cultureGreat campus</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not a very open culture -- cannot chose what you want to work onSlow salary growth and promotionsOnly two locations - delhi & bangalore</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Work For those who want to do it”

</title><pros>Pros – Ample opportunities, exposure to cutting edge technologies and lot of learning opportunitiesGood salary, cab facilities and lot of other benefits.Best suited for womenFixed working hours and can also have flexible timings.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Might subdued by your manager. Not a level playing field for everyone. Lot of discrimination depending upon your relations with upper management. Monotony can also arise.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The experience at C-DoT has been largely disappointing”

</title><pros>Pros – Stable and secure jobGood initial salaryIdeal for settling down, without much hassle</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lethargic work environment in most groupsDisinterested/demotivated employeesFocus only on Govt. projects</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to focus on competitive products. Concentrate on specific areas, instead of doing whole product development. Welcome new projects from all customers and motivate employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good for people who want to setlle in government but want to contribute to their field.”

</title><pros>Pros – it is a central government owned company, so no feeling of job insecutity, but work is not as in govt org, its reserch oriented and you have to do a lot of work also.. homely culture with nice sport and event organisations.. not less salary enough to lead a good satisfactory life.. good place even for starters as you can learn lot of things on a complete basis..</pros>
<cons>Cons – only two branches.(delhi and bangalore). salry growth cannot be compared tp private org..  the field of work is rather a declining field..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – invest more money on wireless based 4g, LTE etc rather than supporting ur age old rax's and max's..</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work culture,good work life balance,some really great R&D projects,....</pros>
<cons>Cons – Timing of work is fixed ,,,,,,,,,it should be flexible</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Freedom to do whatever u want to do, colleagues so helpful.”

</title><pros>Pros – Technical growth, good environment to work</pros>
<cons>Cons – At times goal is not clear but slowly things are changing now.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More one to one interaction with employees. More rewards and awards to motivate people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A company with good work environment and low pay increment”

</title><pros>Pros – good environment along with facilities</pros>
<cons>Cons – less money and takes lot of time to get promoted</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome place for lazy bones ;)”

</title><pros>Pros – No work pressure,Great exposure,a fabulous place to work!</pros>
<cons>Cons – All the research work is carried out by Bangalore office..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give us some sensible responsibility!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Graduate Apprentice Trainee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“opportunities in company”

</title><pros>Pros – great opportunity to learn n enhance personality  for those who r working with the company</pros>
<cons>Cons – no open recruitment as other government companies</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – please start open recruitment on the basis of all india examinations</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Average company to work with”

</title><pros>Pros – being a govt. company u have job security.it has good campus and many sports facilities.Average salary.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Learning is not upto the markExcellence is not rewarded, everybody is getting more or less the same benefits.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – improvement is needed in upper management</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good work culture”

</title><pros>Pros – very good work culture, good place to learn new things for a fresher, no feel of barrier in discussion with people in higher levels</pros>
<cons>Cons – time lag in some projects</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Summer Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Strongest networking company in india”

</title><pros>Pros – Strong foundation of networks and protocols</pros>
<cons>Cons – Location is an area where they need to focus</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Nice</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Student Trainee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My experiences at C-DOT as Student Trainee”

</title><pros>Pros – For any CSE, ECE engineering undergrad at best institutions across india, C-DOT is like a dream come true, I may be overstating the fact, but ask their parents. Too good of a company to be Government owned, big campus, I mean real big; no hectic work schedule, nice compensations, no cubicles for research engineers and then there's the fact "I'm working for my country"</pros>
<cons>Cons – Being govt. owned also counts as a con, fixed growth rate.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please open research engineers job to IT grads to.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Technical exposure is satisfactory”

</title><pros>Pros – Good package, Decent infrastructure for research</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management not very competitive especially now that the focus is drifting away from research</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus should be research primarily or else should make effort to get the managerial aspects right</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Satisfied, could be better”

</title><pros>Pros – No compulsion to work extra hours. That would automatically mean we can leave office at time. So there will enough time to spend with family.The card level hardware design engineers have been given good design works.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay hike is lesser compared to other companies in similar domains.No scope for on site work.In house entertainment activities are a minimum.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It could be better to have a flatter structure. There is a large gap between senior level managers and engineers. The information isn't passed down to bottom. Or lower level engineers are unaware of happenings at higher level.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice place to work at</pros>
<cons>Cons – mangement is ok, could be better</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Exapnd!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good for the freshers”

</title><pros>Pros – Best place to work for the freshers, ll be working directly over the card design , ll be learning a lot during 0-2 years</pros>
<cons>Cons – poor package and management, managers take casually most of the times</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“an ok place to work at”

</title><pros>Pros – good for work life balanceRelaxed atmosphereGood SalaryGood Benefits as compared to similar companiesGreat campusTransport Facility</pros>
<cons>Cons – career development is not that goodLearning is not that goodSenior management is not that involved with the employees</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>