<name>Shedd Aquarium Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Shedd-Aquarium-Reviews-E364645.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Vet Tech Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best Experience of My Life”

</title><pros>Pros – Too many to count, memories that will last a lifetime.</pros>
<cons>Cons – None, I was an intern and heard rumors of low-pay but it's a non-profit organization, so what do you expect?</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You are doing a great job!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Non-profit pay with a for-profit attitude.”

</title><pros>Pros – You get to work around animals and learn about aquatic life.  You can get tickets for friends and family.  People are always impressed when you tell them where you work.  Work life balance is valued.  The history of the aquarium is interesting.  Good benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unless you are in the Marketing department or in Development, you really don't matter.  There is a "good ole boy" mentality at the top.  There is a lack of diversity with upper management.  Promotions are more based on which vice president you are friends with and who likes you rather than your quality of work (its very high school).  Huge disproportion in pay between upper management and everyone else.  There are 25 vice presidents (I'm not kidding).The aquarium won't take a strong stand on controversial issues like global warming because they don't want to lose funding from the overly conservation board of trustees.  The aquarium is obsessed with making money even though they are the number one attended cultural organization in Chicago.  There is definitely an "untouchable" attitude in regards to other museums, zoos and aquariums.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start doing 360 reviews on managers.  Have clear career paths for all employees and stop playing favorites and "fast tracking" certain people.  Create a more diverse executive leadership team.  Take the focus away from making more money to line your pockets and start focusing on making more of an impact on animals in the wild and the environment in general.  Start listening to feedback from employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Ambassador and Summer Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Used to be great, now not so much”

</title><pros>Pros – When you work in the offices upstairs, it's a great place to work and learn about various fields of a nonprofit. Downstairs on the floor, my co-workers made this job, and it was interesting learning about all the quirks and history of the aquarium. I worked here almost 7 years, so I've seen multiple sides of how this company works.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay sucked. For the hours you put in there, you'd think they would compensate their employees better. The internship was unpaid. During the summers 12+ hour days/6-7 days in a row weren't uncommon and the management was awful at making a functioning schedule. They would purposely short staff to save money, but burn out their employees so much faster.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Fix the disconnect between the upstairs offices and the floor workers. Stop caring about bringing in revenue and more about educating the public and being AFFORDABLE for families to come and visit. Floor managers need to listen to their employees and find a good work-life balance otherwise you'll lose all the talent you have.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Guest Experience Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Coworkers are the saving grace”

</title><pros>Pros – Free admission to the aquarium and other cultural attractions around Chicago. Great coworkers, although there is a pretty high turnover, so you don't even get to spend too much time with anyone. Lower-level management is mostly competent, hard-working, and human. people in the departments that deal with animals actually seem to care about conservation and animals.</pros>
<cons>Cons – upper management seems to only care about money and flashy entertainment (like the 4d theater), and not truly about guest engagement or aquatic education. information about ticketing options is deliberately withheld from guests, and policies that would reduce guest frustration about lines are not taken so that more money can be made by selling the highest-priced and/or express ticket. guest engagement reps bear the brunt of guests' off-put moods while upper management enjoys the profits. it's truly an emotionally draining job with no positive returns. 99% of my coworkers hated it.Also, they are ridiculously inflexible about scheduling, which makes it impossible to have a second job (a second job is sorely needed when you get paid that little)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't under-value guest experience reps or the guest experience department. they are some of the hardest-working people in the building, and most of them are having a very hard time supporting themselves and their families on the low wages. many of them are very excited when starting and eventually become some of the most anti-shedd-aquarium people in chicago. this would not happen if appreciation for their work was shown through better pay (there is precedent for this in other museums that don't enjoy nearly the same amount of income that shedd does), fair scheduling (10-12 hour shifts are way too long), and improved support in terms of more staff and more honest interactions with guests about ticketing.look at your online reviews. people don't just use online reviews to complain - it only looks that way to you because there are very few good things to say about a visit to the aquarium in its current state. plenty of businesses and attractions enjoy consistently positive reviews. treat your exployees and guests better, and the will return the favor.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Funnest place to work, and pays great”

</title><pros>Pros – You get a lot of interaction with Sealife, and I learn something new everyday</pros>
<cons>Cons – You can sometimes work late hours, depending what position you're in</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Aquarist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun at the shedd!”

</title><pros>Pros – Customers are always happy when they come. Lots of discounts at all the Chicago Museums and free water taxi rides. Plenty of opportunities to participate in off sight research. Easy to reach by public transportation.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No room to progress in your field. Fairly low pay. Benefits are not great.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More opportunity for advancement.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate/Apparel (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible Management”

</title><pros>Pros – You gain decent awareness of sales and tourism traffic. The people you work with are the best people you'll probable ever meet.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You'll only move up if you are brown-nosing, and I mean brown-nosing so hard your entire face is brown. They fire people without fully thinking of the money that those individuals brought in. They are very condescending and unconcerned about the lives of their sales associates. They promote people based on the PWP's sold instead of their leadership abilities, so you're usually stuck with incompetent supervisors with unnecessarily big egos. Store recovery could be a simple process if the Cash Leads were required to help after they've finished counting down the registers. Instead they walk around and make orders. Pick it up yourself, you're standing right there. PITCH IN!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn to develop a good work morale by motivating your employees rather than bring them down, than sending them out on the floor with a depressing start to their work day.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Guest Experience (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hypocrisy”

</title><pros>Pros – -If you like fish, this is the place for you.-There are some nice part time employees working there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -They say they are environmental and they do things by the book, but only a few are, not the entire organization.-The aquarium is outlook is not good, business is not good.-Senior management truly does not know anything about their guests, they are focused on donors.-Business is ran like a Mafia.-Unfortunately, the few good people are there are usually the volunteers you don't get to work with.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – -Focus on your guests because the paying customers are usually treated like dirt.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Management (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Think outside the bowl”

</title><pros>Pros – Progressive environment, non-corporate, engaging, decent pay, never a dull moment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Undefined room for advancement, no tuition reimbursement or education path, stressful, commanding</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create clear paths for advancement and opportunities, instead of "waiting" to see if something happens or changes (or someone gets fired)</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Public Relations Summer Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Summer PR Internship”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people, lots of opportunity to get experience in the PR industry, partners with Public Communications Inc., great flexibility, includes benefits/discounts for interns</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unpaid, but other than that no real cons</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Would have been helpful for review to include several people, not just one person relaying the opinions of many.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Development”

</title><pros>Pros – Amazing people to work with and always able to help each other out</pros>
<cons>Cons – none I was thrilled with this job</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Educator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Work Environment”

</title><pros>Pros – You are treated great by managementAbility to shadow other departmentsGreat work environmentYou have the ability to make kids (and adults) happy everyday</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is a non-profit organization so the pay isn't very goodDepending on your job, you may have to work some very long hours</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing what you are doing, even after leaving and working a few jobs since, Shedd is still by far my favorite employer</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Ambassador (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – You get a lot of great discounts towards hotels, Chicago museums, car rentals, and water taxis.You, of course, get free tickets, but are also allowed to bring four people with you. You may also leave up to five tickets for friends and family, during non-peak times.The turn-over is so high you get a chance to make a lot of new friends from all over the country.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Scheduling: They are not always so nice when you are in college. Although the scheduling just changed hands so it’s gotten much better. Many people left because the scheduler makes them choose between school and working. It almost happened to me, but I talked to someone higher and got it ok’d. You are expected to work every single weekend (Friday-Sunday) and every holiday. Since they don't do weekend rotations and it's hard to get a weekend off you deal with a lot of call offs, which makes it rough on the employees.Movement: It seems like they have their favorites and give them interesting and unique positions. Unless you have a masters in aquatics or marine life there isn’t much room to grow. There aren’t very many office positions available, and when they are they typically want bachelors or master and five years of experience.Communication: You usually are told last about anything new going on, or sometimes you are not told at all. They are not very upfront with information.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You should implement a weekend rotation schedule. It helps cut back on call offs. Since people are then able to schedule around their weekends off, and it allows the employees to switch weekends with another if they need to time off without having to call off. Create more jobs and make it easier for the current employees to move up.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall good experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity to work for a well-directed mission</pros>
<cons>Cons – very siloed.big ship = hard to turn. slow to innovate."institutionalized"</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Above service expectations, below service pay.”

</title><pros>Pros – Free admission to other cultural attractions.  Access to some amazing fish and aquatic animals.  Reimbursement for uniform expenses.  Great job for high school student or college student; not anyone looking to pay bills and support self or family.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Minimum wage pay.  Expensive health coverage for part-time employees.  Complaining customers EVERY day.  Micromanagement.  Lack of communication between all departments.  High expectations from management without any support or reflection in the pay.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees.  Stop implementing obnoxious protocol when you don't even deal with customers on a daily basis.  Give raises that can support a family, instead of bragging about not having lay-offs.  Give promotions, allow part-time workers a full-time opportunity instead of hiring fifty new temps.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>