<name>Leo J Shapiro & Associates Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Leo-J-Shapiro-and-Associates-Reviews-E371578.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Strategist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fascinating place to get inside the heads of customers and consumers”

</title><pros>Pros – Broad experience both in consumer and B2B research with immediate exposure to client work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Self motivation is needed as the company does not coddle</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Could be a bit more sensitive to employee needs</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Market Research Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Learn what you can, but quickly move on”

</title><pros>Pros – You will learn a little bit of everything that's required to do custom market research. If you can, try and work with the pharma team - they operate much more efficiently and fairly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Below market salary. Extremely limited career opportunities. Nothing reinvested into the company - lagging behind competitors. No vision or brand. Not using the latest tools or methods.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wish they cared about employees more”

</title><pros>Pros – Small company gives you face time with upper management</pros>
<cons>Cons – Below average pay and raises, no bonuses, strict office hours, not much appreciation for dedicated and hard workers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Showing appreciation for when employees go above and beyond would make a huge difference. Employees work really hard, travel long hours, and work nights and weekends to get studies and reports done to very little acknowledgement. It's hard to keep motivated</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Behind the Times”

</title><pros>Pros – The company has been in existence for many years and they have a reputation that can open up doors for more research opportunities when you leave.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited support and opportunities for real advancement. Leadership has tunnel vision with the inability to recognize talent within their own company. They consistently hire from outside the organization for services that can be performed by existing employees. The company is very wasteful with their resources. Management is arrogant without the real talent to support it. Everything is smoke and mirrors there. Morality is low throughout the entire organization with few believing that their contribution makes a true difference. This is not a good place to work for if you want a notable career that you will be proud of. Most employees are underpaid, underdeveloped, and simply uninspired to produce work they can be proud of.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Utilize your research own methodologies to better understand all your employees and how to best use their talent to help your organization grow.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Employer to Make a Career in Market Research”

</title><pros>Pros – - Ability to advance skills- Can work across a range of subjects areas and method- Early opportunities to work with clients and their issues- Good work/life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Multitasking can sometimes be stressful- Sometimes need to stretch to fill project needs- Communication could be better</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - keep focus on employee skill development and training</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fascinating work, family environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Diverse client base and wide range of client issues keeps work interestingLots of long term clientsLong term tenure of staffFriendly and relaxed environment.  Most people are willing to help.Cool building</pros>
<cons>Cons – No formal training programs so development depends on the quality of your mentor/supervisorFamily environment has its drawbacks, sometimes dysfunctionalLack of formal structure/chain of commandSenior partners disconnected from day to day</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide more support, resources and time for development of all employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Needs a lot of work”

</title><pros>Pros – Small company - lots of responsibility right awayLots of opportunity for a variety of projects, including interesting travel opportunitiesGreat downtown locationGood benefits for a small company</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most people are difficult to work with. The ones that are great to work with are not in management roles.Long hours with no appreciation or recognition for your efforts.Below market pay, miniscule raises, no annual bonus, no 401k for your first yearNo flexibility in your schedule - strict business hours and it's not an option to work remotely even for extenuating or occasional circumstances.No training or professional development opportunities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start caring about your employees so that they're motivated to work hard and stick around.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working with smart people is a joy”

</title><pros>Pros – Great environment if you are a self motivated worker.  If you need to be coddled and expect the company to bend to your needs then go work somewhere else but if you like a challenge and want to take it on there are a lot of bright people here to team withGet to work with clients immediately</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes feel afloat but I find it envigorating.  Reminds me of my best music teachers...tough and high pressure but worth it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – A little more communication and one on one development with senior directors would be helpful</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Your experience will depend on your boss”

</title><pros>Pros – Some smart people to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – You will like your job if you have a good bossUnclear, roles and positions not well definedPeople fired randomlyLots of nepotismPoor employee review systemLow morale among most employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employees need development and opportunitiesConsider bonuses</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Difficult people, no appreciation, management out of touch”

</title><pros>Pros – Your first few months will be very interesting as you take on new projects</pros>
<cons>Cons – Below market payNegative attitudes from the top-downStrict work hours - like being in high school againJob/tasks becomes repetitive and can become boring/uninterestingThey use old software programs for data collection and analysis so you feel a bit behind the times/behind the capabilities of other market research firmsAbsolutely no training or development opportunities. Everything is passed down from employee to employee and when one employee with a lot of knowledge quits or is fired there's a lot of scrambling to get back to pace</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A company in crisis - This company needs a dose of reality”

</title><pros>Pros – A few colleagues were friendly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – OUTDATED work environment and work structure.NO flexibility.THE WORST management I have ever encountered - ANYWHERE!CEO is rude and disrespectful.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>