<name>Asit C Mehta Investment Interrmediates Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Asit-C-Mehta-Investment-Interrmediates-Reviews-E371165.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Deputy Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work at if you are looking for personal and career development”

</title><pros>Pros – Extensive focus on employee development and motivation.Good value sets and beliefs.Innovation and new ideas are much appreciated compared to other broking firms.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Need to picture themselves as a more aggresive company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest more in employees so that they translate the company vision to the customers perfectlyFocus on alternative channels for revenure generation( model for revenue generation should not be market oriented)</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Area In Charge (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“it was great experiance at ACMIIL. proper working etmosphire provided by mgmt”

</title><pros>Pros – proper working environment was given to each staff</pros>
<cons>Cons – compensation is not attractive. but it was also not lesser in the industry</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to learn, superb value sets and very transparent”

</title><pros>Pros – Huge amount of transparency in daily working with clients, employees and vendors.Hands-on Management with very strong ethics and value set.Very less politics in day-to-day work life, most of the fellow staff is friendly and helpful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inefficient people are not dealt with as quickly as they usually are in other companies.Management sometimes makes ad hoc decisions.No canteen in Head Office.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more strict with non-performers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Head HRD (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent learning and opportunity to take newer responsibilities, roles and challenges”

</title><pros>Pros – Challenging environment to growth one's career, opportunity to take higher role & responsibilities with department and across, and window of 'idea-plug' to be experimented, accessibility to seniors, sharing of learning from cross segments.</pros>
<cons>Cons – difficult times across financial sector, particularly broking industry in terms of financial constraints; difficulty in numerating client engagement tools and techniques across the organization</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – resource management along with intelligence management will play key to organization's survival and development</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Executive (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for learning and Freshser”

</title><pros>Pros – Small organization gives following opportunity.Carrier Growth .Knowledge UpgradeSkills developmentAdd on responsibilityInteraction with different people for work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited Financial growth.Carrier growth is limitedInterdepartmental development is not happening</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need  to retain  good people for business growth</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Conservative Approach”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly work culture, moderate work pressure.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No career path, below industry avg. salary, no value for talent & intellect, no aggression & competetiveness in doing business, impromptu decision making by senior management, etc...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – gain focus in doing business, leverage on brand equity, retain talent, be aggressive in doing business, bring professionalism in conducting business....</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>