<name>AbsolutData Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/AbsolutData-Reviews-E371814.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you want to work with VERY smart people from an outsourced analytic company - absolutdata is your company.”

</title><pros>Pros – Upper management have some of the smartest, articulate people I have met in the analytic industry.  Also, I've never experience such a company with an positive emphasis on family and individuals. A birthday or anniversary will NEVER go unnoticed.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes there can be problems with IT data flow.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You are phenomenal. Keep doing what you are doing, please.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No Streamlined Company Processes, HR, Payroll especially”

</title><pros>Pros – Get to work on a wide variety of industries and get some initial understanding of trends in various sectors.Put Statistical Knowledge into action.Be a lot more proactive and opportunity to go over and beyond your defined responsibility.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Insights seldom gets converted to actions from the delivered projects.Tend to bend over backwards for a lot of projectsCompany is fond of taking repetitive and easy tasks to continue their billing.It's run like a family owned business</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is one of the best company for people with sycophantic attitude, people of integrity should avoid”

</title><pros>Pros – ADT gives you many chances to explore your philosophical side. It makes you question the meaning of life and helps you get in touch with your inner repressed self</pros>
<cons>Cons – Well, people with high moral values might find it hard to adjust but I guess the work culture is such that you will find yourself at their level very soon</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There should be a separate section on 'sycophancy ability' in the appraisal form so that new recruits are very about what is expected of them</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“still a start up”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work satisfaction for everyone</pros>
<cons>Cons – if u want a start up kind of work be ready for all</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Management Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Small growing organization with opportunity to work in analytics with reputed clients while maintaining work/life balanc”

</title><pros>Pros – Pro-people practices and good work/life balance.One of the better analytics firms in India.Opportunity to work with major Fortune 500 companies.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In spite of over 10 years of existence, hasn't quite yet shrugged off its startup image.Pay is decent, but not anything extra-ordinary.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue expansion plans in order to get closer to the company vision.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good place to learn fast”

</title><pros>Pros – Exposure early in the career, interactive atmosphere and growth opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary is not upto the industry standards, some of the company policies related to HR also not great.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Consider changing some policies and compensation</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“company is good but do not join its research wing”

</title><pros>Pros – Good analytics work , good exposure and work environment in analytic deptt.</pros>
<cons>Cons – not a conducive environment for personality development in research deptt.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please hire people with good educational background no matter what profile you are offering.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of Learning But Low Employee Satisfaction”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Client Facing Role2. Continous Learning3. Ability to grow</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Very little employee focussed2. Internal politics3. Long working hours4. Inefficient managers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more Employee Friendly</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“AbsolutData is an excellent company and recommend it to all aspirants”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent job opportunities / compensation, Experience and Profile of Senior Executives</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work life balance, expectation definition</cons>
<advice-to-management> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not Satisfactory”

</title><pros>Pros – A good launch pad if you want to work in analytic industry</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not very challenging work. Even if you have average intelligence, you can get great appraisals. All you have to do is sucking up to the people who are above you.Some of the people in the senior management are so dumb, sometimes you hate yourself for working under them</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – look for intelligence while recruiting senior managers, not just work experience</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall View of the Company”

</title><pros>Pros – It's an Organization where you get to learn and grow a lot at a fast pace</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some bit of processes are unstructured which are now gettting streamlined</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“AbsolutData - Fun place to work at”

</title><pros>Pros – Energetic and Positive EnvironmentHigh VisibilityAppropriate RecognitionFun @ WorkSupportive LeadershipClear Growth PathYou get friends here not just colleagues. And the best part is that ADT help you make friends in office by regular Fun activities...</pros>
<cons>Cons – ADT is full of work and you will never get a relief for even a second when you are in office but that's where Fun @ Work activities help.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's like a family for me!”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Great founders2. Co-operative colleagues</pros>
<cons>Cons – I think we can definitely improve on the work culture!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Although, epmloyees at ADT are satisfied but as the organization is growing at fast pace and is a brand now, we can definitely do a lot more for employee satisfaction.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“experience with AbsolutData in true lines”

</title><pros>Pros – good remuneration and upcoming organisation</pros>
<cons>Cons – none of the senior management has "Empathy" towards employees, no work life balance practiced, poor leave management system, work pressure- no management around this!! gives a feel of typical Indian Set up, coaching and guidance is required at all people leader level for better nd efficient team management with right people skills, poor seating arrangement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – take serious steps to build better work life balance</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best place to start your analytics/research career”

</title><pros>Pros – Working across various industry verticalsSmaller teams, more access to the client/top management</pros>
<cons>Cons – No specific work timing - a lot of late nights</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Arranging drop to homes for women post 7</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Programmer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was nice experience to work with ADT”

</title><pros>Pros – Good to start, learning environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No personal life, hectic schedule</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice learning”

</title><pros>Pros – Variety of projects across geographies, with very high level of sophistication of clients that demand very high end insights and analysis.</pros>
<cons>Cons – With the geographic coverage and the workload, sometimes it becomes very difficult to manage the proper work life balance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“AbsolutData ensures a good variety of work and fast growth if you love challenges.”

</title><pros>Pros – If you are a person who is interested in Analytics and want to challenge yourself, AbsolutData is a very good bet. It promises you fast growth if you can prove yourself, and gives you wide experience in expanding your analytics as well as people management skills over time. It is a pretty young company and that is the best part - you will enjoy working here. Young people who want to prove themselves - for the majority, it is their first or second jobs. Very friendly atmosphere - people are not competitive, and are willing to help one other out. You will settle in very fast within the team.There is also a recent emphasis on increasing employee engagement - the company organizes various events within to increase bonding between and within teams. All in all, a great place to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Still very unstructured, which is not upto everyone's liking. Not a very flat organization, which I consider a hinderance. In some teams, work life balance is an issue, though the company is taking steps to balance it. Little organizational administrative support - parking and cabs remain issues which the company has been unable to assuage the company of. Presently going through plenty of changes, which is leading to growth pangs.Plenty of attrition and less robust knowledge transfer sharing systems.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Active steps to counter work-life balance problem. Provide more organizational administrative support. Try following companies like Google and Amex. Trust people more, and you can probably save up on high salary costs. People should be ready to work for you if you create a friendler atmosphere inside work. Moreover, need to have more structured mechanisms for tackling problems.</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review”

</title><pros>Pros – Growning companies, good client exposure.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unstructured, processes & policies not properly defined.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Standardize the processes and policies</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work Hard & Party Harder..... A great place to work & learn and an even better place for fun & frolic...”

</title><pros>Pros – Here goes...* Dynamic & employee centric work environment* Competence & Capable Leadership Team* Everyday learning & knowledge sharing* Opportunities Gallore - global exposure, opportunities to interaction with clients & other stakeholders</pros>
<cons>Cons – * Effect on work life balance due to long working hours.* Unavailability of company transport* Low visibility of the brand in the market</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Happy, Growing Organization to work :)”

</title><pros>Pros – The organization is open to ideas and flexible to implement them as well. If you are willing to take initiative the company supports you.Since there is sharp focus on analytics, its a good learning platform for acquiring the nuances of the trade  The organization is in stage of growth so its nice to be a part of a team which is experiencing the  change  and installation of process and systems.The atmosphere in the company is result oriented but at the same time everyone is supportive and helpful and willing to invest in you to acquire new skills.The company also lays emphasis on social bonding which is great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can't really think of any downside of working here just that with the stage of the company you may be expected to fly even before you have acquired the wings which in itself good.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Its nice to see a management which is supportive and follows an open door policy. Please try and maintain the same as we grow bigger.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A mixed bag”

</title><pros>Pros – variety of workOrganisation has supportive colleagues and we do have a lot of opportunities to learn and grow as an individual.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes work can get repititve for a very long period of time and senior management doesn't helps much in this context.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst Trainee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pleasure to work here”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun to work here, Perfection needed in work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management System not very supportive</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please see performance of the candidates, rather than looking into thier personal life</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Knowledge has been great so its good to starts ur carreer here”

</title><pros>Pros – High amount of learning is there</pros>
<cons>Cons – Package is not that great</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unidimensional; limited in scope and too very negative HR policies”

</title><pros>Pros – Offers a glimpse of the analytics/consulting industryOne can learn the basic analytical tools used in the industrySince it is a new company, even small innovations are easily accepted and incorporatedInternational clients provide exposure to fresh graduates</pros>
<cons>Cons – Appraisal and incentive system is frighteningly skewed and arbitraryThere is a huge gulf between senior and junior employeesKnowledge management is very poor with systems for the same not yet solidifiedThe work can get extremely monotonous and repetitive. Rotations are not common.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get more genuinely interested senior managers to make it a place which is valuable for employees to work in otherwise the high rate of attrition will never let the company move forward</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“rich learning and developing key skills”

</title><pros>Pros – Good competitive advantageGreat place to start career and learn the techniques which would be helpful in analyticsExposure in all CPG, Financial/Banking domain during the tenure</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor ManagementNo respect for employees personal lifeNo extra  benefits for employees by companyDon't think on the lines of expansion and growth</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Should improve the quality of resources from reputed collegesThink to grow and expand at better rate than todayShould give more onsite chance and exposure to employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Absolutdata does not give any growth at all”

</title><pros>Pros – When someone does not have any option then he can try for Absolutdata.It is a good company to start career and gain experience but in the long run , nobody can have good growth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No Hike inspite of good business(being in top 50 fastest growing companies)Company did not give bonuses for two consecutive years</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Recognise the work of employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>