<name>Barton G Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Barton-G-Reviews-E373641.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2011-01-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sketchy, Sketchy, Sketchy!”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay is decent when you receive a paycheck on time. People seem impressed that you work here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sketchy business practices!!!!People are never paid on time and people don't last very long here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Go to business school and learn how a real company should operate.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Short-lived and muddledd.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good salary, creative environment, helpful co-workers</pros>
<cons>Cons – Indecisive, confusing, erratic, nasty, brutal</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get out while you can</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Run Away”

</title><pros>Pros – Name recognition.  Some glamorous events.  Some really talented people but a shocking lack of management skill.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This is a very sketchy place to work.    Turnover is very high and there are excellent reasons for that.  Upper management can only be described as abusive towards subordinates.  Screaming, crying, accusations, public reprimand of upper level managers, deflecting blame, and worse...all daily practices.  It is an incredibly difficult environment and if you have any expectation of professionalism, this may not be for you.  The job description I was hired with was not based in reality.  Benefits stink.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I really don't know where to begin.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>