<name>e-VERIFILE Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/e-VERIFILE-Reviews-E373926.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-12-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>CSR-I (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working here was like having your teeth pulled.”

</title><pros>Pros – For the position I was in, I learned a lot about various laws and risk aversion strategies, employee verification, security badge documentation and creation, etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Customer Service was a joke, training had nothing to do with job function, feedback was terrible, and you're assigned the work of 3 people and expected to get it all done in one day. Terrible morale. Everyone I've talked to that has left there is happy to have left.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – This company has been bought out since I was there, so it may not apply anymore; however, my advice would be: If you say you're going to put together training materials that actually apply to your job function, then DO IT. If you say you're going to fix the phone system, then DO IT. Listen to your employees and check your bad attitude.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Integrity and morals of leadership is questionable”

</title><pros>Pros – Front line staff are an awesome group, dedicated and eager to please</pros>
<cons>Cons – CEO has questionable integrity, hired former employee even though they still worked for his previous company and he signed a non-compete agreement.  He hired all of his friends and family.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have integrity</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>In a position that touched all departments (to Retain Anonymity) (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Misguided and Confusing”

</title><pros>Pros – All employees who are not in management positions are a wonderful group of people to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Where to begin. New Ownership does not have the knowledge or expertise to run this company. This company is not a call center and never was. I have worked for both the previous ownership and the new ownership and can, with full knowledge say, this is not a call center! Change is the mantra of the new owner, like magic your co-worker may not be your co-worker tomorrow, unexplained removal of positions and firing of employees. Behind the door secrecy about company objectives (which change from day to day Example: Whole sales team let go within 24 hours with no explanation). Current ownership has damaged relationships that were long standing before the buyout. "C" level management does not understand industry and will not listen to legacy employees. Legacy employees being picked off one by one so there is no dissent. Slave wages for all new employees, you will not find a competitive wage and Management is proud of what they pay comparing it to Fast Food Work.No communication or open doors. If you choose to go to your manager for advise or an issue, you can be assured that everybody will know by the end of the day and you will be chastised for it. The owner keeps sending out "anonymous" mandatory surveys (you will be given a choice, take the survey or get fired) to gauge employee satisfaction and in reality it is used to find those who they wish to remove (it is not 100% anonymous). No chance for advancement unless you are in management. You may have you pay cut when you walk in the door for work tomorrow. No quarterly, 6 month or annual reviews, no annual wage review or increase. Your duties will change sporadically which is the excuse as to why they can not evaluate your performance for a wage increase. Stressful as there is no respect for life outside of work. You get 12 days a year PTO (1 day accrued per month worked and no borrowing future months no carryover) unless you are management then you can go on as much vacation as you wish, because you can afford to.Narcissism is rampant as ALL management worked for owner at previous call center venture. Owner is a megalomaniac putting his personal value above the value of the companies only asset, the employees.Benefits are non existent as most are to costly for anyone but management to afford. As an example, coffee is held under lock and key until potential clients are visiting, then it is shared until client is gone.Your value as an employee is only regarded when you are not questioning anything and being a mindless worker. When you are let go, it will be a surprise and a blessing. A surprise because you did not see it coming and a blessing that you do not have to deal with the stress anymore.You will eventually train your replacement or get back from vacation and find you have no job.To much emphasis on being a "Minority Based Business" with no response to this diversity project since new ownership came in. Mind you the new owner, upon initial meeting with "legacy" employees ( legacy employees is a term often used by management) stated "I am a follower of Jesus and a Black man" which shows the undeserved pride of the owner. You will feel religious overtones as well as minority overtones throughout this company.Monthly meeting focus on "this is the last change for a while" then a week later the same line in another "emergency meeting".  Honesty and integrity are lacking in all "C" level employees. You might be placed under a supervisor that has no business managing people due to their lack of manners and empathy due to their own self importance or find you have a new boss when you return on a Monday.My advise is to stay away unless you are up for a triathlon of challenges.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Find a buyer like GIS or Nexus Lexus and cut your losses. You do not know what you are doing and you are removing those who could guide you, but for your own egos you are systematically removing the key people to save your company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Professional (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Turning a great opportunity into an even greater opportunity”

</title><pros>Pros – This organization is filled with endless potential and opportunities.  The previous owner tapped into a really great market and created an awesome nitch for the organization.  A very solid foundation with a significant client base has been established.  There are some great strategies that can be employed to take the organization to the next level.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is no true leadership.  True direction is severley lacking.  The focus does not appear to be on the best interest of everyone at the company, but on making the new owner look good.  There is a  clear desire for power and praise that has transferred from ownership to ownership.  Although the organization was recently acquired, the organization seems to be faltering and pedaling backwards, as opposed to forward, as was the objective.  The morale at the organization is at it lowest point ever. From interviews of current and former employees, it appears that the new owners have brought in former employees from an original business and have dismissed those individuals that were extremely instrumental in growing and sustaining the current company over the past few years.  Although this organiztion has built a nitch around creating industry-specific compliance programs, the new owners have a different objective in mind, they appear to be going in the direction of a call center.  This call center mentality will no work for this type of organization.  The pay is terrible is not competetive and the environment is no longer friendly and conducive to productivity.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop, and really listen to your staff.  Stop the judgement. And stop looking for worshipers.  Being able to work with all different types of people and personalities is key to being a great manager and leader.In order for the organization to regroup and get back on track, management will need to get back on the same page as their core customers.  Staying inside the "call center box" is not beneficial for the growth of this company.  If you are only an expert in call centers, you might want to read up on how to change up your leadership style to fit this new industry and type of business.  Don't mess up the phenomenal opportunity by inflexible and slow to listen.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>National Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sales focused company”

</title><pros>Pros – Leadership has big plans for the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of clarity on how to make the big plans become a reality.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listent to your employees. Start thinking about what the company can do to make the client experience better. All new employees should spend time talking to  liners in a customer support role. They will learn a lot.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Too Many Chiefs, Not Enough Indians.”

</title><pros>Pros – Experience, experience, experience. You will learn plenty of development frameworks very fast and have a lot of good projects to put on your resume after only 6 months. You hit the ground running at this company which makes it when of the all time best spring boards into a development career.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible management. The only people that are worth anything are the VP of Marketing and the CTO, and they are the only thing holding the company together. The rest of the management will try to each give you their own side projects to do, while still expecting you to complete your currently assigned work in hope that you will kill yourself trying to finish everything. They need to be handled with kid gloves and will make your life miserable the entire time you are there.The CEO also believes that salary is equivalent to all work after 40 hours is free, and will constantly berate you if you don't consistently stay after hours and work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – All the other managers need to stay out of the developer area and let the CTO do his job. If you find you can't do this then fire yourself and hire someone competent to do your job for you while you enjoy the benefits of being part owner of a successful company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great products, poor strategy”

</title><pros>Pros – e-verifile.com has very unique products that set them apart from the rest of the industry. Their approach is easy to explain and gets prospects excited quickly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Their pricing strategy leaves something to be desired, and their IT and customer service departments need serious help. Expect customers to come to you asking for help dealing with customer service.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Look at the long term, take care of your customers, and do something about IT productivity. The short term loss of profit establishing a client in the system can be more than offset by the long term revenue gained from ongoing services.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>