<name>Logitech Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Logitech-Reviews-E3806.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Great workplace, smart people and diverse, awesome products.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company is being re-estrucutred but I prefer to see this fact as an opportunity.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager- Global Education Services (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worked for LifeSize- a division of Logitech in Austin, TX”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits, 50% off of all products, free food and drinks in the facility, great technology, fantastic HR department</pros>
<cons>Cons – Philosophy changed dramatically throughout 3 years, disconnect between areas within the company- especially the US and EMEA.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More transparency- especially when it comes to bonuses.   A clearer and more consistent review process.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-02</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“On its way down...”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice people.  Generally social and positive employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No leadership vision from company management.  Widely regarded internally as an inevitably sinking ship.  So the in-fighting has begun and the fun departed long ago.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get some product programs which make sense.  Since Google TV, the company has lost its design/r&d power.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's been a good run”

</title><pros>Pros – Great company to work for consumer electronics space. Mid size.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work life balance can be better.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exceptional Company Culture”

</title><pros>Pros – I worked at Logitech until 2009.  The company had a fantastic company culture - a blend of European and American values - that placed emphasis on the individual, but promoted a community atmosphere.   The company had many bright and creative people who developed amazing products!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Logitech, at that time, struggled with the ability to merge technologies and products across its many business units.   Its mouse/keyboard, audio, camera, streaming music product groups worked independently - they didn't leverage each other's technologies or business plans.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Small Company, Innovative Products”

</title><pros>Pros – The products that continue to come out of Logitech, especially supporting smart devices and iPads, are really top-notch. And whereas the company has gotten smaller over the years (downsizing), the innovation stays at the forefront of who they are.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As companies downsize it becomes increasingly hard to invest in product categories. Logitech plays in many product categories and that means fewer dollars to spread around. Maybe it's time to shed some product lines and place your bets on the few that will see you into the future.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep innovating and reaching to do great work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Global Product Marketing Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company but changing”

</title><pros>Pros – The product development process is great at getting alignment.  The company constantly comes out with cool products -- products you are proud to show off at home to your friends, and a brand you are proud to represent.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Innovation tempered by requirement of business case to sell volume in short term. Good ideas sometimes lost because resources and time to make it successful are not committed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fairly new at Logitech, but I really like it!”

</title><pros>Pros – Been here almost a year, and I am very happy. Pros include working alongside really cool people in a flexible and casual work environment, with excellent benefits, and seemingly solid management that is trying really hard to steer the company in the right direction to long term stability and growth in a rapidly changing market (tablets/mobility and touchscreen are the future, PCs and mice going away, etc.).</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company has been shrinking to consolidate and maintain itself longterm for a strong future, so there've been a few reorgs and layoffs in the past year or two that have left people feeling a bit demoralized.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Not Disclosed (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Challenged company with still some good $ resources + old-fashioned management”

</title><pros>Pros – "Win" attitude. Smart people (but many leaving...). Still quite a solid cash position giving some flexibility to make the right choices.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Several old-fashioned Sr. executives accountable for Logitech challenged situation are still in the company. Many new executives from very large companies make things worse (affect agility). Some of them are just average in their positions. Rising superstars already left the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Retain top talents (top issue). Work-out a more solid turnaround strategy. Challenged core business requires more disruptive innovation in other areas + more risk-taking.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Project Manager, GMO (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of changes but nothing that points to any growth or strategy”

</title><pros>Pros – Logitech is a pretty easy place to work.  Work hours are flexible, benefits are good, people are nice and the products are fun.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is a serious lack of employee engagement which can make getting things done difficult and frustrating.  This might be because the strategy keeps on changing.  Or it could be because there are rarely key decision makers defined.  Every decision seems to be rethought and then changed from the bottom all the way to the top.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You need to decide what type of company you want to be and then empower the correct employees to make it happen.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Operations (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Friendly but not focused on long-term sustainability”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice place to work. Friendly people, cool products, and don't have to work too hard. Brand is truly known around the world and this is a big untapped asset that still has potential.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the company is not growing, is slowing shrinking, and many entrenched middle-managers are resistant to change. Still a conflict/dysfunction between centralized functions and regionalized sales structure.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – stop believing your own aspirational goals and deal with the harsh reality of the market -- make the big cuts necessary to truly make the company long-term sustainable and stable.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work, but struggling to find their way in the marketplace”

</title><pros>Pros – Great group of people.  Easy environment with good benefits.   Maybe even too easy, as the results show.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Struggling in the market.  Sr Executive leadership is not inspirational.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Develop passion and push people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A once great company struggling to re-define itself”

</title><pros>Pros – The opportunity to work with talented product managers, designers and engineers who are extremely passionate about great product design.  Logitech designs the best looking, feeling and functioning peripherals, bar none.  This being said, to quote former CEO Guerrino De Luca "we are cooks not farmers." In other words, Logitech is good at marrying technologies with exquisite human interface.  It is not particularly good at inventing new technologies.The company, traditionally, has been good at riding the waves though sometimes it gets there too early.  Example: it invented Spotlight five years too early before broadband had reached critical mass.  Five years later, YouTube came along at the right time.Logitech offers a highly multicultural work environment giving you the opportunity to work with interesting people from all over the world and travel to company sites across multiple continents (role dependent).Historically, the company treated its employees very well and morale was high. Though this has changed dramatically in recent years.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Since the company has fallen on hard times in the past few years the employees have come to feel less and less like the company had their best interest in mind.  As a result morale and employee loyalty have dropped significantly.While Logitech has designed and produced great products over the years, and has been good at catching waves, it typically has not been particularly good in developing new markets.  Investment in marketing and brand development have been lacking.Management over the last 7 years focused on too many opportunities.  As a result it missed the opportunity to focus on a select few at the right time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You've laid off enough people now.  Presumably you have or are about to hit bottom.  Pick a "couple" of opportunities and double down on them.  If one of them is mobile music devices, which I believe it is, then you'll need to quadruple down on it as your competition is already investing tons and has been for years now.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Development (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Director of Business Development”

</title><pros>Pros – Logitech designs outstanding hardware peripherals for PCs and mobile platforms in terms of look, feel and function.Opportunity to work with very talented engineers and product managers.Chance to work in a highly multi-cultural environment both in the U.S. and sites worldwide.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Logitech continues to go through hard times.  Ongoing softness in the PC market has resulted in continued depressed sales of PC peripherals, Logitech's core business.As a result it has become a rather stressful place to work, especially owing to several rounds of layoffs which have occurred over the past year.Logitech tends to invest in products but not sufficiently in sustained marketing programs for market development or to compete effectively against entrenched players.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Remain laser focus and invest in marketing and brand building in growth businesses (e.g. wearable and portable devices for music; Logitech for Business).  BTW, Guerrino De Luca is no longer the CEO.  It's Bracken Darrell who took over in January of 2013.  Hence my rating below refers to him, not Guerrino.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – very supportive management, good work-life balance, good benefits, highly competent co-workers, interesting projects,</pros>
<cons>Cons – declining industry (PC accessories), Logitech has been struggling to find a new product line to take on the profitable big role that the declining mouse/keyboard business is beginning to leave</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – find the new "mouse". Take more risks, not so much with big investments, but with new technology.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good company at heart, but some serious transitional problems.  Unstable.  Beware.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Salary and Benefits, generally interesting work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company is struggling to adapt to a market where PCs are second fiddle.They have a pretty disastrous marketing-based approach to developing new product, so be aware you are may be entirely beholden to some marketing person who dictates how you do your job.  If that person is good, it's fine.  If they suck, it can be a miserable slog dealing with someone who has a mediocre grasp of the product.In general, I do not see the company taking the steps necessary to survive and grow.  After the google TV fiasco, they cut a lot of fat and are trying to re-entrench themselves in some core businesses--and add a new line of mobile products--but there are no long-term growth prospects in mice/keyboards/webcam/speakers/etc, because the PC market as a whole is evaporating (not to mention those are all commodity markets at this point).  Company has a mobile initiative that is good, but too little, too late, IMO, and consistently hampered by people stuck in 2007.  Lastly, some of the businesses they're divesting are--IMO--better opportunities for the company (in part because they are complimentary to mobile), but maybe there's some business logic there I don't follow.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start acting like a startup.  Start moving quickly.  Realize--and act on the realization--that you cannot fall back on your existing markets.  No amount of innovation is going to bring keyboards, mice and webcams back from the dead in a world of laptops and tablets.End your marketing driven approach, start making your engineers first-class citizens in the design of new product.  The company marginalizes some of its brightest.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bully management getting in the way of new product development”

</title><pros>Pros – Company has some excellent people with great ideas.  New products, especially those in the new mobility area show great promise.</pros>
<cons>Cons – However certain product groups neglect their primary focus of developing quality products within cost parameters and instead reach to other departments where they have no expertise and run havoc.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Show some backbone and get rid of power hungry product development heads and show the rest of the company that company performance comes ahead of personalities.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>QA Engineer III (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good company whose current direction is concerning.”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent benefits. Some really good people, both personally and professionally. Makes interesting products.  Decent salary.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work/Life balance isn't great. Not as much of a meritocracy as it claims.  Site management can be indecisive.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work with very bright people in a very challenging turnaround situation”

</title><pros>Pros – Work environment, benefits, collaborative atmosphere from a global perspective.</pros>
<cons>Cons – HQ/Western Region relationship has historically been contentious, adversarial.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be quicker to recognize the writing on the wall about dying categories. Focus less on churning out new iterations of mice/keyboards and more on game-changing mobile/audio products/services. Already starting to see moves in the right direction (finally got rid of Quindlen), but probably a bit too late.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Great company culture and overall environment. Got lots of opportunities to suggest and pursue projects, management is very flexible and progressive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Less aggressive in terms of business drive, need to onboard and attract smarter talent for pushing the  limits even further. Salary should be somewhat higher  than presently offerred.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent Company, Poor Managment”

</title><pros>Pros – Pays well, relaxed company culture knows how to have fun, good amount of time off. Logitech excels in its core categories (mice, keyboards), it is just a shame that poor management is keeping it from truly innovating in other areas.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is slow to make decisions which negatively impacts business. The company has made some bad bets and under-funded and promoted certain categories which it is now trying to sell off. Not sure how much longer the company can rely on selling mice and keyboards when we are now living in a touchscreen world.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Empower your working level people to make more decisions and react to changes in the market faster.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Customer Account Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Growth opportunity, great products, friendly people. If you are ready to drive your career, this is the place to be.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Declining PC market, role clarity</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great products but company is mired in politics”

</title><pros>Pros – Logitech has some of the most exciting computer peripheral products. The degree to which product quality is validated is worthy of mentioning. Company feels like a mini United Nations in many ways and has a very unique model of internal and outsourced production.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This is a classic case of finding own worst enemy in themselves. The internal politics and regional (Europe vs US vs Asia) clashes took down what could have been a great company. Very unfortunate.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There are some great minds in engineering and marketing but unless the silo mentality and internal politics can be resolved, Logitech will not be able to rise to the challenge of a diminishing market.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great benefits and good work/life balance, but if you are ambitious, look elsewhere”

</title><pros>Pros – Great health benefits and lots of flexibility for a good work/life balance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Logitech is not sure what they want to be now that momentum has shifted to mobile and tablet use more so than PC. The bread and butter that was mice and keyboards is evaporating and Logitech cast a broad net over many opportunities, but spread itself too thin to really invest in growth areas. New CEO is attempting to turn the behemoth of a company (which is not appropriate for it's actual size) around.Lots of red tape, lots and lots of beaurocracy and no accountability.All in all, Logitech is VERY old school.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Drive accountability down through the organization and better develop your talent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Needs to Change Faster”

</title><pros>Pros – Recognizes that it has problems.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not addressing them fast enough.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Cut more of the fat at the top who have failed the company over and over.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-31</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Network Administrator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Logitech - Management Failures Part of the Culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of freedom, plenty of spare time, work life balance is decent, colleagues are nice.  bring your own phone and flexible desktop support.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of focus from the management, total lack of vision on future of computing industries in general, and price points way out of sync with the market.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get some fresh blood in sales and marketing and stop blaming every other department for the failures.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't work in the region if you are a woman or in marketing”

</title><pros>Pros – Great products.  Above average compensation.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Good old boys club ,especially in salesStyle is more important than substance to manythe role of marketing is to be the punching bag of sales when they don't make their numberBad executive hire made the culture toxic</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Walk the walk... if you say that you care about employees, act like it</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great products, but not the same Logitech.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great culture and fun working with cool tech products that people use and want.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of internal promotions/salary increases, two mass layoff's in past three years, constantly changing Management all signs of a struggling company in today's market.  Lots of good people are leaving to other companies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employees should be treated and rewarded better !</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Logitech”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Leadership is old school and not innovative.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Retire some of the older VPs and bring in fresh ideas.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company, but too much bureaucracy and petty politics”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits, fairly good perks, cool products to play with, a great work/life balance and lots of fun - the Hallowe'en festivities at Logitech are among the best I've ever seen. The current CEO, Guerrino De Luca, came out of retirement to help out the company and he is very good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salaries are on the low side. Way too much inter-departmental politics and clique-building. Management doesn't seem to have much of a direction (though with Guerrino's return, that problem will probably lessen) and there are too many middle managers. There is also too much nepotism.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Cut middle management by at least fifty percent. Get rid of some of the too-numerous product lines. Are you a business accessories company or are you trying to compete with Sony/Samsung/Panasonic/etc? Consolidate and figure out what kind of company you want to be and what kinds of products you're trying to sell.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A company in search of stability”

</title><pros>Pros – good benefits, work/life balance, everyone is courteous</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is a culture of passive aggressive back-stabbing, executives who are out of touch with markets and their own company and not willing to learn. It has been milking the mouse for a very long time, and doesn't have an innovation engine to discover new ideas and get them to market in a timely fashion. The cycle of bloating with bureaucracy and then layoff is unsustainable. It drives people to safe roles, safe initiatives, and risk aversion.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Program Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's fun to develop & launch consumer electronic devices.”

</title><pros>Pros – Product Development process is well documented online.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Need to get back to namebrand identity with less workers from tough downsizing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't cut the critical job functions because the gaps will be wider, and more people will be de-motivated and feel lost.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Marketing Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“CHAOS”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a job but not a secure one</pros>
<cons>Cons – I dont know where to start.The management needs help...A LOT...all work seems to be dumped on some individuals and then those are usually the first ones to go</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – DO YOUR JOB! Stop putting people in charge that can not handle it...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“In transition”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work/life balance. Good people and environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor company morale.  Not a lot of advancement within company.  Employees seem to not care.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to provide career paths to attract and retain talent.  Improve company morale and commitment by employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Idiot Swiss French”

</title><pros>Pros – The businesses they are in are stable but not growing because the growth in the market is to phones and tablets, and those don't take many accessories.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you aren't Swiss-French you have no future in the company...and on top of that, the Swiss-French are total idiots.  So, be ready for a lot of stupidity working there....they seem to like it that way.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire Swiss French folks only, don't torture the rest of us you nationalistic jerks!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Program Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Some cool products. Just an 'ok' place to work for the bay area. Work/life balance depends on which BU you're in.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good products, generally keeping ahead of the market in most business units (but only just)Trying to do agileNow in a new building in Newark which is night and day better than the old placeReasonable perks - gym, discount on products, free coffee etc..</pros>
<cons>Cons – Mismanagement in recent years, layoffs, senior turnover, uncertainty. New CEO has good fundamentals but doesn't get the tech industry.Risk averse management, especially with software investments (admittedly badly burned by the Google TV product).Very little long term product vision.Way too much done in India, higher risk and less control.Weak engineering management resulting in outdated software and infrastructure.Ridiculous hours asked of employees in working with India offices. Constant 20 x 7 fire drillsUseless HR department and terrible medical options (Cigna have the doctors no other providers want)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve core software engineering and product management practices that enable India to function more autonomously.Look at getting revenue from software services as well as hardware, particularly in Digital Home and Music BUs otherwise the company will slowly die.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Executives need to go”

</title><pros>Pros – - good products- willing to spend on system, softwares</pros>
<cons>Cons – - no vision, no leadership from upper management- no accountability- focus on scholars hiring instead of real life experience- performance is not based on merits</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - check out the management's accomplishment - are they really worth retaining? Did you ever question why the recent restructuring wiping out entire departments after all, Logitech spent so much to implement?- Hold your management responsible for wasting money on retrenchment (they hired, terminated, then hired another bunch back), and on failed projects (this could be system projects as well)- stop hiring & Promoting relatives and friends that have absolutely no merits to the jobs</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Electrical Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work before the Great Recession”

</title><pros>Pros – Logitech has good benefits and reasonably enlightened management. Halloween was always a big deal, lots of fun. I'd definitely go back if I had a chance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Logitech has not proven that it is nimble enough to recover from the explosion of tablet computing and smartphones, which don't need much in the way of peripherals. Google TV was a huge mistake.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The company may need to shrink even more drastically to stay afloat.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Where is this company heading?”

</title><pros>Pros – Overbloated salaries to senior managers and low ranking managers alike!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Small minded senior execs, unable to see the big picture, too uneducated to understand basic market principals at the MBA level. Execs steal other employees ideas to label as own, and this is integrated into a unhealthy 'company culture'.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start with mission,vision,goals. Define and reward  leadership skills and stop rewarding cowardice and thieves in a frat boy environment. The basic principals of business ought to include putting customers,shareholders,employees first...or is that only for leading edge silicon valley innovative companies to abide by and honor?</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great, unforgettable experience.  Got me to the next level”

</title><pros>Pros – Culture of Great PeopleGreat ExperienceGood ProductsA Somewhat Cool Factor</pros>
<cons>Cons – Products lacking the wow factorLack on innovation internallyHave become the market followers instead of the market leadersToo many sub par productsExecutive management fails slowly</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get it together, get some cajones and make change.Be innovative, creativeGet the marketing organization organized</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior GPM (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice people, good work and life balance, but falling stock prices, and happy work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice peopleDemocratic decision processGood work life balanceMoving toward Mac platform</pros>
<cons>Cons – slow decision processsenior management seems to be out of refreshing ideas</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – let the lower ranked employees that's in the trenches make the small decisions. a BU VP should not be involved with product features discussions...</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very average experience, below market pay, no development or advancement”

</title><pros>Pros – Good exposure to different areas of the business.  Small company with tight knit feel.  Very social workplace and environment.  Strong market leadership position.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Extremely overfocused on hitting quarterly revenue numbers at the expense of long range strategy and development.  Below market pay and benefits.  Limited learning and advancement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to find a way to keep talent and reward strong employees to stop current brain drain.  Need to limit rat race like focus on quarterly numbers and drive medium and long term goals.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't work here if you are looking for fast paced environment and career advancement”

</title><pros>Pros – - Great work/life balance.- Nice people with a family feel.- Great Logitech discount if you buy a lot of their products.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Management is old school and is not open to changes.- Most employees have been with the company for a long time, so they are just not motivated and unwilling to change.- Company rarely promotes people from within.- Old buildings and no nice perks to work here.- Horrible HR. I have no idea what their HR does all day. When I was hiring candidates for my Department, I had to call the candidates themselves for the initial screening.- There's no incentive to work hard. You will get the same bonus and pay increase as everyone else even if you work your butt off.- Duplicate Management roles and departments.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to let go of the old school upper Management, especially the ones with duplicate roles.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Hardware QA Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Was good at the begining, but degradated later”

</title><pros>Pros – World known company. Good benefits. Interesting job. job require broad experience.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company has serious management problems.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – One engineer has approximately five managers. Usually, managers has low qualification and insufficient education, and unable to perform there job. Some managers does not respect employees. Management attempt to keep employyes opinion inside of deprtment.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall, decent place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good salary and benefits, generally fun products, interesting work.  Overall, a decent place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company struggling to do software "right."  Not good at managing hardware/software releases.  Fragmented products.  A fair amount of political and corporate posturing to climb various ladders.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop pretending that making a keyboard is the same as writing software and you can apply the same processes to either.  Stop gating physical product launches on software.  Understand that Logitech will increasingly be a "software" company, because these days good hardware needs great software to have any possibility of market success.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – High energy, extreme focus on results</pros>
<cons>Cons – poor communication between departments at ground level</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Worldwide Marketing (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Just like a big blue-chip - adjust your expectations!”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work-life balanceIntelligent, knowledgeable people to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management not always qualifiedTop-down approach</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please don't pretend to be interested in ideas from employees if you aren't going to really empower them to make improvements. If you want more of the same - admit it....</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company to work for!”

</title><pros>Pros – Logitech has a wonderfully positive environment, where the employees sincerely care about the products and company.  In addition, one has a feeling of their responsibilities and valued contribution.  The work-life balance is definitely another positive, where managers and peers respect one's daily priorities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Projects not always well defined or thought out from the beginning (though are usually successful)- Fremont location is not the prettiest for a larger-well known corporation.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Define expectations a better- Help with career planning and advancement- Provide more insight to opportunities within the company and company resources</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-31</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall great place to work at.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great co workersFun EnvironmentGreat payHolidays are a big event at logitech.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some employees can be immature and have others cover their shift. Managers tend to only higher employees that have a degree in business. At times the V.P. can make you feel lower than other employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Overall I believe what the managers are doing at logitech are productive.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Systems Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great direction, misguided paths..”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits, decent corporate culture. Great products.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low salary increases yearly, too many organizational changes on a regular basis.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The long-term goals Logitech has are good -- but the steps to get there aren't. Stop stepping on your technical customer base just to improve the footprint of your 'general' customer base.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Cool people, cool technology, relaxed environment on a personal level</pros>
<cons>Cons – decisions made my management take a long time to complete.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More communication is needed to the internal employees about company decisions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Logitech is OK”

</title><pros>Pros – Cutting edge technologyImplement and use products they makeglobal presence and opportunities to work with others outside the US</pros>
<cons>Cons – High rate of organizational change without middle management inputSalary is a bit lowTravel and Education benefits are non-existent except to senior management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in your employees, reduce the organizational change, seek advice from your frontline management. Understanding that decisions cannot be made with too many inputs the level of input solicited is very low.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor management, good people.”

</title><pros>Pros – There are many employees that are very friendly, very helpful, very competent. The staff is full of potential and untapped skill.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The staff is overworked and loosing hope. We've seen people cry during meetings because of stress and being bullied into unobtainable goals.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Clarify objectives and offer support to teams instead of placing the blame on your upper management. Stand up for your team and their efforts.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-09-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A small star in the high tech space”

</title><pros>Pros – Well managed company from Finance to Product StrategyGreat environment for capable and ambitious peopleSmall yet global company feel</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow in making its footprint on the stock market, despite its track recordGreat employee benefits, but too little recognition from the streetDefinitely not as bold as other high-tech companies, e.g. Apple</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees, probe us more oftenStick to the communicated plans, they seem like they will make a difference in getting the company to the next level of growth.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great location, not so bad pay, leadership is sub par...”

</title><pros>Pros – Many people here are nice and relatively genuine. Many also value hard work. The compensation isn't really bad all things considered. The products marketed are fabulous.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Competency in management is a hit or miss. There are a lot of silos. The internal database infrastructure is messed up! No central administration hub for all the darn databases that exist. It's very difficult to find what you need. Some of the process, specifically those dealing with procurement are really ridiculous and cumbersome. Overall, clear communication from management down to the subordinates is not very good...lacks quite a bit of attention.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take some courses on how to motivate your team and harness good skills. Build a backbone for getting rid of ineffective people!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very good place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Respect for work life balance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is a bias to hire from the outside or hire consultants instead of developing or utilizing internal capability.  This may not be unusual, but it can be distracting.  Also, there is a huge variability in management styles from group to group.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you are going to say "our biggest asset is our people" TREAT them like that.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-05-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great products and team support, poor automation and databases”

</title><pros>Pros – Great products with good partners. Clear goals on programs. Clear goals on the key products for the year. Benefits are include a stock program. Logitech is a good corporate citizen supporting charitable causes. Community spirit  for holidays and celebrating accomplishments.  Teams are supportive and help each other.  The products are very good and sleek.  There are clear owners for most functions.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Database are lacking. The dependence on Lotus Notes created Notes only databases.  You spend an inordinate amount of time searching for information and posting in various documents, spreadsheets, and emails.  This means most people spend their days just doing updates and posting rather than looking for opportunities and forward thinking.Logitech has bought several companies, but the consolidation process is very fragmented.  Senior management  allows the bought company to continue business without complying with the Logitech systems and brand. There is no firm schedule and no enforcement with consequences.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It is time to get some real databases and get off Lotus Notes.Companies bought by Logitech  need to be in Logitech systems and online in less than 6 months and senior management has to make it happen.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Development Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company but not anymore...”

</title><pros>Pros – Company had a great  can do spirit. Made fun products that were sexy and funtional. Hardware Engineering especially industrial design is a core competency. Have a loyal following of users. Global company with a european flair. Good coffee!</pros>
<cons>Cons – New management does not espouse the same spirit de core. People are less motivated then they were with previous CEO. New management does not incite the same passions.Headed downhil in many ways, sorry to say....</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get the hell of of there and let someone who knows what they are doing and is passionate about it take over.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun Place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Great products and feels like a family.  Many people even hang out together outside of work.  Had a support management of my schedule and gave me some freedom in my responsibilities.  When communicating with upper management, the response was positive and really heard.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not very good communication from upper management.As with large corporation, its difficult to change things.  Once a process is in, no one wants to "ruffle the feathers".Benefits are average if not on the low side.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have all managers meet with their employees somewhat regularly.  Hard to know exactly what is going on a lot of times.  Slow down some of the product launches.  Barely have time to learn from the past mistakes to change future product launches.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work Hard and try to free up enough time to Play Hard”

</title><pros>Pros – Discounts on the items produced is nice, profit sharing is also a nice thing. I like working here because our group has relative freedom to implement things the way that make the most sense. It is nice being able to get things done and get good feedback about a job well done.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very windows oriented in an environment that is shifting more and more to other platforms, we could easily fill better niches with our offerings, but we don't. Also there seems to be a lot of movement inside of our BU, people leaving and being replaced. Politics are also a pretty huge problem. Meetings, meetings, meetings. But that is corp life it seems!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Although each BU being an island may be useful, we are suffering from not sharing with each other. Also taking 3+ weeks to get items through the mail room is horrible.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Logitech - A good place and getting better.”

</title><pros>Pros – Logitech is a great company.  It's growing quickly which can cause some pain points, but overall the company is working to address those issues.  There are great benefits and a flexible schedule (depending on your department and manager).  There are many opportunities within the company including travel and living abroad.  Profit sharing, stock purchase programs, and nice vacation schedules round out the offering of goodies.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is an overall lack of communication between the higher level execs and the day-to-day workers.  There are also some "managers" that shouldn't be managing people at all.  I don't think there's a clear path to the career step and that hurts the company sometimes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – SPEAK!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company, great people and products”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of opportunities to be involved in making great products, having international business experience and chances to travel around the world - also great set of people to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too many office politics, fair to poor HR system for best match up of employees to roles in the company - also poor succession planning and ad hoc promotions of staff make it hard to understand what's needed to get promoted and success in the company</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More focus is needed on developing people and getting them more engaged in their jobs. There are a lot of new ideas and a lot of passion that we are not tapping into as a company and as managers/directors/VPs</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineering (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not bad, but could be better”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits- 401k match, quarterly profit sharing, espp and 4 weeks of pto to start. Depending on the department you are working for, seems like a family friendly company. Willing to accomidate schedules and allow flexible hours and working from home.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Seems the bigger the company gets, the more inefficient it gets. Too much politics sometimes and tasks are done just for the sake of doing them.  Also, as the company gets bigger, the work increases and more and more is piled on top of employees, but no additional headcount is added. Also, the annual pay raises are very low. Even for high performing individuals, the percentage is not even 5%.  Not much incentive to really meet all the goals assigned.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get back to basics on how it used to be. Stop being so stingy and be open to hiring more people. Soon good employees will get burnt out and start leaving.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good products”

</title><pros>Pros – Product Quality, Concern for customers, location</pros>
<cons>Cons – Building in bad shape, cubes old, poor interior</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have more pride in location</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Mcechanical Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“overall great company”

</title><pros>Pros – great benefits, profit sharing, consecutive growth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – in mechanical engineering, you have to travel overseas a lot and deal with problems related from offshore division. Offshore asian engineers have different mentality compared to the state. When you travel to taiwan or china, you expect to work a lot of hours and get the job done. There is constant communication problem between US and offshore engineers. You may have a design review at offshore site. You are the only person travel from the US and tons of asian engineers sitting in the conference room critique your design. It is not a good ad easy relationship. Product development time line is really short. One project is about 9 months. It started in sept, by march of next year, you better al nail down the issues, because validation coming up next few months, then production in summer and ready to ship worldwide for december holiday season distribution.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – there are political conflict between employees in the us and offshore</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Sale and Marketing (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Loved working there, but........”

</title><pros>Pros – the products, the people and their passion. The global nature of the company mean that you can work anywhere in  the world.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some of the senior management need to go. The Regions need to be pulled back into line, especially the America's region - what a joke! To many people promoted without the necessary skills and experience. Some senior managers cannot make a decision and have abdicated all decision making to the Regions - which only makes it more vague and complex in terms of who does what. To many senior manager decision are not backed up with actions - it's a "we want this to change, now you figure it out' mentality.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Man up! Support your CEO! Start firing dead wood and pull the regions back into line. Get some ROI into your decision making. Find someone with a marketing background to run your marketing org, back up your words with actions. Stop thinking rank and file will fix things - there are to many old timers that don't want things to change so it is up to YOU to make it happen.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice benefits, people, and pay, but insufficient planning, staffing, and communication.”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are nice, the benefits and pay are adequate, the products are excellent, and schedules for most positions are flexible (and often include telecommuting).</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company's downfall is a combination of inadequate communication, too little training and direction, unreasonable deadlines, lack of adequate planning and resource allocation, and excessive workloads due to insufficient staffing.  The company often acts without fully considering execution which creates a stressful and frustrating work environment for its already overloaded employees.  Logitech is a fast-growing company that is buckling at the seams.  Though likely to continue its economic growth, it will suffer as an organization if does not realize the value of its employees and act accordingly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increased staffing goes hand-in-hand with growing a company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Going downhill”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent pay and benefitsName recognition for your resumeCool technologyWorking with some of the brightest people out thereThere really are some amazing people working at Logitech in Toronto (Canada). If you can ignore most of the senior management, it would be a great place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management disconnected from realityAll R & D is tied to products with ship dates already set. Nobody is willing to take a chance on researching something that may delay that.Lack of connection between performance and recognition / respect / payNo direction or feedback from management when projects begin turns into obsessive micromanagement when projects near the finish line.Overall the management strategy seems to be:1- delay making any decisions, and finally abdicate all responsibility when the project risks being cancelled.2- swoop in months later and complain that the project lacks proper direction.3 - micromanage until the project is actually in jeopardy.4 - blame your team because after all, you've abidcated all of your responsibilites.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The harder you try to micromanage, the worse you make things. Step back and let good people do good work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineering Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company, great story, great growth ahead”

</title><pros>Pros – Family spirit, startup feeling, but already a big company at the same timeGreat management team, great prospects, great growth story, and products which are fun to make and to useThis is also a totally multinational company with people from many many countries, and design offices all over the world. Working in such multi-ethnic environment is very stimulating as you learn everyday from others. Job rotations are also promoted and it allows people to spend time in different locations/or divisions learning new skillsThe company is also totally focused on customers and trying to improve its products through customer feedback as much as possible</pros>
<cons>Cons – No downsides, except the fact that we are all very busy. Competition is tough and it keeps the team very active.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing the same great job, pushing company towards growth and keeping the team motivated for success.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Web Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's been over a year, and I still feel relieved to be out of there...”

</title><pros>Pros – My pay was decent.  The profit-sharing bonuses were nice too.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In my department, there was a pervasive lack of professionalism.  I did not trust my supervisor or upper management.  The longer I worked there, the more unethical behavior I saw.  They gossiped, played favorites, openly mocked and ridiculed non-click employees, and found ways to punish you if didn't support whatever they did and said.  The office was dirty and unkept.  They used antiquated, beat-up office furniture, and you had to walk around boxes and junk piled up in every available hallway, nook, and cranny.  Their refrigerators were antiquated and rarely cleaned (pew), and they didn't even replace the handles that apparently fell off way back when.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The only senior management I ever saw was the CEO, Guerrino De Luca, and that was because he was always standing outside his building smoking cigarettes.  He never smiled or spoke when I walked by--not that I minded.  He struck me as a non-people type, a strategist completely focused on stock price and the like.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sr. project manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Logitech made the best periphery in the world, it is funny to test and play with several product.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary not attractive, the management team not lead team to turn around when business goes down</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – the atmosphere of work is going down, many people start to leave Logitech</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly environment, well organized internally, perfect work environment, flexible work process, innovating products.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some processes complicated, need to adapt to market trend faster in terms of products</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – nothing special.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager, Product Management (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – innovative, market leader, great products, lots of upside potential soon, good management, work life balance ok</pros>
<cons>Cons – has 5 tough years behind them, organization stretched, not a lot of negative things to mention</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – keep on going</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Architect (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Architect”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to work, and you will have lot of opportunities to learn new technologies</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is very difficult to predict what is going to happen next</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – not much</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of opportunities to have an impact on business and to develop career.”

</title><pros>Pros – - Flat structure, everyone can't impact the business (Every employee is a "CEO")- Great products to sell and own- Good benefits- Nice culture despite the harder times- Great people</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Uncertainty due to various restructurings</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be less conservative in some areas</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Management sucks, globally, regionally and locally. Lousy HR.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work-life balance, nice colleagues, fun products</pros>
<cons>Cons – This is a company that does not value REAL good work. People cruised for years, doing minimal work, acting as 'postmen' without really adding value to the work, deadlines are missed without explanation, little sense of urgency, little transparency...Lousy management, global, region, and local!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get your act together!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Short term sales driven organisation”

</title><pros>Pros – Great quality products, family working atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No long term thinking, most of the business in sunset sectors, not willing to invest.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of pressure from upper management”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Salary.Good people to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots of pressure from upper managementNo recognition for employee's efforts. All efforts goes in vain and they listen only to management at the endNo work life balance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Automaton Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Freedom to lead and Take ownership”

</title><pros>Pros – ->Friendly environment->Lots of Fun->Agility in product dev</pros>
<cons>Cons – ->Need Better Management->Road Map should be clear</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do not change road-maps very often</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>ECommerce Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not recommend if you looking for job security”

</title><pros>Pros – Very flexible hours, fast decision making process.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too many re-structuring, no clear guidelines. un-analyical global management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“One of the worst companies I have come across! Hire and fire culture!”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexi hours, manageable workload, pleasant colleagues</pros>
<cons>Cons – Clueless and pompous management, both in global and regional teams. Roles are not clearly defined, organizational changes are just superficial exercises, moving people around with no clear push for them to perform in their new roles. People continue to do what they want to do, and not what their roles require them to do, many postmen around, and management does not seem to bother.While at the same time, these same senior managers continue to pounce and pick on other employees, whom may not be the smartest employees but try their best nonetheless.Inconsistent demands from managers to their team members even if they are in similar roles.Unclear roles and expectations from management, primarily because management is clueless themselves on what they want!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You don't deserve!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Channel Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent products but dissapointing team leadership”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible working hours but also means flexing the working time beyond normal working hours daily including Saturdays, Sundays, and public holidays. When you tell people you work at Logitech, they know where you work, and respect the products. Being a small division of Logitech, everyone gets some exposure to what will likely become award winning products when these products are still in the earliest design stages. Being a company that creates consumer computer peripherals and other electronics, you see your work reviewed publicly by the media, through customer reviews on sites and forums such as lowyat.net. A resume that shows a reasonable amount of time at Logitech is likely to anyone's career -- It has definitely helped mine post Logitech.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The politics and lack of empowerment.The Kuala Lumpur (HQ) office is an incredibly political environment, in the negative sense of the word. Very little seems to get done through the well publicized processes, but rather anything accomplished is done through political machinations, and verbally sabotaging other projects with senior management to get resources for your own project.It is a very stressful environment, where immediate turn around is expected on complex work, and "No response & Approved via email but later denies all allegations" are not acceptable at all. Work life balance is not a consideration -- work is expected to come first, at all times of the day, including Saturdays, Sundays, Public Holidays, Medical Leave and even during your once a year Chinese New Year official leave. Yet, you are expected to feel privileged for being given the opportunity to work at Logitech.Project management in the development area is almost non-existant, and is focused more on presenting what senior management wants to hear, and in this case they are expecting you to fulfil 100% of the ops target regardless of the reasons you provide. A few years ago this division was very diplomatic centric, and has an excellent leadership. New young management was brought in to take the team lead despite irrelevant working experience and they gave the new guy complete say over everything, but did not hire, nor train product managers to assume this role.Overall this is a very stressful place to work, and it takes a special person who knows how to work a corrupt system and who has a thick skin in the face of political attacks to succeed here.Very late response and support for communication, event planning, marketing, while sales target are reviewed quarterly with impossible numbers to achieve.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Decentralize management approach will move the company to a brand new level of success</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A nice company, with nice people and harmony atmosphere, but struggling in a sunset industry”

</title><pros>Pros – Great products, in-edge technology, nice people, human-touched environment, less hierarchy, product-orientation, solid brand, thrill opportunities to help people get immersed in the digital times</pros>
<cons>Cons – shrink PC industry, slow culture, vague future, integration and localization, big company disease, slow reaction to uprising competitors, lack of core technology or competence, weak knowledge management, unclear career path, tight headcount, budget and resource</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Getting worse, Hoping change”

</title><pros>Pros – Freedom in work environment. Good colleague. Brand value and sales channel are still strong. Cross site various cultures. Travel sometimes interesting.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too many lousy processes. PC industry downturn impact a lot. Looking for change direction, but no obvious vision yet. Bad working atomosphere due to layoff rumor.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pros and Cons”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun, Team spirit, good products, international</pros>
<cons>Cons – at the time: salaries not in line with market, no recognition, no career paths</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“company culture and environnement”

</title><pros>Pros – flexibiliy, nice working environnement, employees are responsible with goals set up</pros>
<cons>Cons – lack of management, managers do not manage, too much process and heavy administration with unclear responsability and ownership</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more acting & less administation,</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Mixed Bag”

</title><pros>Pros – Some Good Colleagues & Great Products</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some Horrible ColleaguesLack of leadership and vision from upper management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Either retire and move on, or stop being so stubborn and narrow-minded and do something productive.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Scrum Master, Acting Manager, Developer”

</title><pros>Pros – Enterprise Architect is SuperbTop Technologies & Methodologies</pros>
<cons>Cons – Overloaded work schedules makes us working 21 hours per day sometimes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please ensure right people on right job</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Logitech is a good place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people, good benefits, overall good company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some business units are hesitant to innovate. They have the ideas early but don't get management support for development until it is a "me too" product.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start trusting your people. Empower your teams and hold them accountable. Less micromanagement. Tell your team what you want and when you want it, not how to accomplish it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company to work for!”

</title><pros>Pros – Competitive SalaryGreat BenefitsLots of growth opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too many politics between departments</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“not loyal to partners,specially in north region, even sales people incentives are deducted to pay partners ..failed plan”

</title><pros>Pros – good brand support, but not planned to encash much,poor management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – wrong policies , zero in planning, every schemes hitting back, need to drive and chk from top level.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – keep eye on your north head , market repo is very poor.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Large corporation entity - great place for those seeking a corporate style environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Good insight into a PM (Project Management) driven company.  The company is very focused on UX (User Experience) which is the "new" paradigm.  Broad diversity of consumer products with a strong well established brand.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is possible to be sent for long periods offshore (Taiwan for example) with no specific return date in cases where a project is not meeting its release goals.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“bad management and leaders, not clear roadmap”

</title><pros>Pros – no long work hours, low work load</pros>
<cons>Cons – no roadmap, no direction, lack of goog management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – change change change</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager, Product Management (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Head User Experience and Product Management”

</title><pros>Pros – Agile, flat, Dynamic, consumer experience driven</pros>
<cons>Cons – lack of speed in innovation</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Data Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good one”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work -life balancegood growth and cross culture work expemployee benefit is very good</pros>
<cons>Cons – Top management focus & vision is not clear, lot of decision is made by individual not as a team, so whenever new person takes a role, he denies previous decisions.Some manager plays dirty politics to promote their favorite ppl.recently HR started creating trouble. lot of politics is growingTop management is very skeptical and negative about india operations.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to be transparent. be professional, not personal.Otherwise it's fine.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Helpful for professional growth...”

</title><pros>Pros – Good play, pleasant environment, innovative, and more</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slightly disconnected management and lack of communication...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good stepping stone focused, creative and open”

</title><pros>Pros – people are its best assets</pros>
<cons>Cons – salary is the biggest issue as it doesn't match with the industry</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – training</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work culture at chennai office”

</title><pros>Pros – Good money in short time</pros>
<cons>Cons – poor work culturehire n fireNo employee care</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – don't treat people, unhumanly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Golden Days are over”

</title><pros>Pros – Some of the best people I have ever worked with in the trenchesThe products are brilliant, in spite of the company's shortcomingsThe company has a wonderful history</pros>
<cons>Cons – Executive management needs to be replacedThere are no longer opportunities for promotionThe company has a long history of having a passive-aggressive cultureOnce you make a mistake, you are blacklistedAdding complexity and process (or a re-organization) are the only tools they have to manage change</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It's time to go.  Replace your executives who have been there for too long and are the ones really dragging things down.  Set a better example for your staff by empowering them, rather than forcing them to implement your plans, then blaming them when things go wrong.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Struggling to find a direction. Good people.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work/life balance. Competitive salary.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Struggling financially and there are constant reorganizations.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Core products - but speed to market is slowing”

</title><pros>Pros – - some good talent, good people- interesting tech</pros>
<cons>Cons – - alot of people didnt add value- too slow to market</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – In getting back to core, make sure you dont cut too much!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Old School”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits are great. Pay is good. Some of the products are interesting. Good employee discount. There are some fun things like a large Halloween celebration every year.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is horrible! Logitech is stuck in the past with their development practices. Shallow talent pool because the work environment is not friendly. Management likes to lead via fear and intimidation. Stressful work environment with too much formal process.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Quit. Fire yourself and let the board hire competent leadership using modern practices and processes. Do more to keep your good engineers, fire the bad ones and modernize so you can recruit new ones. This isn't 1998 anymore. The days of webcams and mice/keyboards ruling the day are long gone. Wake up and innovate before it's too late.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – - innovative team- good people</pros>
<cons>Cons – - not so good at mentoring- no appreciation for good work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get back the company to its charm and focus on its core capabilities.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great brand”

</title><pros>Pros – - Great people- Great Brand- Part of an innovative consumer electronic experience</pros>
<cons>Cons – - At times, unclear guidelines- Poor communication of organization changes & reorganization- Excessive middle management without unified direction</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Its a truly great company, incredible brand with phenomenal market potential and avid & loyal customer base. But its important for the brand and company to stay relevant with the latest tech trends. The current management infrastructure is not optimized to address the company's greatest competitive advantages - its economies of scale, brand awareness and reputation for being an industry leader in peripherals and an innovative gamechanger. Due to unclear company direction and and non cohesive strategic execution, its cost the company. Recommend having strong management in place, empower employees and clearly define a direction.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work in terms of Worklife Balance but not the best if you want a fast paced dynamic and growing company”

</title><pros>Pros – Work Life Balance is one of Logitech's strengths!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of direction and focus on business strategy.  Lack of investment in innovation and following the technology curve.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Figure out a clear business direction and strategy and stick to it.  Get Logitech on track to compete at the technology table and strive for innovation as a key strength.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK, not amazing”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent hours, free Logitech products.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not very stimulating, lower-than-average salary.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Larger salaries, more autonomy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Work Life balancePeople are super goodManagement is respectfulOpen communicationGood Pay structureTeam SpiritCool productsHalloween is fun!!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – After a while career growth is stalled.Upper management was not much focused on the peopleLonger tenure doesn't mean job security</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Program Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Satisfied and glad that I have the chance to expand my experience into Consumer Electronics”

</title><pros>Pros – - if you excell they will promote- compensation package is consistent with the industry</pros>
<cons>Cons – - very poor mentoring- if you do not excel they will cut you- coordination of message between BUs not well done- product alignment within portfolios needs to be improved</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - ugly ducklings do turn into swans, with a little time and guidance- consolidation of workforce can be a business decision but also an interesting one to make when you throw away the innovation generators- moving core business elements to India may prove more problematic then mgmt are aware of</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Too much turnover...”

</title><pros>Pros – Employee discount on products are good.  People are nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very top down.  No development opportunities.  Management brings in their own people and replace employees already there.  Do not follow policy from within.  Not a teamwork environment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take a long hard look at your Sr Mgmt and what they are doing within their own groups.  Many employees are unhappy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work life balance but lack of growth opportunities”

</title><pros>Pros – Work isn't too much and can always leave on time.  Dynamic company with lots of changes happening in the last year or so.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I was never able to take long holidays during my 2.5 years with Logitech.  My manager would turn down my leave request to since her vacation time takes priority to mine!Although workload is ok but you should expect to be stuck doing the same thing since the company does not value job rotation nor career growth...they just need someone to do the job!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay more attention to the turnover rate in each region - this is an indication of how happy the employees are!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“-”

</title><pros>Pros – Great team. Amazing projects to work on.</pros>
<cons>Cons – lower salaries than expected, comparing to the amount of dedication expected from employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – give higher salaries</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Support Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Troubleshooting incoming calls from from Logitech Customers”

</title><pros>Pros – - Great staff- Very friendly management\- Excellent communication skills between management and staff- Fun place to work and grow your career- Logitech looks great on any Resume!</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Takes a long time to move up the corporate ladder however this is expected in todays economy</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Keep up the great communication styles- Try to invest a little more in those high performers when it comes to career development</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“not bad work here”

</title><pros>Pros – Overall not bad and ok  to work at logitechgood and talent co-workerok salary</pros>
<cons>Cons – Logitech's senior management doesn't value accountability, competence and dedicationbenefitnot very care employeebenefit getting worse</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Believe half of what you see and none of what you hear”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a paychequeGood benefitsGreat people (Logitech doesn't know how lucky they are)</pros>
<cons>Cons – -A lot of talk about how Logitech values employees is just that -talk. Promotions or rewards for hard work are few and far between, and there is little or no career development or training (except the occasional token gesture)-Political environment, often incompetent people promoted over competent. (As long as you work long hours you will get recognized regardless of output)-Moral is low in Mississauga office, people disappearing constantly (by choice or not) and head count is not replaced-If you are looking for a long term career move don't come here unless you are planning to move to India soon.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make sure your words and actions line up (because they don't, and your employees know it)Stop treating your employees like children and be straight up with them.After a tough restructuring followed by two years of hard work employees need a little bit more than a free dish of ice cream at a townhall meeting to thank them for their dedication.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Thinking to join Logitech - better think twice. It is all about the $, not about you.”

</title><pros>Pros – Bonus is paid quarterly.Good discount for Logitech products.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Scrum/Agile means justified chaos, lack of vision, and 2 weeks deadline.Unpaid overtime required on a regular basis.Management is selected based on words, not achievements.The deadlines are unrealistic.The rank and file contributor is bullied on a daily basis.Too much effort is required to get things done.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management should be about providing vision, care for your employees, and getting things done. In your place is about politics, control, and Agile dogma.Participating in a Townhall in Logitech is a sad experience. There is nothing about employees. It is almost like you talk with your stockholders.Create a culture or you will dissapear.You shouldn't make mass layoff when you have double digit growth.Your oursourcing effort to India, shows why lowering taxes to big corporations doesn't mean they will create jobs.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good top managementgood employee discount</pros>
<cons>Cons – Career growth is very less or have to have connections.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take care of employee's career growth and salary increments</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Products do not reflect the disorganized work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – if you're a gadget geek, then working for Logitech is great because of discounts.  If you are comfortable doing the same thing and are good at it, you can have job stability.</pros>
<cons>Cons – internal communication is terrible.  lots of confusion and it feels like the company reacts to what the market is doing instead of forging ahead and looking forward.  innovation seems reactionary.  there are a lot of people who i would say are weak links that work here.  it always amazes me that they can keep their job while some people who are pretty good get let go.politics are a large part of logitech.  if you want to advance, you most likely need to change groups.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – please provide org charts that make sense and show how one might want to advance their career.  make job descriptions available and adhere to them.  everyone is working outside the scope of what they were hired to do.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Logitech's senior management doesn't value accountability, competence and dedication.”

</title><pros>Pros – Challenging products, international exposure, good brand.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Logitech's senior management doesn't value accountability, competence and dedication.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work but very chaotic and fast paced, some very immature employees”

</title><pros>Pros – Management shows appreciation through paid lunches, team outtings, off-site meetings. Great profit sharing plan in this very profitable and growing company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some very immature and arrogant employees who need to grow-up.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Deal with the immature employees.Be open to new ideas for products and services rather than being dismissive.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“overall good co-workers here”

</title><pros>Pros – good company culture and a stable environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – a bit fragmented, and quite many silos</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – building your team is as important as building power</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Used to be a great company to work for, but lots of growing pains as it scales”

</title><pros>Pros – Global environment.  Nice people.  Flexible if you get the right manager.  Decent worklife balance expectation, although some people are way overloaded.  Fun and innovative products.  Good balance between a big and small company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor communication of priorities and vision from senior management.  Has become too process-driven - too easy to spend too much time in the muck of navigating the system instead of on the content of your job.  Very little cohesive marketing vision to pay off the great work on product.  Mediocrity is sometimes ok, and high performers are not always recognized the way they should be.  It's also very difficult to tell what the bar should be to get to the next level.  Some people without much accomplishment are inexplicably labeled as high potential.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – We need real vision and STRATEGY.  Help us connect the dots to where this fragmented company is going.  We have amazing products and technologies.  We have lots of the pieces.  But it sometimes seems as if no one at the top really has a vision for how it all fits together...and when bits of that vision emerge, it can be a letdown.  We have a lot of fruitcakes and priority lists, but that middle layer where it's supposed to translate down to execution is missing.  Oh, and HR is a liability.  Human capital is not seen as strategic; it really feels like we as employees are rather expendable.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Logitech Review”

</title><pros>Pros – Culture is great.  People work hard, but it's a fun place to work so you don't mind.  The executive staff are visible and available to everyone.  They are not in their ivory towers separate from the rest of the company.  Communication from the top down is important and management stresses that.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Offices could be polished/upgraded.  A majority are 20 years old and really show it...a bit embarrasing with customers, etc.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the culture alive!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Please respect your employee!”

</title><pros>Pros – People are friendly. Very nice colleagues to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company has infrastructure changes since 2009. Positions have been transferred to India to save $$$. Many people were cut off recently. Overtime is usual.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please respect your people!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent Place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Products, People, International Experience and culture</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours, 24x7 response required, travel for long periods</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Offer programs to help work/life balance. Actively solicit and respond to input directly from Employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great, supportive work environment, interesting projects involving cross-functional and cross-cultural teams.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited career opportunities in non-US offices.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't forget your offices outside of Fremont!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Logitech a new place”

</title><pros>Pros – We are working on new technologies that are very hot on the market including: WCF, WPF / Silverlight, Web Services, etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – We are following the agile project management methodology and the work is very intense. We have 2 weeks iterations and the deadlines are comming fast all the time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would like to have more involvement from the management, looking over the people and making sure they have a change to develop and they don't get burn-out.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Neutral place to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. 50 percent off all products is a nice perk2. Good working environment as everyone is friendly and kind</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Bad location2. Salary was not good3. No proper career advancement or path</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – HR really needs to be focusing on engagement and career advancement</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great passion, poor processes”

</title><pros>Pros – People are great--have a lot of passion and energy for the products.  Amazing products and innovation. Small startup company feel.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Failure to adhere to processes. Passionate people turn into verbally abusive people at times.  HR function is WEAK. Redoing things constantly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in your existing talent.  Be fair in the way you approach your employees' growth.  Create an environment that supports growth, mutual respect, and synergies.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineering Development (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Talk too much, do too less”

</title><pros>Pros – - Very good  products with talent smart patent- Do what you can do .  A lot of meetings is kind of relaxing time</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Do more or less , doesn't matter due to most of  managers are not knowledgeable what they are doing /talking.  Working culture is  encouraging - " SPEAKING MORE, DOING NOTHING , THEN GETTING PROMOTION "</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get rid of the bum managers. Keep the talent engineering resources. promote real R&D value. improve productivity /effectiveness.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-08-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Intern software engineer”

</title><pros>Pros – People are very nice and helpful. My supervisor was a PHD so very knowledgeable. Everybody treats me with respect, as an intern it is very valuable...</pros>
<cons>Cons – One of their office is in Vancouver (WA) which is a small town. The location is not ideal but Portalnd is close and one can easily live in Portland and work in Vancouver.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Nothing in particular, my manager was very nice and available when I needed him. He also helped me to find occupation during the week-end.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Developer, Harmony (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Recently joined the team. Cool products, cutting edge technologies, opportunity ahead!”

</title><pros>Pros – Joined the Harmony division of Logitech 6 months ago. Love working here. The products are cool and there is  great team environment. The company has grown from a start up mentality to a professional company. Recently some outstanding engineering professionals have joined from some well known companies. Some of the best engineers can be found here today. Company is changing fromI" to "We" , some people left or ... as this happened. Lots of customer research, usability studies - engineers are encouraged to attend - very new for me  good learning experience !</pros>
<cons>Cons – Fast paced environment requires you to keep you to speed on all the technologies. Learning some great new skills and technologies. Training is awesome - hard to sometimes keep up. Will like to hear more about other products from Logitech.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stay on path! Love the focus on developing people. Encourage engineers at Harmony to bring their friends to come work here!  Reference bonus will be nice :)</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Respect professionals”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a globally recognized company. You feel yourself a part of a big team. The company has gathered many great professionals and just great individuals, who create a friendly working environment. The company provides in most cases a fair balance between work and private life of people, though stressful situations and pushing from top down occurs quite often as well.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of technical leadership. The top management does not respect the feedback from the engineers. The product development roadmaps are built with no serious analysis of technical and ecomomical factors. A good help would be a detailed analysis of the competitors' products. The analysis should include the choice of technologies, general architecture, set of features, model lines, etc.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to the professionals, work as a team, not as a commander and a batallion of soldiers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor software product management and good products”

</title><pros>Pros – 1) Excellent product, globally leading products, Harmony Remote.   2) Software team is developing brand new application.  After the outside crisis it should be in a good position for growth. 3) Management is trying to develop and grow people.  Training investment. 4) Scrum process 5) Excellent General Manager 6) People are generally very good and competent 7) Relatively solid and creative working relationship 8) Innovative 9) Good investment in usability and consumer research</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1) Too much top-down approach to schedules and planning 2) The mgmt. (both Mississauga and Fremont) is disconnected often from realistic goals - often the wish list   3) Product management (director level) in New York very disconnected and extremely poor in doing things.  A lot of bad decision and incompetent work from them. Vendor management non-existent.  A lot of grandstanding without results.  A lot of money spent with very small results  4) Software product mgmt. extremely bad, minding the things they don't understand and does not complete their own job (example major rewrite of stories done by someone else) . The new PM hopefully influence change.  4) Meeting quality within projected timeline is not realistic 5) Product /hardware team has a lot of organizational and execution challenges 6) Expectations are sometimes too high and unrealistic 7) Longer hours for someone 8) Support team business model broken (too costly)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 1) The layoff was too deep, sooner rather than later you need additional good people2) Software Product management is a lot of talk, with negative results not even zero results.  Top down needs to be changed, starting from New York's director below to the more experienced PM.3) You need to bring additional engineering talent4) Hardware side has execution challenges.  Main delivery challenges are there.5) Right type of investment and help from Fremont is needed but additional creative freedom would be helpful6) Get realistic plan and closely monitor real not presented to mgmt. progress7) Be aggressive with the market push8) More real innovations9) Develop sound support business model</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Spirit of Logitech”

</title><pros>Pros – The unique fun, dynamic, and entrepreneurial work environment but which is quickly changing to a more standard multinational corporate setting under the new Sr. Management. Exposure to a wide scope of tasks in your daily job, you develop more general skills in a shorter time frame and career progression is faster than average, again also less true today than a couple of years ago. Still have some fantastic products and super engineers working on the next ones, I cross my fingers that no one will break that.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Typically less structured work environment and mostly short-term goal oriented. Career progression is faster than average, in some cases leads managers to focus more on their next step up rather than doing the best at their current job. There is a bloated and too inexperienced middle management layer, and need more strong individual contributors in the more junior positions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Should take example from early leaders. Build back the unique Logitech spirit and management's strong multiculturalism that made the company's strength for 25 years. New Sr. management seems less hands-on and more disconnected from the realities of the marketplace leading to sometimes miss-aligned objectives and policies. Logitech needs stronger processes and organization, but not at the cost of what made its brand and unique work environment.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>6</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Political, Stressful Place to Work with No Employee Empowerment”

</title><pros>Pros – When you tell people you work at Logitech, they know where you work, and respect the products. Being a small division of Logitech, everyone gets some exposure to what will likely become award winning products when these products are still in the earliest design stages. Being a company that creates consumer computer peripherals and other electronics, you see your work reviewed publicly by the media, through customer reviews on sites like Amazon and in various forums. A resume that shows a reasonable amount of time at Logitech is likely to anyone's career -- It has definitely helped mine post Logitech.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The politics and lack of empowerment.The Mississauga office is an incredibly political environment, in the negative sense of the word. Very little seems to get done through the well publicized processes, but rather anything accomplished is done through political machinations, and verbally sabotaging other projects with senior management to get resources for your own project.It is a very stressful environment, where immediate turn around is expected on complex work, and "No" or "let me think about it" are not acceptable answers.  Work life balance is not a consideration -- work is expected to come first, at all times of the day, and you are expected to feel privileged for being given the opportunity to work at Logitech.Project management in the development area is almost non-existant, and is focused more on presenting what senior management wants to hear rather than managing projects and risks, and presenting the facts to management.A few years ago this division was very development centric, and a stronger product management role was needed. New senior management was brought in and they addressed this issue by giving product management complete say over everything, but did not hire, nor train product managers to assume this role. While this is a difficult situation for other functions, I feel most sorry for product managers who are now required to make every decision.Overall this is a very stressful place to work, and it takes a special person who knows how to work a corrupt system and who has a thick skin in the face of political attacks to succeed here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Walk the talk.You hold a lot of town hall meetings where you talk about things like empowerment, and customer centricity, and then do the exact opposite.Saying you are empowered, because the video we showed you says this is a good thing, while removing decision making power and centralizing it with extreme senior management and product managers doesn't jive.Talking about the importance of listening to the customer and then selecting projects that customers are clearly saying they don't want but that are pet projects of senior management doesn't jive.You need to understand that you are managing a very intelligent work force, and feeding them platitudes and rhetoric while acting in an opposite manner, and publicly rewarding people who act in the oposite manner, is noticed and greatly impacts employee morale and completely erodes your work force's oppinion and respect for you and your decisions. Which means, that in the end many very smark people don't work hard or care about the products they work on any more</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-02-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – A good place to work. With good benefits and perks.The main reason to join or keep working here has to be the technologies and the exciting products being developed.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Often you don't get recognition for work done.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The ratio of managers to developers is unreal!!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-02-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people and products, drowning in a sea of organizational despair!”

</title><pros>Pros – Really cool products. Fun, challenging problems to solve. Great team atmosphere among organizational peers. Many really talented employees, and an excellent manager or two.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots and lots of hard work, with very little thanks. Creative and innovative engineers are stifled in an overly political and sometimes hostile work environment. Management is not willing to accept responsibility for the consequences of their decisions. Too many decisions are made trying to have their cake and eat it too. The schedules are unrealistic and the stress of meeting unreasonable deadlines is downloaded onto engineering.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you want to make more innovative, leading-edge products, cultivate an environment where creative expression is welcomed and praised, instead of instituting mind-numbing, ill-informed processes which allow the dead weight to further entrench themselves in the organization. Build time for innovation and learning into product schedules. Find out what makes your engineers tick and use that information to leverage their full potential.One last thing, just because you say something, or put it on a slide, doesn't mean its true, or will just happen. Back up your words with a solid strategy and personally ensure it is put into action!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-12-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Quality Assurance (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“New management sucks large”

</title><pros>Pros – Most are good people.  Some are jerks.  Great products (sometimes).</pros>
<cons>Cons – New management blows goats.  Re-orgs killed the morale across the board.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The remote is not a mouse.  Get to know who your staff.  When you say you care about customers, mean it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A software company that also makes cool cutting edge products”

</title><pros>Pros – I am a software engineer in the Harmony Remote division - have learnt more in the past 6 months than I learned in my entire university life. There is so much cool software being developed at Harmony (web, embedded). What I love most is the adoption of  scrum/agile development. It is an amazing process for developing software - enables lots of collaboration across the team. I also like the coaching management style and the opportunities we are being given to develop our skills and apply them.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are other businesses at Logitech which are also developing some great products. At some point, would like to more closely with them to look at integration opportunities.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It is great to see your commitment to quality and customers. Great job in communication and creating an informal atmosphere that allows lots of interaction and communication.The management focus in developing teams and people is good - we could use more training in certain areas.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>QA Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good focus on team, quality and customers.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good team and fun place to work - everyone gets along and wants to help each other. One gets a chance to learn new skills. Have the opportunity to learn about customers and their needs. "Lunch and learn" sessions about customers are great. I have not worked in a company that has so much focus on quality and customer experience. It makes it hard for all of us as we are asked to meet tough standards but in the end is great for our customers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not much of a downside but have to work with the teams from asia. It would be helpful to have classes in chinese so that we can communicate better with our partners in Asia sometimes. Also, we need to balance a lot of things at any given time. Would also like some formal outside training.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Good effort on sharing the strategy. Would like to be involved earlier and have a chance to contribute more ideas. Management should encourage employees even more to share ideas with their functional and project teams. Also, the team appreciates easy access to everyone in the company including management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Engineer. (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good team -getting better every day!”

</title><pros>Pros – Cool company that makes exciting products. Management team does a good job in communicating with the employees. The management team has made lots of good changes in the past year. There is focus on hiring smart people. Many people have been promoted from within. I have never seen so much focus on sharing customer knowledge. There is genuine interest in people's careers - that is unique!</pros>
<cons>Cons – The facility feels cramped at times. I hear we are moving shortly. The management team has made some tough decisions in the past year - they should have anticipated some turnover and prepared for it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Like the new direction and the new technologies. Keeps our skills cutting edge. Your focus on building the right team is correct and will pay off in the future.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work in a company with lots of trainings!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent products!!  I would have a lot of cutting edge toys available once in a while.  A huge number of trainings -- to a point that you might not have time to do the real work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It seems to be a company that treats outsider (consultants) more than its internal employees.  You will need to prove really hard in order to earn the trust that you should.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take actions on what the employee said.  Don't just say I agree in front of the employee, and acts nothing afterward.  It is truly unrespectful to the employee.  Allocate more time for employee to work on his own.  More creative and outstanding product will be created.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>11</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You'd be stupid to work here”

</title><pros>Pros – There is a certain prestige in working at the company with its name recognition</pros>
<cons>Cons – Incompentent executives, no respect for employees at all, no understanding by the executive team of what is required to get a product out the door.  Executives listen to employees that have no respect of their peers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Quit.  Seriously, look at the number of people that have left and the quality of the people you have lost, explain why you fired the only manager that was able to get products out the door.  If you can't do that, leave before you do more damage to the company and the Harmony brand of remote controls</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Program Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fantastic place to work, outstanding management and R&D team!”

</title><pros>Pros – There are an excellent group of people that work at Logitech in the Remote control business unit.  All employees have a genuine interest in seeing the company succeed.  The dedication, team work and sense of pride within the company are outstanding, proof positive is the company’s journey of continual improvement which includes but is not limited to professional training and personal mentoring programs.  Logitech is truly interested in doing whatever it takes to build a team of successful individuals whom are focused on being the leader in every market they enter....these are not only words, they put their dollars behind it....whether people work as customer service agents..... or directors, there is a true sense of investing in continual improvement.  Harmonies is the leader in our segment and continue to improve our R&D, product mix and people in an effort to improve and dominate our existing line of products while entering new markets.   The management team brings a wealth of experience and knowledge from a variety of industries and is extremely focused on making Logitech the world leader and innovator in the remote controls business.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Logitech is growing at an astonishing rate, with that comes some hick-ups.  These are not uncommon when dealing with this type of business.  The team is overachieving in managing its growth and is as dedicated and competent as any other organization that I have been a part of.  Comparatively speaking I think Logitech is a great place to work and it will only get better.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I think they are doing a great job, I don't believe they should make any changes.  Any setbacks they may have experienced are simply growing pains that all company tends to experience.  Keep up the good work and dedication to the success of the company and its employees and shareholders!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>6</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Administrator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ambivalence”

</title><pros>Pros – Logitech provides some great benefits like flexible work hours and flexible location.  They do not skimp when providing me with the tools to do my job.  Brand new equipment is ordered as necessary, ranging from workstations to laptops to servers.  Being a consumer electronics company, they are not shy in giving away their products to employees for home office or office usage.  I have a fully decked out home office with Logitech shwag and more hanging out in my desk in the office.  No complaints in that regard.  The work from home ability totally disconnects you from office politics and allows you to focus on your work instead of people's hurt feelings.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Communication is poor across the board.  From top down and bottom up.  There is also a culture of laziness within the corporation, especially to hire consultants to do the job of the employees.  No accountability for people's actions as a result of hiring of consultants, and the constant looming budget problems as a result of people unwilling or simply unable to fulfill the mandate of their positions.  When a job is done poorly, there seems to be little repercussion and this does not fill you with any sense of pride.  A job well done is always overshadowed by the incompetence of another or the failing to do the right thing in order to ship a product out on some mythical line in the calendar.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work on the communications.  Seriously.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-07-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type> Network Administrative  (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The great employees, products and ideas are overshadowed by incompetent managers and politics.”

</title><pros>Pros – You get a nice mouse and keyboard to work on.  Sometimes a free engineering sample might come your way.  The "non management" people are generally great to work with.  There is the very rare manager that is excellent but that is the exception and not the rule.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some managers can't find their ass with both hands.  It truly surprised me that some managers were not fired and in fact many get promoted.  Also don't bother working hard because your manager doesn't care and neither does anyone else.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start to clean house because you are not making as much money as you could be while carrying all the dead weight.  Moral will improve and so will your products.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>8</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Designer/Team Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't expect to have your great efforts recognized or rewarded.”

</title><pros>Pros – Best-in-class products, the chance to work on actual product developement.  You get a really nice mouse, and some other nice techy gadgets, too.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Wow, where to begin?  They have a pretty good process around hardware production, but for software, they suck.  I work in the Harmony Remote business unit, and we make a very software-intensive product, and I can tell you that senior management has not the least gently-caressing clue about how to manage software development.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Wake up to the fact that Harmony remotes are not just another kind of mouse -- that the early success of the product came mostly from the genius of the software founder and the later efforts of the original Harmony software team.  Learn to recognize the achievements and contributions of the excellent development talent you have, or had.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>9</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Developer/Senior Team Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“"Empowered" to update my resume and get the hell out.”

</title><pros>Pros – Profit sharing pays off - We haven't had a truly bad quarter for years (there was one with only single-digit growth... for shame!)Flexible work hours.. though there seems to be movement to restrict that.Working from home... some are able to make it a regular thing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Incapable Project Managers; too many unproductive meetings,  PM's that require babysitting by their own manager (doesn't that inspire confidence?).  Projects that are apparently run by two or more PM's at the same time (and who really knows which controls the project), PM's who don't understand what they are being told (or don't want to), others who couldn't motivate a dog to wag its own tail.Product Managers who have their heads so far up each others asses that they haven't got a clue what they really want in a product, or from their engineers.  Perhaps that's not fair - they want everything, they want it now, and they don't want to spend any money to get it.  While there are elements to this that constitute so-called "good business practice", Logitech's Project Managers seem to take this to extremes, resulting in an endless barrage of complex functional requirements with ridiculous cost and schedule restrictions - you can't spec-out, design, build, and validate a "10x Customer Experience" on $2 worth of (mostly new) hardware in 5 months.  Especially when you are STILL SPECCCING IT OUT (hardware and software) with 5 months to go until Feature Complete.Lack of respect.  I observed an employee asking the PM for assistance with collecting some data in order to produce a valid document required for a project Gate transition.  The manager proceeded to explain that "we're a team", "we're all in this together", and that the employee should stop using the word "I" and get his work done.  Ultimately, this employee was unable to accomplish the task effectively, and was called down for it.I later had a similar experience with this same so-called leader.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen, and I mean REALLY listen to what your engineers have to say.  Trust their knowledge, experience and especially their effort estimates - they're doing all the work, they know what it takes.Empowerment isn't just a line on a presentation, if you are really serious about empowerment then stop handcuffing us.Innovation requires risk.  We can't be "Empowered to Innovate" when you consistently follow the path of least resistance.  Doing the easy thing, making the easy product in order to make the easy money isn't going to attract the ace talent you're going for.  You'll be lucky to retain what you have.Saying we're all Empowered is one thing, but I have yet to see any evidence.Stop Hiring Managers and start hiring Engineers.  Managers do not design and build products.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Embedded Software Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I think its a great place to work for Hardware and QA Engineers -- but not so much for Software Developers.”

</title><pros>Pros – -> Can work from home quite frequently.  Logitech often allows employees to work remotely.-> Intriguing technologies.-> Logitech truly has a dominant market position for most of its major products.-> Compensation really isn't bad.-> The hours are somewhat flexible (except during crunch times).-> There are some exceptionally bright people at Logitech.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -> Don't pay overtime.-> Performance reviews are missing glaring details.  Performance review scheme involves highlighting and focusing on negatives.-> Often fail to recognize and reward excellence in the workplace.-> Software development process is flawed.  Release processes are better suited to hardware products.-> There are some exceptionally dumb people at Logitech -- people who are rude, boorish, discourteous, and insulting.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – -> Please try to understand what's really going on in the company.-> If you have achieved record profits this past year, please feel free to share some with the little people at the bottom.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>