<name>E-Meditek Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/E-Meditek-Reviews-E380370.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Experience at E-Meditek”

</title><pros>Pros – division of work is their and you can meet top people if you are in corporate sales.their is clear division of workyou can give preference of week holiday</pros>
<cons>Cons – earlier division of work was not properpreviously maintained database contained errors which needed to be rectified.work life balance is poor, sometimes you get loads of work and other day tou are idle</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – See what happens under your nose, old employees working from start are not doing anything and always get their portion of work done new employees, they just sit and relax</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Vice President (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“poor employee moral due to mismanagement”

</title><pros>Pros – never work for emeditek as not employee friendly after you join</pros>
<cons>Cons – financial and work etheics are not there</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – try to be employee neutral if you cannot be friendly, chnage management style try to be professional</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“software developer”

</title><pros>Pros – got to learn sql and insurance industry</pros>
<cons>Cons – no appraisals,nothing new to learn technology wise</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – please provide time to time training for new technologies</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-31</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“single person manages everything this size not possible to manage employee avarage span 6 months”

</title><pros>Pros – nothing great about this company it is a poor show</pros>
<cons>Cons – poor management and no values, nobody gets salary in time and people leaving dues are never settled. funds are channeled somewhere else.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – ????</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Relationship Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“In E-Meditek i have come to know how to deal with clients, provide solutions to their queries & make them happy.”

</title><pros>Pros – Proper HR policy; co-ordination from immediate senior to top most senior, works like a team.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Politics between one department employees & other department employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to know the emotions & need of the lower level employee & make them satisfy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-14</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Distt Co Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bakwas”

</title><pros>Pros – World best Company from the last</pros>
<cons>Cons – Every month salary late credited in ac... Expenses never credited</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Nobody wants to listen...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>