<name>G Adventures Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/G-Adventures-Reviews-E382163.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-03-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Adventure Specialist, Inside Sales (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing job if you have another form of income”

</title><pros>Pros – Tons of opportunity for travel with an exciting environment and amazing trips. You get to talk travel all day, entrepreneurial environment.  If you work hard and put in the time opportunity to advance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – very low pay (almost min wage) and long hours.  A”cult type" environment, where most peoples personal life and work life is one in the same. A lot of inter politics. Management can be arrogant and usually without post-secondary education or management experience.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – raise the pay at least enough for people to be able to buy food.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly staff, always ready to assist</pros>
<cons>Cons – too much work load at times</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Division of labour in foreign branches</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Chief Experience Officer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome Experience, Not for Everyone”

</title><pros>Pros – Tons of travel, meeting great people, learning new languages and cultures, once in a lifetime experience.  Each day really was a new adventure, I was always learning, meeting new people from all parts of the world.  Lots of fun excursions and experiences.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited salary as a tour leader, but if you learn to budget and make good tips, it is plenty.  Difficult to maintain personal relationships, not much time off, no real "home" while leading tours, but contracts are generally for less than two years, so it's worth the trade-off for the fantastic experience. Had the occasional difficult passenger, and some sticky situations, but all were learning experiences, too.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I had a great experience with my supervisors and still keep in touch.  Somewhat limited opportunites for tour leaders if they don't want to work at HQ in Canada.  Would like to have had more support making connections for sustainable travel projects.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“fast paced exciting environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Exciting work in the travel industry.  Decisions are made quickly here and departments are very agile.  Everyone is a contributor and it is very empowering.  They put a lot of emphasis on culture not just skills.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Job can be stressful with long hours and variable working hours.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Chief Executive Officer (Tour Leader) (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome experience - a tough job, but worth it.”

</title><pros>Pros – Meet amazing people, see amazing places, once-in-a-lifetime experience</pros>
<cons>Cons – The job is 30 days on and sometimes only a few days off in between, so it can be exhausting.  Contracts a generally minimum of 18 months which goes fast, but can feel long.Usually passengers on the trip were fantastic, but dealing with the occasional difficult passenger can be hard, especially being stuck with them on a trip.Difficult to have any kind of personal life outside of work during hte contract, and the lines of personal and proffessional sometimes blur between tour leaders and passengers and this is, quite rightly, frowned upon.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work!  I had a great experience with the managers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Chief Experience Officer - Sales (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sales Department Needs A lot of Work”

</title><pros>Pros – -All Apple Computer Company :)-Cult like environment, if your into that sort of thing.-Get to travel once a year but recently, the limitations on it make it not worthy to have a job at the company JUST to travel. (No flights included, etc - with such low pay, you can't afford the flights anyway)-GapStock-I'm sure other departments are better</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Up to your eyeballs in work (100+ Emails a day and not enough time to do anything with them) Afterwards-No Commission-Raising pay levels is near impossible-Impossible to get through your work in the day and you are expected to work overtime (without pay) if you can not get through it.-Most of their "core values" mean nothing to them-Their idea of customer service is to go above and beyond on one client... while doing nothing for the next. READ REVIEWS!-Low Energy Department, most people look like they are going to pull their hair out for the little pay-Misrepresented job, you are not doing what the job description says, if you think you are going to be talking to people about travel all day, you are vastly mistaken.-VERY preferable treatment towards certain employees while shafting others.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – We work like dogs, management needs to realize this. Get the computer systems right and use them to make our jobs easier, not harder. Do not choose favorites as easily and look at the good in each individual. Have the ability to except constructive criticism and don't just believe what other management says. You need to have SOME sort of commission, this is the travel business, how can you possibly get enthusiastic about selling something when it makes no difference in your pay. "do the right thing", and bring back the internet department. Most Travel agents I spoke with were shocked and appalled that we would not getting commission after all our hard work. Be more open to new ideas, most of your staff is pretty intelligent. You need to back off on some people or you will have a bigger turnover.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>