<name>John Q. Hammons Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/John-Q-Hammons-Reviews-E3831.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“John q hammons”

</title><pros>Pros – Looks good on your resume</pros>
<cons>Cons – Has changed a lot since Mr. Hammons passed away</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You deserve better...”

</title><pros>Pros – Stepping stone if you can endure.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Currently, Marriott ranks 64th out of the 100 best companies to work for.  John Q. Hammons is nowhere to be found.  I've developed practices that saved the company time and money.  Still, a raise pay freeze was in effect for 3 years, while management bragged about record profits and high scores.  Workload between employees was unfair.  If you were buddy with the boss, got his lunch and agreed with everything they said, you were given less work.  Senior management too busy projecting future profits to realize that we were cherry picking who received Event Satisfaction Surveys and who didn't.  I did not receive sales/leads/revenue because of other employees cutting me out of the process.  Management should not "hit the bar" before showing up to client events. Intimidation among other tactics including yelling were used to try to correct problems. Even when warned from the General Manager, it still happened routinely.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Send Event Survey Satisfaction surveys to all clients, not just the ones with events that went well.  Do not promote management based solely on Event Satisfaction surveys alone.  Provide incentives to employees that save the company time and money.  Promote and utilize an equal workload to all employees.  Employees walking around getting coffee and water should be put to better work.  Be proactive, find the problems and solve them, before employees come to you.  Have better supervision over employees texting friends all day long.  Management should set more of an example of displaying honesty and integrity.  Management should not make promises they can't keep behind closed doors.  Give careful consideration and take the time to properly "groom" your General Managers.  If you want employees to reach their full potential, follow Marriott's lead and treat them accordingly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Set Up (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Set up”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly co workers and fun</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay could be a bit higher</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Went downhill VERY quickly.”

</title><pros>Pros – The only good thing I have to say about being employed by my particular property of JQH is that most of the staff tries their best to work as a team. Also, there is almost never a shortage of hours, which is good if you want as many as you can get.</pros>
<cons>Cons – With that being said, there is never a shortage of hours because 90% of the time, your department will be understaffed. Understaffed, overworked, and under appreciated. What staff you do have, HAS to learn to work together because the managers don't count themselves as part of "the team". Being understaffed does not effect the managers in anyway because they will not pull extra shifts to help out their overworked employees to give them a break. They will go weeks and even months without hiring to fill the gaps because they are not feeling same amount of stress as their employees who are working 10+ days in a row while their manager is having their usual days off. There is also no room for promotion. Ive seen too many times now, GREAT AND QUALIFIED employees apply for higher jobs within the property and get denied for whatever reason/excuse the management can think of. The sad thing is, this property is filled with honest, very hard working people and the management does not deserve this type of staff. I am a firm believer in "get respect, give respect" yet, it is only a one way street. Seniority also does not exist within this company. Neither does professionalism. Most of the staff know more about their jobs than the managers do. On top of there not being an official training program, there is a lot of trial and error learning when "training". You are trained by other members of staff and not your managers. So if you are taught the wrong way by another staff member, and are caught doing said wrong procedure, chances are you are going to get what is called a 'write up' which goes on file for the company..when you were not properly taught how to preform the procedure in the first place. Many (not all) policy write ups are based off an employee handbook. I, personally, never received an employee handbook. As any other job, you are encouraged to give your work availability... but its not like it makes a difference because they will schedule you whenever and however they like. Also, there is no "open door policy" as much as they claim their is. The staff stands alone apart from all management. Ive also seen many times when a guest has expressed concern over a situation, and the staff is told "do what you can to make the guest happy" so when the staff member makes their best judgement call, 9 times out of 10 the manager will say that it was the wrong thing to do and still yet the finger is pointed at the staff member for not "properly handling" the situation when in reality, the manager should have handled the situation themselves. A "judgement call" is based on an opinion, and if the manager does not share the same opinion as the employee, the blame is placed on them. This particular property is going to lose its hard working staff members, that is keeping the place afloat- sooner or later, and its going to be ran into the ground by management. Its just a matter of time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start being a team player. Bottom line. Dont point fingers,.. and accept responsibility for when things go wrong--because they will. Treat your staff FAIRLY. The saying "treat others the way you want to be treated" really will go a long way. Develop some sort of manager/employee training program so that we are not being taught in some sort of "domino effect" of other poorly trained employees. This will enable the staff members to learn faster and more efficiently. Which will lead to less write ups and less frustration overall from your staff. LISTEN TO YOUR EMPLOYEES. We are the ones that deal with guests and listen to their over all experiences on the DAILY, when we tell you something, its not because we are talking to hear the sound of our own voice. We are the first impression of the property...if it is obvious that your staff is unhappy, it quickly reflects on the guest as well. You wonder why GSS scores are so low? Take a look in the mirror.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Catering Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Once a great company”

</title><pros>Pros – Great opportunity to get experience working for full service hotels with the capacity to handle large groups/events.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The benefits are not that great, especially the PTO system.  I am unimpressed by the leadership skills of those who hold Executive positions and their ability to engage associates.  These individuals are oblivious to the needs, successes, and challenges of the different departments.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest more capital in the upkeep of the hotels.  Clients do notice the wear and tear on the buildings and how dated they are compared to competitors.  Walk the hotel more often and be more in tune with what the associates need in order to be successful.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Do a good job, you get to enjoy no promotions”

</title><pros>Pros – Co-Workers seem to care about each other.  Ability to learn a lot.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I have watched it over and over.  The employee that is doing a good job, becomes a valuable resource so they discourage the employee for even applying to positions of promotion.  Many times the employees are told "you are not ready" for advancement.  These same employees are essentially doing their own job, others jobs and their own bosses job and are more qualified then the person managing them.  However the hotel would suffer if the employee were promoted.  There is absolutely NO TRAINING PROGRAM for new hires.  Sure there is orientation and brand training but NO TRAINING on how to actually perform the job.  This causes the worker to get discouraged or looked down upon, only because they do not know how to do their job properly because they are NOT TRAINED!  There is no corporate trainer, no corporate training department, and no focus on training.  Just think how successful you would be if you invested in these things.  WOW there would be more money so perhaps you could actually pay us holiday pay.  Did I mention there are NO PAID HOLIDAYS AT ALL FOR ANYONE!!!!!  It is unconscionable that in 2013 holidays are not paid.  The hysterical excuse is we are a 24x7 company and we lump all time off together into PTO, and they say this like it is a good thing.  WHAT A JOKE! Almost every other hotel is 24x7 yet they pay for holidays.  Really?  You think we are all that stupid?  These are just some of the reasons your good people leave.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Imagine if you trained people, they knew how to do their job, were happy and stayed with the company.  What might happen?  You might be able to make your revenue goals.  I could only hope the owners review this site and see how many employees are talking about one basic item - holiday pay.  To the owners, I plead to you, make JQH pay holiday pay.  Happy employees, will get you more productivity and more money in your pockets.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Rounds Cook (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The renaissance”

</title><pros>Pros – There are some great thing about JQH like the benefits of being able to stay cheap at hotels around the world.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Way to top heavy.  Corporate takes all the money for themselves leaving low pay for most everyone else.  Most of the time my hotel is poorly staffed and they do not seem to care. HR runs our hotel which is really not the way it should be.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Go to a management seminar.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Banquet Server (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great People”

</title><pros>Pros – Awesome people to work with for the most part, are usually fed after events are served, get to meet and serve a variety of different people, events, cultures.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours, unsteady schedule which can make budgeting nearly impossible. LOTS of turnover of employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest more in trying to find a way to keep the employees you have rather than having such a high turnover rate</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-29</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people, terrible benefits.”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are excellent to work with. I really enjoy my job. Everything is run by the book and seems to work well. Management team is excellent and work very hard. Advancement opportunities are ok. I've seen many people get over looked because they were too good at their current low paying position.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You can't take a PTO day until after 6 months of working there. Even after six months, you only earn about 5.5 days that year. No sick leave, no holidays, and no holiday pay. Worst PTO policies I have ever encountered. Had I known beforehand, I never would have accepted the position. Hard working people deserve better, and will probably get it elsewhere. Even after 10 years.. You'll only get 21 days off. Which doesn't sound bad until you minus 12 holidays, 4 sick days,... Then you can have a nice week off. Most companies give 11 holidays + 12 vacation/sick days the first year. Better off anywhere else.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Advice to corporate. Need holiday pay, at a minimum!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Hotel room rates; Some good co-workers; It is a job</pros>
<cons>Cons – Underpaid; Bad compensation; Overworked; Bad work/life balance; You have to not only do your job but the job of others; Mostly bad co-workers; No support system from management; No room for promotion; Hard work is not rewarded; Laziness is tolerated; No accountability; No bonuses; Poor inventory control leaving staff under supplied; Broken machines</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Never should have sold out to Atrium. Do not care just about the bottom line. Invest in your company and employees. Set goals and give bonuses when the goals are reached. Hold people accountable. Reward hard work and create career advancement. Update old machines/systems. Realize that these problems are happening on most properties as it is apparent that many others are having issues when reviewing this company and fix them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fantastic Environment”

</title><pros>Pros – My review is based upon the property I work for in St. Augustine.  I realize each hotel is run different but I have to say our GM's style is fantastic.  Not only does he care about the direction of the hotel but he cares about each employee.  It is rare to find an EC team that works to make the hotel a better place and our jobs better.  The pros are the EC team, and the asset itself is beautiful.  Promotion from within happens at this hotel which is really nice to see.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I would say that the biggest downside is that due to the way JQH operates the benefits are lacking.  As many reviewers stated the PTO policy needs work.  Not paying for holidays when so many in the industry offer this benefit is in poor taste.  I think just adding paid holidays in addition to the current PTO would give morale a big boost.  Like all hotels there is gossip in the workplace.  I can’t fault the hotel or the company it is just the industry but I do see it as a con.  The hotels operate independently of each other and being in sales I would prefer to see a culture that the hotels work together more.  Perhaps an annual sales meeting with all hotels.  An annual sales incentive trip would be great too. Retaining staff is difficult, which puts more work on everyone.  If benefits were changed perhaps we could attract and retain good staff.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please revise your benefits.  Several people who have left mentioned the benefits really turned them off.  The health benefits are okay - not the best and not the worst.  However the unpaid holidays with the low amount of PTO really should be evaluated.  At least pay for Thanksgiving Day, Christmas Day, New Year’s Day, Memorial Day, July 4th Day and Labor Day at the minimum.  Competitor hotels are paying for 6-9 paid holidays per year.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Hotel Operator”

</title><pros>Pros – Great company structure that knows how to build and run a hotel.  The number of management personnel that have decades with the company shows that they are well run as this is a somewhat transient industry.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It seems as though we have become more micromanaged over the last few years.  Nobody gets a holiday off unless you take a vacation day, inlcuding the sales force that sits and twiddles their thumbs if they come in to work on those days.  Goals also have seemed to become unattainable which is off putting as a sales manager when you know that you have no shot at bonus.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Adapt to the reality that just because we are a 24/7/365 industry not all staff needs to be in on holidays.  Goals need to be made that are attainnlable, otherwise staff can get demoralized and not be as productive.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you value your time on the career ladder, JQH is not for you”

</title><pros>Pros – Great employee rate at other JQH hotels when traveling.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Manage by fear; no trust; no comraderie; no common goal; managers not engaged</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be true to your word.  Value talent.  Provide better training.  Honor promises.  This company recruited me away from an independent hotel, where I was very happy, promoting their ability to transfer me to one of the other 78 hotels in the country.  I knew we would be relocating in 2 years which I shared with them.  Having received a raise, a bonus and other valuable perks, I thought a transfer was in the offing.  After 5 months, not only did the transfer not transpire, they kept contacting me with new opportunities - distracting me from external opportunities - then dismissing me with not a word.  Highly unprofessional, would not advise spending valuable time with this company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Rigid expectations”

</title><pros>Pros – Great hotel design and product, fair compensation for the job</pros>
<cons>Cons – No room for thinking outside box, focus on minutia and reportsHigh turnover of personnel hurts continuity</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cheap Company, there are others in the industry to get a job with”

</title><pros>Pros – Hotels are nice.  There are discounts you can get at other hotels which helps if you want to take a vacation.</pros>
<cons>Cons – One of the cheapest in the industry.  Bad benefits, lack of paid time off, now no bonus checks.  What a joke.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If others can do it and give good benefits, time off, holiday pay, bonuses, why cant you?  Check yourselves.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No benefits, bad hiring decisions, high turn-over”

</title><pros>Pros – You get pretty significant discounts on rooms at various hotels and some of them are very nice. Starting pay is pretty good. Fairly laid back management which can also be a con. Several opportunities for advancement. There are a few very good employees that have stuck around for a while but would happily leave if offered something better because they don't feel valued.</pros>
<cons>Cons – While there is opportunity for advancement they often make bad hiring decisions and often times the employees they hire quit within the first 30 days. It is hard to get off time and the employees tend to no-call no-show with no repercussions. The benefits are a joke. You have to work for the company for a year to qualify for insurance and the insurance you get is simply a "discount plan." You still pay $100 to go to the doctor and get a slight discount on prescriptions. After two years you can get real insurance but it's still costly and even more expensive if you're a smoker. Every year they do a survey to see if employees are happy and how they feel about the property as well as any problems however; they don't make any changes and things seem to get worse instead of better. There's been a freeze on raises for years. There is a significant lack of training in every department.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Show the employees that are doing well that you care and you notice them. Get rid of the people that aren't invested because they're causing the veteran employees to feel as though they shouldn't care about the business anymore. Stop hiring people from outside the property to do management positions and instead promote those within. Stop throwing people into the jobs and actually train them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Front Office Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Step up from other Franchises”

</title><pros>Pros – - More organized and well run that other franchises (but not as owned hotels - Marriott owned, Hilton owned, etc)- Nice properties- Many properties in Midwest and most are large so many opportunities if you like that area (centralized in Missouri)- Respectable among franchises</pros>
<cons>Cons – - No Holiday pay- Too much paperwork (and that is coming from someone that has been an accountant). As a manager if you aren't organized and disciplined with it you can spend days catching up and organizing when audit comes due (and in my case I inherited the mess from previous managers).  As a front desk agent you have to complete paperwork for too many transactions - charges that are adjusted or transfered, paid outs, any charges made to the room manually such as valet, late checkout, dry cleaning - everything.  This also makes night audit very lengthy in auditing charges and collecting paperwork.- Pay: large hotel and one of the biggest and best in the area.  All housekeeping earned minimum wage and everybody else just slightly above that.  Wage freeze (no raises) for several years. (may be different regionally)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I think the little things go a long way with associates.  Pay for holidays - pay for employee appreciation such as outings or parties.With management make sure training is provided.  At our property we had a ton of first time management and there was no training, expectations, or orientation.  A fellow manager was sent to a training class because she was viewed as incompetent but I had the same position and was not sent because I appeared competent.  I would have appreciated the training as well.  And she wasn't sent until about 5 months after she was promoted and already caused a ton of damage to employee morale and guest satisfaction scores.  As a first time manager I would have appreciated more training, coaching, and counseling as opposed to hearing completely new things once I reached my performance evaluations.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“REVAMP = RETAIN TALENT = MORE MARKET SHARE = BETTER BOTTOM LINE”

</title><pros>Pros – From what employees are told it appears to be a financial sound company.  The properties are nice and for the most part the employees are friendly.  Its a great place to learn.  It is so sad because it could be so much better with some changes to match others in the industry.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Vacation, Holiday and sick pay are all rolled into one.  This would be nice except you get VERY FEW actual “vacation” days.  After holidays in your first few years you have VERY LITTLE PTO.  The time off PTO policy is not competitive with others in the industry.  Salary is low in comparison to competitors.  The health insurance cost to the employees is high and the coverage is not that good - again not competitive with others in the industry.  The policies are based on the thinking of the 60's-80's and need some serious updates.  Some of the policies are backwards.  Having worked at other properties when you hear some of these policies you think it is very odd.  The policies get in the way of actually having the tools needed to do your job well.  If you are a manager no matter what dept you are going to work a ton of hours.  This company is not about work-life balance.  You learn a lot but because of the structure of operating on very little staff and not having certain mid-management positions you get burned out rather quick.  A lot of the long timers at this company have not work significantly for other properties/companys so they dont understand how much better things could be.  All in all I would say if you are new to the industry it is a great company to get a year of experience, then move on.  If you want job satisfaction and work/life balance dont plan to stay here long.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Revamp your policies - bring someone in from a competitor management company or a major brand to look at your policies and bring them up to 2012.  Or create a task force made up of employees from various properties and roles to get input.  We do the job daily we can tell you what works and does not work – we can help but you need to really listen to us.  The policies are so behind the times that it actually gets in the way of performance.  Restructure PTO so that including holidays people have at least 10 days off of “vacation/personal time” a year.  Time off is important to recharge and then people will not burn out and quit.  The health insurance needs to change.  Other companies smaller and larger then John Q are not self insured and therefore offer insurance with better employee premiums, better coverage and better co-pays.  Stop being so cheap, give better benefits, it cant be all about the bottom line because if things continue the way they are you will not retain strong talent. This will bite you because you need your strong talent to make your goals.  It is very difficult to grow if you can not retain the good talent.  It is also difficult to attract great talent because the salary and benefits package is weak compared to others.  Salaries are low compared to others in the industry but you could make up for this by having better benefits.  It is hard to want to stay with the company when you know you can go somewhere else and make more money and have better benefits and more time off.  Add to the staff - dont operate so lean and mean - you are burning your people out.  They will continue to leave and go somewhere where they can make more money, better benefits, more time off and work a more regular amount of hours.  You are losing some very talented people because of this.  You may not see it now but your talent IS interviewing other places and will leave.  Your employees are your greatest asset!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall, good.”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent Chef and Sous Chefs, very knowledgable and willing to teach. Primarily a relaxed environment, yet professional as well. I learned alot.</pros>
<cons>Cons – For the most part, the only cons were the corporate rules, had it not been for one of those, I would still be there. If you are interested in working and learning, the cons are few.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Review company policies to relate to the workplace and not what a person does while in the privacy of their own home. If it doesn't adversly affect performance, leave it alone.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Anyone can do better”

</title><pros>Pros – The hotel I worked for was pretty flexible when it came to time off. Too much as times certain managers take full advantage and well beyond! Many unique and innovative properties in OKC. Mr. Hammons did well for himself considering the size of the company and being a lone hotelier.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is simply not competitive with other hotel companies. Especially considering the amount of work they are expecting. New hires and internal transfers are typically not qualified from what I have seen. Not bad that inexperienced folks are given an opportunity, but God bless those customers and as far as those competent co-workers......look out! If you have legitimate hotel experience and you are very good at what you do look elsewhere and get paid what you are worth!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay people what they are worth, get rid of the so called "leaders" taking advantage of their subordinates, co-workers, and company and invest in your future and promote and hire qualified staff and develop them!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Experience but”

</title><pros>Pros – The experience received here is beneficial.  You have the ability to challange yourself.  The staff is great.  Company is in a strong financial position.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The benefits and pay are on the low end. There are many policy's in place that are micro-managing. This results in an inability to create a balance because you work many hours. PTO is the lowest of anywhere I have experienced, know this going in and negotiate.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take a look at the benefit plan. It is expensive for the coverage received. PTO needs to be re-evaluated.  Reports about sales activities defeat the purpose if you spend so much time on reports that it takes away from your selling time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Banquet Captain (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“alright”

</title><pros>Pros – people i worked with were awesome</pros>
<cons>Cons – the pay is not competitive</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Guest Services Associate (Front Desk) (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hospitality Career? Do Your Homework!”

</title><pros>Pros – With experience in hospitality advancement to a well paying, salaried position is possible without a formal education.  Experience is in demand everywhere in the world and you can choose your favorite climate or property type. For individuals who thrive on helping others and problem solving, the work can be very satisfying.  Not all properties are the same. JQH manages some Marriott properties and some Embassy Suites among others.  This review is for the hotel industry in general.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Starting wages are low.   Since most jobs are hourly, when the season is slow, employees can be asked to clock out early.  Job satisfaction, growth, and work/life balance is directly related to management.  Bad managers can linger for years barring your path to advancement and making work miserable in the meantime. No matter the management style, vicious or incompetent, if the "guest satisfaction" scores are good, bad behavior from management is often overlooked. For the older worker, there is a hidden trap in a career transition to hospitality: It may take much longer to be promoted than anticipated. Financial stress, unpredictable hours, and the company health insurance plan could result in a long and complicated escape.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Find out who your best, most loyal associates are.  Listen to their advice. They know who the poor performers are and how to make the team the best it can be. Franchises have vastly different computer systems and different operational guidelines.  Get to know them and don't be too proud to ask for help.  Some of the computer systems are highly complex and the learning curve is steep.  Since your front line associates are grossly underpaid, job satisfaction is the only thing preventing your best talent from walking out the door.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Catering Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Neutral Employee”

</title><pros>Pros – Most of the people are wonderful to work with and truly care about you, as a person.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is difficult to have work/life balance, which is hard for anyone with a family.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“stay away”

</title><pros>Pros – none, poor culture, inflexible managment</pros>
<cons>Cons – low pay, expensive benefits, poor time off policy, outdated computers, archaic rules.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to learn”

</title><pros>Pros – Wonderful staff that has been with the hotels for some time.  Great place to learn because there is so much to do you get to work on things other then what you were hired for (good and bad).  Really nice properties and depending on which brand you work for some nice discounts on hotel stay for you and your family.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Benefits, pay, company culture, corporate direction (of lack of).  The biggest problems is the good old boys club and corporate management not getting with the times.  We get change takes time but it has been long enough.  Its 2012 and you dont pay for holidays????</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – WAKE UP!  Change some policies.  A lot of us would not have left if we had pay that was equivilant to others in the industry.  Come out of your perfect world thoughts - the world isnt perfect and neither are your management or properties.  You say you are the best - why, what is this belief based on?  You can say you are the best but you need to act like the best and be the best for all of us to believe you are the best.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Revenue Management (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This is a good company to work for, with opportunity to grow.”

</title><pros>Pros – New upper management additions are making a good step towards positive change.  Financially sound company.  Management believes in people and promotes from within.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Benefits could be better.  Pay scale is not always up to par with other management companies or brands.  Lack of bench strength in many departments.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work on health benefits and vacation time.  Sometimes these items will make up for the lower wages that most positions are paying.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Area Revenue Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Could be so much better!”

</title><pros>Pros – Work from home. Hotels are nice. The Hammons name was an industry leader. Thankfully, many people don't know how far they have fallen, so the chances of you getting another job with this company on your resume isn't necessarily a negative.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Cost cutting is an issue. They won't pay for your home office phone or your Blackberry, yet you are required to have both. Travel is non-existent, so you may never meet your teams. PTO time is the worst I have ever seen in my entire career. I am in Revenue Management, and it's been tough not to have people at the top to look up to or to rely on. We live in a silo. There is zero training at all. There is no support at all from a workload perspective. There is no coverage when you are out or off, or god forbid you are on vacation.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more sensitive. Rumor has it, this is the hospitality business. Stop the cost cutting - enough is enough. We need to meet our teams and each other. Hire more experienced people who can move revenue management forward. This new alignment is just bad. Do you really think the Regional Directors of Sales know and understand revenue management? Really?</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales and Catering Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Indentured Servitude”

</title><pros>Pros – Attractive Hotels full service hotels</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours were very long, the expectations were work your ass off. The turnover rate was extremely high.  Employees were promoted who had no experience.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Promote people who do a good job for you, not people you are friends with or your involved in an intimate relationships with.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A company full of ups and downs”

</title><pros>Pros – Depending on the property you work at-because these are franchised hotels and carry the names of other hotel brands like Marriott, Embassy Suites, Holiday Inn, etc-, you can be linked with great discounts on hotel rates world-wide for both yourself and friends and family.  I worked at several different properties, and one hotel in particular had the nicest people I have ever had the pleasure of working with.  Do offer to do matching if you choose to do a 401k with them.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Perks and benefits are not very appealing with JQH, and lack significantly when you look at what other hospitality chains/brands are offering.  Management at some of the properties is incompetent and promotions are biased and made purely out of a "who knows who" mentality.  Turn over can be quite high, and wages quite low at many properties.  Not many perks for staying long term with the company, either.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be universal in decision making, and aware of your weak links and how they are affecting overall staff morale, motivation and property perception.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very positive overall.”

</title><pros>Pros – They promote a true team spirit. Possibilities for advancement are excellent. Bonus potential is excellent.</pros>
<cons>Cons – PTO is probably the lowest in the area of all hotel brands of similar quality.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Offer benefits package on par with other hotel chains to attract quality staff and to motivate existing staff. Company is already known for being on the low scale with salaries, make benefits more attractive to attract talent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Once proud company falls”

</title><pros>Pros – Great reputation and a stable of hotels in cities with low costs of living make John Q Hammons a natural choice for many.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In general, the company is run by a bunch of cost cutting and out of touch individuals who are clueless about the profound effects of turnover on our industry.  Benefits are a joke and opportunities for advancement are nil unless you are a 50+ year old white male.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Move your headquarters to a city where you are able to attract competent leadership or become aquired by a company who has what it takes to move forward.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>