<name>Johnson C. Smith University Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Johnson-C-Smith-University-Reviews-E38386.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-05-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“What Happened?”

</title><pros>Pros – There is a core group of employees that LOVE JCSU. It shows in all that is done for the university. These individuals are the reason that JCSU exists. They are the heart of the university.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper Management lacks focus and a strategic plan for the university. There is always "talk" but the reality is that the actions don't match. The idea is that everyone (staff & faculty) are expendable. If you aren't with the plan for the day you are encouraged to leave.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – What Happened? How did you go from a warm loving environment to utter chaos? You have GREAT employees; listen to them. You have a few in leadership that can move the university to where it needs to go. The staff & faculty should not be as easily expended. Who needs to be expended is upper management that are not worth a hill of beans.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very Dissappointed”

</title><pros>Pros – There are a few very good members of faculty and staff. Those who are there to do their job to the best of their ability and help those around them.</pros>
<cons>Cons – So many it is way too hard to list.  In the time I have been at JCSU the main things I have learned are that the ones who work the hardest and are the most competent are the ones who get treated the poorest and with the must disrespect. The ones in management/supervisory roles only with to destroy the ones around them whom they know are better than them. There are so many things going on that are 100% wrong that it is unimaginable. For being an HBCU organization and speaking so highly of diversity and cultures there is much racism here.  If you are salaried, don’t expect to Ever work an 8-5 shift. One you sign on with JCSU you literally sign away your life to them not only mon-fri 7am to 8pm but also weekends and holidays.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Lead by example! If you want your employees to be the best, you should be the best! Take responsibly for YOUR actions and do not place the blame on your employee just because it would make you look bad to take the hit. Your success depends on the success of your employees. Therefore if you want to be successful and respected, respect your employees and help them be respectful. NEVER be derogatory or undermine your staff, they are the ones who enable you to be where you are without them, you would be no where.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't work here. Seriously. Just. Don't.”

</title><pros>Pros – There are zero pros to working at Smith.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everything. The work environment is the worst I've ever encountered.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>