<name>G-Star Raw Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/G-Star-Raw-Reviews-E385120.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-04-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good experience, great staff benefits and friendly staff”

</title><pros>Pros – - 50% discount + Clothing allowance- Good pay rate- Like-minded employees- Fun energetic store environment- Reputable international brand</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Difficult sales targets and KPI- HR and Management constantly expect more</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More realistic weekly store sales targets and KPI</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>G-Star Raw (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“quite good”

</title><pros>Pros – uniform, possible to grow, possible to visit other countries ( Fashion weeks, Bread & Butter, other)discount for staff, etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – low salary per hours in some of the g-star stores</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – prices for items must be more adequate depending on country</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working at G-Star Raw is a fun and exciting experience and dynamic environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Aside from the great employee discount (50%) ; the product line is both edgy and classic catering to anyone and everyone's needs. You'll find something in all the pieces that you can appreciate allowing you to close that sale! Management is fairly reasonable in balancing both work and personal schedules. They are equally personable and professional. You will find clientele from all of the world to the casual and to the die-hard fans of the brand. As a whole, I learned a few things and had great experience there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The product training was not as thorough as it should have been. It should have been more intensive so associates would not be guessing or giving inaccurate information to the customer resulting in bad customer service and even embarrassment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide a solid, thorough and intensive product training - reading material on the history and production process as it a denim company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>