<name>I Trade FX Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/I-Trade-FX-Reviews-E389102.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2010-01-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Broker (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“i-Trade FX was full of new ideas, then the bottom fell out.”

</title><pros>Pros – Working at i-Trade FX was an interesting place.  Back in the day, it was a place with a future and a lot of new ideas going forward.  Then they had a bunch of layoffs, and it slid downhill.  Company management didn't go out of their way to try to change things up.Overall though, it was a pleasant experience while it lastedCompany management cared a lot about their employees while I was there.  They tried to learn everyone's name and interests, and holidays were the best.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management didn't listen to ideas as much as a small company probably should.A lot of people didn't know anything about the forex business, but acted like kings.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn to listen to employees and not just push a management style for the sake of itself.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was an interesting look into the political world within every corporate job.”

</title><pros>Pros – It was a new company so ideas were welcomed from all employees and in most cases implemented.  Any person had the freedom to walk down the hall and speak with the CEO, a luxury that most do not have at their jobs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Its pro is also a con, because it was a new company the budget was small until the company starting doing well.  Once the firm starting doing well it was almost impossible to get a raise past the senior managing members of the firm.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take care of the employees that truly give all of their effort to help you succeed, instead of taking care of the people you like and have known.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>