<name>Club Z! Tutoring Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Club-Z-Tutoring-Reviews-E389408.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tutor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good part-time job for teachers”

</title><pros>Pros – Club Z! makes a strong effort to match you with students who fit your particular personality in addition to your academic area.  They communicate regularly and provide raises after you've gained experience with their students. The schedule is very flexible -  you choose how often you would like to tutor.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everything depends on students being available for your age group/subject, though the same would be true with any tutoring company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Alright, but not great”

</title><pros>Pros – The pay was decent for part time work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You are pretty much on your own with the curriculum, unless you want to use the sub-par lesson plans provided by the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More direction and better quality curriculum.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Flexible job that provides nice supplementary income”

</title><pros>Pros – Very flexible schedule. You can select which clients you take on based on location and your schedule.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Submitting payments was sort of a hassle and took quite a bit of time (which you don't get paid for).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Franchise Development (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nearly 10 years with the same company says a lot”

</title><pros>Pros – Great company. I've seen the evolution first-hand the way the company has catered to the needs of the clients who use our tutoring service by adding curriculum and new programs and to the needs of franchise owners by adding resources to help them grow the business and and enhancing the services they offer. I really enjoy helping people get started in a business they really love.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are always ways to improve but I see the corporate office constantly making the steps to improve by listening to the clients of our franchise owners, our franchise owners and the company employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue being proactive to remain the leader in providing affordable in-home tutoring service and providing affordable business opportunities for individuals who've always dreamed of starting their own business.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tutor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hiring experience very poor.”

</title><pros>Pros – Assignments close to your home work since the cost of gas is so high.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The tutor is asked to pay for all background screens and are deducted from your pay. You literally do not get paid to tutor until your third session. It's my understanding the parent is charged 50-65/hour and the tutor is paid $17. Again, financial insult to educators.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tutor”

</title><pros>Pros – Good pay you choose your schedule and great manager</pros>
<cons>Cons – no job security and no reimbursements for gas</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-28</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tutor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – Wonder experience! Great boss, flexible hours, had a chance to make a difference in kids' lives.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Since tutoring was at the home of students, sometimes the drive could be rather long, and if siblings were around, but not being tutored, the atmosphere could become a little distracting.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Would have been great if I had been paid what I earned”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible scheduling and rewarding to see the kids succeed.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The franchise went out of business in the town where I was a tutor and I never received my last paycheck which was over $500.  Be careful! It's not worth it to work for them when you can make twice as much working by yourself.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I have contacted Club Z 5 or 6 times in the past 10 months with no response any of those times.  I have also never heard back from the franchise owner who closed down.  If I was owed more than just $500 I would've taken you to court by now to get the money that I earned and that you are withholding from me.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Math Tutor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for starting out.”

</title><pros>Pros – Find you clients and screen them.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Keep over 50% of billing. Set schedule can be somewhat inflexible</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Academic Tutor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“well organized and equipped in-home agency.”

</title><pros>Pros – Agency has a good system of tutor-student reporting that keeps parents informed and students motivated.</pros>
<cons>Cons – it is up to the tutor to organize a schedule that is favorable in terms of route and time usage.  there is no guarantee of staying in the specified tutoring zone.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-28</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Area Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Love this job... can't wait to October”

</title><pros>Pros – Meeting new people & helping kids reach their educational goals...</pros>
<cons>Cons – No Health Benefits,travel not paid!!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Should pay for mileage {Incentive}</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tutor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Beware of what you are getting into.”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible schedule. You do NOT have  to accept a job if you don't want to. No limitations to tutor/work elsewhere while still employeed at Club Z.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inexcusably poor Communication. Fake attitude about concern of employees AND students. No room for advancement. WEAK and Inept management. Tutors are leaving all too often, so management tries to find just tutor to take a student, even if the tutor isnt qualified for that subject. If management does not get what they want when they want it, they stop offering students and/or simply fire you. Not compensated for traveling or any material expenses. Will only contact you when/if management wants/needs something, regardless of your pleading e-mails phone calls to them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Practice what you preach. Learn professional and consistent communication with/to your tutors. Realize why tutors are leaving you all the time and how this impacts the upset parents. Sarcasm and rude attitudes NEED to end. Offer incentives for tutors to want to continue to tutor with you (pay raises, opportunities for advancement, etc...).</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Club Z Franchise Owner In Peachtree City GA (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Club Z Tutoring Franchise Owner in Peachtree City GA has had a great experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – Club Z has a very supportive and responsive corporate staff.  They allow franchises local flexibility to adjust for their area.  In addition, they are always scanning the horizon for better ways to do business.   I think the staff is very capable and is given the freedom they need to do their jobs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Because of their growth and the changing nature of electronic marketing I think Club Z is sometimes a little slow to incorporate new practices and technology.  Our previous web site was not reflective of the quality of the company and it took several years to get it fixed.  However, it is very nice now.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to nurture the open friendly culture at corporate.  I've never sensed a climate fear or bullying.  Develop your bench so as you continue to grow, the support capability is maintained or improved.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tutor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Management good, able to make own hours, good part time job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work not always available.  Dependent on demand.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Glad to work here.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tutor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great fun to work as a tutor”

</title><pros>Pros – You get to pick your schedule.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometime clients cancel at the last minute.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing what you are doing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tutor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Club Z Tutoring”

</title><pros>Pros – Company finds clients for tutors</pros>
<cons>Cons – You work for someone else and share the profits.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Part-Time Tutor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK Part-Time Tutoring Job”

</title><pros>Pros – -flexible hours: you choose which assignments & which subjects you want to take-rewarding job helping students-easy way to earn some money during the high academic season-tutor and client policies are clearly laid out in writing: for example, parents have to provide advance notice if they wish to cancel a session</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Irregular work loads (depends on demand)-you have to drive to the student's home or to a public location and aren't compensated for either the driving time or gas prices; so the pay rate of $20/hr may end up being much less when you factor in all the hidden costs. But this is the ClubZ model: remove the overhead costs by providing in-home tutoring, shifting gas & transportation costs to the tutor.-you're not compensated for prep time-you're not compensated for the time-consuming paperwork you have to submit, yet you may have to compensate ClubZ  if the paperwork is not submitted on time and is not in order: this is true if you're working for one of the government-funded programs of which ClubZ is a private vendor</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>