<name>Peace X Peace Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Peace-X-Peace-Reviews-E395166.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2011-05-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Executive Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Incredibly satisfying work, wonderful co-workers, but the acting CEO was unqualified.”

</title><pros>Pros – The mission of Peace X Peace, to connect women around the world for peace, was one that I was incredibly proud to be a part of. The other women I worked with were wonderful, knowledgeable, compassionate, and fun! They opened my eyes to things I'd never seen, and made the world both a bigger and smaller place for me.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The acting CEO at the time was not qualified to run the organization and thus the organization had to lay of 50% of the staff - with no warning - just to keep from shutting down completely. The founder seemed to have created Peace by Peace more for vanity and/or status among the DC elite, than because she actually cared...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do not try to grow too big too fast. Continue to make the focus on the everyday woman, and not on big shows of philanthropy or by getting big names attached to events and projects. The women of the world will make Peace X Peace what it is truly meant to be!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“They just didn't have it together”

</title><pros>Pros – The work is not difficult</pros>
<cons>Cons – But it is not clear what you are supposed to do or anyone else is doing, or what the organization actually does</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There needs to be more clarity and focus on a particular direction as well as a clear sustainability strategy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>