<name>Euclid Infotech Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Euclid-Infotech-Reviews-E396439.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Administrator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its Nice company for freshers.”

</title><pros>Pros – You will get hands on almost everything they have in there infra.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Its not a IT Company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No growth if sorted out on long term!!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Good fro fresher alone cant see future for exp one!!!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Internal Politics, highly opaque culture</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be a long term player, Dont focus on short term goals only</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for fresh start”

</title><pros>Pros – -Good learning environment as its medium size company.-Maintain balance in life.-Its experience gets count for being a ISO certified private limited company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Cant see future in this company.-Pay scale is too low.-Office politics sometimes harms freshers.-Backward in terms of technology.-Colleagues are not highly educated.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – -Try to grow up technically.-Hire employees on educational and conversation skills instead of references.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Trainee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“satisfied but growth wise not satisfied”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly...environment ,no targets,easy to work out</pros>
<cons>Cons – No growth in salary,no management support</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Personal  growth to be take care</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good For Data Entry and Marketing”

</title><pros>Pros – Good For Data Entry and Marketing</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not good for long term</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more innovative</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Development Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Provides a Biz Opportunity ...”

</title><pros>Pros – Tendersinfo is the leading business opportunity platform that provides latest up-to-date information on tenders. All Tender Notices, request for proposals, competitive bids which are advertised through Newspapers, Trade Journals, Departmental Publications and Notice Boards, and on Internet are made available at Tendersinfo.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 24*7 Mind Draining work , Target and Expectation are high by the Company ...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good experience, got to learn a lot and met some fantastic people.”

</title><pros>Pros – nice working environment, nice colleagues, good working culture. Tendersinfo is the leading business opportunity platform that provides latest up-to-date information on tenders. All Tender Notices, request for proposals, competitive bids which are advertised through Newspapers, Trade Journals, Departmental Publications and Notice Boards, and on Internet are made available at Tendersinfo. Get all the detailed information at Tendersinfo about Global Tenders, Indian Tenders, Government Tenders, Public Tenders, International Tenders, Competitive bids, Tenders Offer, Tenders Notices, RFP, RFQ, Bids, Corporate Tenders, Private Tenders and Tenders news.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Employee benefits should be more. Tendersinfo is the leading business opportunity platform that provides latest up-to-date information on tenders. All Tender Notices, request for proposals, competitive bids which are advertised through Newspapers, Trade Journals, Departmental Publications and Notice Boards, and on Internet are made available at Tendersinfo. Get all the detailed information at Tendersinfo about Global Tenders, Indian Tenders, Government Tenders, Public Tenders, International Tenders, Competitive bids, Tenders Offer, Tenders Notices, RFP, RFQ, Bids, Corporate Tenders, Private Tenders and Tenders news.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increase Employee benefits.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>