<name>Vitamin T Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Vitamin-T-Reviews-E397575.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Talent Agent (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wonderful. Lots of resources and support so you can be successful.”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexibility. unlimited vacation days. determine what works for you and as long as it works, they're good with it. supportive teams. Very transparent and keep all employees informed. Monthly calls from the President where she show where you've been, where you are, where you're going and recognizes employees accomplishments.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can expect a lot out of you. Some busy work. Lots of tasks for agents.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Recruiter/Agent (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Mediocrity at its best”

</title><pros>Pros – - Unlimited vacation days- Nice office- Co-workers in general treat each other with respect- High base pay</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Too HR oriented- No way to grow your business- Worst comp plan in the staffing industry- People seem to coast along</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop rewarding and pacifying under-performers as this just creates a bad team dynamic and promotes laziness.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Vicious Cycle”

</title><pros>Pros – Work life balance, friendly atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is not experienced as actual "Managers", therefore they do not have the skill set to manage a group. Vicious cycle of continual same issues of problems with FTE's, Management and turn over.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Agent (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“don't work here.”

</title><pros>Pros – you'd be employed, so that's a good thing. going to events sometimes can be interesting if that's your thing. there are some nice people. not the most educated bunch. The pay is decent. It's usually a cool environment(meaning decor). They use macs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – they make you post fake jobs, they don't actually intend on helping you find a job. horrible management, if you can even call it that. It's just all bad news if you're an agent or sales person. which it's all sales, just to be clear. No room for growth. not a chance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – get rid of Vitamin T and just be Aquent. just take it away.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Too busy creating FAKE jobs to post online.”

</title><pros>Pros – They look very competent and cute on paper.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Recruiters don't know anything about what they want to place you for. Just sales persons.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience - but be prepared to bring your A game”

</title><pros>Pros – -I've been really impressed with how much they care about their talent, each other, and their clients. Not every staffing agency makes a huge effort to "wow" their clients, act as career advocates for their talent, or invest as much energy and resources into growing their internal employees.-Open-door policy with management. If you have an idea, a suggestion, a problem, even the top level of management is accessible and open to hearing it.-Super fast turnaround times to service clients AND talent are part of the culture and it goes a long way. You can be successful pretty quickly here, build loyal partnerships with clients and with talent. If you've never worked super fast, you'll learn to here. You will be amazed at your own growth.-There is a lot of work here; you'll never be bored. If you're not on top of things, you can easily fall behind, so if you work here, you'll become a pro with prioritization and having a laser focus to keep many things running at the same time. Really positive place to grow professionally.-Work-life balance. Unlimited vacation time.-Fair compensation.-Top notch health benefits and 401k plan.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Client list could improve. They have some good ones, but Vitamin T is a division of a much larger company (Aquent, which serves the Fortune 500 brands), so some of the clients are "challenger brands" or companies that neither you nor your talent have heard of. Clients can be hit-or-miss.-If you're an agent, you have a lot more work on your plate than your sales counterpart (in my opinion). That got a little old after a while.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – -Overall, extremely positive experience. I think things are really on track here and I would recommend people to work here.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Recruiter/Agent (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Another typical agency...”

</title><pros>Pros – You may be able to make some friends. There are interesting and cool people that work there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -poor management. They will make a manager out of someone with zero leadership skills. Other managers are remote so they have no clue what's even happening at their own locations.-They hold you to hitting FTE goals that are impossible to maintain. If you don't hit them, they give you another impossible goal to hit as a warning. If you don't hit it, you'll be fired. This happens nationwide and all the employees know it.-They lure you in with promises of work life balance, unlimited vacation time, a house in hawaii, promotion from within. It's a sham. It's a flat organization by design, and it will stay that way. They say you can work 9-5, but in order to get everything done you have to stay late, take work home, or work on weekends, not to mention all the events you'll have to attend. There is no such thing as unlimited vacation time, with any employer in the world-that claim doesn't even make sense. Think about it. Forget about the house in Hawaii...just.forget.it.-This is not a job for rational people.-This is not a job for entrepreneurs. That would mean that you have some say over what you do on a daily basis, and trust me, you do not.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be honest with prospective new hires. Give them the specifics about what it takes to hit 5-10 FTE's and how they have to maintain the FTE's.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sporadic work, unprofessional recruiters.”

</title><pros>Pros – I earned a small amount of paid contract work through this company. Their gigs paid well and their insurance would have been nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No direct hire. Just more temp job hopping. They expect you to drop everything and start working at a place the next day through short, poorly written, unprofessional emails and no interview process. Otherwise, good luck reaching them. They will only respond about 50% of the time and sometimes will send you to a client without all the information you need to be successful.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Manage your employees and hire more carefully.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Director of Business Development (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“start-up company backed up by a 25 year old corporation”

</title><pros>Pros – - my first job where I work a 40 hour week (I used to work at ad agencies)- fantastic benefits- I have never felt more supported by positive feedback</pros>
<cons>Cons – We are growing quickly so there is the "start-up mode" but that can be fun!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Come visit Seattle!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Recruiter (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Best Place I've Ever Worked”

</title><pros>Pros – I've never worked at a place that values it's employees more.  We truly get unlimited time off and as a result the people here work hard and don't watch the clock.  The health benefits are unparalleled.  The job is extremely satisfying - finding other people work, helping them to feed their families and fulfill their career aspirations  - it just doesn't get any better.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company is extremely focused on metrics, sometimes to the fault of any strategy.As a recruiter, I have what sometimes feels like an unrealistic amount of responsibilities per week.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Track the relevant metrics that lead to orders.  For example, if a recruiter showcases 5 talent a week which leads to 5 orders, that should be more important than activity for activity's sake.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-22</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Director, Business Development (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Vitamin T is a growing, fast paced place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Co-WorkersGood balance between work and personal lifeConstant and consistent educationEver growing</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you enjoy being "micro managed" this company is NOT for you!If you are not a self starter or do not like a fast pace- this company is not for you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Agent/Recruiter (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast (paced), fun, and fantastic”

</title><pros>Pros – It's kind of the best of both worlds. Vitamin T is a start-up with the backing of a mature company thats been in the creative staffing business for 25 years. If you like change, if you like creative and if you like building a business from scratch, this is the place for you.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you're not "good" with time management, this is not the place for you.  We have ambitious goals, thankfully there's plenty of help to get there. Yet, not everyone can hang with being held accountable to specific goals under tight deadlines.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>User Experience Dev (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Paycheck was a month late”

</title><pros>Pros – - Nice benefits plan, however, it can be cancelled at the last moment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - They got me a job without an interview that lasted 3 days (it was supposed to be a week.)- They were over a month late in getting me my paycheck. They kept giving me excuses before sending it to me. I'll never deal with this company again.- They have a try before you hire policy. This means you can be fired without any warning, and this can hurt your resume more than it helps it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Freelance Graphic Designer”

</title><pros>Pros – Got a freelance job after a month of interview, and I worked for a month. Pretty nice pay, but that's it. Never got another job after that.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The jobs are not that excited.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Recruiter/Agent (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't be fooled.”

</title><pros>Pros – The company has a  great reputation.  Vitamin T is backed by Aquent and both talent and clients know the name and respect it. They have a pretty cool presence on Twitter and other social media outlets.  The pay is pretty decent too.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You'll have a manager, but there is very little leadership or actual management. There is no training, just expectations.  You will be totally on your own to figure out everything.  Then your manager will tell you that you're doing everything wrong and have no solutions to help.The FTE system is nearly impossible.  To get 1 FTE you need to have 2 people working full time hours and that's extremely difficult when all you have to offer your talent is short term freelance projects. Then when you don't have enough FTEs, you'll be "warned" and fired.They'll say that work/life balance is important but it's not.  You'll find yourself stressed out, overwhelmed, working late, taking your work home with you at night and working on the weekends trying to get the jobs filled.  And that still won't be enough. Of course you have the option to work 9-5, but you'll learn quickly that's not in your best interest if you want to keep your job.In the interview process you'll be told over and over again that the Agent roll is not sales, then you'll find that you have to cold call clients for new orders.  Feels very bait and switch.They say it's unlimited time off.  Please do not believe that.  First of all it won't be long before you're afraid to ask for time off.  Then when you do ask for it (and if it's approved)  you'll still be expected to follow up with emails, leads etc while you're supposed to be off.Please don't believe that this is a job for people who are good at connecting and matchmaking.  You will fail miserably at this job if you try to make connecting/matchmaking your focus.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please actually manage and lead.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Recruiter/Agent (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Vitamin T will burn you out..”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent work-life balance and you don't have to work past 5pm-Ability to be an develop your own style-clients and talent poolRelaxed, casual environmentHappy Hour in the office</pros>
<cons>Cons – One week of training about the corporate culture and how to use the database-Branding is big as VT is a division of Aquent-but wants to be seen as an 'Agency'-cool and funky, but alas is all under the Aquent umbrella.You will be given training and let lose to 'fill orders'-6-9 months later you will be told it is all wrong and if you don't make your Full Time numbers for placement you will be fired.Working under the gun with no direction of 'how' to fullfill Full Time roles will stress you out.  Word to the wise is VT DOES NOT offer Direct Hire, however your numbers are based on full time employment.  The model does now work and you will make NOTHING in commission as designers do not want short term gigs.Turing away Direct Hire roles is a huge mistake for the company.VT only works small companies and you are limited to who you can work with as the large clients with all the money are property of Aquent and the recruters there.The orders are not distributed to all agents-you will have an area of 'expertise' and those roles go to you.  If you are an expert in Graphic Design, you can fill roles, UX expert, good luck!Each week you go over numbers, but not how to get them up, except for 'fill more orders', bring in more talent.MUST be an Entrepreneur-if not you will fail at this role.  Not for the faint of heart or those who think they can be a matchmaker.Turn over is HUGE as VT is only about 1.6 years old now.  Individuals who worked for Aquent for years and came to the VT side have bailed and are at competing agencies-and happyOH There is NO advancement in Vitamin T.  You are an Agent or Business Development.  No Senior titles, continuing education, etc... Maybe if you are friendly with your Manager and have been with the comapny 10 years they may call you Sr.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – While the open vacation policy is great, how about NOT taking 3 consecutive Friday/Mondays off in a row in a single month.  My supervisor was gone having fun with friends and family more than in the office.  Also, the 'tools' you are given from your supervisor to better do your job are a joke because they are just words-like get on the phone more, or push the client to hire your talent.  What does that mean, get on the phone more and do what?It would be nice to have my supervisor in the trenches as well-interviewing talent, bringing in orders-show us how it is done.  Even if your supervisor has been and 'agent' or 'biz dev' years ago-be a role model of how it is done.  Stop playing on FB and Twitter.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Recruiter/Agent (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Love, love love my VitaminT!”

</title><pros>Pros – -Work life/balance! (no cap on days off, flexibility with schedule)-Rewarding work (getting people jobs, hello?!)-Entrepreneurial spirit (you run your own biz)-Part of a larger Aquent family (big company benefits)-My team - I absolutely adore the people I work with, and we rock it out!-Susie Hall, the President, is such a stud-Positivity! We get rewarded and patted on the back for our successes</pros>
<cons>Cons – -I've heard some teams are not as stellar as mine, in terms of management-You need to be fast-paced, quick-witted, and VERY INDEPENDENT to thrive-Limited upward mobility (some people stay in their roles for many years, not sure if that's because they like where they are, or there isn't opportunity)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Vitamin T lets you create your own opportunities.”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Work/life balance2. Ability to create and move into new roles3. They truly want you to succeed and give you the tools to do so4. There is always something fun happening.5. Admit when they've made a mistake with changes</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. The salaries aren't low, but they could use a better raise system/scale2. Commission structure is low in comparison to other staffing companies</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-31</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor Overall experience”

</title><pros>Pros – The negative review that was posted a few weeks ago, could not have said it better.  The only plus I can think of is that you will get to leave at 5 every day.  As you'll leave, there's a good chance you'll be miserable.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As has been stated on here before, you're on your own.  And with the wrong manager (and that term is used as loosely as possible since there's no actual managing being done) you will be miserable on a day to day basis.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Review what your "regional managers" are actually doing and how much contact they have really have with the people the "supervise".  So of the decisions they are making, for example promoting people with little to no experience, are downright idiotic.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Recruiter/Agent (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sad to say an overall Terrible Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – I wish I had more positive things to say, since I went in with high hopes after their sales pitch-like interview process.  One thing to mention is that no matter how they spin it, Vitamin T is a Division within Aquent.  Vitamin T is NOT a standalone company or even a spin.  All Aquent corporate policies, rules, guidelines and paperwork  are a part of Vitamin T.  There are no Vitamin T offices...you work in an Aquent office.  This is a positive thing, since Aquent seems more stable and filled with better people.  Generally GOOD people.  The same can't be said for Vitamin T.One plus to note is that your base salary will be higher than a lot of staffing firms out there.  This is because despite what you are told in the interview process, your bonuses will be next to nothing.  You may never have to work late at Vitamin T, but on the times that you do, it literally has no affect on your commission.  Commission-wise you'll make more with one direct hire fill at another staffing firm then you will here in 6 months and that is NOT an exaggeration.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This review is more of a TAKE CAUTION notice.  If you are put on a certain "team" (based on location) within Vitamin T, your experience will be a nightmare.  Easily the worst managment I've ever seen.  You will receive almost zero supervision, support, coaching and even direct contact with this manager.  You will be forced to learn on your own and then two months later will be told that everything you've learned on your own, is wrong.  The worst part then is that you won't be told or supported in how to fix this, you'll just continue to be told that it's wrong.  The turnover rate on this team alone is 50% and climbing.  Take great caution...I wouldn't wish my experiences as part of this "team" on anyone.Vitamin T has gone to great lengths to brand themselves with an "agency" feel and look.  But that is exactly what it is...a look.  No matter what they say, Vitamin T is a division within a very large corporation (Aquent).  And with that come all the normal policies and procedures that go along with working for a large corporation.The unlimited vacation policy looks great on paper, but is worthless if you're afraid to use it.  Overall, hands down the most unprofessional experience I've ever encountered in far too many ways to list here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The FTE system doesn't not work.  It's great for Aquent employees that have been with the company for ten years and have long standing relationships with clients who always require freelance talent.  But for  the Vitamin T side it's a joke.  In this economic climate, creatives DO NOT want constant freelance work.  They want the stability that comes with a full time job.  To not offer direct hire is a complete and utter disservice to your creative talent, clients, and employees as a commission bonus.  Without direct hire, Vitamin T will continue to be run over by staffing firms that do offer it.  Ask yourself as a job seeker, are you using a firm that requires you to go temp to perm or one that has a "direct hire" option?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>