<name>H. Lee Moffitt Cancer Center & Research Institute Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/H-Lee-Moffitt-Cancer-Center-and-Research-Institute-Reviews-E40232.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-25</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Staff RN, Manager, Nursing Supervisor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Staff RN BMT, Manager BMT, Nursing Supervisor”

</title><pros>Pros – Love oncology patients and the care of them</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lately many changes made business for important than patients.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Job satisfaction though pay for my position needs to be re-evaluated.”

</title><pros>Pros – Laid back environment in my department. Great working with patients and meeting new people each day. Most staff members are easy to work with and have good attitudes.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay rates and having to pay to park in lots that may not be close to the hospital.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall Fantastic”

</title><pros>Pros – Life/Work balance options, promotes from within, great gift shop and everyone knows that their sole purpose there is for the patients.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Parking can be a problem because you are on USF property. They have levels of paid parking.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Communicate with your staff, engage more.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Anonymous Employee”

</title><pros>Pros – Great life/work balance. Love the culture here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Subpar benefits. No career opportunities if specialized.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen and implement</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Bio Statistician (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“biostatistician”

</title><pros>Pros – relative comfortable working environment, department boss is good</pros>
<cons>Cons – staff faculty treated very differently, staff does not have voice in department develpment, bad health insurance</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Oncology Technician (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is a great experience!”

</title><pros>Pros – I work with very nice people!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Often, we are working with not enough staff.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-28</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exciting to work for a mission driven organization”

</title><pros>Pros – - Strong mission and culture- Great work ethic among co-workers- Unique benefits like on-site daycare and Employee Acute Care Clinic- Focus on diversity</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Since Moffitt is a non-profit  organiization, salaries are sometimes in the lower end.  However, funds are needed to treat and research cancer.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep focus on mission and help employees understand contributions to organization's goals</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Bioinformatics Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very Happy at Moffitt Cancer Center”

</title><pros>Pros – There are many training and learning opportunities available to employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – None that I can think of.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>PAR (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I Dream of Moffitt”

</title><pros>Pros – Giving best customer service to patients.  Co-Workers are great team mates fun to work with we help each other.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No increases, salary low, no incentives, no growth, managers need to do the jobs themselves so they understand struggles with work load.  Don't care if you are sick you get written up, occurrences.  If you make you employees happy they will give you 100 percent. Favoritism towards certain employees.  Employees sleeping on the job same one everyday.  Hard workers don't get recognized.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire competent Managers. Managers that will listen and just not delegate. Review the policies. Each department should have team update polices and make sense of them.  They are written poorly and do not make sense.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Enjoy opportunity to work from home”

</title><pros>Pros – Moffitt allows for flex scheduling, working from home, etc.   Although benefits have decreased, they are good in comparison to other healthcare systems.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Non clinical departments work in silos.  Employees often struggle to work on multidepartment teams. Communication from leadership is slow.  Employees often find out news about company thorugh reading outside publications</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Communicate with employees regarding company changes before sending announcements to the media.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Heavy on process; disorganized and dishonest management”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent flexible work arrangement possibilities for some IT staff--work from home one or more days per week, or have a compressed work week (i.e. work more hours a few days per week or pay period and have one weekday per week or pay period off).Very good pay for certain positions.Fairly generous time-off accrual and a PTO 'cash-in' option mean one rarely can't take time off or benefit financially from not taking time off.The environment is fairly casual with respect to expectations. Anybody with any competence is very likely to find it easy to appear much more capable than his co-workers (but: see the 'con' re: tolerance of inferior performance for why).</pros>
<cons>Cons – The benefits package underwent a huge downward 'adjustment' in the 2012/2013 year; I would rate them at well below averageCommunication from the executive level down to the lowest supervisor is painfully absent. Frequently direct supervisors and their immediate supervisors provide conflicting information regarding policies or new initiatives.Within my department it is clear that the managers and their director are frequently on completely separate pages. I have been told two different things by my supervisor and his boss on more than one occasion. It is also very clear that my immediate supervisor, his peers and their boss do not have a unified direction in mind for the department. There is nothing that binds our teams together, or even that binds the individuals on my team, to work toward a common goal, so I often find myself wondering why we're organized the way we are. I work directly with individuals in other teams and departments, and it seems this isn't just my department.There is a high tolerance for continued inferior performance and competence among management and non-management alike. I often find myself thinking it's subconsciously deliberate so that an environment of expected mediocrity is the norm: that's demoralizing. Compounding this is a glib and ready hand to hint at the prospect for promotion, but it always seems to be "6 to 8 months" down the road.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate I (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Research Associate”

</title><pros>Pros – Wonderful Cause, Wonderful culture and traditions.Cohesive staff.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Faculty plays favorites and doesn't provide as many opportunities as possible for learning</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on increasing diversity.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“HR and Sr. Mgmt are a joke/Employee morale is in the toilet”

</title><pros>Pros – It used to be a great place to work, with every employee happy to be there and contributing to the prevention and cure of cancer.  That was in mid 2000.</pros>
<cons>Cons – "More with less" is the mantra.  If you press your boss for that promotion they promised after years of "exceeds expectations" and making them look good (by taking all credit for your work), then you suddenly get re-assigned, re-evaluated (as a poor performer), and shown the door. Going to HR is a joke, because all they do is inform your manager you have a problem with them.  Going to Sr. Mgmt is a joke, because they are all poorly trained in how to effectively manage people.  This happens in every department in all of Moffitt.  Anything that looks like a nail is quickly hammered down.  I hope Alan List is able to change this systemic mentality.  For an institution dedicated to curing cancer... they certainly allow malignant people to persist as managers.  If you need a job, fine.  If you want a career, look elsewhere.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay attention to your departmental responsibilities and the people in your departments.  Stop treating your employees like crap just because you can (no other employment options in Tampa for many roles).  Happy employees are a lot more productive, and offering some respect is free.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Culture Good People”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent commitment to mission, smart dedicated employees, true compassion for the customer and desire to  find the cure for cancer.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours, unclear goals, benefit reductions, less focus on research more focus lately on processes and procedures.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Communicate consistently with employees on future direction of company even if not clear</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-31</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Largest Cancer Center in Florida with great potential”

</title><pros>Pros – largest cancer center in florida, leading research in personalize medicine, increasing number of cancer patients with high satisfaction rating. enough grant funding and  plenty of publication in leading research journals</pros>
<cons>Cons – still growing but with slow expansion. recent change of management, just doing OK financially due to health care reform and NIH funding situation. weak support for cutting-edge research.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Research Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Moffitt is not what it used to be 4 years ago”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent research leading to fighting cancer, noble cause.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Moffitt doesn't treat its staff the way it used to be 4 years ago</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Support the advancement of current employees in the research area.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Intense”

</title><pros>Pros – It is an honor to work for such a worthy cause as curing cancer and you get to do it with brilliant people who are also passionate about what they do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It sometimes feels like we are trying to do too many things at once, with not enough staff.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Postdoctoral Research Fellow (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Great learning environment for beginner researchers, great developmental opportunities for research agenda</pros>
<cons>Cons – A little bit too much bureaucracy</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work and stay in touch closer with employees from all levels and departments</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Release of Information Tech (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok....Pays the Bills”

</title><pros>Pros – I learned a lot working in medical records.  It is a good job to gain experience for advancement in your career.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay and very low pay raises.  The benefits are not good.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Interact more with your employees and be available when you are needed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Data Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Moffitt for Profit”

</title><pros>Pros – You're helping people deal with a horrible disease, which is always admirable. For some, this is all they need to be happy in a job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's all about money and not about patient care. It is not a place where a voice can or will be heard unless you carry MD after your name. Very political, and treatment is based on who you rather than what you do.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treatment of employees should be fair across the board. Firing someone for a perceived offense that the majority of senior staff is also committing will eventually catch up to you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Graphic Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A place to make a difference and touch the lives of others.”

</title><pros>Pros – Get to work with great people and professionals. Have an opportunity to help other people battle cancer. Knowing you make a difference in what you do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The only items that come to mind are, working in different locations and having restricted and limited space in parking on the main campus.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to the employee and the experience they share. Be willing to change with the times and new managerial skills. Open your mind to new opportunities and procedures.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent work environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Management is supportive.  There is collaboration.  The work and life balance is great.  As an employee you are helping the cure of cancer.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The worst con which is very minimal is the parking.  It is spread out so there may be offsite parking where an employee would have to take a 5 min shuttle that runs every 15-20 mins to the building they work in.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The general workforce were mostly committed to the institutional mission while leadership was not.”

</title><pros>Pros – Dedicated employees are genuinely proud of the Center and its mission and patients for the most part have positive experiences.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Impressions are more valued than substance and truth. Patient care is not truly valued. Leadership has been essentially clueless about some key issues for 25 years.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Truly attend to all of those employee survey data. There is great skepticism and mistrust because of the lack of genuine response.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Coordinator II (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – The work was rewarding and fit my interests well... I loved what I did and felt my work was appreciated by my superiors. It was a great place to learn and grow. Moffitt offers numerous opportunities for work-life balance and also seminars & lectures where employees can learn more about current research in their field. They actually had an impressive schedule of guest lecturers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working for a research company is a somewhat unique situation and Moffitt uses a dual-report system where employees report to an administrative supervisor and principle investiagor. There is sometimes a disconnect between employees and administrative supervisor. It can sometimes be frustrating to have to report to an admin spvsr who you feel didnt know you or the caliber of your work. But I also recognize the benefits to such a system to allow investigators to focus on their expertise and not have to deal with the bureaucratic nonsense.I felt that I wasnt paid what my skills were worth when I was there... but don't we all? I worked there during the worst part of the recession and Moffitt was making serious cuts around the office (no coffee in the breakroom--couldnt even get your hands on a plastic fork!), but the employees recognized that times were hard and I think it was appreciated that these cuts were made rather than letting employees go.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Moffitt is generally a good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – good family work life balance is achievable, great benefits, nice to feel a part of the good work that is done at moffitt</pros>
<cons>Cons – not much room for advancement in research, company focuses on clinical side and research is somewhat neglected, management is ok, but not stellar</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – stop meeting so much and act, many things could be streamlined, the internal website could be made much more user friendly</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a bad place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – I work part time and it is very hard to find a comparable job in the area that compensates as well.They also have great benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very high stress work environment which is reflected in the attitude of the employees.Not much opportunity for growth in certain positions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more actively involved the employees beneath them, communicate more effectively, and make yourself be seen. The only time I have ever seen the CEO is on television during a Rays game.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Friendly Staff”

</title><pros>Pros – Most of the employes are warm and caring. The building is spotless. There is a Starbucks and a cafeteria on site.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There isn't enough self parking. The hiring process takes too long.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get a better HR department.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-31</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“its good.”

</title><pros>Pros – good benefits, nice compensation, inside look on my future</pros>
<cons>Cons – sad to see some patients</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – be a little nicer</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I am a pleased and proud Moffit employee.”

</title><pros>Pros – Moffitt employees are treated as team members working toward a common goal.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The economy (insurance payments, etc) has a major effect on Moffitt, even though Moffitt is a not for profit institution.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Moffitt”

</title><pros>Pros – Dedicated employees on the patient floorpatient focused and very understanding</pros>
<cons>Cons – not for profit attitude, not profit focused</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Evaluate talent better</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Postdoctoral Fellow”

</title><pros>Pros – NIH designated cancer centerFC Tampa Bay Rowdies (Soccer)BeachesWeather</pros>
<cons>Cons – Tampa, FLlow educated peopleengergy wasting company (no solar panels)no/few opportunity to come by bicycle and take a shower</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – no</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Moffitt Cancer Center good for translational research”

</title><pros>Pros – The Moffitt Cancer Center is well positioned with both a world-class cancer hospital and research program.  Both the hospital and research center share facilities and faculty, which enables for a great flow of scientific ideas.  Performing translational, high-impact research is easy due to these attributes.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The downside to working at Moffitt is that there are no/few biotech jobs in the Tampa area.  This forces postdocs to have to relocate to another city to pursue new positions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Leadership is very competent and listens to the complaints of the its employees.  Leadership provides employees with ample seminars/workshops to for continued education.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>