<name>Larry H. Miller Group Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Larry-H-Miller-Group-Reviews-E4028.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Just ok...”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits while living in Utah. LHM pretty much owns anything and everything. Great location, easy to get to on and off the freeway.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Health Insurance is very expensive, but good coverage. Since it is a "Family" run business, no real room to move up. Not real salaried positions. Micromanages...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get to know your employees. Have at least yearly reviews. At least pretend to care about your employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Just ok, but heading downhill”

</title><pros>Pros – If you like sports and want to work in a pro sports environment this is a great place.  You have  the ability to learn what it takes to run Professional sports event.  There are great people that work here and can at time be a fun environment to work in.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you are looking to advance your career, this is probably not the place for you.  Once you are hired you are hired, and you learn that all the valuable employees don't work for the company yet.  If contributing new ideas is your thing, look elsewhere.  The management is happy with the status quo (but they will ask you to innovate, only to crush every idea you bring to the table).  And the pay, make sure you get what you can live with for the rest of your life.  It is not a company that feels that employees should receive increases during their career (5 years counting with no pay increase).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Look at your employee base and begin to appreciate them, they are the ones ensuring that you have a job yourself.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Concessions (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible”

</title><pros>Pros – Two free movie tickets, and the group of people you work with are really nice and they become your best friends.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low Pay, no room to move up. Management are rude and selfish.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Working in concessions is stressful as it already is and the annoying rude customers don't help. Working at 7.25 for 8 hour shifts a day, and only 30 minute breaks? You're a million dollar company! worth more! Make use and raise the pay.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-01</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Sales Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I was the go-to manager, training other managers, finance managers and employess”

</title><pros>Pros – I thought Larry H. Miller was a great group and expanding so I chose to work for them. The reason I am no longer with them is I had a major knee reconstruction and in my downtime, I felt that I wasn't making enough of an impact on others around me. I want to contribute to society. I've had family die of diabetes, Cystic Fibrosis, Strokes and Heart attacks. I want to give back and I know that working for a group like you would allow me to do that.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I worked 6 14 hour days no matter what. After 20 years, I feel that my mind was being caged. I have such a mind that works overtime and is always thinking outside the box. I adhere to rules and regulations but I know I can give more to society than what I'm doing now.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I learn quickly, I train just as I learn, I have a great positive attitude which transfers in how people are treated, I think everyone is the same regardless of color and if you want it, if you are qualified for it, why not make the move to do it. You will be the one who lays down at night knowing you may have assisted someone in a positive manner.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Car Salesman (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tough business. Can be rewarding.”

</title><pros>Pros – Income potential is real. A person can earn several thousand per month</pros>
<cons>Cons – Tough to last while building a pipeline.</cons>
<advice-to-management> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent”

</title><pros>Pros – Great pay, well structured, able to perform</pros>
<cons>Cons – More difficult advancement in such a competitive business</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-11-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Finance Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Larry Miller Group (Automotive Dealerships)”

</title><pros>Pros – They have good benefits packages compared to other automotive dealerships.  Compensation is average  comparatively with other dealerships for the Oregon region.  Bonus and spiff programs are average as well.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inner Circle Politics.  Lack of communication and unwillingness to stick to a plan.  Unclear expectations of what job responsibilities and performance should be.  Favoritism for friends and family, instead of experience and genuine passion for the business.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Better communication with employees on the ground level.  The auto business is notorious for being an "old boys" club, which means innovations of newer employees are sometimes stifled because "that's not how we do things here".</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I met a lot of great people”

</title><pros>Pros – great peoplefree moviesflexible work</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad managerspoor payfelt very replaceable</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>