<name>Space Exploration Technologies Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Space-Exploration-Technologies-Reviews-E40371.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast paced, busy, and long hours in cutting edge work”

</title><pros>Pros – working with top of the line technology, young culture, rewarding, cool CEO, relaxed bosses, open office environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – sometimes had to work ridiculous hours (sometimes 7/12's) as an intern.  Even then, the work was pretty rewarding.  Also, company is heavily dependent on launches: if a launch fails, the company would likely be in trouble</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Build, Test, and Fly Rockets...literally”

</title><pros>Pros – -Work was very challenging-Extremely interesting-Rockets everywhere</pros>
<cons>Cons – -60+ hour weeks and weekends</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing place to intern”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are incredible at SpaceX. Not just bright and capable, but really passionate about what they do. The engineers are not simply there to endure a daily grind to get paid and go home - they care about what they are doing and are personally invested in the success of their projects. You are provided with all the support you need to work effectively, from an excellent computer to cheap/free food.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hours are long. Even if the work is interesting, there isn't as much time for other things during the week. If you aren't careful, you'll burn out.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep pushing the envelope on what's possible, but also remember that employees are people too, and want to have lives outside of work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast-paced, exciting place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – - High-energy, collaborative environment - People work long hours, but usually because they want to and the work is exciting - Lots of employee perks - Everyone is very smart and there is tons of room to innovate and bring your ideas to the table - People are rewarded based on merit, not too much beurocracy - Launching rockets!</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Can get a little hectic/stressful at times with the aggressive schedules</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not what you think”

</title><pros>Pros – New factory, very modern and upscale. Fancy meeting rooms. Free lunch once a month.</pros>
<cons>Cons – SpaceX only wants to squeeze the most work out of you until you burn out, like a paper towel you use and then throw in the trash. Very little career mentoring and developing. Many people say the management is awful, and trust me, IT IS. You work yourself to death because you believe in the goals of the company, but management only cares to pin point and emphasize what you have done less than perfect. It is very difficult to stay motivated in an environment that does not reward good work and shames you into working harder regularly.People from the outside see the great things that SpaceX is accomplishing but on the inside it is very different. Great, outstanding engineers and experienced technicians leave every week. I have received too many "Farewell..." emails, it is beyond sad. The recruiting team in HR does a great job of hiring top talent but there are no good managers to keep them with the company. Thing is that everyone is threading water to stay afloat and if you lend a hand to train or help someone else, you will sink.Very few managers actually have any interpersonal skills.The management style of this company is unsustainable, they burn through engineers like an Olympic runner burns thru shoes. The company gets away with paying substandard salaries because of the cool company image and the stock options. But the thing is that it is not a small company anymore, it is a fairly big company now and the stock options do not make up for not having 401K matching and low pay. No tuition assistance either to get your masters.If you joined the company 3+ years ago, sure the stock options will pay for you. But joining now you will not make money with the stock options.Do not recommend at all, to anyone, single or married, with children or no children. This company will suck the life out of you and leave you demoralized and an empty shell of your former self.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire good managers, this company needs leadership! Or train people to be good manager and give direction to its employees and motivation. Not the standard "you suck, your are not working hard enough" to people who work 60 hour weeks.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Intern - Review”

</title><pros>Pros – Very fasted paced, but you are treated like a full-time employee as an intern. Good pay and provided first month of housing for interns</pros>
<cons>Cons – Worked close to 70 hrs a week. The intern bus schedule forces you work at least 50 hrs a week. Make sure to negotiate your salary based on 50 hrs+ rather than 40 hrs.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technician Trainee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great job for any non-sleeper!”

</title><pros>Pros – The company pays very well and there are many perks. Most of the old dudes are pretty easy-going. I loved working here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The scheduling is terrible, especially when working to met project deadlines. When you're hired, you are told that you may be working any 8-hour period for up to five days per week but never to exceed that. During my time there, I worked 12-hour shifts, 6 days a week. If that were expressed to me prior, I may not have had a problem with it. Since it was more so of a surprise, it was slightly upsetting</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management is dog-eat-dog. Most of the supervisors just want to look good for Elon. They're nice to you when you do something good, but if ONE person on the team makes a mistake, everyone is punished.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exciting, Fast-paced company to intern for”

</title><pros>Pros – I had an amazing experience interning at SpaceX.  You get to work on projects that you would never see at another company.  They give you real ownership and value their interns' opinions.</pros>
<cons>Cons – SpaceX expects all of its employees to work very long hours, including weekends.  There is almost a competitive feel for who can commit the most hours.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – promote efficiency vs long hours</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Avionics Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wonderful Chaos”

</title><pros>Pros – You work for Elon musk. Long term focus is on changing history rather than pleasing a board. You get a sense that we are going places. The Lunchpad, coffee bar and froyo stand are nice.Manufacturing and engineering in one place.The overall caliber of engineers is very high. The amount of knowledge in one place is incredible.</pros>
<cons>Cons – SpaceX is no longer a small company.Work Life balance varies greatly by dept.Located in LA</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Beurocracy creep is a silent killer with a very real potential to remove SpaceX's edge and bring us to our knees. Make sure engineers and skilled techs maintain a high level of autonomy.Find a way to differentiate the pizza boy you just hired from the skilled techs with experience. They are not the same. One can follow a procedure. The other is highly valuable and has a brain that should be put to use.As SpaceX matures, find a way to encourage people to move roles within the company when their current roles are no longer needed or they are becoming burnt out. Without a pathway for renewal we risk becoming an aerospace behemoth full of vestigial people pushing TPS reports but holding on for a job. Many people could be better utilized. We are nowhere close the efficiency point of Siemens or Boeing but are not as nimble as we used to be either.Avoid hiring more people. Use the ones we have better. More people = worse communication, diminishing incremental value per person and higher burn rate.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-22</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Development (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Challenging, hard work, and worth every minute.”

</title><pros>Pros – SpaceX is trying to change the world for the good of humanity, and being part of that is an awesome experience.Plus, the company is a great place to work. The people that work here are smart, passionate about what they do, and not afraid of hard work. Employees are given the opportunity to take on big challenges, which is incredibly rewarding. And come on, you literally get to work at a ROCKET FACTORY. How cool is that?</pros>
<cons>Cons – Despite how much the company has grown it still seems like there's always too much work and not enough people. As pretty much every review says, you'll likely work a lot of hours, so you really have to make an effort to maintain work/life balance.Many potential "cons" depend on your personality and the type of work environment you prefer. For example, schedules and goals are agressive and employees are given a lot of responsibility and are expected to consistently perform at extremely high levels. This can either be really rewarding or super stressful depending on the person. (But to be fair, even people who like this type of environment can burn out after too much of it.)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep it up...Mars or bust!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-22</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tough but rewarding”

</title><pros>Pros – After working here, I can't imagine working anywhere else.  Definitely has the most passionate and dedicated workforce in the industry with everyone invested (and vested) in the success of the company.  Not a place for 9-to-5 workers, but those who are willing to put in the time and effort to make sure that SpaceX changes the way the industry does business.SpaceX gives everyone the chance to set themselves apart and will give increased responsibility to anyone who excels.  Not a company to just breeze by, its a company where one is to step up and accept the next challenge (and there are typically some mighty challenges).  If you prove yourself, you'll get the additional responsibility.Benefits are good, salary is at least on industry par (and from what I've heard only gotten better over the years), and stock options are obviously great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hours are long, deadlines are difficult, and challenges are tough - but that is what makes SpaceX what it is.  Its a given coming in, so no one should be surprised when they get there.  What makes SpaceXers different is that they are not there for a job or a career, they are there to impact the future - and that means that it will be harder than the typical aerospace job.  But who really wants a boring job for a company that they don't care if it succeeds or not?</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The little things matter. Continue to increase any perks or morale boosters to show the employees that their efforts are acknowledged. Things like numbered mission patches mean a lot, even if they haven't flown in space. Take things slow - don't need to change everything at once, take some time to build up successes. If we don't have those, we may never get the opportunity to go what we are reaching for - Mars and beyond.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Propulsion Technician (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“bad leadership”

</title><pros>Pros – the end of the month employee appreciation luncheon</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much work and giving up your free time(weekends/days-off) to make deadlines because some people in the upper echelon made a mistake and didnt say anything untill the product was finished. Bad vibes, just bad vibes..but that depends on which department you work in. Did i mention bad leadership? You cant use marine corp leadership to get things done.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Structures Engineer”

</title><pros>Pros – Awesome work environment, great leadership, doesn't really feel like work when you're building rockets that launch into space and writing the future.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work-life balance is tough, depending on the department or project you are on you can expect to see yourself going from 50 hour weeks to 70-80 work weeks.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Rock on.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Structures Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very demanding but with killer rewards”

</title><pros>Pros – Amazing sense of accomplishment with current pace of the company and high contributions of each employee.  Get things done insanely quick compared to the industry standard.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Difficult to maintain work life balance with workload.  High workload and degree of stress that comes with the nature of busy schedules.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tough but fun and rewarding!”

</title><pros>Pros – Sending rockets to spacePeople we work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Parking is tough but supposedly there is a parking garage that is starting construction this summer that we are putting in.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Culture is important</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Like 1950s Science Fiction, Without the Super Geniuses”

</title><pros>Pros – SpaceX is an exciting place to work. Elon Musk has the courage and funding to do what people were saying for decades--quit tweaking 1950s technology--and combine lessons from the past with cutting edge manufacturing technologies. Lots of incidental perks, from a really good on-site restaurant to fancy coffee machines. The software challenges are probably just about right for many engineers and the corporate goal of Mars settlement is one that could change history.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not really Cons, just caveats.  It seems as though many people find the programming challenge given to job applicants hard. It seems to be a fairly good match for the difficulty of much of the Flight Software work, so if you don’t find it especially hard, and complete it successfully well before the deadline, you might not find the work as challenging as you hope. If you are a participant in open source activities, ITAR (International Traffic in Arms Regulations) makes for a huge hurdle. Hours expected are sometimes long enough that some people nap at their desks. Most of the software developers are pretty junior. Glad I read other reviews because it gave me a pretty good idea of what to expect.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Communication, communication, communication.</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you are the BEST, then you are SpaceX material”

</title><pros>Pros – All the pro's mentioned in previous reviews are true. Now...remove all the make-up (the perks) and you get the cons.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Overzealous engineers that have been led to believe that sacrificing their lives and families while making 'history' makes them "rock stars" (yes, this is an actual review classification in the company!) I work here and my work keeps getting heavier as good and intelligent people leave and we are left with the overworked interns and rookie managers. If you want to succeed in SpaceX all you have to do is pretend to do your best by making sure people notice your lack of sleep (due to long work hours) or by missing Christmas to pull in some critical work ! Like many others I have not left because I have a family to feed. But will do as soon as I can.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop pretending to be Google ! stop spending $ on trying to keep your people happy and hire real managers or TRAIN the ones you have, or even better, buy tools to your technicians! Stop belittling the people that decided to leave the company and recognize your loss !!! Its irritating to read other current employee reviews that say that people that left left because they are incompetent. It almost seems to be that SpaceX engineers make themselves look bigger by telling themselves they are and by belittling the rest of the world. Stop messing with people's lives and stop hiring until you find out what it is that you want as a company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>FPGA Integration Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A inspiring place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Fulfilling workInspiring work environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – None from the top of my mind</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Kepp up the work</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Responsible Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Job Experience Unlike Any Other”

</title><pros>Pros – -A CEO who is passionate about revolutionizing the space industry-A President who cares about her employees-Teams of dedicated colleagues who give their all towards advancing the human race-Everything is designed, built, and launched in America!-A real opportunity to make a difference in the world-Walk the production floor whenever you want -- all of the major components are built in house, so there's always something new and amazing to see-Work with on-site NASA representatives who want to see SpaceX succeed-Tons of gourmet catered meals</pros>
<cons>Cons – Make sure you know what you are getting into before accepting a job at SpaceX because it is not for everybody. You will be given more than you think you can handle. You will work long hours. You will need to take on responsibilities outside your job description. You will be required to prove yourself when on Critical Path. At the same time, you will have the opportunity to be a part of a team who is writing history. It's up to you to accept the challenge.I can guarantee that many other people would have given up if faced with the challenges that I have gone through while at SpaceX. Nothing is easy, nothing is laid out perfectly for you. I chose to press through the hard times because I love the feeling of seeing my hardware lift off the launch pad on its way towards outer space. It is a feeling that can not be adequately be put into words.Go SpaceX!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Establish more ways to reward employees who constantly perform above and beyond the already high expectations</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager, Production Department (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Constantly Challenged to Innovate”

</title><pros>Pros – if you are not bringing innovation, change, and results to the design, production, and quality of the launch vehicles and spacecraft designs you will be immediately challenged by your peers, supervisors, and execs to up your game - on the double time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – if you are perceived as not bringing innovation, change, and results to the design, production, and quality of the launch vehicles and spacecraft designs you will be immediately challenged by your peers, supervisors, and execs to up your game - on the double time.  And your job is absolutely on the line at all times.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in training, especially up front for new hires.  Some of the turnover could be reduced by keeping some potential rock stars long enough to provide advanced training for many of the very advanced techniques we use as SpaceX.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Production Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Still the place to be”

</title><pros>Pros – Surrounded by brilliant, dedicated and extremely hard working people. Everything is working to do something truly awesome, and be an inspiration to others. You get thrown into the mix and given alot of responsibility - either sink or swim. Those that are good swimmers quickly make a name for themselves and rise to the top. It is a meritocracy.It is a helluva work experience!</pros>
<cons>Cons – As mentioned above, it's a sink or swim kind of place. Those that are complaining on these reviews just couldn't swim well enough or were not prepared to. It is very demanding. Other aerospace companies are more relaxed, but then again look at how much more SpaceX has accomplished.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – SpaceX is going through the awkward 'teenager' phase of it's life, where the average age is going from ~24 to ~30 or more, and people are starting to want to do more with their lives, and have families etc...Advice is to challenege every employee to work smarter not harder. Work from home more, and cut out the childish jokes about 'pulling a half day' if someone doesn't work 12hrs. Encourage weekends off, and consider offering every second Friday off to those who deserve it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Propulsion (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Intellectually challenging and inspiring”

</title><pros>Pros – I cannot think many things more inspiring than making space travel a legitimate reality. The best part of working for SpaceX is knowing that you can significantly contribute to it. You are given a lot of responsibility right from the start, whether you're the owner of a product that will be in space within months or working on a project that will advance humans into space. Additionally, you are in close contact with some of the brightest minds in the world, and there is a great deal to learn from anyone in the company.The environment is very unique as well. It's fast-paced, but also very laid back. Expectations are high but not unreasonable, and there is usually someone there to help you out if you get stuck. There isn't a lot of red tape either. You're encouraged to think critically and challenge things that don't make sense from both a technical and business perspective. There are other great perks too... free frozen yogurt, cappuccinos, fruit, milk, occasional lunches, gym membership, stocks, benefits, etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours. With a lot of responsibility, there is just a lot to do that most people cannot get done in a standard 8 hour day. But also, the general mentality is if you stay less than 8 hours, you can find someone to help.That said, having a work-life balance is manageable as long as you get your work done and can work efficiently</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep hiring bright people.Also, some transparency on details for big milestones would be nice.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Avionics Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Demanding and exhilarating”

</title><pros>Pros – -Cradle-to-grave lifecycle of space hardware measured in months, not years or decades. I saw my designs fly to the ISS 8 months after I started.-A culture that prioritizes functionality and capability over flight legacy/risk aversion. This in turn drives innovation, elegant design, clever solutions, and utilization of emerging technologies. Completely avoids the "Well, we know this decade-old technology worked before, so we'll just use it in perpetuity," mentality that makes all good engineers sad pandas.-Highly meritocratic structure. Promotions, bonuses, and raises are based entirely on performance. (The only thing seniority gets you is nicer parking.)-Free frozen yogurt and coffee. Frequent free gourmet food.-Stock options.-Flexible (albeit lengthy) hours. Work-from-home options.-Working with the most intelligent, dedicated and (increasingly) accomplished engineers and technicians in the field. It is an honor and a pleasure to work with and learn from my team. Good sense of humor all around, too.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Persistently lengthy work hours, occasionally brutal. (Orbital mechanics wait for no one.)-Some groups can develop a toxic interpersonal work environment when mismanaged for a long period of time.Not for people who:-Want to work a 9-5.-Can't work weekends at least some of the time.-Can't/won't innovate.-Need handholding.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>6</upvote>
<employee-type>Composite Technician (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Companies like this need to be put of of business”

</title><pros>Pros – The building is well kept and clean.Free lunch once a month.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor hiring practice/high rate of turn over. The Company hires people based on lowest bidder, this causes tremendous amounts of problems for experienced people having to work long hours due to having to pull the weight of less experienced people.I know this happens everywhere but not in the extent that is present at SpaceX.Poor Management, Managers do not know what is going on the floor. To compound the problem of hiring/promoting unqualified persons to management. The high rate of turn over in all managerial position means SOP are always changing and there is no set way of doing things. As you can imagine this creates a big problems for people on the floor trying to achieve "production" like manufacturing.On the floor as a technician, the company will change your working hours very frequently. One month it could mean you are working 8 hours a day 5 days a week. Then the next month you could be working 80 hour weeks. The hours make it very hard to balance work and personal life.Lack of equipment, self explanatory.Substantially below market in wages. On average you can expect to start 30% or lower below industry wages. The company's reasoning is you work more overtime and have stock shares to compensate the difference in wages. Every year they talk about going public the following year but never do, also the overtime is very sporadic.There are a lot more cons I can list, but it just feels like I am beating a dead horse so I will stop.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Change everything.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent start up”

</title><pros>Pros – Its a start up environment that really gives a wide range of skills and a lot of room to develop as an engineer.  It also very much values its employess, makes for a more rewarding environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The parking situation is a bit tedious.  It accounts for about 40 mins extra to the work day, its time that i would love to have back every day</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep going, we are behind you...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Avionics (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“History in the Making”

</title><pros>Pros – Space X is a company that is always moving forward. They are making history happen whether you realize it or not. Innovation is a key factor here, and it is the momentum this company carries. Everyone here is expected to be excellent, so that means there will be challenges along the way. This is why people are only getting better at there job and why this company has such a great succession rate. What makes this place even better though is the great people that work here. Everyone is friendly and easy to get along with. Plus all the workers are wanting to be successful.I work in the Avionics floor and have nothing to complain about. They take care of you here and everything is always moving forward.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The are very few cons such as, working a longer hours and putting in a weekend day or two. This is what it takes to make success though.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Propulsion Technician (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Non-stop adventure!”

</title><pros>Pros – There are way to many Pros to list but here are a few:-Being apart of history-Working on advanced technology-Fast paced-Life changing expirences-Being apart of something bigger than yourself.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I have been here almost 2 years and i have not ever had one problem here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing what you're doing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Design Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Space X -”

</title><pros>Pros – None. When you first come here, you will think it is a great place to work, only to find out the company has unrelenting schedules and had unreasonable expectations requiring 60 to 80 hours per week and has a burn  out rate higher than 50 percent. .</pros>
<cons>Cons – One of the poorest  managed companies in the US  They work young employees( aged 25 to 30 ) 60 to 80 hours per week promising them stock options that never pan out. The average employee stays less than two years or is managed out of the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Realize people have families and have a life outside of Space X</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“One of the most challenging yet fulfilling places you will work”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of great perks (food/restaurant onsite, free frozen yogurt, catered meals, free gym membership, masseuse, laundry service, stock options, free medical/dental/vision, great vacation etc..)There is a very entrepreneurial spirit at SpaceX and you get the opportunity to make difficult decisions, leaders tend to lean on you to help develop programs, processes etc. more than them just barking orders. Its like no other company I've worked at, the opinions of people from top to bottom are valued. If you have an issue or concern or think something should be changed, you will be heard and taken seriously from the leaders like Gwynne and Elon. They want to be sure everyone has what they need in order to get the job done the best and most efficient way possible which is like no other large company that I know of.It's a true meritocracy.. no one is going to get  promoted or a pay bump just because they've been there for a long time. It's truly about performance and contribution and it pays off with both bonuses, stock and compensation. Work hard and do well at SpaceX and expect a lot of responsibility as well as recognition and respect. Not something you can always get with these other large aerospace companies.You watch the launches right in front of mission control if you're at HQ or at the cape if you work down there, it's a great feeling to see that rocket get off the ground knowing you had a part in it.You'll work the hardest you ever worked and accomplish things that you didn't think you could physically do, you'll stretch the limits of your body and mind and realize that you're more capable than you ever thought. It's the most exciting fulfilling job/company I've ever worked for and I don't think I'll ever find another company quite this exciting.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is definitely a feeling of always being on your toes, that comes from the top down (which isn't necessarily a bad thing). Elon is very hands on and does sometimes create fear in leaders who are not confident in what they're doing.This isn't your 9 - 5 so be prepared to work long hours, we're doing something that hasn't been done before so the expectation and risk is high and therefore a lot of people seem to struggle with a work/life balance, however, it is possible. Also, sometimes expectations aren't always clearly communicated, so if you're unsure ALWAYS be sure to get email communication and clarification of this so you know exactly what is expected of you.You can't be too sensitive to work here either, if you're offended easily or can't take criticism or critique, don't come to SpaceX. Everyone is very type 'A' and will have no problem confronting someone that isn't doing something correct without sugar coating it.I would like to shoot down what seems to be a common theme/rumor in some of the reviews I've read on glassdoor.. a lot of people mentioned that you get chewed up and spit out and fired for no reason etc. If you DO NOT perform, you will get let go, Elon is trying to make history and people on here seem to make him out to be a villain, you can't make history by carrying those who don't want to work and/or ask questions to make sure they're doing something correctly. We need smart, capable people. SpaceX actually has a smaller percentage of turnover than your average large company with 2500+ employees. So that common theme that I see from others writing is just flat out not true.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – This is an area that is lacking, however if you have a great idea or an issue you can always bring it to Gwynne or Elon and they will listen. Besides that I think Management needs to take more ownership and quit placing blame on others for fear of losing their jobs. That being said, there are a lot of young leaders still learning and that's part of the beauty of SpaceX.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Avionics Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great opportunity to learn while doing something meaningful”

</title><pros>Pros – Fulfilling workInteresting workSmart people who enjoy sharing their knowledgeas much responsibility as you can handle (and maybe a bit more)flex hoursIf you come up with a good idea and pitch it, people listen and will often implement it</pros>
<cons>Cons – long hours, though this has been easing off as the company growsno overtime pay for salaried employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Set realistic deadlines.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Avionics, Hardware Development (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You will work with some of the smartest engineers on the planet!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Seriously, everyone here at spacex is EXTREMELY smart, talented, and driven.  Your work ethic and your engineering skills will go through the roof if you come here. There are plenty of company perks that make working here enjoyable like our new company restaurant, coffee booth, frozen yogurt booth, stock options, discounted messages, and coming soon...our very own intra-company bar!!!  Yes, that means we will get to drink beer during working hours starting in March!!!  Another very cool thing about this place is that you can move around within the company but you have to be highly proactive to make this happen.  However, all this and the chance to make history comes at a price...</pros>
<cons>Cons – ...the working hours.  60 hours per week is usually the bare minimum that salaried engineers are expected to work (hourly techs work standard 40 hrs/wk).  In time, this may kill your social life outside work or strain your relationships with your significant other.  If you're young, energetic and don't mind working late with other young engineers, this may be the company for you.  However, if you are older, value your free time or your family, you should know that this is definitely not a family or time friendly company and can lead to divorce.  You've been warned.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire more engineers so that the existing ones don't get worked to death.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome but Hard”

</title><pros>Pros – The quality of engineer that enter this place is overwhelming, working at this location you will work with the best and brightest from across the country on rocket technologies. Engineers function with a lot of autonomy as long as they get their work done. Outstanding career opportunities await if you can make it through your first couple of months. Expect to be challenged (in a good way) in terms of your abilities and workload. Did I mention you are building rockets that fly to the ISS?</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nobody said building rockets was easy. Long hours are the norm, do no expect a lot of sleep. Sometimes designs and assemblies can be rushed, leading to disastrous results.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try hiring a few more engineers/technicians instead of squeezing the life out of the ones that you have.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Mission Ops (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A sprint towards vesting”

</title><pros>Pros – Considered to be an elite company to work for.  Stock options.  Working everyday at a rocket factory.  Looks good on a resume.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Stock options only matter if you can stick around long enough to vest.  Aside from Elon, extremely poor management.  'Stuff' rolls down hill, in every group.  There is a strange mentality that celebrates being the last person in the office - like whoever leaves last somehow wins...  Employees are given very few tools to do job they are tasked to complete.  Extremely high turnover before the initial 12 month vesting period - something like 75% of people who get fired get let go prior to vesting.  Very little opportunity to advance your skill set; they hire people who are experts in a particular field, and expect them to work 80 hours a week stagnating in that skill set.  VP's are almost exclusively hired into the company, not promoted from within.  Did I mention extremely high turnover / burnout?Expect to be 'managed' toward your exit.  If a superior becomes displeased with you for performance or personal reasons, you will be placed on a 'Performance Improvement Plan' and given a job outside your core competencies, then given 30 days to reach unreachable goals and let go.I was really pumped during the recruiting process, and the first few months in the job were thrilling.  But, SpaceX is a grind and it is a really tough place to be successful.There are a lot of great companies out there, nearly all of them take better care of their people.Oh ya, Hawthorne sucks.  South Central Los Angeles is a great place to be if you want to get car jacked.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Your management style may have worked when it was a company of 200 people.  There's a reason why you have to hire Vice Presidents from the outside.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Structural Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Making history causes a lot of burn out.”

</title><pros>Pros – - You are working with very passionate and intelligent people who are come to work every day to make a significant change in the world.- You get to tell people you are a rocket scientist</pros>
<cons>Cons – - There is no work-life balance. You are expected to be on-call or at work all the time. If you get an email at 3am, you better be at the ready to answer it. If you have a family, they will suffer.- Compensation is extremely low in comparison to other companies and the number of hours worked.- Constant stress from the workload- No job security. You are at risk of being fired at any moment, even senior management that has been there since the beginning.- People are passionate but also immature. The work environment is quite young, and some of the jokes/pranks get out of hand.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start focusing on retaining the good employees by being realistic with company demands, and allowing workers the ability to see their families.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>6</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineering (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Gives space a bad name..”

</title><pros>Pros – Not sure..too hard to say..</pros>
<cons>Cons – The beloved leader is surrounded by a lead team of lackeys. The lead team got their minimal experience by hiring and firing experienced staff then calling themselves chief engineers. New engineers come in and face a roulette wheel-type scenario - try to complete tasks and hold onto possible stock options or get a miscalculated assignment from management and go down with their project so that the lead tem can tell the leader they fired the responsible party. Or if they dont like you they will give you a task way outside your proficiency to cut your tenure short. Miss-use of staff experience and bungled assignment length estimates mean that engineers are lucky to see eight months. Graduates come in by the droves as they all believe they wont come up short on this roulette wheel and experienced staff who wonder at any 30 year old calling themselves the chief engineer are sure not to last long. After each flight the staff get numbered patches. From this you can work out the 15/20% staff turn over between flights. Yeah its that bad. I know that they dont want waste but it seems more systematic for the core team to abuse assets while securing government funding - obviously smells of some .com labor pyramid scheme. SPACEX itself rather than having innovated have cherry picked all the NASA studies that NASA didnt have the funds to exploit themselves and are calling themselves revolutionary. Smart graduates are to advised to either start their own business or go to real aerospace companies that try to get the best out of their employees. Experienced aerospace professionals should be advised that your thoroughness will bring ire from management and you wont last long. Gives a bad name to the word space.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – oh geez...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Logistics Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good but long hours”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with cutting edge ideas and technology</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management not using time efficiently on projects and directing staff</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Mechanical Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exciting Place to Work and Apply Your Engineering Skills”

</title><pros>Pros – The level of autonomy for engineers is very high, almost overwhelming at times.  Many decisions are made by the engineers, and the assignments are very challenging.  Often, workers must take the initiative to discover, analyze, and address potential issues.  Watching the launches is nothing short of entirely exhilarating.  The company buys us all lunch each month and throws a great holiday party.  The president, Gwynne Shotwell, is particularly concerned with making employees happy.  Having worked at a big, established aerospace company, I can say that SpaceX is completely different.  While they're taking two months to add a doubler at a stress concentration, we're troubleshooting far greater issues in less than two weeks.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Depending on where you work and whether you are "the long pole" driving the schedule, work hours can be very long.  Some people burn out, and some people are able to pace themselves a bit better.  I think the technicians are ridden particularly hard to churn out hardware.  Management sometimes makes decisions that are baffling to us engineers, and sometimes they refuse to make decisions and opt to just blame the perceived guilty party when things don't work out (not always--it's gotten a lot better).  There is a constant prevailing sense of urgency and risk (could be a good thing).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Taking large risks is necessary, but sometimes being a bit conservative is prudent as well.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>7</upvote>
<employee-type>Statics Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exciting place but not a realistic workplace for adult & professional parents”

</title><pros>Pros – great and exciting product, the engineering team is wise and most of them very fun to work with, the company sponsors fun events to keep employees happy, full of sugar and caffeine. Christmas parties and launch parties are a blast. If you are buddies with the right people in the engineering team you will be invited to some great house parties. Make sure to find a DD.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Spacex will hire and fire as quick as the flavor of the months comes and goes, some management is comprised by inexperienced youngsters with no leadership skills, profane language is widely used, the team practices very little fellowship, work hours are in the range of 13 hrs+ daily including weekends. Great place for an intern but not so much for professional parents that need the stability of a set work schedule. The company is going through some growing pains and your happiness here will depend on how much you are willing to tolerate and who you are buddies with. If you mind a harsh non-collaborative culture that endorses the use of profane language, and work hours in the  rage of 13 hrs+ daily then this place might not be for you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in management and leadership training for your managers. Establish a culture of respect among management and downwards. Value people for their skills and stop the tall-telling to evaluate someone's performance. A  buddie's opinion isn't always right and unbiased. A buddie's seniority shouldn't play a role in his/her value to the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Propulsion Technician (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good if your new in aerospace”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits and flex hours.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible management in propulsion dept. (components and turbo pumps), unfair treatment, racism, and harassment. Micro management overload. Fire for any reason</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire management and people with aerospace background so they at least understand why we need time to complete task.. Not sowing back packs here...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Avionics, Hardware Development (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast pace work with brilliant people”

</title><pros>Pros – Most employees are young, which allows for a fast pace and constantly changing environment. You will never be bored.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As an intern, I found it hard to balance work and life. The job was very demanding.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing what you are doing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>8</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Employees are overworked and discarded for any issue”

</title><pros>Pros – Some of the greatest and most hardworking people all working together to accomplish amazing feats under tight schedules.  The amount of support you recieve from technicians, machinists, welders, and other support staff is astonishing.  People will do whatever it takes to get the job done.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No matter the anount of work that you put in or what you accomplish.  The ever shifting upper management will discard you if it prevents them from having to face the CEO.  Snap judgements are made and people scarmble to place the blame.  Schedules are unrealistic.  Knowledge is lacking.  Methods are questionable.  Highly unprofessional upper management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop trying to blame others for shortcomings and understand that you're not building cars.  Understand what it takes to actually design and build these parts and assemblies and the sacrifices that it takes to achieve the impossible.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>7</upvote>
<employee-type>CNC Machinist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“super cool at first then you burn out.”

</title><pros>Pros – free gym membership if you have time to use it, frozen yogurt, lunch once a month, good benefits, decent pay, stock options if you started at the right time now there giving very little. great if your a work aholic and love to kiss butt.</pros>
<cons>Cons – high stress especially if you work in manufacturing, high turnover of employees, very little training when you come in unlike other aerospace companys, managers play favorites, long hours with no praise from managment, engineers are very inexperienced but act like there the best in the business Boeing and Lockhead have better engineers, constant changes production is a pipe dream, i predict more flight failures once falcon 9 1.1 launches, lots of broken promises for training opportunities.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – grow up and start treating employees like human beings and not robots, stop letting engineers change stuff so much the more change the more likely you will have a failure in the future, you had a good rocket in falcon 9 now your reinventing the wheel in the beginings of a 1.6 bil contract very risky if you ask me.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cutting edge, but work-life balance gravitates towards work and long hours.”

</title><pros>Pros – Cutting edge, and doing a very cool mission trying to make, with a young atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A lot of turnover at this company, with long hours worked. Work never seems to calm down with increasing demand upon the support apparatus with no end in sight.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Compensate people better, and understand that not everyone is like the CEO where they like to work 80 hour weeks. Burnout is a problem here, and a lot of talent has left because of this.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>8</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You will be worked until you either quit or get fired”

</title><pros>Pros – There are some very smart, talented engineers at this organization.  This is a plus when you are working 80 hours a week.  There are also some very dedicated technicians who will break their backs for the right folks.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours expected to work are absolutely asinine.  The expectation is really in the 70-80 hour a week range and you will be duly chastised on a daily basis if you do not adhere to this.  I have seen many folks sleeping on the floor in their cubes because they can't go home.The management is completely in over its head.  There are mere "children" making programmatic decisions based on nothing more than if it will keep them from getting crucified by Elon.  A culture of management by fear is rampant in this organization.If you came from the Aerospace community with any level of experience, you will be looked at as part of the problem because you would like to apply the scientific method to solving problems.  Absolutely a terrible way to build a launch vehicle.There is never a good word or sincere thank you offered to the staff for a job well done.The pay is sub-standard for the most part.  You can negotiate to a reasonable level if you have the right skill set, but the majority of the staff is fresh outs and hourly folks who have never done this.Be prepared to leave a good bit of your professional morals at the door.  You will be asked to compromise them to meet the very demanding and unrealistic build schedule.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Grow up and learn how to lead.  There is a dramatic difference between being a manager and a leader.  Stand up for what is right and make the hard, right decisions rather than the easy wrong ones just to avoid a confrontation with Elon.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-29</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Would not recommend”

</title><pros>Pros – Company has a cool image, tries to come off as being like a dot com businessSome smart individuals who think outside the box</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unrealistic Schedules resulting in 60-80 hour work weeks and no holidaysUnwilling to spend money on tools and partsLots and lots of travel from site to site (for months at a time)Zero balance for life outside work (don't work here if you have a wife and children)Some very poor management with no idea who to manage people or schedules.Not at all like a dot com (google, facebook, microsoft).  You will be treated like a number and expected to work endless hours. When you can't you will be terminated summarily.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do NOT allow engineers to become managers.  Hire REAL management who have skills in interpersonal relationships.  The solution to every problem can't be "just keep going."  People are your most valuable resource, and you are squandering that resource at an unsustainable rate!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent experience, fast paced environment, and the chance to put rockets in space.”

</title><pros>Pros – High level of exposure, high level of engagement. You work on programs that are changing the face of humanity and space flight. It feels like you are back in the Apollo days.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Terrible organization. Schedules are all over the place, you can work insane hours due to a lack of planning and transparency.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be transparent. Understand the issues each employee has and relay up to CEO. Schedules can be aggressive, but they need to be reachable too.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Avionics Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Intense, rewarding, exciting.”

</title><pros>Pros – As someone who grew up without the obsession with space, I can say that this company got me excited about space exploration.-The company, though it has grown, still feels like a startup company.-Many perks for employees (frozen yogurt, soft drinks, coffee, massage chairs(!), etc.)-Work with many smart people; always helpful in answering questions and offering suggestions.-Given my own project with responsibilities and deadlines-Learned so much more than was possible in class-Somewhat flexible working hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – -LONG working hours + weekends fairly often-Compensation is decent, but can be difficult with the cost of living in CA</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the startup atmosphere and get to Mars!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Propulsion Development Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best engineering company to work for, period.”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexibility, freedom, hands on environment.  You can grow as much as you want as fast as you want.  It's a very free flowing environment, people don't breath down your neck, they just expect you to get your work done.  You have a lot of responsibility and a lot of exposure.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours, very little rest.  Often work weekends to keep the pace!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“it was demanding but hand on job”

</title><pros>Pros – frozen yogurt and gym membership</pros>
<cons>Cons – very time demanding, terrible for you social life.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great learning experience”

</title><pros>Pros – SpaceX is a great place to come in and be part of something dynamic.  Responsibility is given in very short time.  Learning is done with an immersion method.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work hours are long, priorities change on a regular basis.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More training for management.  The managers are great engineers, but they have no formal training in how to manage while maintaining an their engineering work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exciting place to work, but management is lacking.”

</title><pros>Pros – Amazing company on the forefront of Space access.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Employee personal needs are not met. Issues not adequately confronted. There's way to much "drama" for a professional workplace. Even though the majority of the company is young, there isn't enough professionalism a lot of the time. Many managers definitely play favorites, in a way that may be detrimental to other employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-31</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Demanding, but rewarding.”

</title><pros>Pros – SpaceX is changing the world, and that's an exciting thing. Everyone's highly motivated, high energy, and very intelligent. If you want to make a difference, this is the place to be.</pros>
<cons>Cons – SpaceX can also be a very challenging environment. The hours are long, and the deadlines are unforgiving. Be prepared to sacrifice large chunks of your free time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Wish to Remain Hidden (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you are not an engineer, you are useless, dirt”

</title><pros>Pros – Not many good things unless it is your first job out of school.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hideous hours (long), Unrealistic expectations, Talked to like dirt from young recent grad engineers. Treated like an idiot if you have any experience other than academic crap.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Grow up, get a clue on how to treat people that are not engineers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Incredibly long hours and lots of work, but great seeing your product in the long run.”

</title><pros>Pros – Hardworking, helpful employees.Great having frozen yogurt and drinks available.Excellent place to intern.Good resources available to broaden your horizons and knowledge.Engineers are involved in all phases of the project; design, analysis, manufacturing, testing, and installation.When traveling for work, you are really taken care of.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management does not talk to employees.One hand doesn't know what the other is doing... not organized very well.Hard to balance social life and work.All mistakes are noticed or reported, but no praise for exceptional work.They claim to take the top 1%, but some management and early employees do not resemble their own criteria.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An amaizing, high pressure environment with excellent employees and poor senior management”

</title><pros>Pros – SpaceX does amaizing things and has amaizing goals. You will work with some of the most intelligent people on the planet, and on some of the most interesting hardware being built anywhere in the world. Stock Options.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor communication to top leadership, scape goat based firiings, poor salaries, extremely long hours, poor work life balance. Benifits are worse than those of competitors.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Spend more time trying to balance work loads and keep the really good people moving. How about rewarding people for their hard work before they burn out? Not just constantly say "Beatings will continue until performance improves."</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“awesome”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of opportunity to grow your expertise</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work is fairly demanding.  Balancing life and work can be difficult</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An ideal place to work. Everyone is eager and willing to help everyone else. Overall a great experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – People at Space Exploration Technologies have a "work hard, play hard" mentality and are always motivated. There is a great sense of constantly contributing to the greater good of the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most people work very odd hours of the day, which makes for a relatively inflexible schedule. Sometimes lack of communication between departments.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Propulsion Design Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Finally and exciting fast paced company, full of hardworking engineers who care only about results.”

</title><pros>Pros – Your working on the newest, coolest technologies, at a company that is moving the fastest in the Aerospace industry. If you just want to get stuff done, then this is your company. The hours are also great, not the cushy 35-40hr/wks of other large aerospace/automotive companies, but no one is watching your hours arrive and leave as you need to just get your work done!</pros>
<cons>Cons – I am perplexed by the negative reviews. There definitely is a work-first mentality. It's not a social atmosphere and no one will seek you out/hold your hand, but everyone is helpful/knowledgeable and very friendly if asked. If you're a results driven person, who is hardworking, independent, and not afraid of self introductions then this is the company for you. If you need a strong social atmosphere at work and a manager to hold your hands through the first couple months... then this definitely is not the company for you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – A consolidated library/resource of information for new hires would be very helpful in getting new employees up to speed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unique opportunity to be involved with all aspects of space flight.”

</title><pros>Pros – No place quite like it, applying a vertical model to space flight.Factory is in the back, can get hands on hardwareVery talented co-workers.Unique experiences with test and launch.Stock options a plus.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation is seemingly on the lower end.Expect a "work first" attitude.Not very team oriented, often a single person takes the fall.Function organization, dividing the stakeholders.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Product oriented structure would be ideal.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>6</upvote>
<employee-type>Propulsion Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting yet disappointing”

</title><pros>Pros – Aerospace experience is great on a resume.  Good experience working here but I wouldn't say a good career company.  Good for recent graduates.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Benefits are not up to par compared to my previous employers.  A great deal of unfairness happens within the company.  Borderline discrimination and favoritism.  I'm currently searching for other opportunities.  Salaries are low.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Put an end to criticism and favoritism.  Let's build some rockets.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a good place to develop your career”

</title><pros>Pros – So far, SpaceX is the only company putting their money where their mouth is.  When VPs or Directors want something done, it gets done right away.  Engineers do get treated very well, despite the long hours.  The company is very young, so seeking for career advice is limited but it makes it more comfortable for those coming out of school.  Easy to move up in the ladder if you make the right friends.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working with certain groups or at different sites is like being back in High School.  If you are not part of a click, you will be cut.  Engineering leads don't have any managerial experience.  Despite having a strong technical background, if they do not like you personally, they will find a way to get rid of you permanently.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get rid of the High School like clicks, especially in Texas.  It is not professional and not the way to run a business.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-08-31</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Propulsion Test Technician (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You may not want to work here.”

</title><pros>Pros – People hear that you work for this company and they think you have accomplished something with your life. They are jealous of you. Your family is proud of you. I think this is just about the only good thing in working for Space Exploration Technologies.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The overall work environment is horrible. The amount of hours the employees are forced to work is un-Godly. The pay is low but the stock options look like it could pay off.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The only advice I have for the management of this company is that you should treat your employees with the same level of respect that you would expect for yourself. Making someone work more then 15 hours a day in harsh weather conditions is never acceptable. One last thing, let your employees take a break every once in a while, A REAL BREAK.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing opportunities and job satisfaction awaiting those willing to put in the effort.”

</title><pros>Pros – Note: This is from an Engineer's perspective.SpaceX has been in a state of growth since I first started at the company, constantly increasing the scope of it's projects, it's capabilities, and it's vision. With that comes the amazing opportunities that only comes from a small/medium sized company!There aren't many companies where you can have something you designed or built in space within 1~2 years! If flying something you've worked on in space is a career goal of yours, I can't think of a better place to be.Another side effect of a rapidly growing company is the opoprtunities for increased responsibility. SpaceX employees often find themselves responsible for very important elements very quickly. Responsibility it placed upon people based more on merit than tenure, which allows for career growth not possible with larger aerospace companes.In my experience, SpaceX does a good job of rewarding efforts and successes with perks and bonuses. While compensations may be below aerospace industry standards initially, SpaceX (in my opinion) does a better job of rewarding performance.At the end of the day, there isn't any thing quite like watching a rocket take off and a spacecraft at the space stations, and SpaceX captures that excitement and passion of that dream!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hours and work/life balance at SpaceX is likely the biggest and most-common complaint, but in my experience it is what each person wants to make of it. SpaceX will take as much as you want to give it, which for a lot of energetic fresh from college engineers is alot. There are lots of folks who have made a successful transition from 60+ hour workweeks to something more sustainable, but you must make a concious decision to do so.For better or worse, there is definitely less structure, organization, and training at SpaceX than other companies. Nearly all of the training and learning is "on the job" training, as there are minimal mentoring programs. Also, some of the institutional protections of larger companies will not there at SpaceX (for better or worse).</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Technician”

</title><pros>Pros – Being recognized for the work you perform as an individual.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours but seeing success in your hard work become a reality makes it bearable.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have Techs work less hours.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Technician (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unbearable”

</title><pros>Pros – Working on space technologyAbility to work in multiple disciplinesStock Options (If they ever IPO)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Stock Options (this company has been around 11 years and no IPO)Long miserable hoursUnrealistic deadlinesPoor management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop pretending that you can work 80- hour weeks forever because you are better than other comparable companies in the industry.  Workers are human beings, not machines.  And enough with the endless schedule changes.  Sit down and make a realistic plan, you guys aren't the first company in the world to do this.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent Leadership, Best People, Hardest working”

</title><pros>Pros – Growing and developing company, and a chance to be part of history. If you have ever wanted to work with the best and brightest, this is the place to be.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Growing and maturing company. It is a start-up, and the character of the company is maturing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work. What you are doing is incredible. Thank You.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was aight”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun to work with smart people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hard to work with limited budget</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Advertise more</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Liberally chaotic”

</title><pros>Pros – You have a voice equal to all others.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Your voice is no louder than any other contributing to the noise. It's as much of a challenge to be heard as it is as much as it is to hear. Sometimes feels as if some people are too loud  to listen.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Propulsion Technician (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Star gazed at first, then reality sets in....”

</title><pros>Pros – Really cool and interesting things to do, if your an engineer.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If your not an engineer, it is like a labor camp with a "click" like atmosphere to boot. As long as you party with the right people, live your life with no days off, you are in. If you have a life outside of Spacex, do notwork here, you will be judged and eventually booted. By the way, if you have any outside Aerospace experience, you are a moron to an engineer.  Good luck</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start hiring people with actual management experience, not promoting an engineer straight out of school, first job, but has tenure to be a manager. Kids managing kids never works.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cool, but tough place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Cool, fun coworkers.  Lasting relationships.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management does not promote positive moral.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Praise and thank employees for their hard work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>