<name>D-Link Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/D-Link-Reviews-E4041.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-01-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Internship”

</title><pros>Pros – Freedom and relaxing.  Great place to start your career as a recent college grad.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Don't have me sit in on meetings.  I feel clueless sometimes of what is going on when given some pretty important work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get a consulting firm to brand the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“High employee turnover, company not giving out yearly raises, some employees have more than one position.”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible schedule, some nice people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No chance to grow or expand your career. Executives are micro-managers. High turnover in key executive positions. Lunch is okay, microwaves, but no actual food is served. Outdoor basketball court. Close to a Starbucks, Costco, and Mcdonalds if you want coffee, lunch, or run errands.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take a stronger leadership position. Post  positions  so that every employee has a chance to interview instead of "handpicking" an employee and giving them the job and shutting everyone else out. Hire qualified people instead of new college grads with no business experience.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you want excitement and a dynamic environment, this is not the place (US Office)”

</title><pros>Pros – Quiet... not much to do...</pros>
<cons>Cons – Quiet... not much to do...   this is a chinese company... it's ran like a chinese labor farm...    the US office is pretty much a shipping warehouse and translation factory and human interface/support to US customers... don't expect any groundbreaking technological advances or any actual product development, that all happens in Asia... the US has no actual effect on the direction of the company...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place for low to mid level career”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible work conditions, comprehensive product line at the mow to mid range target audience</pros>
<cons>Cons – salary is lower than the competition. Some micromanagement</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay people based on the competitive environment</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-31</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great People!”

</title><pros>Pros – D-Link has hired great enthusiastic people to work with. The culture is very laid back but there is a lot going on. Opportunities for interns to step and get noticed are plenty if you ask. They are very laid back for days off and PTO.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not too much of a social environmentThere is so much red tape it takes forever for something to be approved</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Shift the focus to customer based rather than product based.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Friendly environment, but not a place for young talent or ambitious employees”

</title><pros>Pros – Casual environment, flat organizational structure makes it easy for executives and other employees to communicate well. Employees are encouraged to innovate. Hours are flexible and there is a basketball court with regular games.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Comparatively low pay with nonexistent performance-based rewards. Many useless meetings with too much politics not enough emphasis on results or accountability.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop having using meetings, project manager is desperately needed, focus on accountability and reward those who perform well. Match marketing and technology trends in the market.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ignored”

</title><pros>Pros – They have a basketball court and these mexican taco trucks that come for lunch. They left me alone for the most part and I didn't have anything to do. So I don't know about the work there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They pretty much put me in front of a computer and ignored me. Pay was a bit low as well.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Restructuring”

</title><pros>Pros – Company went through some restructuring and is emerging from its dark times. Executive management has started HR initiatives to boost employee morale. Company goals have become clear from top down. I've personally gotten along with all international employees, executive management, upper management, co-workers, and interns. There is plenty of work to get you through the day. There are/is a basketball court, showers, and a ping pong table. The US building is going through restructuring to further improve working conditions. Marketing department was a collaborative environment and truly a pleasure to work in. Convenient location. Changes also allowed access to new technology - I was given a new laptop and software. The D-Link Boxee Box has become a media center in my home.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No improvement without growing pains. There is constant bickering/politics at the top with no moderation/solution by executives. Workload seems to be dumped unevenly into specific departments. Roles have not clearly been defined yet. Company is very top heavy with few middle class workers. Pay is on the low side (after negotiations). Employees were kept after hours to meet with Taiwan executives. There were a LOT of meaningless hour long meetings.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Identify the workhorses vs. the complainers. Reward the workhorses and deal with the complainers. Plan for the future better and more quickly. Stop meeting so much and hire a project manager. I've come out of 9/10 meetings feeling like nothing has been accomplished. There was a lot of talk and not enough doing. Executives need to give deadlines and hold the owner accountable.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Marketing Specialist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Waste of my time”

</title><pros>Pros – monthly ice cream and cake for birthdays</pros>
<cons>Cons – Condescending management who have cronies.  Turnover high and they promote incompetent people to important positions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Recognize talented people and let them shine.  Don't hire competent peoples and then be prejudiced against them so they eventually leave.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Director of Product Management (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“D-Link”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a good place to work for if you are a fresh college graduate. It offers a great place to learn and accumulate work experience.For sales, it's a good place to work for if you can deliver the numbers</pros>
<cons>Cons – . No work performance review from the top management.. Pay was bad in comparison to other high tech industry.. The executives had inadequate knowledge or expertise in some areas in the market and consequently provided little or no leadership.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take the initiative to learn and lead instead of waiting for someone to feed you the info</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-11-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dissatisfied-Linking”

</title><pros>Pros – Work here for personal growth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Outdated software and system, long hours, crappy benefits, no company culture and teamwork. There is no room for growth. A lot of finger pointing when mistake arises.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn how to manage and treat people and dont act like you know it all.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK Environment to work. Good environment to learn. But, stagnated growth.”

</title><pros>Pros – Open Environment, great supervisors, good colleagues..</pros>
<cons>Cons – No career OR learning opportunities....</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Development Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good company for people don't look for challenges.”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice work environment, friendly colleagues and very stable.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Politics, not look for any new changes</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you want to work with networking - try Cisco or Netgear”

</title><pros>Pros – - Interesting products- Be part of building a connected world- Learn anything/everything about B2C and B2B networking- Some smart/friendly colleagues</pros>
<cons>Cons – - A lot of overtime- Low salaries- Very poor management- People stay a year or two and then move on (unless you are top exec that have a high salary for doing very little)- Sexual harassment and verbal abuse towards women- Working hard does not mean you get a better salary or position at the company</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Be firm, stick to what you say - don't change directions on a monthly basis- Screaming has never been a good way of making people motivated (yes it's happens often in big European meetings)- Make sure to reward people that work hard</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales and Marketing Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sales and Marketing Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Targets are achievableA good place to learn</pros>
<cons>Cons – lacks employee empowerment environmentDoes not have a good reporting structureRelationship between management and subordinate is non existence</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Managers should create standards and give people clear expectations so they know what they are supposed to do, and wonder why they fail.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Testing Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The products D-Link made are all easy configure and stable”

</title><pros>Pros – The company  filling in competition atmosphere, colleagues are all want to grow up with the company</pros>
<cons>Cons – The product still have some issues which customers do not like , like the router or switch will be crashed because heat is too high to afford</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“PM”

</title><pros>Pros – No specific SOP or R&R, so it all depends on you. Good learning environment. People are easy to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Dictatorship. Run the company more on intuitions rather than numbers in some cases.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Sit down to really plan well instead of making rush decisions and regret later on.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent Learning Opportunity”

</title><pros>Pros – Close knit team.Freedom to define own role.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Small company environment with related limitations.Limited vertical growth potential.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dlink”

</title><pros>Pros – Everything, good job, nice peoples,etc...</pros>
<cons>Cons – too much germans, closing the EEU region :(, business going down,etc...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – nothing</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Vice-President (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's been quite enriching so far”

</title><pros>Pros – Huge brand recall, certain extent brand loyalty.</pros>
<cons>Cons – public perception of a channel company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – enterprise-centric promotion and brand building.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Typical Asian company”

</title><pros>Pros – Able to play basketball on premises</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everything, work environment, shady executives and bosses, relationship driven promotion throughout the company, etc..</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Talented colleagues with challenging work”

</title><pros>Pros – Supportive colleagues, good technology we sell, great brand</pros>
<cons>Cons – Easy to get too comfortable, revenue doesn't seem to be growing but just going sideways</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Figure out how to grow the company with new exciting products, innovate more and invest heavily in the business so hopefully this will reflect in revenue</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good”

</title><pros>Pros – Good experience here at D-Link</pros>
<cons>Cons – None that I have so far</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Marketing Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I love it!”

</title><pros>Pros – A lot of growth and welcoming work culture.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Obviously, there are politics involved.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A nice place for junior and need practice”

</title><pros>Pros – You are free to try something (because no other people can couch you).The working hour is okay.Can buy launch in office, parking space....</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. You don't know what manager doing.2. You can't see your feature.3. Manager will not tell you anything except your task have to be done.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I don't think you know what should manager do.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good team work”

</title><pros>Pros – good team work, small company with friendly work environment, people are nice, regular after work hangout and even some weekend/holiday get together</pros>
<cons>Cons – lack of career growth, different part of the company need to be more integrated, more power is needed for D-Link US</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more power is needed for D-Link US (even it's TW based) so the company can keep growing and leading the industry</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-14</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good people, bad management”

</title><pros>Pros – most people who work there are warm and fun to be around</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad leadership and management. doesn't value employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Temporary”

</title><pros>Pros – You get to know different people in different continents.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most of your work will go unnoticed and unappreciated</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Grow some balls and take some risks for the sake of D-Link's future</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Opportunistic company”

</title><pros>Pros – Medium size company. Provide full depth of networking products</pros>
<cons>Cons – it needs better career plan for employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – prevent high turnover ratio and support individual's career growth</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice coworkers and friendly management conducive to productivity”

</title><pros>Pros – Respect amount colleagues. Casual relaxed environment that is important to me</pros>
<cons>Cons – Difficult to grow. Flat hieraracle structure that.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – no</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“D-Link Review”

</title><pros>Pros – D-Link manufactures very solid products in the switching, wireless, IP Surveillance, and storage arena. D-Link has a strong presence in both Europe and Asia.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Serious brand awareness in North America.  Very tough to win over Enterprise level accounts.  Senior Management leads through fear versus inspiration.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Senior Management should work on encouraging and inspiring their employees through positive leadership and promoting a winning team business model so that all team members can work together instead of being isolated silos.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent Company to Work with”

</title><pros>Pros – Transparency, Family like culture. Growth prospects</pros>
<cons>Cons – Market intel & competition product against the likes of CISCO, 3com</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More Mkt activity</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working at D-Link”

</title><pros>Pros – People are friendly and easy to get along with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You get lost in the shuffle and there are times you are unaware of where the strategy of the company is.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More feedback on employee performance.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor, Poor Organization”

</title><pros>Pros – Some good solutions for the business class market, alot of good competent unhappy employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited product line, outdated software and CRM, Mediorcre business class products, Terrible management support, Company likes to blame others when things dont get done or sales arent met, Alot of backstabbing , very expensive health benefits</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upgrade software and change culture</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-08-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type> Engineer  (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review D-Link Singapore”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits for D-LInk Singapore office. Leisure working time. Nice environment and friendly collegues. Not stressfull place to work in</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not much career progression. You will most probably be stuck at your current position unless you are well like by a "group" of people who thinks highly of you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Wake up and explore other sales revenues instead of just depending on SOHO devices. You are earning but you could earn more! Why be complacent?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Opportunities to improve”

</title><pros>Pros – International company with global offices</pros>
<cons>Cons – No clear work structure and dialoge inside</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have more open planifications, let the employees know what is happening, open conversations, better dialogue</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>