<name>Q-Cells Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Q-Cells-Reviews-E40456.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-10-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Line Technology, Chemistry Division (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It gave me a valuable insight into the PV industry and I also learned a lot about solar cell manufacturing processes.”

</title><pros>Pros – - friendly colleagues- relaxed working atmosphere- many PV-related companies are closeby.- flat hierarchy.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - very remote location: closest relatively big city is Leipzig - 50km away.- housing close to company is difficult to find.- faces severe Asian competition, some of the production has to be relocated.- long-term employment has more chances of success and you also feel much better integrated in the work environment if you manage to get your German to a "working knowledge" level, although most of the employees speak English relatively well.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Staff (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Top notch solar company, still struggling internally five years and growing”

</title><pros>Pros – Great team environment, hard working, and still likes to have fun. Great location. Good corporate support and guidance from parent co in Germany. Ability to make decisions quickly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company acquired by Korean conglomerate and boy did things change! No more perks! Inefficient decision making process, too many parent companies making decisions. Communication faltered, vision and goals became a mystery.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Communication.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Solar Cell Manufacturing Business”

</title><pros>Pros – good company for personal development.</pros>
<cons>Cons – too biased organisation and poor interaction among workers....</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Equipment Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It has been a new experience for me in the solar industry.”

</title><pros>Pros – Safe place to work in Qcells. Knowledge are well transfered between counterparts. Daily tracking on the issues . Good support from HQ.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor communication from management towards employees on updating on the company status. No technical development done on site. No personal development plan done.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to have clear communication to the employee. Should provide clear road map for the personal development plan.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Production Improvement Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I am part of the pioneer team member in Q-Cells started off as Manufacturing Engineer at 2008 until now.”

</title><pros>Pros – Work without pressure but with leisure</pros>
<cons>Cons – NO carreer advancement . Too complex of organization.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Benchmarking on most of the major semicond company and overlook on how thier style of management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>