<name>H. Lundbeck Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/H-Lundbeck-Reviews-E40684.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Market Access Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“CNS specialized company”

</title><pros>Pros – CNS specialization and commitment to improve lives of people suffering from psychiatric and neurological diseases gives you opportunity to focus on one part of the market and to develop high level of expertise within these fields.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Narrow portfolio and dependence on a single product brings insecurity and uncertainty among employees in the future of business.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Lead by example. Be more flexible in work with subsidiaries (not all countries are of same size).</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Country Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I'm satisfy and growing together with the company”

</title><pros>Pros – CNS market is tough because of difficulties in generating new compound however Lundbeck is still heavily focusing on this therapeutic areas</pros>
<cons>Cons – Due to the market environment changes is necessary and at times it impact on employees confidence</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – On the right track and should be a little more careful in strategising future growth</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The leading CNS company”

</title><pros>Pros – The leading CNS specialty firm, and only company with a late stage pipeline in the big disease areas depression, psychosis and Alzheimer's</pros>
<cons>Cons – Development risk is still high, and recent patent expires make cost optimisation important, commercial plans and ideas will get closely scrutinised before being committed to</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – This is still a very Scandinavian company, in particular in HQ, which has benefits and disadvantages, overall it is a good thing, plus it's small enough for individual managers to still be able to make a significant impact on the overall company</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Affairs Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“didn't make any career progress”

</title><pros>Pros – feels like a big family. some people have been there a long time, which can be a good thing - sometimes. not US influenced, whigh means the company's culture is very relaxed.</pros>
<cons>Cons – no recognition of the need to advance employee careers. commercial managers are too conservative but hold too much influence over company direction</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Knowledge oriented”

</title><pros>Pros – To know more about new research  & study of molecule in Neuro-psychiatry segment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – More transparency must needed to improve organisation.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – to start carrier</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wonderful if you are Danish”

</title><pros>Pros – Copenhagen is a wonderful city (for tourists)Danish culture is good to experience (for a while)Home - Work balance is valuedThe ethics of the company are admirable.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Don't expect fellow employees to socialise outside work hoursCulturally rigidVery HQ based and focussed, for an international companyOld Boys network in senior management and board levelIf higher management were to underachieves or miss goals it may not noticed because of continually changing and reorganising departments.Subsidiaries are considered subsidiary to HQRenumeration/benefits are not comparable with other countriesTaxation in Denmark is a major issue for relocating foreign workers to Denmark  for a long period of time</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – International representation on the board and in senior management is desperately neededThere are other ways of doing thingsTry to get something internal through phase III.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lundbeck International”

</title><pros>Pros – - CNS focused company- Aggressive sales/marketing- Open to innovative marketing approaches</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Highly Danish and Danish Male centric company. No women, minorities in senior management. Lip servce to diversity- No attempt to bring in international thinking at the senior most levels- Heavily reliant on the old (Danish) boys network- Provincial & parochial at times- "Fairness" interpretation means that nobody gets rewarded above a certain HQ-based norm</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Get out, see the world, replace HQ-based travelling managers with real managers with real hands-on operating experience.- Break the Danish stranglehold on senior management- Bring out something worthy from R&D and also licencing- "New" CEO has had about 18 months and changes have been mostly related to cost savings, rather than real ones. US appears to be the solitary focus.- Listening is alsos a great skill!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>