<name>Plan C Agency Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Plan-C-Agency-Reviews-E406539.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great stepping stone for an ambitious individual”

</title><pros>Pros – Due to its limited size, the agency will entrust in you tasks that a person with your same title would have at other agencies.  This gives you invaluable experience.  Also, the team is very family-oriented.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The agency does not have many flagship accounts and hours can be erratic (like any other agency)</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Production Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good opportunity to get a foot in and learn about the industry”

</title><pros>Pros – Exposure to interesting projects. Fun, energetic co-workers, in the heart of Koreatown, good opportunity for growth and learning.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not much room for promotion, communication within company strained at times, a sense of a lack of organization at times.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – While throwing interns into the process is a good way to promote learning and growth, it is also important to take the time to teach and mentor as well.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Really terrible decision to work here”

</title><pros>Pros – You get to work on some "cool" projects related to entertainment and the Asian American community. Meet lots of new people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay, long hours, not appreciated by management, they fool you into thinking you are working for the "greater cause" for the APA community. Management is more concerned with putting money in their pockets and cycling through naive, cheap labor. The employee turnover here is ridiculous.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start treating your employees like human beings</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>