<name>Circle K Stores Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Circle-K-Stores-Reviews-E409865.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Enjoyed the work, but not the corporate attitude.”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with my fellow employees, including training in customer service, customer interaction, proper way to be acurate in entering transactions and collecting payment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As a store manager, I was responsible for making sure that the store always had staff working 24 hours a day.  Store was never closed.  Corporate took over hiring staff and did not manage to keep the store at an aceptable staffing level.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Allow managers to do thier own hiring.  Allow them to hire the personell they want in thier store.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Just another job”

</title><pros>Pros – Meeting new people and experience</pros>
<cons>Cons – Promises are always broken. Without a decent manager your experience will suck. At my location we have lost a lot of customers due to her attitude and her putting down employees.Screaming at them and then rude to the customers. Like I said..its just another job. Nothing I plan to stay with.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get it together. Honestly, most managers are pretty great. The one I was handed is just terrible. My advice to my managers boss.. my boss is 69 years old, shes losing you customers and money everyday, she is making 25 dollars a hour off you people for being with the company for over 30 yrs...if I were you Id find the tiniest things to get this woman out. I wouldnt waste another penny on her ruthless self.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Better Management needed”

</title><pros>Pros – Good looking stores from a structural landscape perspective.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor customer service, managers not present when business needs demands. No long term goals or initiatives at the store level. Outside appearance is dirty and disorganized overall. 4 among C-stores that customers will visit.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire honest, experienced, passionate managers and DM to hold their employees accountable. Ignore trends from competitors and focus on the basics to regain profit shares.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-31</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Management at Circle K Georgia”

</title><pros>Pros – Gave input at meetings more</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not enough hours to work people</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More sit down talk to manager on any defects</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Steady, reliable work but mostly hiring part time”

</title><pros>Pros – flexibility, hours of operation, and decent management, at least on the store to employee management level for the most part. Customers are loyal and it's nice to see them on a regular basis.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management, specifically geographical VP, not making decisions on a store to store basis, just "your all bad and I'm here to make you better" attittude is frustrating. Upper management should seek more individual input from the real "ambassadors" of the business. The CSR's are the first impression our customers get of Circle K not manager's. CSR's get the vital feedback from the customers (good and bad) and should have a voice or at least an outlet to support the good and bad of the business and help make Circle K the best convenience store there is!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give the real "ambassadors", the CSR's, an outlet to make suggestions on a corporate level not just to the local market manager, who may not give a hoot about your suggestions on how to make Circle K the best it can be. Store managers and market managers are to busy, buried in redundent paper work to have time to hear suggestions from the front lines! CSR's are the real "ambassadors" of the store's! A clean store and a friendly smile are the first impressions the paying customers get when they enter our stores! That's when they decide " hey I really like this place and the cashier was super nice"</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unapreciated, underpaid,  don't work there!”

</title><pros>Pros – Customer service, always have something to do,</pros>
<cons>Cons – Underpaid, overworked, nasty customers, management is terrible u mean nothing to them no matter how hard u work. Lousy hours, no breaks work 8 hrs and don't even get a break.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Appreciate your good workers, increase pay working for under 8.00 an hour after being there for 3 yrs. is  ridiculous!  Hire More caring managers who are people friendly!   Lots of favoritism among store managerment  even if you work hard you might not  be treated fair!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decentralized management structure allows for favoritism and failure to maintain Couche Tard standards or that Couche Ta”

</title><pros>Pros – Alain Bouchard is very nice</pros>
<cons>Cons – Fifedoms and rivalries in regions and mangement</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do not let the regions know the store locations for exec. visits in advance.  Never know what stores are really like.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This is a terrible place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – There are no pros to working here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bad management, NO LUNCH BREAKS OR ANY BREAKS. Isn't that a law? Terrible pay. I've worked there for 3 years and still haven't cracked the $8 barrier.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast paced, decent money”

</title><pros>Pros – fast paced environment, hours pass by fastdecent money for managementsee the same customers daily, makes for good customer interaction</pros>
<cons>Cons – low pay for cashiers24 hours--- if you are a manager and your employess flake out, guess who gets to cover their shiftnot too much room for growth, going from manager to a market manager would be a huge step and usually requires a degree</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – cant really think of anything to change, its a convenience store and gas station, it is what it is</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Terrible Company”

</title><pros>Pros – There is nothing positive to report</pros>
<cons>Cons – Doesn't care about employees, especially minorities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employee engagement</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – There is something new happening every day, it's not a boring job, it keeps you active, you do not spend your time sitting on a chair.You learn a lot and the work atmosphere is good. The pay is decent compared to other retail companies.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Having to work 6 days a week.Having to be on call 24 hours.Company does not pay for cell phone or gas - which are both used a lot for work purposes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work hard with no chance of advancement.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great store layout, very loyal customers, paid vacation time, time and half holiday pay.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Non managerial health benefits are nothing more than a discount program. Once you hit store manager thats the career roof. Unless a market manager dies (which happend) don't ever expect to move up the company ladder. They don't promote and reward employee's from with in. Manager bonus incentives are almost always unobtainable and unrealistic. I appreciate setting the bar, but changing the rules for bonuses to make them nearly impossible to obtain is just down right mean and counter productive.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Reward and thank all employee's for a job well done not just management. Like wise, weed out all the dead wood. Mix up and promote or get rid of stale market managers and above. Sometimes a fresh pair of eyes is just what the retail dr ordered.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great entry level position!”

</title><pros>Pros – Comfortable environment, friendly customers and co-workers. Good store experience.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Potential of working late hours.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Circle K is just a paycheck.”

</title><pros>Pros – Weekly pay was the best</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management and schedules is never easy.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees and don't forget that you once had to do the same job.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Job security or no job security that is the question?”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay isn't too bad could be better, free soda & coffee, some store manager's are great and the same with market manager's, temporary job go for it, not much said.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Store manager's are there for a job not to care about your feeling's or that you have a family to support, plus they change too much anyway.2. Market manager's are sometimes helpful but remember they arn't your store manager.3. Store manager could change at anytime and you would be terminated when they like.4. Can't be nice you cannot be over or short a penny or you'll be suspended or terminated5. You get written up all the time for small stuff that doesn't matter6. NO JOB SECURITY7. There's not much pro's so keep that in mind.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start a "Manager Tree" where the bad manager's "RED MANAGER'S" are told to be nicer to their employee's or  they are terminated and "Green Manager's" are either promoted or praised for the work they do. Only have one store manager per store regardless of how management see's the store. Give days off to at least first come first serve day's off. Don't suspend employee's when they know there's no good communication. Keep shift's always the same always give full timer's the amount of hours you told them when they were hired. Investigate "Red Manager's" Do something nice for your employee's to show them you appreciate them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Circle K”

</title><pros>Pros – Challenging, strong growth potential, work/life balance encouraged, strong financial performance, ability for creativity and forward thinking</pros>
<cons>Cons – compensation not parallel with growth opportunity, need to watch balance of men/women growth;</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Starter job”

</title><pros>Pros – Great for a starter job such as just turned 18 and need a summer job before college, or through out college with part time. They have image day which if you store wins (ours has) all employees get a 50 dollar bonus. We have secret shoppers and if you pass, you get a 20 dollar gift card for the store itself.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management doesn't really look into problems. I wish that our manager would really stop ignoring all the people who are violating many polices at work which cause work not to get done. Sometimes I wish the DM's would come and take a look at everyone, and possibly have a group meeting with everyone from time to time so that the higher guys can see our concerns that are not getting worked out.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Working there over a year, Loved it for a while and punched in a ton of hours. Now it's to the point where I wish we got new management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is just a job.”

</title><pros>Pros – Automatic deposit and health insurance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – For most employees this is the only company they have ever worked for.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There is more than marketing that makes your company successful.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a Bad Place to start in Managment”

</title><pros>Pros – Good starting job for college grads</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not very good raises. They are usually 5% for a good review.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not the greatest place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Store discount of 20%; very few other perks; health benefits are definitely one of the best things about the job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Strict budget; hard to get staff when competitors are offering so much more for the exact same position; barely any incentive for staff.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management could save so much money by matching competitors' wages, which would reduce the extremely high level of turnover. Then Managers are expected to train new employees with barely any budget for it, giving them little to no chance of reaching bonus objectives.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was very educational and fun”

</title><pros>Pros – There is a fun staff to work with.  It's also awesome to learn about all the products that a convenient store sells and to memorize all the special deals to share with family and friends.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You have to stand the entire shift and the lunch break is very short compared to other jobs I've had.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up all the good work! I really enjoyed the online training program that we all needed to go through in order to work in the store.  However, I wish there was more interaction between stores and the management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Market Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its a great Company that is always moving forward with innovative ideas.”

</title><pros>Pros – I'm treated as family, the people are great. There is work / life balance at all levels. There is room to grow and develop with the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary package is not great, bonus plan could use refining for store managers and Store Asts. Store Asts are not payed as well as other competitor companies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employees enjoy working for the company, but would see less turnover if salary package and bonus plan was comparable to other retailers. There are great employees that have stuck by the company's side during the economic down fall and did not receive a pay increase or received very little. There should be a nice boost for them for the next annual reviews.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Custimer Sevice (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Hard phsically, no structured breaks”

</title><pros>Pros – The fellow employess, their is a team atmosphere.  People help each other</pros>
<cons>Cons – Simply, the pay is too low, I can see minimum for a starting period, but after 90 days any employee that survives should be bumped up.  =</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work a few shifts, a shift is worth a thousand words.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exhausting, Frustrating, Not a fun place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Meet people, Stay busy also something to do!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not given credit for working extremely hard, no breaks, bad pay for what u have to do! People are extremely rude,  they  look down at  you . it is not just standing at a counter waiting on people you have 30 other jobs to complete also with a smile!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More support , and credit when due not just complaints.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>