<name>R Stahl Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/R-Stahl-Reviews-E409846.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Outside Sales - Houston Market (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Executive management nightmare - what a shame for a great company”

</title><pros>Pros – Great product and capabilities. Excellent people in engineering and inside sales support</pros>
<cons>Cons – President is an complete moron. Doesn't know the electrical industry, distribution or reps either. Needs to be replaced. Last guy there got promoted because he was really good. Company flatlining in sales since previous CEO left</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Replace President of company with someone competent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-25</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very pleasant place to work, very good people, growing company”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits, great vacation plan, great advanacement opportunities- people with heart and great values.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company has grown a lot in the last few years, sometimes we play "catch up" with our processes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get better organized and strengthen employee communication</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technician (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Incompetence, Lies, and Deceitfulness at Stafford Location”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Benefits is all this company offers if your willing to put up with being thrown under the bus.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company only looks at your mistakes or negative aspects of most employees. Stafford location moves people up that have no leadership experience. The managers lie straight to your face. DO NOT SAY ANYTHING AROUND THEM THAT YOU DONT WANT USED AGAINST YOU.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – FIRE THEM</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Back seat management, ridiculous, micro manage, liars, highly stressful”

</title><pros>Pros – The pay is good, benefits are good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The most ridiculous place that I have ever managed.  Upper management uses this position to be cycled so they can keep their jobs.  Once you have been two Germany for training six months later you will be fired or asked to resign.  They hire management for this position once every year.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You won't listen why bother</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Micro manager, constantly looking over your shoulder, never satisfied.”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay was good, good benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company goes through one project manager per year since 2004 on the average.  If you're hired you will have to go to Germany for training within six months  after coming back from Germany you will have its three to six months before you quit or ask to resign.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Design Sales Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent. Work is according to appropriate positions”

</title><pros>Pros – There is Good Working Environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Communication from headquarters/ distributors/clients might have a delay</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – NIL</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>