<name>Corporacion en Investigacion Tecnologica e Informatica Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Corporacion-en-Investigacion-Tecnologica-e-Informatica-Reviews-E410778.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-04-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Fund Accountant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It has been a place with many opportunities and challenges”

</title><pros>Pros – Overtime eligible, Summer Hours, Fairly flexible work environment, typically busy in the first half of the month with some down time in the second half.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management more focused on revenue than profitability, Alot of talk of opportunity but better off coming in as an external hire</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great benefits, clients treat you like an idiot”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits start day one, the company keeps you updated with training, clean and well maintained facilities, Paid time off.  A few of my managers were exceptional, most of them are no longer with the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unfair company policies toward clients and employees.  As a Customer Service representative you are chained to the phone - health breaks limited to scheduled breaks only or the time is counted against you, you are judged by the time you are on the phone with a client.  You are encouraged to get on and off phone, no relationship building, not encouraged to give service par excellent.  Expectations and requirements change constantly - very unsettling - difficult to do even a lateral move in company - I have a BA and am pigeonholed where I am even though I have other capabilities.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>AML Analyst Temp (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible”

</title><pros>Pros – Good AML training. I like the gym and the cafeteria.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Citi hires a lot of temp workers trained them and let them go.You have a mentor and if your mentor doesn't like you, you don't have a job, even you have a very good review. They truly waste people time. I believe they get money from the government for each temp workers. Citi is the worst place ever.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You need to reinvent the entire AML structure.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“underpaid”

</title><pros>Pros – global, great people, diverse, great women organizations</pros>
<cons>Cons – management dont want you to move around, grow</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – offer cross functional rotations within same business lines to increase retention</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Vice President/Senior UNIX Administrator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I like working here”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people to work with.Good technology to work with.  You can really learn a lot.You get training.Lots of vacation time.Can work from home.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots of paperwork to do so you just your everyday job.Unrealistic due dates on projects,Performance reviews are meaningless.  Employees are given a bad review to met a "quota".</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Plan projects better.Real performance reviews.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice middle of the road place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Family oriented people with good camraderie.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Large and beurocratic organization with a long learning curve.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Advisor and Vice President (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The worst place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Potential banking leads and referrals from branches</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management has no clue what is going on</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need new management</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Unit Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall a positive experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great healthcare and time off package (though costs keep rising as with anywhere else). Great people to work with. Enjoyed it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Disconnect between our site and other sites and between higher management and lower management. Seemed overly stressful at times. Repeatative job</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There seems to be disconnect on upper levels of management of what the expections and ratings are for success for lower management</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great”

</title><pros>Pros – Global firm with a lot of opportunities. The biggest advantage working for Citi is it's global presence and career mobility opportunities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Red tape, and a lot of organizational processes. There are a lot of silos, however that is slowly being fixed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I think Citi's leadership team is highly competent and well regarded in the industry. There should be more focus on promoting diversity, specially women in senior leadership positions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great in the beginning but it slowly tapered off to simply unpleasant”

</title><pros>Pros – The company, citi,  has great benefits and allows time off when needed- especially if you are meeting your sales goals.</pros>
<cons>Cons – to piggy back on the statement above- The goals are always changing and the company that monitors the sales call will deem calls as "high risk" if youre too close to a huge payout.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay attention to the needs and expectations of your managers, associates and clients and this place could be a great place to work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Program Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It has been not so fruitful”

</title><pros>Pros – Close to workStrong in Process EngagementSome flexibilityProject mgmt deiscipline</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited growth opprtunitiesNon rewarding CulturePay Strucutre</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do what you say</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“unprogressive”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits, unprofessionalism on part on management</pros>
<cons>Cons – Uncompetitive salary, limited growth opportunity</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – work on establishment of competitive wages</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-31</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No opportunity for growth, dead end job”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits, remote work, vacation, flexibility</pros>
<cons>Cons – Incompent leadership, limited opportunities for growth, limited training and development, non-competitive salaries, exceptions made to people in positions who are not capable to handle job responsibilies</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Appreciate talent of employees and skillsets, adhere to policies and procedures that are put in place to streamline processes</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent learning, Above average pay, 15-hour workdays”

</title><pros>Pros – Aggressive and detailed training provided;Excellent intra-company movements as per choice of profile;Better than average industry pay;Good management skills</pros>
<cons>Cons – The workdays are too long. They also stretch to 15 hours in many cases. Challenging working environment gives way to competition.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“We do not get paid enough”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits are ok.  Internal lateral moves are encouraged. Mid-level managers are knowledgible, encouraging and helpful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours are very long, the salary is very low, Expectations are too high, you are not always shown that you are appreciated.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you like working fast, this is not the place for you!”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay and working conditions are good, and internal mobility is heavily promoted.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unfortunaltey, Citi is held back by some of it's own system.  It could be a great place to work, but internal policies and systems seemed designed to make what should be very easy tasks extremely frustrating.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Remove the bureaucracy in Citi.  It is holding your staff back.  Internal systems such as Marketplace are hampering projects and delivery.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good”

</title><pros>Pros – team members are nice and boss is friendly</pros>
<cons>Cons – no tea time and long hours</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – pay more attention to employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great”

</title><pros>Pros – it is a place always changing. change is the constant in citi.</pros>
<cons>Cons – competition is strong. citi never sleep</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more pay</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Citi - ok but you can do better”

</title><pros>Pros – easy job, not too stressful</pros>
<cons>Cons – but very little opportunity for growth and learning</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dreadful, utterly dreadful”

</title><pros>Pros – The people who actually did the work were great - committed, competent, friendly and hard working. Sadly there were very few of these people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inept senior management, bereft of leadership and communication skills. Bureaucracy beyond words, with labyrinthine structures crammed with level upon level of inadequate senior management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The fact that the business completed a reverse takeover and killed its own brand says everything about the "leadership" of the business.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“excellent company”

</title><pros>Pros – global company that has presence in more than 100 counties</pros>
<cons>Cons – too big to implement certain global applications</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Vice President (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“not a place for growth, lay back and slow in comparison”

</title><pros>Pros – work life balance is very flexible</pros>
<cons>Cons – bureaucratic, most unnecessary procedures that people follow blindly</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good learning experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Good place to learn about the banking system. Management has clear objectives and these objectives are communicated to employees. Strong infrastructure.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Eventhough you have a specific title, you will wear many hats. Deadlines are very tight specially at end of month or when implementing new federal regulations.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to be more of a mentor to employees, the leadership is there but employees need to know that senior management can also be models and are willing to share their knowledge and experience.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good and comfortable environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Knowlege gaining and learning involved</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing I as far as my experience</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Nothing I as far as my experience</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Contractual”

</title><pros>Pros – It is easy and convenient.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is contractual and not permanent.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Muddling along”

</title><pros>Pros – Global opportunities, sizable support infrastructure, constant international collaboration, broad range of work - career paths, too big to fail implies a certain level of immunity from corporate collapse in near term.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Musical chairs management, middling pay, leadership by reorg, patching the patches (systems), reliance upon external hiring to fill senior levels, heavily siloed, very bureaucratic.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please focus less on the respective group/division 'turfs' and more on developing an actual product  offering/strategy and putting in place the systems/operations/staff to support it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Vice President Fund Administrative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Going downhill”

</title><pros>Pros – Reasonably good work-life balance. Overtime not as excessive as in some other hedge fund admin companies. Pay is just about competitive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very low growth on the hedge admin side, hence few opportunities for advancement. Company has performed badly in competing for new business. Strong emphasis on implementing new systems/precedures without staff consultation. Rarely are these developments positive.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Far more consutation required with staff in respect of systems and procedures. Sen Management needs to perform better in competing for new business. Also, promotional opportunities tend not to be widely advertised internally.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's a job”

</title><pros>Pros – life and work balance is good</pros>
<cons>Cons – pay is not across the board, there is usually a thirty thousand range for each job. One person can be making tens of thousands dollars more than a co-worker.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was in a friendly environment, but not challenging enough.”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly colleagues, diverse atmosphere, some opportunities for career advancement. You can find yourself among people willing to communicate and collaborate.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not receiving good feedback after a task has been performed; opportunities for promotion may not be given to the right people.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management should be able to recognize when someone should be promoted by his accomplishments, not how well they speak the corporate  language</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent experience, little reward & compensation.”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent experience & challenging environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation not satisfactory. Work life balance extremely poor.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't prioritise cost over talent</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not bad”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. flexible culture2. not too stressful3. approachable manager4. great teammate5. very close to business6. Normal working hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. compesation is poor2. I can not think of anything else in terms of downsides and so I am still working at CITI now :)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 1. Improve release procedure (not to the leadership really...)2. Improve bonus3. In general, I think the leadership at CITI is not too bad at least in my team :)</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Teller (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A positive experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – They offer competitive pay and benefits package, with health, dental, and vision plans with a 401(k) match. They are a huge company with room for growth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I am the bottom of the totem pole so there is no shortage of work. As a teller I work Saturdays.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Growth opportunitiesGlobal CompanyAlternative workplace program</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bureaucracy makes projects move at very slow pacepoliticsLack of transparency - hard to define goalsworkloadsalary raises are minimal</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>