<name>I Imagine Studio Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/I-Imagine-Studio-Reviews-E411999.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing internship”

</title><pros>Pros – Working at I Imagine Studio was an amazing experience. As an intern, I looked forward to going to work everyday and working there made me realize just what I want from future job experiences. The people I worked with are all friendly and extremely helpful -- I never felt like I was out of the loop, and because it's such a small work environment, I got to work on lots of different projects and see what I liked/excelled in.Also really great that they trust their interns with so much work -- and it's not silly busy work either. Most days you'll be doing work along the lines of what senior level employees are doing. At the end of the internship, you'll have a LOT to show, and a lot to say that you've done. They also trust their interns to work on all their clients, big and small.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No real downsides at I Imagine. They're the same downsides as any other place -- sometimes the office can be a bit empty and days can be slower/quieter, but for the most part, you'll be kept busy.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Disappointing experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work experience for someone straight out of school, employees and freelancers were often very talented and interesting people, clientele is a diverse group.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management was very difficult to work with, low compensation, unprofessional and unpleasant work environment, no processes in place.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat employees with respect, make yourselves more available to employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Negative work environment, lack of direction & communication”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a small company, so I did get to play multiple roles on projects. The clients and projects were diverse, allowing me to be able to work on a variety of projects – both digital and print. I met some great, talented people that have since moved on from the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A lot of the work is done by interns and young professionals with little guidance and oversight – while this is a great learning experience for those employees, it does effect the quality of work and creates a negative, stressful work environment. There is little company morale due to the long hours, the "figure it out" mentality, and a lack of recognition for those passionate employees that put in the effort.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Invest in your employees, communicate, be a more positive mentor, and give recognition when it's due – the work and the company itself will benefit.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I Imagine really needs to work on communication and find some new executives”

</title><pros>Pros – Diverse clientsSmall agency so you get to know everybodyAble to make meaningful contributions (when management is too busy to do something)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Awful managementPoor in-office communication/ communication on projectsQuite a bit of busy workSenior members lack respect towards new employees and their ideas/opinions</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Creative environment for ambitious artistic talent”

</title><pros>Pros – I Imagine Studio allows creatives to be responsible for their successes and failures by involving them in all stages of creative and marketing process. This is definitely a place where you can learn a lot about industry by working on multiple projects and developing a broader skill set. Overall, it is a fast-paced environment that rewards initiative and hard work. Also, IIS provides opportunities to further sharpen your skills once you become stronger in a certain area. It's a challenging but exciting environment where you are expected to find a balance between working fast yet maintaining high design quality.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Since IIS is a small marketing boutique there is not a lot of room for career growth.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-27</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place for a versatile designer.”

</title><pros>Pros – - A great place for a versatile designer.- Many opportunities to learn and design for award-winning campaigns and various media, including online, mobile and print.- Team oriented, collaborative approach to design process- Flexible hours and time off.- Very creative environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Demanding for a junior designer fresh out of school.- Sometimes deadlines are very challenging.-  Internal reviews are too close to deadlines.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please find more reasons for your employees to stay exited and produce an award-winning work.Timely feedback for all internal reviews will be helpful.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Place to learn and grow”

</title><pros>Pros – Being a full-time project manager for 5 years, I have learned so many different things in marketing industry, that all my recent interviewers/ employers surprised about it.  There are a lot of responsibility involved which allows you to grow rapidly. Team is very creative, collaborative, you can be involved in pretty much everything and see tangible results of your work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Small agency has a different culture which is not suitable for everyone. It is like a family- everybody is involved in your life. If you are willing to be open,  not to hide anything, share yourself boldly- this is a right place for you. If you are not able to be involved in honest, effective communication - this won't be a good place for you</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Set the level of expectation at the very beginning of the project.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wonderful place to grow as a new marketing professional”

</title><pros>Pros – The management at I Imagine Studio has a progressive and fresh attitude towards solving client problems, and engages employees at even the lowest levels with client development, strategy development, and project management.  You are given a lot of responsibility at an early stage, which demonstrates both the management's ability to hire the right employee and its interest in harnessing new young minds.  I Imagine Studio is a great place for young talent to develop and expand their project management skills, creative insights, and skills in strategy development and client relations.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I Imagine Studio is a boutique firm, so there are fewer opportunities for advancement than there might be in a larger firm.  On the flip side, this means that you interact and learn from the managing directors on a daily basis, which is unparalleled at larger firms.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No direction, management is not good at what they do”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people (except for management), very small so there's a lot of flexibility, not much else in terms of pros</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is incompetent for the most part, give vague directions and then get angry when something is not done the way they would have liked, very unorganized, have a select group of people doing the majority of the work and the rest of the team doing busy work/pointless tasks/nothing</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Either give clearer directions or don't get angry when something is not done the way you wanted, stop hiring so many interns– there isn't enough work to go around</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Copywriter, Associate Art Director”

</title><pros>Pros – Their flexible work environment and work ethic inspire solid work from everyone on their team.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They are surprisingly unorganized and wildly over-promise. While they work hard, they don't seem able to stick to timetables or know where their assets are for their projects.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A true jump start to a career in a creative field”

</title><pros>Pros – If you are looking to learn from one of the most talented designers and really be involved in all the aspects of creative process, it is a place for you. I Imagine has a fresh outlook and ideas towards any marketing project and lets you exercise your creativity regardless where you are in a company chain. It was a true jumpstart of my career  and a unique opportunity to learn all the intricacies of marketing processes and client management. In short 3 years I was promoted from an intern to a senior web designer and was able to build an impressive portfolio that opened up a lot of doors in Chicago creative world. Six years later I am still applying acquired marketing  knowledge and design skills that no art school could ever teach. </pros>
<cons>Cons – I Imagine is a place for harnessing initiative, self- discipline and time-management, so if you are looking for a corporate-like muliti-layered highly structured environment, it is a wrong company for you. You will work hard, wear multiple hats, multi-task and be exhausted, but you will get the best experience by learning from the best marketing specialists and designers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>