<name>E.ON U.S. Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/E-ON-U-S-Reviews-E414.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2009-02-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>IT Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An overall great company to work for in a small city.”

</title><pros>Pros – Probably the best local company in Louisville to work for: excellent pay and benefits, high quality people, very low turnover. E.ON is also an exemplary community citizen, going to great lengths with regards to community safety, conservation and development.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Now a subsidiary of a German-based energy conglomerate, thus the occasional interference from the German HQ must be dealt with. Also, due to the very low turnover, it is difficult to get rid of the few sub-par employees: most of whom have become middle managers. The management structure would be well served by being flattened out and eliminating many of the first-level manager positions and replacing them with individuals who have specific skills and expertise.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Flatten the organization; replace the middle-management tier with a supervisory level that has actual job expertise and knowledge.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-08-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a bad place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Safe during economic downturn, well capitalized and committed to renewables business</pros>
<cons>Cons – poor management skills in certain areas, little established advancement opportunity initiatives</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – focus more on managment skills and styles when hiring people and less on technical pieces.  Management is about experience, but it also is management of PEOPLE.  Some people are smart and experienced but cannot manage people.  Pay more attention to this.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>