<name>NextMed Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/NextMed-Reviews-E414884.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“NextMed is a challenging and fun place with cheerful employees”

</title><pros>Pros – Exciting new projects gong onDirect access to Senior ManagementGood work/ life balanceGreat IT team</pros>
<cons>Cons – Job can be monotonous, "sterile"</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Laser Tech (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“alone”

</title><pros>Pros – pay is good overtime is there depending which city your in</pros>
<cons>Cons – be ready for backstabing most communications is done via email so you dont know what is being said. zero accountability middle managment will send an email to you saying something is wrong and they also forward that to senior management then come to find out you did it right and it was there error in the im sorry email you wont see that forward to senior management. You will be thrown out to the wolves and dont expect to make any changes or suggestions yourslef that will get you in a deep deep hole with your supervisor and if he or she does take it dont expect that your going to get the credit for it</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – cant give advice to those who dont listen</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent Job, just don't expect a compassionate Management group.”

</title><pros>Pros – new skill sets to be learned, lots of new experiences.</pros>
<cons>Cons – lack of compassion from Mgmt. Zero recognition for a job well done. Lots of begin "thrown to the wolfs" so to speak. Zero accountability for corporate/management mistakes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Enhance Communication with field reps. At least act like you care about the well being of your employees who are the real face of the company. Happy employees = good work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>