<name>e-con Systems Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/e-con-Systems-Reviews-E414575.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-05-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“e-con systems good and bad”

</title><pros>Pros – Flat structure, open culture, energetic teams, very motivated engineers, almost all across the company are very helpful and handy if there is a situation you need help for....If management feels your the perfect match for the job, they pay you what you ask for, otherwise you will need to find a middle ground.You are not fired surprisingly.....Lots of technology driven work, place to learn....</pros>
<cons>Cons – You wont get pay stubs on time.Finance department is not employee friendly, you will find out of box thinking working with them.IT department is very minimal.No good hotels around, place gets really dark after sunset not good for women employees without vehicles...management arranges vehicles on request for women employees.Managements stinginess will appear in few places in terms of resources to employees, work benefits etc.,Working on alternative Saturdays and reason behind makes no sense from the managementMisc: Lunch place is very un-hygenic, toilets are not good, people use words like madam and sir.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please use good software in finance department to get pay stubs on time and remove manual work.You are growing the numbers, so eliminate stingy policies straight away and become employee friendly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not for Enthusiastic beginners”

</title><pros>Pros – Bit of flexiblity in work and timing</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation and growth in ladder is not as good</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – can be better</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“developing device drivers & BSP portings”

</title><pros>Pros – Very flexible company, Nice place to work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation and other benefits leave a lot to be desired.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>