<name>K-12 Teacher's Alliance Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/K-12-Teacher-s-Alliance-Reviews-E415654.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cohort Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Amazing managementRecognize hardworking employeesYou will move up fast if you prove you are a hard workerFun company events</pros>
<cons>Cons – No health care or other benefitsSome late hours no many but some nightsThe president was not great but new management is amazing</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up what you are doing!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-29</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible place to work...”

</title><pros>Pros – I honestly cannot think of one good thing to say.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No job security at all. Training was horrific. They give you an hour of training and expect you to know the job inside and out. If the president wants to reduce costs they just start firing people for no good reason. I personally wittiness multiple black Fridays. Then within weeks they are hiring new people at lower pay. The president also verbally assaults the employees calling them horrific names and using fowl language. In addition to that the president smokes like a chimney in a non smoking office. He is a looses cannon and no one has the guts to stand up to him, not even his partners. The directors tell you to come to them with any issues and then when you do they tell you to figure things out on your own. And the HR department is a revolving door with at least 4 people in the position in a 2 year period. No insurance benefits at all and my guess is that they will find a way to skirt around the new laws regarding insurance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop allowing the president to assault your employees!!!  Your Directors are keeping you in the dark and anyone that has been with the company for any amount of time is looking for work elsewhere. You have good, dependable employees who actually have good ideas and are willing to make a contribution but the ideas never reach your desk due to your directors lack of actual management and people skills.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Hours were decent. Other than that I have nothing positive to say.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The President is a loose cannon, screams with fowl language at people on a daily basis and calls his employees names. To make matters worse all the partners turn a blind eye to the presidents antics.  The president also smokes like a chimney in his "non- smoking" office.They fire people at will for no reasons, just because the president wants to cut costs then rehire new people at lower wages. The Directors, whose responsibility it is to run the business, ask you to let them know if you have any issues or suggestions and then when you go to them with suggestions or problems, tell you we can't use your suggestion and as far as your problem, figure it out on your own. The company give you minimal training and then expect exceed all others right away. The HR department is a revolving door, having had 4 HR people in as many years. The newest HR person does not have anyone's back except the presidents. Don't bother going for help it is a waste of your time. All this and no benefits...run don't walk away from this tie bomb.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – This company has the WORST morale of any company I have ever seen. You have great, dependable employees that are walking on egg shells for fear they will be let go because your upper management (and lower management) teams are so awful and do not know the first thing about employee relations. All management appears to be able to do is tell the Partners "everything is fine". Watch out, hardly anything is fine!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“RUN”

</title><pros>Pros – Starting pay was more than fairSome of the staff were very nice</pros>
<cons>Cons – -The owners of this business have NO tact, class or professionalism. I'm actually shocked they haven't been sued-They will fire you, then laugh, then tell all the staff why you were fired. Some management may even make vulgar references about you.-No health insurance-Employer was NOT upfront about the details of the position-Management showed extreme favoritism to attractive female employees only</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Find your souls</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Less than Ideal...”

</title><pros>Pros – Rigorous training and support is provided for anyone working in the Cohort division. Opportunity for growth in the cohort division. Some opportunity to travel. Simple business model.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No benefits/insurance offered. Call center structure. Other products and services outside of Cohorts have not been successful due to the lack leadership, product management, and strategy. Senior Management is very reactive rather than proactive.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-01</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Could not be happier with my career move to K-12!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great working atmosphere, great co-workers, non-stressful work environment, great morale, great boss, great VP over department, love what I do job duty wise, time off with pay right away, recognition and respect for work done, recognition programs for hard work, company first looks to move employees up before hiring outside giving room for advancement, casual Fridays, great kitchen break room, beautiful building/working environment, great HR person</pros>
<cons>Cons – no health, dental or vision insurance, took a pay cut to work here because the job was what I was looking to do career wise</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Look into insurance options for employees and pay increases that are more up to scale. Maybe make casual days everyday if employees are not meeting with clients. Keep up the awesome non-stressful work environment and the wonderful bosses in the Marketing teams!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cohort Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's a Sales Job”

</title><pros>Pros – Paid time off and work balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – The only thing that matters is getting people to apply to your program.  You're pretty much lied to from day one.  They tell you its not a sales job, but it is, you're just not cold calling.  The training has little to resemble when you get on the call center floor.  Management has very little direction and forethought.  Everything is done at the last minute without much thought put in.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop firing people you don't like.  Give employees a chance to find their feet.  Train employees for the area/school they will be working with and don't tell employees their conversion rate doesn't matter when that's all you look at.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-14</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No professional growth, Don't waste your time”

</title><pros>Pros – If you like working in an isolated environment you might enjoy this position. The pay isn't great but the company does offer a lenient work schedule and a lot of paid time off.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are no health, dental, or eye insurance benefits with this company. They also do not have a 401k plan.There is terrible training working with this company. They do not take quality time to train you for the job requirements they ask of you. There is a very high turn over rate working here. The work environment is very uneasy because there is always a lot of pressure to perform well or you most likely will be fired. I worked there for a short time and there were many employees who talked to myself and others about the high turn over rate. This shows a lack professionalism from management and leaders because the employees should not know the personal business of any current or former employee. This also contributed to the uneasy work environment. There is no consistency either. Things change weekly and you are still expected to perform well or be terminated immediately.Be aware that you are always being watched and when things do not go as expected management, and even other employees are looking for a scapegoat.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You should work on being professional when hiring and firing employees. The entire staff should not know anyone else's personal business. Be honest about the requirements and expectations when working for the company. A dishonest company will not go far. You also need to work on finding health benefits for the employees. In our country this is extremely important and it is almost impossible to take care of a family or yourself without health insurance. Take the appropriate time to train your employees. We are all human and make mistakes so firing people is a lazy way of trying to get your company to progress. Conversion numbers on a sheet of paper are not always accurate to that person's work ethic, professionalism, drive, or personality. Therefore, training is very important if you value employees meeting the expectations of your company. There is not a good outward or inward appearance of the company because of the lack of training and high turnover rate. This is very counter productive to the growth of the company. This company will not go far if it continues at this rate.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Drupal Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Teachhub was my worse position ever”

</title><pros>Pros – I would say my co-workers but only some of them where actually good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – K12 uses up contract employees with the same plan. They hire you on as contract-to-hire tell you if you put in the work that you will be rewarded with a permanent position. This is not the case, this is a ploy to get you to work harder on your project to get it done sooner so they can relieve you of your position. They lie to agencies and employees to keep this going.They also offer NO benefits to any employee.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – if you have no intention of hiring an employee don't tell them to fight for a place there are way better tact's to get ppl to work diligently.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I regret taking a position with this company. Don't even interview here”

</title><pros>Pros – The only pro's to working here are my coworkers. I have made friends with a lot of people and there are many great people who work for this company, caring, friendly, considerate, and wonderful people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Those great people I work with? They get treated like crap by the management/owners/higher-ups. I was told in my interview that they were going to add insurance benefits since it's now required. When I asked again after I was hired, I was told to not hold my breath because the company will pay the fine and not offer us the insurance. Really? Could they care any less about the employee's. Also since starting here I've seen about 15 people fired and atleast 8 or 9 who quit. There are 120 employee's, and that turnover rate is bad! Bad news! Just stay away from this company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop lying to the new hires and in the interviews. I was told many things in my interview that was complete BS. I was told there was room for advancement, well that's only if they don't fire you for no reason and you wait around for 3-4 years. I was told that they train you well and get you up to speed, not really. They just look for reasons to fire you right away. This place is horrible</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cohort Coordinator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“overall not horrible, but not great”

</title><pros>Pros – I started working here about 3 months ago. I definitely felt their goals to advance teacher's education and serve the teachers was a good concept. People were friendly and since I didn't have benefits at the other job I was working, I took a position here even though I felt like the salary was too low for my background. In training, everyone was positive and friendly and I like the other people I work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Since being out of training my opinion has changed a lot. We were told that the conversion rate and numbers were not a big deal. If numbers are low, they coach you and train you more. NOT TRUE AT ALL. They just fire people if you don't get a lot of applications to programs. The cohort position is inconsistent. There are days that busy and stressful, then days where you have nothing at all to do.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop firing your employees with low numbers. Train them or move them to another team. The workplace morale is low when 5 people are fired in one day alone. Not only did you fire 5 people, but now the other employees are looking for jobs because they feel like they are in a sales environment where only the numbers matter. Also don't tell people you have to cut/fire employees not that you are required to provide health insurance. That is the worst excuse ever... providing health insurance to your employees is a great incentive, people work hard when they feel appreciated and care more about the company if the company care about the employee. This company does not care at all.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cohort Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You are truly just a number”

</title><pros>Pros – SOME of the people who work there are great...SOME. Willing to help you get acclimated, very friendly, and make you feel like you fit in right away.  No nights or weekends, semi laid back atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You are being judged from day one and on.  Even after training management told us that they were coming in to "sit in" on our training, just to see who they would they would like on their teams. Honestly, how can you judge people who are just sitting in a conference room for a week and not getting more than an hour or two of hands on experience in a day...sometimes.  Management treated team placement as if it were a fantasy football draft, making trades and such, and were vocal about it as well.They also told us our conversion rates do not matter, but it is a LIE! If you walk onto a team, who is already not doing so great in registering students, ie low conversion rates, you will lose your job, even if "the numbers" have absolutely nothing to do with you.Also, I noticed that when I worked there, most of the employees had only been employed for a little under a year, or a little over a year. Very high turnover rate.  Do not expect a career because your job could be gone in the blink of an eye.No benefits or 401K through the company is offered.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Point blank, Market this job as a sales job, because it is completely that.Do not make people think that if they have a semi low conversion rate, that you will help/coach them to do better, because that did not happen. Ensure some job security because most of the people there know that they could be gone at any given time, no one wants to feel like any day could be there day to leave. Especially when they will not see it coming.Recognize hard work, and employees who go above what is expected.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Would be much better if they offered benefits”

</title><pros>Pros – Great job that helps educators become stronger.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No benefits available - medical, vision or dental.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>