<name>E.ON Climate & Renewables North America Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/E-ON-Climate-and-Renewables-North-America-Reviews-E416874.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E.ON provided a great environment for professional growth and knowledge in the renewable energy industry.”

</title><pros>Pros – The people within E.ON all share a common goal of success through a combination of cross-department collaboration and limited supervision. I was able to develop and administrate my department through my own decisions with little involvement from my superiors.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Communication from supervisors and approval from the executive side can prove to be difficult at times, and this issue proved to be a fatal flaw in some activities.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Define the roles of your subordinates, maintain communication with them, and listen to their needs for mutual success.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I was proud of the positive environmental work we did.”

</title><pros>Pros – E.On Climate & Renewables, formerly known as Airtricity, was an Irish-based company until it was purchased by German-owned E.On.  Airtricity was an incredible place to work.  A place where I was thoroughly satisfied with my work product and company management.  I was proud to work for a wind-farm company and raved about the company to my friends and family.  It was a very special group of people doing very rewarding work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As with many corporate buy-outs, things changed, although not immediately.  As time passed, senior management began to leave.  New, non-Airtricity folks were hired into senior management roles, and the company lost its synergy.  A competitive rift and distrust formed between the Chicago and Austin offices.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay attention.  Senior and middle-management employees with tenure have left and continue to leave.  Ask yourselves why.  Stop making excuses.  Face the issues.  Fix them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Place to Work”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice people, great company, like it</pros>
<cons>Cons – no room for advancement, or clear career path</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – do more to promote from within</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>