<name>Infomedia 18 Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Infomedia-18-Reviews-E420043.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-06-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Deputy Manager Systems (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sometimes mistakes make your life.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Environment, Great culture and Best place for new comers</pros>
<cons>Cons – A little marketing can make this company grow like google.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Marketing and distribution are the right keyword to bring the business to profit</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Web Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Work Culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Very Good work culture and lots of scope to learn new technology</pros>
<cons>Cons – Experience wise need to improve salary structure</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No Comment</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Company to be with for a long while”

</title><pros>Pros – good family across the country,more professional than any other company i worked with</pros>
<cons>Cons – sales part,which makes makes not so good</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – nothing to be advised,everybody rocking</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior General Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dream Journey from SE to Sr.GM”

</title><pros>Pros – Security, On the Job training, exposed to multi-division, credit given when deserved, exposing to start-ups</pros>
<cons>Cons – underestimates the value of their assets. Not able to take risks. Follower instead of initiator</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – keep up with market trends (new media). initiate new blood and ideas</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's been great!”

</title><pros>Pros – The work culture is pretty much like that of a start up. We work on best technologies and some very good problems and challenges. Technical teams are very brilliant. Learning and improving skills is the best part here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – One of the main downsides here is a 3 Month notice period. Within organization getting promotion is difficult. I don't like the current process followed for development.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please come up with some new bright ideas to take burrp to next level. Also a change  is required in the currently followed software development process.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>