<name>Rent A Wheel Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Rent-A-Wheel-Reviews-E420669.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2011-10-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience, solid business model, poor execution and associate development.”

</title><pros>Pros – Rent-A-Wheel offers competitive compensation with tremendous bonus potential.  Rent-A-Wheel offers reasonable hours of operation with the ability to support a solid work life balance.  The company appears to do a good job recruiting from business peers and competition allowing them to gain experience from a diverse talent pool.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Extremely high turnover.  It appears that the company does not have a long term associate development / retention plan.  Many new employees become quickly alienated based on the lack of personal engagement, support and communication.  There is little to no leadership / management training.  Process training consist of online modules and any experience that you bring with you.  Employment retention decisions are often made off site and out of the market confusing and frustrating local teams and leadership.  These type of decisions can also cause additional premature loss, the onset of integrity issues and fear / morale concerns with the remaining team members and neighboring locations.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus needs to be placed on associate development, retention and process management.  The brand is being compromised by mid level confusion around corporate objectives opening the door for lower level morale and integrity breakdowns that can potentially impact the business model, brand and future of the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very high turnover, unethical sales expectations, bad benefits”

</title><pros>Pros – The company accepts employees with previous convictions. Easy to get a job, beacuse the company is always looking for new employees due to high turnover and expansion. An acceptable place to be while searching for another job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unreasonable sales expectation, for example they expect you to sell nitrogen gas for the tires to each customer. Some locations employ unethical sales tactics to obtain their sales goals. Bad benefits: only five days of vacation per year, no sick time, only four paid holidays, expensive health insurance. Stores are usually understaffed due to the high turnover (most people don't make it to the next year) and the new employees are not properly trained. This is not a good company if you have long-term career plans.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upper management/owners: Focus more on your employees and customers, not only on making money for yourselves. Employees will stay longer, customers will be happier, and it will be better for you in the long run.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>