<name>Research Now Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Research-Now-Reviews-E420629.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Caring people and streamlined processes”

</title><pros>Pros – Great pay, fun environment, organized company</pros>
<cons>Cons – difficult to standout as company gets larger</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – put the same effort into mentoring your employees as you do answering to your managers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“What is the direction?”

</title><pros>Pros – Culture can be fun, the company has a lot of potential to do great things if the direction was better defined and leadership worked together.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots of long hours, change is constant and not managed well. Reactive, no real structure for development or career path except through politics.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Define a leadership strategy with true corporate goals, not personal goals at the top level so the rest of the company can have something clear and consistent to follow.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>IT Technician (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Can be great or terrible depends on the department”

</title><pros>Pros – Free drinks (bad for health though);Friendly employees except a few;Exposure to new technologies.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Politics;Work and life balance;Middle level management is disappointing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire some professionally trained people for middle level management positions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Administrative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent workplace...”

</title><pros>Pros – Free coffee tea soda's, Green Environment, positive energy around the office. lots of smiling faces. Nice cubes with lots of storage. Lots of employee interaction.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots of meeting, some people are very unorganized, Noise level is high at times in cube environment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep reaching out to your employees... listen to them and take their advice and ideas and implement them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Graphic Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Solid company. Good values, good communication.”

</title><pros>Pros – Pretty great work environment for a typical "corporate" environment. Competitive pay, pretty laid back. Lots of good perks beyond healthcare and salary. Good communication between management and employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The work got pretty monotonous. I needed a little more variety.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Production Specialist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall a solid company”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a good place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company doesn't have any bad things that I can name</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great People, Long Work Hours, Unappreciative Clients, Poor Management, Low Pay”

</title><pros>Pros – The people you work with; free beverages and good coffee; casual dress environment; charitable events.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company does not give recognition to those who deserve it - it seems the same people are awarded and promoted over and over again due to politics. They make it seem like a requirement to work weekends and long hours and if you don't, you get reprimanded for not answering your personal phone on holidays and you never see salary increases. This is usually because most of the clients are accustomed to treating the RN employees like second-hand citizens and that mentality spreads to RN management. Health benefits are not free and you still end up paying a lot out of pocket. Company has made a lot of poor business decisions and it seems only management level is growing while the people doing the actual work are taking more and more on without getting the additional support they need. Many of the PMs seem like they are hanging on by a string most of the time and the main reason I left was because my husband told me he felt I was neglecting my children and that I shouldn't work so hard for a company that wouldn't pay me appropriately. When I asked for more money, my manager laughed in my face and told me I was overpaid already which I know isn't true because others with the same experience as me were making almost $6,000-$10,000 more - again, politics.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Offer hard-working employees more opportunities to grow, rather than accepting the 14% attrition rate that has haunted this company for years.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Research Now is not a Great Place to Work”

</title><pros>Pros – Coworkers were always very friendly and great locationFree fruit on MondaysFree parking</pros>
<cons>Cons – Senior Management does not know how to lead through change at all.Too many politics and favoritismNo work life balance. It is expected for you to work 24/7You will be told you are doing a great job, you are a high performer, but they will not compensate you for it or promote you.HR sells this Great Place to work survey and you take it and nothing is done about it.HR does not know what they are doing and HR people that were good leave the company</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>TReam Lead (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Team Lead”

</title><pros>Pros – It was a positive work place</pros>
<cons>Cons – now not so much - mid level management is a problem</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great experience- great place to build ur protfoloio- you have to be a go getter to excel here.”

</title><pros>Pros – opportunity to do anything you want</pros>
<cons>Cons – you don't have great leadership- however that said the company is young and needs leaders.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – it wouldn't hurt to take some online leadership and management courses to learn about managing your team.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for building experience, however don't expect to rise quickly without playing the politic game.”

</title><pros>Pros – Easygoing work environment, free soda, special events occasionally. Most people here are very nice and are always willing to help.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you want a promotion you have to point out everything good you've done constantly, and practically beat a VPs door down to get any headway whatsoever. Senior management is commonly out of touch with the ground level, and tend to never listen to what junior staff say go right or wrong. HR department is completely out of touch with the rest of the company as well.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The people under you are invaluable in understanding market movements. A report helps, but getting a first person perspective will solidify the data you already have. Treat entry level folks trying to work their way up with more dignity, instead of finding every way to undercut them for the bottom line.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst experience in my career”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a job.  Some nice people.  Office refurbished last year, nice sized bright cubicles.  IT team is wonderful, always ready to help.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very low pay, benefits not competitive, extremely political, uneducated workforce overall, not professional, like being in high school, gossip and back-stabbing.  High attrition.  No cohesion among departments.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get rid of Great Place to Work because it isn't and no one pays any attention anyway.    Stop micromanaging long-time great employees.  Recognize those contributing instead of your friends when promotions come around.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Work Environment, but compensation leaves something to be desired”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice environment and corporate culture.  Pretty laid back</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can be stressful and the pay is not great</cons>
<advice-to-management> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager II (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“excellent”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible hours, very talented staff, WFH possibilities, great team atmosphere</pros>
<cons>Cons – salaries are not in line with the industry</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – open your pocketbooks and retain the extremely talented team you have on board!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager, Client Services (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Project Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – -Great Benefits-Wonderful group of people</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Poor work/life balance- Poor training- Weak management, there is little leadership here</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – While the vision may be apparent to the executive level, by the time it trickles down to management level, the overall vision has weakened and is not incorporated into daily work life.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company does not recognize employee's contributions and provide advancement opportunities”

</title><pros>Pros – Company tends to hire young people straight out of college or with little experience.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company has systematically lowered it's contribution to it's bonus plan to where it is very minimal percentage of base pay. In Operations, bonus used to be passed out four times a year, then changed to two times a year, now it is once a year.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Executive leadership needs to allow employees the opportunity to communicate feedback without penalizing them.  CEO's open comment at one his quarterly meetings in 2013 was if you were not happy at ResearchNow then leave.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Okay pay, good team but dead end job”

</title><pros>Pros – The pay can be okay, depending on your department. Sales is better compensated.Depending on office the atmosphere can be pretty relaxed, people work from home some days. No issues taking some time off.Good co-workers, willing to help. The team is great and the company only succeeds because of hardworking individuals</pros>
<cons>Cons – No career path. Almost all titles are meaningless and if you're not in the right office or friends with the right people not much opportunity for growth.No training outside of internal tools. You'll probably have a hard time explaining how your time here is useful at another company.Management is not very transparent, constantly in flux and many decisions are rushed and not very well thought out.Long hours are expectedVery clunky and bureaucratic</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Offer more training to people, offer more consistency and listen to feedback from employees.It feels like management only cares about the image the company has to the outside in hopes of selling or going public. Not a lot of long term planning.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager II (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Has been mostly a great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with clients is satisfying. Most of the upper management is good and cares about the business and the employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It really depends on which team/business unit you are on. Let's just say half of the client service area is well managed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – To the less well managed client services side I'd say just let your people do their jobs and stop working so hard to micromanage. The other team does it right and the results speak for themselves.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't work here if you want to grow”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people to work withFree drinks</pros>
<cons>Cons – Research Now is a young company that is full of potential. However, MGMT needs to wake up and recognize that it's not going to keep employees happy but giving them low to no pay raise, no career development opportunities, and standard benefits. Morale at this place is low. People are overworked and tired of the useless and incompetent management they have to report to. The structure itself is disorganized. Kurt is a great CEO but he heeds no one's advice. I wish I could recommend working for this company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Clean house. Recognize that MORE employees is not the answer--it's hiring the right people in the first place.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Long hours, very low pay and no regard for work/life balance.”

</title><pros>Pros – Casual environmentNice coworkersFun company eventsFree drinks/juice/coffee</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very low pay. Low. Raises are basically non-existant.Expected to work past normal hours (9-6). 40 hour work week? I wish! Forget that.Barely any recognition or bonus if you do exceptional work.Make any mistake (short email/long email/attire/anything) and you are basically blacklisted from high management.Micro-managing to the max. Management makes you feel/treats you like an intern regardless of tenure at company. Do you like being told what to do? Work here! Higher-up approval before sending any email to a client? Work here!High turnover.You also get no real experience here. Anyone can do this job. There are people who didn't graduate college working here from a million different career backgrounds. The only experience you get is honing your time-management/multi-tasking skills. Nothing else you do here will apply/help you anywhere else unless you work for a competitor.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Reduce company events/food and pay more instead.Hire managers who know the market research industry.Hire managers who are calm and don't believe the sky is falling over every miniscule bump. Newsflash: a million robotic-like emails/updates to the client makes us seem crazy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good people”

</title><pros>Pros – Multi-national company with leading market share in its space that is still growing. The best part of the job are the friendly co-workers. Management is moving company in the right direction.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Client-facing positions can be very stressful. Needs to continue finding ways to improve efficiency between systems and departments. Some departments have limited career growth opportunities.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep finding ways to grow revenue.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent team members, great morale.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Systems are constantly in flux. Lack of 360-degree assessment of supervisors by employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not much room to grow or learn.”

</title><pros>Pros – Exposure to a lot of different market research companies..  They do recognize your hard work and performance and reward you accordingly... Not necessarily always in money/salary but in Work from Home allowances, holiday considerations, etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Depending on the team you're on you could be overworked and underpaid.  Workload is not balanced and titles don't really mean anything.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Spread the workload</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Project Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Co-workers are great.  Young group of people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Terrible MGMT. Employees on PM side are over worked, under paid, demoralized, micro-managed and treated like children. MGMT has no managerial skills...and too many bosses.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Clean house and get better MGMT.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“big disappointment”

</title><pros>Pros – very solid and highly professional project management team</pros>
<cons>Cons – very not competent management on all levelsno employes appreciationno career pathlow salarieshigh stress levellong working hours and its expectedalways some technology related issueslow moral</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – start hiring smart, intelligent professional leaders with solid understanding of the industry and proven records, promote people from the inside, stop playing politics and games, value people who work for you (without them you are nothing), make business processes effective, easy andreliable, hire more people (60-70 hours business week is not good for the business).</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was ok....lack of structure within company”

</title><pros>Pros – Pays pretty wellCoworkers were niceGreat teamworkFast paced companyConstant learning opportunitiesExtensive trainingGreat client relations development</pros>
<cons>Cons – The internal systems were constantly changing making it hard to become solid in technical processes. Management was either lazy or underqualified and it was usually a friend who got promoted instead of the most talented.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Better communication is needed for employees to feel valued. Also, better treatment of your employees is a must.  Stop looking out for your friends and promote the best qualified.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a Career place”

</title><pros>Pros – There are no best reasons, except Bagel Mondays, and decent salary package. Location is might also be and incentive but that is all.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No career growth, managers have zero managerial skills, the structure of the company is not solid overall not a good company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Managers need to take managerial skill courses, not everyone has the ability to be a natural leader they have to be trained.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ehhh...it's an okay place to work.  Think long and hard before joining this company.”

</title><pros>Pros – -  Great employees-  Fun environment, for the most part-  Box suites at the AA Center and Cowboys Stadium-  Free drinks-  There is not a lot of micro-managing-  The Recruiters were great to work with!</pros>
<cons>Cons – -  Minimal growth opportunities-  It's like a high school up there / rumors flying everywhere, people talking trash about people, interoffice relations (some sr leaders, too)-  Work the employees to death / Everyone is spread too thin-  All depts needs more employees-  Some of the mgmt in HR were incredibly stupid and hard to work with or even talk to-  Sr leaders are somewhat incompetent and annoying-  Some senior leaders like to play favorites-  Mgmt tends to hire the wrong people more often than not-  Some of the senior leaders are "just there" / Not really engaged for the amount of money they are probably making</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop overworking your employees and hire more people.  Don't just try maximize the bottom line.  You need good employees to have a successful company. You are running people away daily, so you need to make some changes quick.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is a fast paced, professional environment that requires a lot of focus from its employees.”

</title><pros>Pros – Depending on department, there can be a lot of flexibility in schedule. The benefits are pretty good. Though the company is large, it is still a very social environment. There is a 'secondement' program which allows individuals to move for a few months to various office locations around the world.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There aren't many opportunities for growth within the company itself.Very performance driven, often at the cost of employee work/life balance.Salaries are generally lower than market.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Share the wealth... create a structure that provides for more movement, and personal development.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Demanding, fast-paced”

</title><pros>Pros – Some of the team members are great to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – limited promotion opportunitiesLittle management supportLittle positive feedback on job performance</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Frustrating”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of bright people, you learn a lot on the job</pros>
<cons>Cons – Execs are pretty much on cloud 9, not caring to relate to the proletariat's day to day frustrations</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Live among your worker bees in satellite offices.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great colleagues hardly compensate for incompetent management”

</title><pros>Pros – Social environment - lower level staff are a friendly, fun bunch of people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I worked at RSN for over five years and in that time multiple people were repeatedly refused promotions to jobs they had all of the responsibilities for - with none of the benefits and nothing to show for it. Senior management often went up the ranks due to tremendous growth in the first couple of years - NOT because they were adept at the job - and it shows.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I was once told by a very senior member of management that providing training, growth and career prospects - if not increasing pay - were unnecessary because "people are lucky to have jobs" and "Tesco doesn't do it that way". I've got news for you - this isn't a supermarket chain, it's research. Your staff turnover is high for a reason, RSN.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Micro manages the staff”

</title><pros>Pros – Very friendly and social company</pros>
<cons>Cons – No Work/Life BalanceLow salaryManagers micro manage staff</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop micro managing</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good fun people (on the whole)”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are (for the most part) really fun to work with.  There is a good work ethic among teams and most people get on well and socialise a lot together.  Most managers are flexible with their teams and allow extra perks like working from home and other benefits.  The benefits also just got a bit of a revamp and are better than they were.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours can be quite long, and there are challenges with working for a company with the head office in the USA.  Although I think there are more opportunities for training, it would be good if there were more.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have more decisions made in EMEA.  A bit more recognition to best employees.  Also, more investment in training & more of a long term view on providing training for employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good people, low salaries”

</title><pros>Pros – Loads of efforts were done to get some social life into the company, the parties are great and the colleagues too. It is a fun and youthful atmosphere.Training opportunities are available to people who ask for themMngmt is on the ball, the future of the company seems safe, mgmt ready to seize opportunities in the market</pros>
<cons>Cons – Creativity can sometimes be stifled by technology issuesLow salaries, and bonus scheme isnt the most generous out there... vouchers do not replace a low base...lack of clear career plan "it's all on you!"Processes can be very heavy to moveOperations teams overworked and undervalued, long hours expected.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I have none.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Horizontal organization, everybody is very easy to reach</pros>
<cons>Cons – Difficult to ramp, if your direct boss is selfish, you have nothing to do</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Set clear and feasible goals, be realistic with price positioning against competitors, you're the best in the industry but others are just much cheaper.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No career growth opportunity”

</title><pros>Pros – A lot of friendly, hard working people in the companyFree drinksBenefits are ok</pros>
<cons>Cons – No promotion/career pathLow salaryLow bonusCan expect to work long hoursLack of training</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to keep the best people from the organization.  Value, promote and increase the salary for your best employees.  A lot of of good, very knowledgeable, hard working people have already left this company.  Quality of work has gone downhill.  Since a lot of people left, company is hiring anyone who can just do the job even with no work experience.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Needs to pay more”

</title><pros>Pros – Good social activities, good social events</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay, and bonus scheme was rubbish</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increase base salary!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of exposure to market research methodologies”

</title><pros>Pros – Giving back to the communityGood office atmosphere</pros>
<cons>Cons – Does not promote from within</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Develop your existing employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of change. Fun & stimulating place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Always things are changing, which gives rise to lots of opportunitites.Friendly people & good teamwork.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slightly long hours culture in London office.Some challenges with having a Head Office in Dallas, but no different to any other US owned company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get employees more invovled with changes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Flexible but somehow unambitious workplace”

</title><pros>Pros – Diverse people and good work/life-balance. It is a nice community feeling at least in the panel management team and people are friendly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not the best place for ambitious people, different parts of the company seem quite disconnected. The office is not very inspirational although they partly refurbished it last year.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people, interesting work, fair pay</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of focus from leadership of various departments</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stronger collaboration is needed across departments</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“nice youthful atmosphere, people are great to work with”

</title><pros>Pros – The people that work here are great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No retirement plan / pension plan</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – N/A</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>