<name>i-maritime Consultancy Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/i-maritime-Consultancy-Reviews-E422643.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-03-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Strictly OK”

</title><pros>Pros – - slightly higher than market salary- surrounded by high calibre IIT/IIM grads- lot of responsibility- interesting work</pros>
<cons>Cons – - no work life balance</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Only for Marine Engineers”

</title><pros>Pros – Employee Bonding is very good.No dirty politics between employees to go up the ladder.The company makes u learn very quickly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. There are very few knowledgeable people left in the company.  Only 2 to 3 people are running    the show. Total no. of employees is approximately 25.2. The salaries are not paid on time. Usually 11th  or 12th is the salary date.3. There were innumerable examples of people who were on notice period but never get paid for it.4. HR policies are not employee friendly. Head HR left the the company because of this. As if now the HR dept is in doldrums.5. The financial condition of company is not good.6. The attrition rate is almost 200%. The company seems new after every 6 months.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – A total changeover of the top management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Aweful!!”

</title><pros>Pros – None. This company is an epitome of "what all can be wrong"</pros>
<cons>Cons – No policies and salaries are delayed by over 15 days every month.The company's accounts are frozen by GoI on account of non-payment of service tax for over 5-6 years. IT department's pending liabilities are awaited.Separation policy is a faff and pending dues are never paid.Bonus is just on paper and when it comes to paying, it is conveniently declared as "0".</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Awful CEO/Owner.The company is heading for a close down for its poor work and poorer client satisfaction.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>