<name>H.BLOOM Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/H-BLOOM-Reviews-E422913.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-10-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you want to dive into the exciting and dynamic start-up world, H. Bloom is the perfect fit!”

</title><pros>Pros – With the company thriving, your hard work, passionate energy, and commitment to excellence will allow you to flourish at H. Bloom. Your talented, ambitious, and goal-oriented colleagues will drive you even further than you could have imagined.</pros>
<cons>Cons – With the rapid growth in each market, it can be difficult to achieve flawless functionality. Growing pains will be a part of the mix, but definitely help to keep things interesting. There is never a dull moment!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keeping employees informed of changes will help facilitate better understanding, greater trust, and  dedication to the team. Incentives to exceed goals would help foster healthy competition.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“BE WARNED!”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible work hours and except for a few very bad apples, the people are pretty great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management here is terrible!!! Company seems to have a clear direction but does not have the resources nor the management in place to get it there. They put on a very good front during interviews but once you work there, it is every man for him/herself. Although it is a start up and you would expect a little bit of craziness, it is a very unprofessional environment. This company will not make it if major changes aren't put in place soon.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You're going down if you don't clear house and put people in charge that actually care about the future of the company and are willing to put in the time and work. Just because someone has been with the company for a while doesn't mean they will make a good manager.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Great Opportunity that Comes with a Price”

</title><pros>Pros – -fast paced environment - never a dull moment ever-great people/coworkers-work with amazing products that you can feel really proud about-great health benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – -So much is expected of you that within the first 6 months you WILL feel burned out, no matter what kind of person you are, being dedicated to work 24/7 is a guaranteed recipe for disaster-there is no HR management. if you get injured  and go on disability, expect to get fired, no matter what level position you have or how close you are with the founders-upper management has no loyalty to those who grew the company in the first three years. if my data is accurate there are only 2 manager level employees left at H. Bloom, other than the 2 founders, that were original hires during the first year of the company. turnover is high, expect your stay to be short.-the founders prey on young people who are new to the area and dont have family or friends nearby. if you have any type of life outside of work, you might as well forget about it if you plan to work here. your work will be your life for the entirety of your short stay.-if you have a family and young children, you might as well consider yourself an absentee parent during your time as an H. Bloom employee. although you will likely hear stories of the founders' kids and their nannies and the school they attend with famous peoples kids-H. Bloom's founders are so focused on building the bigger business that they forget about culture and employees, it is the epitome of afterthought. the only culture there is created by the middle management employees. -H. Bloom's founders are so focused on building the bigger business that they forget about culture and employees, it is the epitome of afterthought. the only culture there is created by the middle management employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the ideals you had when you started H. Bloom. Keep the ideals you touted about work culture and life balance. It may take 3 extra months to get where you want to go - but at least you'll have experienced employees following you wherever you lead.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Expectations fall flat at this revolving door "start up"”

</title><pros>Pros – -easy hours-fun young people-office is in a great location-met alot of fun life long friends</pros>
<cons>Cons – -horrible HR dept takes no responsibility for the turnover which affects morale-constantly changing compensation plan for account executives-no career path and a lot of ambiguity in roles- not challenging and very monotonous</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on and thank your employees now. If you aren't focusing when you are this young, it definitely seems like  you won't be in future.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>SEED (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast Growing Start-Up”

</title><pros>Pros – H.Bloom has great leadership.  There is an abundance of opportunity for growth and career development at this company and the leadership team seems desirous of their employees taking advantage of that.  All H.Bloom employees currently have an opportunity to make a large impact on the company and everyone seems excited about that.  H.Bloom consists of a diverse group of intelligent and ambitious individuals which results in creative and innovative working environments.</pros>
<cons>Cons – H.Bloom currently does not have a very robust HR department.  As the company grows, they will have to have more structure around the new hire procedure and other HR related issues within the work place.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to learn ALL about a business”

</title><pros>Pros – At H.Bloom I'm able to contribute to every aspect of the business.  Many of the pieces I get involved in are ones that I had zero experience in prior to joining the company.  Sometimes I get involved because there's no one else to do it.  And sometimes it's because I find something interesting on insert myself.  I think after this experience I could practically start my own company from scratch!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes having a hand in everything means you end up doing some things you wouldn't have chosen for yourself.  You end up having to take the good with the bad.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exciting startup with big ambitions”

</title><pros>Pros – -The founders of the company put a great deal of trust in their employees, so you have a very good chance of having a large impact on the business quickly.-H.BLOOM has put together a solid group of hard working individuals and the work ethic is contagious.-CEO Bryan Burkhart is shooting for the moon, and it is exciting to see your work contribute to the common goal of making this company big.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -The company is growing very rapidly and it would benefit from having a little more structure.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Blooming!”

</title><pros>Pros – Working for such an innovative company with great leadership is a wonderful experience. It's hard not enjoying providing people with a beautiful product!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working for a start up has its day to day surprises, but it also keeps each day interesting.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great, Growing Company - Fast Paced”

</title><pros>Pros – H.Bloom is growing incredibly fast and it's a great place to get a lot more experience than you would in a larger organization. You're constantly learning, being challenged and getting more experience. There is little bureaucracy and politics. There's a lot of energy and everyone is willing to pitch in.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hours are long and the pressure is high. The time off policy, take what you want, is great in principle but schedules are so demanding that it ends up being impractical.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Creating personal, non-work relationships with everyone on the team would definitely help the culture. Investing in more team events will help everyone connect outside of the office. Also, a real kitchen.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Buyer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Chasing Perfection One Stem at a Time...”

</title><pros>Pros – Being able to build a department from the ground up and to nurture it to its fullest potential is something most managers are not able to say they have the support or control to do.  At H.Bloom each employee; regardless of their role; is hand selected because they are the best in their field, have the best intentions for the company and have the foresight to see how their dedication will shepherd this somewhat antiquated industry into the future.  Each manager owns their part of the business from start to finish with the freedom to mold it the way they know best.  The trust that our founders have in us cannot be surpassed.In addition to having a fabulous management team, H.Bloom has an amazing arsenal of the most cutting edge designers in the industry.  Day in and day out I watch as they sculpt living art from nothing more than a list of varietals on paper.  It's amazing to see the dedication and talent that goes into each and every piece that makes it out the door in each of our three cities.  They are an inspiration to work around and masters of their task.Our Tech team is forging the way for the entire company as they roll out countless upgrades and software models that help us to reach our goals at every mark on the path.  With this group of engineers on board H.Bloom is unstoppable disruptive force to the floral industry.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Great success is only achievable through massive dedication.  Finding a balance between work and having a personal life can be challenging as all H.Bloom employees are expected to be turned on and tuned in 24/7.  But if you're the type of person who can look past the hours that you put in now to be able to enjoy the show later on, then this startup is for you!  Besides, to compensate for this "con" we have learned to rely on each other for support and when you are truly happy with the work that you are doing and feel like family with those you are doing it alongside of, it's much easier to find that balance!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – As we strive toward excellence, it's important to make sure everyone has time to stop and smell the roses; especially since we have such beautiful ones!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-25</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Brand Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Incredible opportunity for professional growth in a demanding and supportive environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – H.Bloom offers the competitive, fast-paced, entrepreneurial environment of a startup with the resources and the leadership of an established company.  I love working with a team that was selected specifically for their top notch talent and creativity.  I walk away from every conversation with my colleagues feeling inspired and motivated.There's an environment of collaboration that is unparalleled in any other work environment, and a genuine commitment to corporate transparency that allows each person to make meaningful contributions to our business.H.Bloom is a company that has committed to investing in young talent and encouraging well-qualified individuals to rise to the challenge of leadership within the business.  Despite the environment of self-sufficiency, there isn't a laissez faire attitude around management.  From our founders to the other members of the senior management team, there is a constant focus on collaboration and guidance as we each work toward our individual priorities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – H.Bloom is a fast-paced environment and each person is expected to perform at 110%, 7 days a week.  It isn't a relaxed start up.  Certain people respond well to that environment, but there are those that might find it stressful.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Let's keep up the good work.  We have the opportunity to create systems and behaviors now that will ensure we keep running optimally as we expand into new markets.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“H.BLOOM is a great place to gain experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a young company so there is a lot of opportunity for advancement within roles. There is also a great atmosphere between coworkers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There isn't much of a work-life balence and compensation is below the market. The hours are long and you should be prepared to work weekends.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Develop the talent internally and promote from within instead of drawing in new employees to fill positions. Please hire the correct number of workers for the amount of work we have.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome team and motivating environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Working at HBLOOM has been great so far.  Everyone has a positive attitude about their job.  There are a lot of moving parts here; it's important that each person owns their share, it's a great feeling to know that each day what you accomplish has direct impact on the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours are definitely long just with any start-up.  As long as you feel your work is leading you somewhere (which it most definitely is) then there are no issues whatsoever with working hard.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The space is definitely feeling a bit crowded, but I understand there is a push to sign a lease in a new space soon.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-10</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A rare find”

</title><pros>Pros – This may be flowers, but engineers are surprisingly empowered.  An engineer here is basically analogous to a film director having final cut or a musician having artistic control: you're trusted to do what you think is best because you're expected to kill it.  You also get to hand-pick your development rig and there's no dress code!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Engineering is and probably will always be a relatively small part of the company (I don't really view this as a con, but potential employees should be aware that it's not like Facebook where the majority of the employees are engineers).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-10</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“One of a kind start-up experience”

</title><pros>Pros – H.BLOOM is filled with amazingly talented and driven people which make it an amazing place to work.  The backdrop to everything that goes on at H.BLOOM is the huge market that we know is ripe for the picking.  That makes every day exciting as we see another piece fall into place on our way to becoming a national brand.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pace can be fast and furious.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working at H.BLOOM is a fun-filled, action-packed adventure!”

</title><pros>Pros – H.BLOOM is a true team environment.  Every employee's opinion is greatly valued, which allows all employees to have an impact on the company.  The company is also growing at a very rapid pace, so all employees will have a chance to contribute to the company and watch it flourish!</pros>
<cons>Cons – H.BLOOM is still a relatively young company, so things can get hectic at times.  The company is also growing at a very fast pace, which forces you to adapt to constant change.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great start-up experience, Good entry level sales”

</title><pros>Pros – Great atmosphere, young same age coworkersAwesome work/life balanceIf you hit your quota, great pay as well as incentives and bonusHands-on management of your accounts</pros>
<cons>Cons – Start up company means having to pitch in when its needed, so i hope you do not mind getting your hands dirty!Moving so quickly, hard to know what is new and what is changing!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep an open line of communication to your employees. They want to know where the company is going, so they can see themselves in the company long term!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great culture and experience!”

</title><pros>Pros – H.Bloom is not your average find on craigslist. This company is a goldmine just waiting to be struck. It is amazing that there is still "striking" to be done. H.Bloom has just begun to advance into the level of success that the future holds for this company. It is an excellent adventure to be a part of and a once in a lifetime opportunity.Working for H.Bloom for almost a year now, I have seen the company grow from 11 (I was the 11th hire) to almost 40. It is inspiring to step into an office that is consistently growing and consistently having great results. H.Bloom is not  a great fit for the "average joe" however, if you are a "go-getter", the result will be a beautiful combination.One thing that is very unique about H.Bloom is the people. Upon stepping in the office you will feel a much different vibe than 90% of your classic New York businesses. The people at H.Bloom are truly enjoyable and fun. The attitude of work hard, play hard is definitely portrayed on a daily basis here.If you are hard working and aspiring to be bigger than you know, H.Bloom is definitely for you.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Start-up world is not for everyone. If you are prone to looking outside the box or being challenged by new situations, this may not be for you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Phenomenal Opportunity”

</title><pros>Pros – This is a company focused on growth, and on developing entrepreneurial minds.  You never lack for chances to take on more responsibility, good ideas are always welcome from any level, and you can see the impact of your actions almost instantaneously.It's great being in a company where everyone is focused on the same goal, and were no one is above jumping in and helping out.If you like working hard and being recognized for that work, then H.Bloom is the place for you</pros>
<cons>Cons – As with any startup, the responsibilities shift as needed to make the business succeed.  Some days a salesperson may be out delivering, a manager may be taking cardboard to the recycling center, or a founder may be running to home depot for supplies.And pollen does stain like you wouldn't believe.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – As the company expands (rapidly), keep the markets all connected.  I love the sense of being on a team here, and would hate for that to get lost at scale.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Growing Fast”

</title><pros>Pros – H.BLOOM is an incredibly exciting company to work for, largely due to its rapid expansion.With a team of young and ambitious employee's, the company has an infectious energy that makes work fun and rewarding.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Rapid expansion makes it difficult to keep up with everything that happens in a given day.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Absolutely fantastic people to work with, and for”

</title><pros>Pros – There is always room to grow here at H.Bloom. Working for a start-up allows you to be exposed to many aspects of the business, and this is definitely true at H.Bloom. There is a great company culture here. I love our sales team, as everyone brings different qualities and experiences to the table. We all work together to achieve a broad goal, and we strive to achieve our individual goals as well. I feel like I can always approach my manager about issues or questions I may have. I also like how we have a relaxed dress code! I do not mind getting up in the morning to come to work - what a wonderful feeling! No two days are the same.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You may have to get up extra early to do floral deliveries. In sales, there is always some rejection associated with it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's interesting and challenging.”

</title><pros>Pros – I like working in a fast pace environment. H Bloom is a very busy company so I always have exciting projects to do. I also love working with talented people. At H Bloom, I work with very talented designers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I work really long hours everyday. So I often find it difficult to balance my personal life and my professional life.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I really think that balance of the driving force and the production force should be given serious and equal attention.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to learn and grow”

</title><pros>Pros – I started at H.BLOOM right out of college and was given the opportunity to take part in the SEED (leadership) program. I'm amazed by everything I've learned without having to go back to school. In the program we were given business classes by the CEO, received personal attention from each department at headquarters and operated the NYC branch for a week.My favorite part of working for H.BLOOM is the feeling that we're doing really great work. At the end of each day I'm excited about our projects, impact and the rate at which we're growing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's a start-up, so you might end up building office furniture or setting up your own laptop.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A real startup experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Dynamic company - things changing & moving forward fastGreat people - coworkers genuinely like one anotherPromising market - huge opportunity, competitive advantagesStartup environment - you can get your hands dirty here and really have an impact</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pollen stains white clothing. Beware.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make sure to keep the lines of communication open - the company is growing so fast, sometimes it's hard to keep up with what's going on!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-25</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Positive atmosphere, Great place to work, Incredible benefits and great pay”

</title><pros>Pros – The "start-up" atmosphere is unlike anything I've ever experienced.  Every one of my colleagues are young, outgoing and driven.  It is the ever changing day to day tasks and responsibilities that keeps me waking up every morning and looking forward to getting to the office.  In order to be successful in this company, you need to give 100% in terms of positive attitude, willingness to work long hours when needed, and being a team player.  However, the leadership and executives in this company keep you motivated to do so!</pros>
<cons>Cons – I don't think it is a "con" but some people may: Your responsibilities and what is expected of you very often go way beyond your specific "job description."  It is an all hands on deck attitude that you must embrace.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None! Great job all around!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast Growing Company with Great Learning Opportunities”

</title><pros>Pros – H. Bloom is a great opportunity for someone who thrives in a fast paced environment.  The company is growing daily and senior management is devoted to getting feedback from all of the employees. There is also an abundance of opportunities for you to grow your career and create new positions.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Like with any fast growing and young company, employees are pulled in many directions and could benefit from a bit more structure.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – As H. Bloom continues to grow, management should  place a greater emphasis on developing the culture and having a more structured HR division. Management should also think about outlining a formal stock option policy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Challenging, rewarding, lots of hard work with some fun!”

</title><pros>Pros – - Contributing to building something from the ground up- Something not working well? You have the ability to talk directly with the people who can fix it! Or you can fix it yourself!- Young, ambitious work force creates a fun work environment- Flowers are fun & pretty to work with!- Accessible upper management- Plenty of room for growth, both for the individual employees as well as in the industry in general</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Start up environment = lots of work & long hrs sometimes! Whatever it takes to get the job done & done well, which is not for everyone.- Could be frustrating working with a start up where everything is new & policies/procedures are either not set or not smooth, but that's more the nature of a start-up than H.Bloom-specific- No set career paths. As the company grows, opportunities are needed & therefore made. Not ideal for the person that needs a path set out before joining!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good experience, exciting company”

</title><pros>Pros – Great experience. The Account Executive position is H.Bloom is truly unique. Most larger companies divide this role into three separate positions: lead development, account executive, and account management. It's great to have the experience of all three positions.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low base salary, can be stressful trying to find the balance between account management and sales.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – In general, a great job. It can be a bit awkward bring multiple people to a meeting so I would reconsider making it mandatory to bring sales managers to meetings. Particularly for those who have been with the company for a while. Additionally, I would recommend a dress code. Casual dress is fine, but it is important to dress appropriately for meetings to accurately represent the brand.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Most Rewarding Work Experience of My Life”

</title><pros>Pros – Its challenging everyday and you get to see true growth happen in real time.  I prefer to be at work, making progress, and getting inspired, versus doing anything else.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes there aren't enough resources to do everything you want to do and when you are used to things happening so rapidly, you can grow to be impatient.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast-Growing with New Opps All the Time”

</title><pros>Pros – As a part of this team, I can say I'm truly proud of what we've built, and what we're building: A fast-growing company, a portfolio of happy customers, big and small, and real career and growth opportunities for me and my amazing colleagues. To boot, everyone here is good people; I like the people I work with, across departments, seniority levels, and geographic locations.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Growing pains: We've expanded so fast, some balls are bound to get dropped. In the sometime-absence of clear processes and precedents, I've known everyone here to do the right thing and keep customers happy as best they can, so mostly, slip-ups haven't had effects that are too far-reaching.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Over-communicate and stay transparent about our successes, failures, goals and direction.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Never thought I would sell flowers to Moving across the country to sell flowers :)”

</title><pros>Pros – The company doesn't necessary search for the person with the most experience for each job opportunity. A main factor that has build the amazing culture that is H.Bloom, is the type of people they hire. They look for positive, outgoing, driven individuals that want to be a part of something big and will bring something new to the table. I have never worked with more inspiring people and I never look at a day in the office as "a day in the office." You don't find that everywhere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Communication/PR. Though the company uses several outlets to communicate across markets, there needs to be more strategic ways for each market to know how every other market is doing--All their clients, all their huge trials/closed deals. Also, I think we need to reach out to more high-level PR avenues. Especially when opening new markets--we should be EVERYWHERE! No head should turn without knowing the "H.Bloom" name.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – With any start-up, things are moving a million miles per hour and sometimes there is a lack of communication between upper and middle management. As much as the company tries to encourage open communication, I think middle managers should be more involved/aware in decisions/processes since they will be the ones mostly involved on a day-to-day basis.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Supportive start-up environment with impressive growth opportunities for employees”

</title><pros>Pros – H.Bloom is growing very quickly, and there is a feeling that everyone is together on the journey to build something great. Everyone works very hard, and it's clear that the founders and employees have a real passion for the business. I'm continually impressed by my coworkers and really enjoy learning from them.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours are long, and the nature of the industry requires some staff to be available nearly 24/7.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take the time to help new employees get acquainted with the company and staff so they will feel like integral members of the team from the beginning.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This is a great company to be apart of, the people here are awesome and we are all working together!”

</title><pros>Pros – Room for growth, fun place to work everyday, people are awesome, management is driven to reach and exceed our goals</pros>
<cons>Cons – We work long days at H.BLOOM trying to achieve our goals, there is always work to do, crowded workplace</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to invest in SEEDS and successful, experienced account executives, offer free trials to any consumer sub or corporate account</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great opportunity for growth with a great company that has a unique business plan.”

</title><pros>Pros – Start-up company with a great concept and business plan. The culture of this company is awesome- the people are all very nice, yet driven and motivated to succeed.Completely different than any other company in the market so we set ourselves apart from out competition. Great sales experience for anyone who has never done sales before. Teaches you how to build a steady pipeline of business and strive to do more and more each day. Flexible schedule and vacation are great for me and allow me to have a good work/life balance.They also have amazing opportunities for growth within the company. I want to get into management at a young age and H.BLOOM  promotes growth from within.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No Brand Recognition yet so closing deals is somewhat difficult. Any start up company will have that.Base salary is very low- but if your good at selling you can make some good money for being young</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give employees more sales training and product knowledge- would be helpful to know something about flowers.Hire more designers. Difficult to find time to work with designers on ideas for clients.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A hands-on experience into the world of start-ups.”

</title><pros>Pros – The company is growing quickly which provides excellent potential to excel personally. Being part of such a young start-up is an incredible learning experience. The executives are really receptive to employee feedback...And of course you're around flowers all day, so it can't possibly be that bad.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working for such a young start up is really rewarding but it does require you to be flexible and fill in where help is needed, which can sometimes take away from your "actual responsibilities". But then again, this aspect while at times an inconvenience is really great for helping to understand the intricacies of making the company run smoothly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – As the company continues to grow it is going to take more and more effort to have all of the offices outside of NY feel the energy and the sense of unity currently associated with H. Bloom. The execs are currently doing it, but keeping up the constant communication with individual offices really helps infuse the company culture and serves as extra motivation to AEs.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Extremely innovative company that encourages creativity and entrepreneurship.”

</title><pros>Pros – H.BLOOM is truly a team of amazing people.  Not only do I really enjoy the people I work with, I also am a flower enthusiast who can say 100% genuinely that H.BLOOM's flower arrangements are stunning.  The quality control, the attention to detail, and the talent of the designers and the buyers is absolutely astonishing.  It is a lot easier to sell a product that you whole-heartedly believe in, and H.BLOOM always stands behind its product.  Customer service is top-notch.  If a customer is ever unhappy, almost every time the flowers will be replaced or fixed.  That level of integrity makes me proud to work for H.BLOOM.  People here really care about what they do, take pride in their work, and want the best for the company.  As a creative person with a strong entrepreneurial nature, I feel like I found a really exciting opportunity at H.BLOOM and am looking forward to growing with the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is a young startup, so all of the kinks have yet to be worked out.  That's not always a bad thing, because it forces you to problem solve and navigate through difficult challenges - building character and making you stronger, and smarter.  It can, however, be frustrating for highly ambitious people who want to be more successful than barriers in the system sometimes allow.  I am confident, though, that as H.BLOOM grows, progress will be made, challenges will be overcome, and the system will sail much more smoothly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work!  I hope you continue to focus on what you believe will make H.BLOOM wildly successful and what will make H.BLOOM an exciting and rewarding place to work.  Happy flowers need happy people behind the scenes making it happen!  I know that company culture is a top priority of H.BLOOM and I hope it stays that way as the company grows.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Once in a lifetime opportunity to help build a national brand”

</title><pros>Pros – -Surrounded by smart, talented, hard-working people-Gain first hand experience on how to build a company-Selling a product and service that you can be proud of-Working as a team to accomplish things that have never been done before within the industry</pros>
<cons>Cons – -No personal space (something you'll always sacrifice at a start-up)-Communication tends to lag behind when growth is so rapid</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – -Try and stay grounded to the actual core, day to day of the business as much as possible.  Decisions on talent, brand, and customer service will benefit as a result.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>