<name>e-Solutions Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/e-Solutions-Reviews-E425440.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-07-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Recruiter (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E-solutions Review”

</title><pros>Pros – good place to develop your skills in recruitments. good leaders who have good experience of the recruitment business.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Rarely though but, work pressure may be a concern.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They listen to the each employee. so no thoughts crumbling in mind, just go ahead and speak.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Totally unproffesional company”

</title><pros>Pros – No Pros and i dont think there can be a one.They dont have thinking power to think in correct direction.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They will kepp you working and fire you just on the call without notice.Salary is diffrent then what they offered you.They will force you to work more then 11 hours in a day if you refuse you lost the job.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employees are also human beings dont use and through them away.They are working for you think once before holding there salary without any reason.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Writer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Company to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – none, but they must get more clients</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Recruiter (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Totally pathetic company can't refer it even to my enemy”

</title><pros>Pros – Good HR team, smart enough to befool a person about job salary and work culture.Good management who saves money by not paying salary of the employees and to make them work for free.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unproffiesional company doesn't have cordination between HR and upper management.HR completed your joining formality but after 15 days management refused your employment.Even they make your official mail id they gave you ID card even then.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't let anyone leave his job if can't povide him beter oppurtunity.Train your HR people that hom much a job is important for a person stop playing with that by giving him an offer and orce to resign and when he joined you after 10 days tell them he is not an employee of this company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Resource Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My first job as a business resource analyst in IT recruitment field.”

</title><pros>Pros – growth and incentive are very good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is US staffing so working in night .</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – no comments.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>