<name>RNP Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/RNP-Reviews-E426015.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Environment for learning and professional development.”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity to develop and implement new management and business models since it is a fairly new organization trying to respond to their rapid growth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Rigid structure and very slow decision making process.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It is necessary to communicate better the company´s strategy , set clear goals and manage performance and results. It is also necessary to empower middle management giving more autonomy to act.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Material Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to show your idea knowledge and skills”

</title><pros>Pros – The Team and nature of work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation benefits and allowance given</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more benefits to satisfy employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Your cheese is always in movement”

</title><pros>Pros – - Great environment to work;- Good opportunities to self and formal development;</pros>
<cons>Cons – - although RNP is a great company to work, it is necessary to analyse in which organizational area you are going to work. You can work in heaven or in hell.- low maturity level</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-22</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible Innovation Advanced Technology Network Research Education</pros>
<cons>Cons – Career path under construction Weak matrix structure</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent team! Great environment. Great team work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is nothing that I can say, as I had an excellent opportunity.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the excellent work!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>