<name>Stereo D Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Stereo-D-Reviews-E428913.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Depth Artist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Roto is not the most fun, but if you need work, this is the place to go.”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of people work there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours and sometimes no paid overtinme.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Like beating a dead horse”

</title><pros>Pros – If you want feature films on your resume</pros>
<cons>Cons – Where to start... this is one of the worst studios I've ever worked at. The company treats their employees like slaves. You're just a number to them. With an impossible to reach quota that's never ending. Quota is everything to them. Even if there's no way to reach it. Mass layoffs are the norm around here. If you're not working crazy over time, be afraid that you're going to be laid off. They will clean house without any notice. They will start with temp artists because that's easiest. It's too much hassle for them to ask the leads who are good and bad artists. If you're "lucky" enough to be around when it hits 40hrs a week, you won't be happy for too long since they don't pay you enough to survive on 40hrs. Raises pretty much don't exist. They will also claim to give performance based reviews and the leads will even rate all their artists based on guidelines that are set up to make sure the artist is average and therefore no raise. Then they'll proceed with giving the studio a blanket percentage raise that will amount to pocket change. Or it just won't happen at all. If you end up working there just remember, there is no reward for going over quota. Just stop and save it for the following week. Because you're no better than the artist who doesn't show up for work or ever hit quota.I say it's like beating a dead horse because Stereo D will never say no to work, even if they are already over booked. Weeks averaging 80-100hrs a week are normal. Upper management will force you to work 12+ hrs a day while they going home at 6pm every night. When holidays come and they have to give it off to us or face paying double time, you'll have to make up those hours since they didn't account for holidays in their calculations for quota. They will burn you out repeatedly and then wonder why so many people are calling in sick or just not showing up at all. The studio is like a bunch of dead zombies somehow working to put shots together. Even though most movies need at the very least 6 months. We do the vast majority of a movie in about 2-4 weeks. The quality is crap and they're just praying the client can't see stereo. Most artists have to work 12+hrs a day, 4-6 months at a time with no days off. Kiss your social life goodbye and for that fact, say goodbye to your spouse, children, family, friends and soul. You'll never see them.HR is not there to support the artists. They are there to support upper management. We went through 4 HR people in 2yrs. Some left because they realized they couldn't help the artists and even one got let go for promising temps that they would be full time after a certain amount of time. If you do decide to work there, get everything in writing, because they will lie to your face. Know your rights, they will take advantage of you.A lot of the work falls onto the leads and the senior artists. The supervisors and stereographers are so far removed from reality of what's happening on the floor. They will yell at you for not getting shots into dailies and then proceed to note the hell out of the shots that are in dailies. They will only approve shots on fri/sat, because they have to hit quota for the week. Mon-thurs, be prepared to have your shot noted over and over again. Then come friday they will approve a weeks worth of quota and that will consist of pretty much anything that is in 3D regardless of the quality. Their head of stereography who has "final" say on everything before it goes to the client is a psychopath. Everyone who is below him is deathly afraid of him. He could snap on you at any moment, even if you did exactly what he told you to do. "Party in the front" will become a phrase that will haunt you for the rest of your life. He doesn't care what stereo direction is given from the client/director. He only cares about his stereo vision. He will unapprove shots that are finaled and make you start over from the beginning and then preach about how you shouldn't crap on the pipeline. He believes he runs the company and can do whatever he wants. Many good artists have left because of him. Even worse is that upper management and HR knows this and does nothing. Most of the sups and stereographers have gotten to where they are by being friends with the right person or by kissing ass. They are not supportive and will constantly contradict themselves with their notes. There are but a few good sups there who will try to fight the never ending battle of artist abuse. But they are mostly silenced by upper management. Anyone who has been there longer than a week can see that the company is run ass backwards. It's so blatantly obvious.  Whatever is logical, they'll go in the opposite direction. Burning out artists is so unproductive. You're pretty much just throwing money down the drain at that point.As other people have said, please only work here if you absolutely need money or you just want to add some resume fillers. Make it a transition between jobs and not something permanent.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I know for a fact they've seen these reviews and laughed. They don't care. They'll never change.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Roto-Artist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Long hours”

</title><pros>Pros – People are nice. Provide dinner once in a while</pros>
<cons>Cons – Expected to work 7 days a week, 10-12 hours a day.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Stereo Conversion Artist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Recommended for Experience Only”

</title><pros>Pros – Working on Hollywood filmsGain knowledge on the industryAmong creative individuals</pros>
<cons>Cons – Extensive Over-TimeNo room for growthLack of communicationDemand vs Pay</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There need to be better negotiations between the studios to prevent so many extensive days and weeks.  We shouldn't be working over-time to make ends meet.  Hold more social gatherings to show appreciation for your employees or teams, the ones who do a good deal of heavy lifting to satisfy the customer needs.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Professional Artist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience with a 3D vfx house.”

</title><pros>Pros – Stereo D has a knack for creating top notch post vfx for major motion pictures.   The tools they use in implementing such great visuals is state of the art.  Everyone that works there is extremely talented and hard working.   The contracts Stereo D gets are huge in popularity.   And the work-load is quite satisfying.   Unlike other animation and vfx houses,  Stereo D is very good at paying their overtime to the artists who work on their projects.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Every studio in Hollywood, including the big deal makers,  has their share of challenges, issues and problems.    The trick is, when working for any studio in Hollywood or elsewhere, is to work hard,  do your best and try to get along with everyone.    Stereo D is no exception.    There is no happy studio to work at,  a talented Disney artist once told me.   So if a relationship at Stereo D or any other studio in Los Angeles doesn't work out than maybe it's time to move on.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Talented artists and technicians are people too.   They are the backbone of any project.   Perhaps a little more compassion for individuals who do their all is required.   Poor management has always been the detriment of companies.   Crash and burn is for studios is never good.   Nor is being a flash in the pan.    Good solid people skills is what keeps a good company or Hollywood studio alive and thriving.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great artists and cool projects, but extremely unstable”

</title><pros>Pros – High profile projects, great co-workers/mid-level management.  Also the work can be challenging and entertaining</pros>
<cons>Cons – pay, hours and the general feeling that at any point and time that you could be laid off.  It is not uncommon to come in and hear about large layoffs.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – communicate better with your artists, rumors should not be the only source of information that workers have.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Depth Artist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poorly Managed Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Coworkers, your fellow artists will carry you through all the high stress seasons.  You will find that your motivation comes from your fellow artists and not the upper management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As Stereo D would say, "The long hours supplement the low pay" which is a $20.63 average according to Glassdoor.  The problem with that model is, the long hours kill our motivation due to a decline in health and when we return to 40 hour weeks we are demotivated due to not being able to earn a decent paycheck to maintain our and our dependents' lifestyle.Absolutely no loyalty to employees, even senior staff members.  Bad news can come at any time to anyone without a single shred of warning.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – In Regards to pay and hours, your current model is like a teeter totter. Whether it's long hours to supplement the low pay or 40hr weeks to rest, people are unhappy and demotivated.  The best solution is to increase pay slightly (atleast get an average of $25/hr) and maintain a solid 50hr weeks.  It is a perfect balance of life and work and your employees would not be tired all the time, they'd be awake and focused, healthy, and happy.Making your employees feel respected goes a long way towards creating a great company that produces the best quality stereo in the industry which is the motto of Stereo D.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Depth Artist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a Loyal Company”

</title><pros>Pros – High probability that you will meet some very talented artists here, and also make some great friends. They will help you through your hellish slog at Stereo D/be your best drinking buddies/your shoulder to cry on should you be desperate enough to seek a job there. For this reason, I was tempted to give Stereo D 2 stars instead of 1, but then realized that they have nothing to do with the quality of artists there, and are just lucky that the industry is as slow as it is right now, which makes them look *shudder* desireable...</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pretty much every negative thing that has been said about Stereo D so far is absolutely true. This is about as bad as it gets, and they are -willingly- setting an extremely bad example for the ever-crumbling VFX industry. You will miss your social life, your family, your friends (outside of the studio), and your soul. Management here is extremely close-door'd and wishy-washy with their words. You can't believe anything they say for even a second. The rumors that go around the studio amongst the artists and leads are the most reliable source of information you will have; whether it's a rumor that layoffs are coming, or a new movie is coming in, or that the studio didn't get a movie they thought they were going to get, etc.Stereo D does not treat its employees like humans. They will straight up lie to your face to get you working for them. They entice potential employees by promising a Full-Time Evaluation once you've worked for them for 6 months. This rarely ever happens, so -do not- count on it. No matter how many long hours you put in for them, or how many shots and frames you make past your quota, Stereo D does not want to pay for employee health benefits, and this is made very clear as they will lay you off weeks or days before your evaluation, and will lie to you about their reason for the layoff. Sometimes they will even stretch the timeframe to 7 or 8 months before they even consider making you Full-Time. They have even been known to hire groups of people with the intention of firing them when a certain movie is finished, without even telling said group that this is their intention. Rarely will you ever get notice ahead of time that you will be laid off, so always have your demo reel and resume up to date.If you must seek employment here, view it merely as a temporary stepping stone on the way to your career. Stereo D is limbo for lost souls, (picture the scene from Beetlejuice), and you will not advance or improve your career by working here at all.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do not force employees to work past 8 hours. Nothing, and I mean -nothing- ever gets done after dinner time. By then, everyone's ready to go home and just mentally check out until it's time to clock-out. This is a huge waste of employees' time, and the company's money. What needs to be done is cut hours down to 8-9 hours per day, increase artists' wages, and offer health benefits. This will immensely increase company-wide morale, which will greatly increase productivity, as artists will actually have an -incentive- to work; the amazing ability to actually go home and enjoy life. The increased pay will merely compensate for the lack of over time and double time. The health benefits will let employees know that the company actually cares, and will treat artists like humans for once. Finally, enough with the pathetic, passive-agressive, kindergarten-grade floor meetings where you tell artists that they're doing a good job but need to work harder and focus more, and that this is the final stretch of the never-ending crunch. We know you're lying, and it's extremely demotivating and insulting.This is how you run a company, Deluxe. I'm sure you don't care enough to read these reviews, but if you do, please take notes, because you obviously have no clue what you're doing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>5</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A new standard for sweatshops”

</title><pros>Pros – Resume filler; long hours = tons of double time payFor the most part, the crew you will work with is dynamic and fun.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Resume filler; long hours = tons of double time pay (The pro IS the con...).During my time here, I have worked on 11 feature films under 7 months (all that work is exclusive to the "D"). Understand what this mean... Most other studios, you will typically work on 2, maybe 3 shows throughout the year.First starting out, yes the money will seem great, that is only because you will have logged 90 hours a week for 6+ months non-stop. Crunch here is the norm.If you have a family or a significant other, Stereo D will no doubt test your relationship.There is no loyalty. You will constantly be reminded of just that...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No point. In their reality, everyone is expendable, no matter what you think. You can count on getting paid the time you work. For everything else, you will coincidently be laid-off the second you push for more.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-14</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>6</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Please, Do not work for Stereo D”

</title><pros>Pros – Yes, there were some Pros. The Co-Workers, who are all seemingly trapped in the same situation, are some of the finest Artists I've worked with. The Mid-Level Management also do their best with a really bad situation. The Production staff, as well, do their best to try and make a bad situation bearable</pros>
<cons>Cons – Were do you begin to list the Cons. From the very beginning, the job you walk into doesn't begin to resemble the job described going in. You are given a one week training course, and then you are placed on the floor, expected to know everything, with little to no support, in some cases. The schedule you are expected to work is completely different than the schedule they tell you about up front, and be prepared to be expected to work 7 days a week, 12 to 18 hours a day, for months at a time. You will be given impossible to reach daily and weekly shot quotas, and depending on your Lead, you may, or may not be allowed to leave, regardless of how long you have been working that day. Stereo D operates in a permanent "Crunch Mode" which means there is no let up in the stress levels, expected/demanded/mandatory work hours, near endless sleep deprivation, and the resultant extremely low moral. Add to that, some of the most Demotivational Floor Meetings, where members of the Upper Management seem shocked and dismayed that news of extended hours, on top of the already onerous schedule, isn't greeted with clapping and cheers.To put it bluntly, Stereo D is run like a Sweatshop. You have to understand that.If you have Family, or other close relationships, be prepared to watch them suffer, as you will have little or no time to attend to them. If you have children, and/or a spouse, really ask yourself, are you prepared to be away from them for months at a time, outside of the few hours you have to sleep when you get home, before you have to return to work? There are NO guaranteed days off, even on the weekends, and even when they do tell you that you "might" have a Sunday or Saturday off, be prepared to have that change at a moments notice, sometimes at 1 or 2 in the morning, the day of your alleged day off. Not that the the cancelled day off will be rescheduled, it will likely just be cancelled, regardless of any plans you may have made.Ask yourself, will your spouse, or your child be satisfied with that? Will they be satisfied with you being, for the most part, a non-participant in their lives? Will they understand that once you go to work for Stereo D, for all extents and purposes, your life, with the exception of the few short hours you'll have to sleep, belongs to Stereo D?Will you?Now, if none of the above matters, and you do decide to pursue the opportunity with Stereo D, do yourself a favor, ask for everything the recruiter or hiring person promises you in writing, and make certain it is signed off, officially, by HR, this includes scheduling, post first 90 days benefits, etc. If they promise you 6 days a week, 12 hours a day, insist that it be put officially in writing, with you In and Out time clearly stipulated, and be prepared to stand your ground. Same thing with promises of staff positions after 90 days, or medical benefits. If it's not in writing, do not expect any of the promises to be upheld by any of the Upper Management.Another suggestion, for the sake of your own sanity, insist that you be given a 2 week "Trial Period" with the Lead you are assigned to, with an option to be re-assigned to another Lead upon request. Get that in writing also!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I'm under no delusion that Upper Management will take anyone's suggestion, so rather than a suggestion, I will present this as a plea. Please, stop treating your workers like slaves, or worse, cattle. You have fine people working for you, and you are, in short, killing them. Is that the reputation you want Stereo D to have within the VFX Community?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Long Hours, Low Pay, Complete lack of humanity”

</title><pros>Pros – Most of the artist, production staff, and producers are friendly</pros>
<cons>Cons – the upper management makes it clear that they do not care about the artist or production staff. 16-18 hour days are common. they give you an impossible goal to reach each week, and once you work 70 hours straight to reach it, they tell you its time to start all over again. expect to get no sleep, lose most of your close relationships, and feel sick, tired and hopeless 24/7</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – remember that us employees are actually people, not caddle. getting to see your wife, kids, friends, etc... once in awhile would probably be nice. Don't hire everyone and then fire them in bulk 6 months later.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“StereoD don't care about their staff”

</title><pros>Pros – + Nice to get facetime with higher ups on rare occasions+ 1 hour lunch break located in the Yahoo building with a cafeteria+ Producers are very easy to work with and friendly+ Up and coming proprietary software+ Excellent client theaters and review theaters</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Long hours, once worked 100+ hours in a week- Constant desk moving- Executives treat production staff people poorly while giving artists and upper management priority- 90+ days before receiving benefit, have to get recommended to receive it- Morale is low because of high stress and quotas- Very difficult to move up, likely to higher you one position lower than your current status</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't higher qualified people to work in lower titles. Higher people that are qualified for their position. Asking people to take position lower than their previous title is demoralizing and moral kill.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Better than Bakersfield, but no dream job”

</title><pros>Pros – Pros are simply my fellow artists. The artists are very understanding to each other and are very willing to help out one another. They have plenty of work. So, you pretty much have job security as long as you perform well.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Let me take a minute just tell you the interview process as it was. Just getting in was an uphill battle. When I first was called, they called me at a random time, like 3pm. Not a problem. I call back the next day and I hear nothing for two days. Then they call me back at 6:45pm. So, I call back the next day. Nothing for a day or two. Then I call back and finally get the recruiter. He sets me up for the interview and is to email me an application and all sorts of goodies before I come through. Doesn't happen. So, upon my interview, I don't have any of the documentation that they wanted to see. No biggie. A week later, I call back just to follow-up and they want me to start. This time the recruiter emails me while I am on the phone and waits it out until I receive it. Good job on that one. Upon my training day, in conversation with other new artists, I find out they had similar issues. It just wasn't organized.The training was very thorough, I will say. Now, you have just one week of training and if you do well on that Wednesday, you are job specific. If you do just okay that Wednesday and do good on that Friday, then you are less specific and actually get to do more as an artist. As stressful as it was, I really enjoyed training. I liked it a lot. You will get an email on that Saturday after training to let you know if you report to work Monday or not.Let's talk about their shot system. In most feature films, you have several shots that are shot from the same angle, and this can possibly help you when cleaning up your shot. You are only allowed access to the shots assigned to you from the main shot que. So, unless the a helpful shot has been dailied, you have to backtrack and pull in random shots into Nuke to see if this will be useful to you. Usually, it just becomes a waste of time and you need to just do what you need to just to clean it up. But when a production wants something pixel perfect, it really could come down to using one of those shots. Sometimes, they say there is a matching shot and link it for you, but I have only seen it once.The hours are insane. Being fresh out of college or something or if you are completely new to the industry, it is not a bad gig for you. You will learn a lot in a short time and have to use it to it's fullest. Many times the hours are not just 89 hours, but 7 days a week. One can only do that for so long without being totally burned out. Also, the tasks are fast and furious. In other productions, you may have to get 1600 shots out in 3 months. Here, you may have to push that in 3 weeks. The hours would not be so bad if you knew for sure you had at least one day off a week to just sleep or decompress or whatnot. Most of my fellow artists work until roughly midnight to 3am (with the occasional go getter working til 4am) and coming in between 9 and 10 in the morning. It doesn't sound so bad until you have to live it. I had an artist tell me one day, "You just get used to being tired." Working past 11 hours, really isn't efficient and if you are doing that 7 days a week for a month, it is definitely not productive.The Management: Actually, the managers for the most part leave you alone. They let you do your work and check in occasionally. The biggest issue is really, the weakly demotivational meetings. Once a week or so, you will get a meeting and they tell you what a great job you are doing. Although, sometimes, this is followed up with a reward, it is usually followed up with bad news like you are working 7 days a week for the next 2 weeks or working til 12am or longer every night this week. Usually, these meetings tell you that you need to stay focused and work harder. I have never heard those phrases so many times in my life in one company. There are some leads like the trainers that I see at their desk working consistantly while also reviewing shots. The other leads? I have no idea what they do.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – My advice to management is to simple look and listen to your artists. Yes, they can get the work done in the time frames you have pushed them into, but it should not be standard. It should be an occasional thing. I stand by the founders of the company to the technological marvels that is stereo conversion, but I believe they are either blind or do not want to see the struggles that the artists go through to make this magic happen. This is a great company as far as what it does and what the world sees. It's the little people that are definitely forgotten in the process.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stressful”

</title><pros>Pros – Great group of artists,Good perks in the cafeteria/lunchroom</pros>
<cons>Cons – Incredibly stressfulRelatively low payUnlikely to have any permanent positionsIncredibly long hoursMore concerned about getting it done than getting it done right.Upper management is either unaware or unconcerned with widespread low morale among a majority of its artists.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Instead of going full steam and burning out artists why not decide to maybe take on one or two less movies a year so that the artists can actually live happier lives outside of the office, additionally this will make all the shots improve and the efficiency and morale improve.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good people, poor time management, and management is wishy washy.”

</title><pros>Pros – work is easy, coworkers are nice and work hard for the most part.</pros>
<cons>Cons – pay is very low, supervisors are generally good, but the ceo/cfos type people aren't very supportive.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – to keep your employees, try to pay them what they deserve and don't treat them so much like cattle.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Digital Depth Artist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exciting and rewarding,....but challenging.”

</title><pros>Pros – The studio thus far has been able to garner very talented and popular directors for 3D conversion.  With studios like Digital Domain and others going out of business it's good to be working at a studio that get's work.   And the work can be top rate if not better.   The people are fun to work with as well.  Quite a talented bunch of individuals.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is a bit low.   Unfortunately though VFX studios have had to  bid low in order to survive and not have to file for bankruptcy or loose the contracts.   So the work suffers a bit in order reach timelines and crunch periods.    Management's use of fear tactics based on performance reviews is a bit too aggressive,...but that's the film industry for you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – A little bit more breathing room for the artists.   A little less on the fear tactics.   Companies crumble that continually use fear tactics on their employees.   (Ex.  Digital Domain).   Follow Pixar's example of good management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Soul Crushing”

</title><pros>Pros – 401k, Health & dental plansStaff Positions for lengthy periods for top workersExtremely talented  artists work hereFreedom to customize your desk within reasonA good place to get a wage while looking for other work in the area.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low WagesYearly evaluations that equal a set raise across the board no matter your evaluation score.A lot of work being outsourced.Low Morale between all employeesCutting back hours by over 33%Lots of firings, I've seen this company on multiple occasions take 30 artists into a room and fire them all at once.Frivolous spending, while refusing to raise dismal payrates.You can't get any work that you've done for a demo reel, not even Alpha Mattes for roto artists</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop outsourcing every bit of work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“disorganized”

</title><pros>Pros – Yahoo did a great job with the campus!</pros>
<cons>Cons – impossible to tell who to trust</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Put good people in management roles, train them, then listen to them!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Depth Artist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Everything Changed when got acquired by Deluxe”

</title><pros>Pros – Great for entry level, get your feet in the door of the industry</pros>
<cons>Cons – Over worked, under paid, dont expect raises, if the stereographer doesn't like you your done in the company, Deluxe overrules any company decision, if you are roto department you are just fixing outsource material, paint takes all the budget, sometimes you have to work for 21 consecutive days, Non of the work you do can be used for Demo Reel, ever, so your improvement in career is in halt, and doing stereo conversion doesn't help you get a job unless</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There is no point since they don't listen.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to get some experience in the industry,but beware of unexpected layoffs”

</title><pros>Pros – Big name titles that look great on resumes, learn the some of best tactics in the industry in the realm of stereoscopics.can have a great work environment in this place. 401k. A great place to start off your CG career,can learn much from this experience.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The downsizing that occurs after projects are completed with no warning.Supervisors and leads often dont agree to certain workflows or situations,which can become an unnecessary headache.can have a tendency to not do 6month performance and compensation reviews,went almost a year without one.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – value your artists and their time,on and off of work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Pipeline TD (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very challenging, but certainly rewarding”

</title><pros>Pros – Great employeesHigh profile projectsHuge desksExcellent development team</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours can be tough, and artists aren't always treated respect but I say if you can't stand the heat... get out of the oven. There's people who would gladly take these jobs and it's not to difficult to train or find qualified workers for the nature of this work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Negotiate better credit deals. I know to not be credited in this industry is common, but it would help morale.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Depth Artist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Some good people work there. State of the art equipment, HORRIBLE management!”

</title><pros>Pros – A good place to start your career journey (if you know when to stop).great technology and office space.There are great artists (and many) working there, so you may find your new family members there (since you never go home).</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible management! Constant rush time that translates into 80- 90 hrs weeks almost constantly.Long time workers are in a terrible psychological state and they don't even know it.Some senior management and Executives have ZERO people skills</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get a clue on how to treat your people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>