<name>M. Price Distributing Company Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/M-Price-Distributing-Company-Reviews-E430664.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-01-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people and work environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – This family owed business treats their employees just like that....part of the family.  Everyone is so friendly here and I have never worked at a place that everyone gets along so well on a business level.  The owners and management are not afraid to get in there and work right along with you to get the job done.  It is definitely a fun place to work because of the people.  That's what keeps me around.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working holidays but you get used to it.  Plus everyone pitches in to help each other and if possible you can get off early to enjoy the holiday too.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Should be a great place, but isn't.”

</title><pros>Pros – The time until you are allowed to be on the company insurance is short. Sometimes you get a task that takes you out of the building. Occasional beer and wing get togethers every month or two.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company president can be pretty cool to hang out with in an afterwork party, but I've witnessed what was mentioned about her taking things out on some employees. I've never seen anyone get so close to someone's face and just start screaming at them without the police coming in to break it up. Some people treat it like a rite of passage, but it's simple assault as far as what I saw. It could be an order mix-up, or something you really didn't do, and when she's done screaming at you, and finds out that you didn't cause the problem.... no apology from her. After the second time I saw that, I started looking around for a new job. I didn't want to be a part of that.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I don't know what anyone can do when the problem is at the very top.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't work in the warehouse”

</title><pros>Pros – Good insurance. Beer and wing parties every few weeks. Sometimes pizza. Get a case of beer free every once in a while.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is low for the work you're doing. Management will not listen to you if you have a problem. Company President is often hostile and takes things out on workers. If someone stole something and they can't figure out who, they'll fire everyone and start over. They use Chinese overtime where they pay you a decreasing rate every hour past 40. No matter the workload. Is this legal? They also tried bringing in Guatemalans to work in the warehouse, but they couldn't handle it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I never felt like I was a part of the company. Management needs to listen to the employees. Instead the communication is always one way... or the highway. I don't know who gave good reviews to this place but they sure didn't work in the warehouse.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Place to Work”

</title><pros>Pros – This company has been around for a really long time - almost 80 years.  Stability.  One of the few industries that isn't hugely affected by global economic instability.  Great insurance coverage and the company pays a huge portion.  Family business with owners that are present and involved.  Open door policy with all senior management.  Employee pizza/cornhole parties regularly.  Random giveaways of beer, SWAG, etc...</pros>
<cons>Cons – Seasonal business.  Gets extremely busy in summer.  Beer industry doesn't close down on many holidays.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No company culture. Family-owned business and you're frequently reminded of that.”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a job. Sometimes they'll give you an occassional free case of beer, but it's usually close-dated product. Some of the front office staff are friendly. Generally good environment for salesmen. Health insurance coverage isn't bad.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Family owned business. Very poor communication, especially coming from upper (sales and admin) management and/or family members. No responsibility taken at the highest levels when things go wrong, instead witch hunts often occur. Difficult to get problems resolved; instead, the person bring up the problem is often treated as the problem. Workers who are not in positions of directly selling product (office clerks, warehouse), are often mistreated and considered disposable. Very low reimbusement rates for mileage, and no insurance for those using their own vehicles to do company business.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The company should stop looking at justifying what they do by looking at other beer wholesalers. Their houses are just as bad. Instead, take a hard look at the processes outside that line of business if they wish to clean things up. Give credit where it should be due, and, family members: try going directly to the employee you wish to task once in a while instead of trusting that word will get there through a supervisor. Most side projects, which have little to do with a worker's main responsibilities, will rob the company's productivity and hurt morale.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>