<name>E-TechServices Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/E-TechServices-Reviews-E432257.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Little personal, financial, and career opportunity or growth beyond basic entry-level experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Good for entry-level sales or technical job-seekers.If hardworking and loyal, they'll be pretty flexible about hours and working remotely.Small company that offers extensive interaction with upper management.You'll learn a lot about computer hardware and software salesAll employees are family-orientedWork ceases after working hours for most employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – They simply don't make enough profit to pay people correctly or offer substantial wages. They've downsized a lot in the past few years.Upper management isn't flexible in regards to new ideas or different approaches to how projects are managed.The tendency of upper management to micromanage has proven to be counterproductive.The inability of management to acknowledge their own intellectual limitations and shortcomings in a productive and mature manner.Management is composed of personal relationships that span decades and sometimes they forget that not all employees share this and therefore are not willing to tolerate personal habits and tendencies that have been tolerated in the past.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat your employees like adults and recognize that while you do have many years of experience, they may be able to contribute innovative ideas. Micromanaging to the point of inefficiency is counter productive and a waste of time. Don't fix things that aren't broken; do fix things that are glaringly broken.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“e-TechServices”

</title><pros>Pros – If you are looking for an entry level technical or sales position, this is the place. The salary is for a new person to the industry. You will learn computer hardware sales and pre-sales. Do not expect to be paid industry standards for an IBM reseller.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The training plan will sound good, but the reality is in 90 days you have to start selling on quota. The commission will always be "up to x% of Gross Margin". This really means zero until you have generated over $300,000 in margin.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat your employees like you want to be treated. They deserve respect and positive words. Do not through temper tantrums when you do not get your own way. Be a professional.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>