<name>ROCHE PALO ALTO Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/ROCHE-PALO-ALTO-Reviews-E432148.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-08-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Roche is better than most other biotech companies.”

</title><pros>Pros – A good place to work</pros>
<cons>Cons – They closed the site and moved to New Jersey and laid off almost everyone.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Success is built on the backs of the peons, treat them a little better.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate III (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was difficult the last years knowing site was closing and not necessarily knowing your fate.”

</title><pros>Pros – The Campus was fabulous.Their were many resources available to get work / project  done with many areas of expertise.Most folks were more than reasonable to work with.Company seemed to attempt to focus on long term health of company.Benefits were pretty good, though not as good as Syntex.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You felt like a pawn in a big chess game.You could see decisions being made from very high up that made no financial / strategic sense at the local site.No company stock purchase plan.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The squeaky wheel always got oiled - too bad I was the wheel that maintained itself.”

</title><pros>Pros – Reasonable pay. Exercise on-site. Nice environment - places to run and bike right outside work. Good benefits compared to others.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not family-friendly. Your life can be miserable if you get stuck with an incompetent, insecure boss. Educational benefits only available if your boss approves it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get rid of dead weight employees/managers and reward the hard workers who actually make significant positive impacts to the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-10</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dynamic and result oriented”

</title><pros>Pros – My healthy experience and skill</pros>
<cons>Cons – I never worke for paul alto</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be transparent and trust your employee</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Big Pharma - Small Biotech Hybrid Model”

</title><pros>Pros – At its peak time, RPA was one of the best companies in the life science sector in northern california. The culture, the environment, and the management are among the top ranked in the area. Great benefit and career development opportunity.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As a business in pharmaceutical R&D, RPA failed eventually to survive as a result of the parent organization's strategic restructure.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>