<name>ion interactive Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/ion-interactive-Reviews-E435022.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – ion is a progressive work environment, where intelligence, collaboration, and passion for doing good work are highly-valued. The people are sharp, the work is interesting and variable, and the growth opportunities are significant.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work-life balance can be a challenge, however, this is not a company-culture issue by any means, and is more of an individual area of focus. I love my work, so I have to focus on my balance!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Senior management is open and responsive; I don't have any advice to share here that I wouldn't share with them directly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ion is a great company to work for!”

</title><pros>Pros – If you are looking for an energetic, passionate, and positive work environment then this is the place for you! Its three co-founders run the company on a daily basis - they are passionate, hard-working, and honest individuals, and make sure that culture is spread throughout the office. Employees are well taken care of and there is a great work/life balance. The company is continuously growing and with its growth come many opportunities!</pros>
<cons>Cons – My experience so far has been great and do not have any cons.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast growing company with lots of room for growth”

</title><pros>Pros – I am in my 5th year at ion interactive and I have learned so much along the way. ion interactive is an industry leader with some truly amazing innovative thinkers running the show. To be able to learn form and directly work with the Leadership here at ion has been an invaluable experience.While at ion, I have been able to work with customers across the Globe and help them to grow their landing page programs from the ground up. Working in this industry is unique because it is always evolving and changing giving you the opportunity to continue to learn and get creative!ion is full of smart, driven individuals who work really hard to raise the bar in all that they do. This environment makes ion a truly inspiring place to work, learn and grow.</pros>
<cons>Cons – When you work at ion you need to have a lot of self control because they are regularly catering delicious meals and providing a wide variety of snacks!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Glad that's over”

</title><pros>Pros – Cool modern office, catered lunches a couple days out of the week, walk to the beach.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Weak female driven management. Using scare tactics to get work done. Turnover rate was unreal, from the time I started no department remained remotely the same as far as staffing. People drop like flies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Sell the company, retire.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Passionate team of online marketing rock stars!”

</title><pros>Pros – Passionate leaders, awesome product, hardworking people, culture of growth & opportunity, exciting brand & dedicated customers! I have worked for the company for nearly 8 years and have been a part of the company's explosive growth. ion prides itself on its love for what we do and passion for our customer's success (and they've had plenty of it)! The three co-founders are some of the most hardworking, dedicated leaders I have had the opportunity to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some pains associated with growth over the past couple of years, but that is to be expected. Being privately owned, the company is run tightly by management. If you aren't an A+ rock star, you need not apply :)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Team Member (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“weak management”

</title><pros>Pros – ion is located near mizner, the location of the office is nice and there is a lot around the area.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the management is weak, the pay isn't good and it is very clicky. I see people get fired for personal reasons, which puts everyone in the office on edge. We don't want to make the wrong person mad and end up without a job. You can tell all employees are in fear of the unexpected, because management doesn't make anything clear. You never know if one day you will be praised, or the next repremanded.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Praise employees more, and take a closer look at your management team.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>