<name>C-Edge Technologies Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/C-Edge-Technologies-Reviews-E442522.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for fresher”

</title><pros>Pros – Good working experience for a fresher as a lot to learn for a fresher with so many banks. One can gain knowledge in technical and functional of banking.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No distribution of work. Lots of hard work with day and night working.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Systems Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice Environment”

</title><pros>Pros – It gives me great opportunities to work with clients like TCS and SBI. Great hickes and a wonderful team of HRs</pros>
<cons>Cons – follows 31days cycle so delay in salary on Feb month.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Thank you for support</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Need to go long way”

</title><pros>Pros – > Outsourcing biz as learning curve can be build as that is core model o C-Edge.</pros>
<cons>Cons – >Need to get professional culture and focus.>Misnomer like being operating Cloud technologies need to go as it is plain hosting of core banking system for client rather than SaaS based model which has elasticity, rapid management is missing.>Most of the clients are not satisfied with core banking system services. Expect core RRBs client churn are expected.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – >Professional evaluation of some of the key position holders.> Re-Brand and get away from TCS and SBI shadow>Look beyond Core banking and make money from other banking software services as ASP.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My 1st company .Great to work with .A good team and some nice exposure”

</title><pros>Pros – A TCS subsidiary . SO all the values of TCS are inculcated in this company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No Onsite opportunity as all the projects are India Geo-Centric. All projects of Rural Regional Banks and Cooperative Banks so the amount of exposure is low keyed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems SUpport Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exellent”

</title><pros>Pros – HRPolicies, Customer Saticfaction, Quality Managment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Need some Transpirancy with Employee</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – NA</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>