<name>R. Sabee Company Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/R-Sabee-Company-Reviews-E443710.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-03-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Machine Operator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“myexperience at R Sabee has been very up lifting!!”

</title><pros>Pros – the production manager is great!  very understandable when it comes to emergency situations! He takes the time to address your situation and will try to work around that!!  The wage is compatible with everyday living expenses, but I do have to mention that a lot of employees there don't deserve the wage they have because either they r down right LAZY or they know that others will pick up their slack!!!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – I don't have any downsides of working there!! Ppl have to remember that the R.Sabee company is in business to make money and if they don't make money ppl won't have a job !!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upper management must b doing something right, the company's been in business for over 50 years!!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dysfunctional Company”

</title><pros>Pros – This facility is unionized so some of the wrongs that are done by the company are able to be corrected.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management does not reach out for the opinions of employees. Management does not share vital information with employees either. Overall this company has a lot of improvements to make. When they do communicate they lead you to believe that things will change but nothing actually happens. It's a very depressing place to work and the office and production floor have a low morale rate.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – RESPECT your employees. They know they are there and they have a job but where is the Employee Relation? Sometimes a simple gesture will go a long way. The employee just want to know you appreciate them working and lining your pockets with funds they do not get.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>