<name>William F. Ryan Community Health Center Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/William-F-Ryan-Community-Health-Center-Reviews-E448003.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2011-10-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Community-based”

</title><pros>Pros – Union BenefitsThey care about their patients</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor communication by management.Lots of jealousy and bickering.Drama filled</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Community Health Center Disaster: Not a good place to receive Medical Care or to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Locations around New York City, Lovely Motto (Health care is a Right, not a Privilege), sliding scale for uninsured, acceptance of many different Health Insurances</pros>
<cons>Cons – Patient wait times, patient appointment availability, poor phone access (no one ever answers the phone).I wouldn't  recommend this place to my worst enemy. Honestly!! The Administration is horrible. They are a bunch of bullies and gangsters. No matter how hard their employees work, they don't give them any respect or signs of gratitude. All they do is bully you and threaten you with unemployment. They don't treat you like a very hard working adult. We have lost great Nurses, Pediatricians, Specialists, and Receptionist for no good reason. They have no reluctance to fire anyone, no matter what their title.  The turn over rate of all employees is faster than at McDonalds.  When you go to a place and hear that this person is new and that person has been here for a couple of months then you know there is a problem.  The Pediatric Director will boost about how long a couple of the Pediatricians and Nurses have worked for the Center (A COUPLE!) -- but will fail to tell you how many Doctors, Nurses, and Receptionist have left, or how many they have fired. They were GREAT workers too!!!  Three of the Pediatricians within the past year have even sued them because they were VERY WRONGFULLY fired.  Yeah, ask about all that if you are going to interview. They WILL call you for an interview too because they are terribly short staffed. The patients are even tired of the high turnover rate of Physicians and many of them have left the center because of it. Continuity is lacking!  They don't care how hard any of their employees work or how late they  stay each day in order to provide quality care to their patients. They just have the 'ON TO THE NEXT ONE' attitude.  If you don't believe this review, ask them BEFORE your interview about the  high turn over rate of Pediatricians, Specialists, Nurses, and Receptionists.   The Administration can care less about complaints from the patients or the staff.  As long as they can bill Medicaid or any other health insurance they are happy.Their motto, "Health Care is a right, not a Privilege" sounds great but Treating Their Employees with respect should be a Right and not a Privilege too!!! Congressman William F. Ryan must be  rolling over in his grave.  Trust me, don't waste your time with this place. Visit if you want and talk to the staff. They are not happy at all.  I'm tired of the high turn over rate and the VERY wrongful write-ups of the staff. After the holidays I am going to happilyresign!!  That will be a gift to myself. I would tell you to print out this review and ask the Doctors, Nurses, front desk staff, custodians, and security guards to comment on it but theyprobably won't give you an honest answer because they know the bullies will be after them. People have children to feed and bills to pay so giving you, a stranger, the 'Heads Up' may  not be in their best interest (no matter how badly they want to tell you the truth).  Seriously, keep looking. Send your resumesomewhere else.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have a heart not an open hand</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Case Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Most rewarding experience as a former employee”

</title><pros>Pros – benefits, advancement and excellent trainings to prepare you for ever changing healthcare</pros>
<cons>Cons – very anal with lunchbreaks, breaks and unnecessary write ups</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Allow your workers to breathe and perform the job tasks that's required of employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>I worked there (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bad Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Central ParkStarbucksSubway is right off of BroadwayLasker Pool 2 blocks upColumbia University near by</pros>
<cons>Cons – High turn over rate.Management is horrible, does not provide adequate training and expects you to learn overnight.  This is just one way to prepare you to be overloaded with work.Too many contract positions, which is not good and not adequately explained during the interviewing process.I felt as if my movements more monitored and there was lack of communication between management and staff.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be honest during interviews when you are hiring new candidates.  I think potential employees need the right information to make informed decisions about their professional careers.   Orientations should give new employees the opportunity to ask questions, no matter how long it takes.  New folks should never be rushed through the process and ushered out of the office because you have no more time to talk.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Patient Navigator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Extremely Stressful with bad management -- Doesn't care about their patients or employees.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great mission. Provides services to low-income peoples in high-need areas. Has satellite centers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The higher-ups in administration are terrible. One of them specifically believes that screaming in Spanish is the answer to careful management. Some employees gossip about patients and clearly don't care about them as much as they should. Obviously community health centers will be more stressful environments (compared to large, well-off private hospitals), but I thought that would attract more open-minded people who sincerely care about people, but terrible management made me (literally) want to lock myself in the storage closet for hours. I quit when I started to dream about hanging myself in that said closet. Also, if the patients stress you out by running around, throwing food all over the place, and losing their children, implement proper rules and regulations. It's safer and more hygienic that way.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Nurses need to be appreciated more, as well as the administrative staff. There is a reason there was a high turnover rate while I was there (and the years before). I know several people (other than myself) who cried daily after work due to poor management taking out their (personal) frustrations on us. There is no reason to roll your eyes and yell "OH DIOS MIO" all the time in people's faces -- explain to them clearly what needs to be done and when. Everyone is too scared to approach you (for help) to do their work correctly (maybe). Treat people well (especially when you're paying them less than minimum wage, as they're supposed to be "volunteers"). Respect them and they will respect you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Helping others can be frustrating”

</title><pros>Pros – Get to directly help patients</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is very high turn-over within the Network, which shows that people are not extremely happy.  The pay is a little low for all of the hours put in and the stress of the job.  It is a non-profit though so this can be expected.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be nicer to your staff!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>