<name>C Spire Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/C-Spire-Reviews-E453680.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good company overall.”

</title><pros>Pros – There is a great company culture and great health benefits.  Stores are always closed on Sundays.  There is no cap on commissions, the more you sell the better your check will be!  Good incentives and promotions.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The commission structure changes often, making it hard to know what you need to sell to make more money.  Blackout dates during the holidays make it hard to use your vacation days.  The job can be very repetitive- informing new customers of the same things over and over again.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Repair Technician II (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was okay...”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people to work with. Everybody gets along (almost). Very solid company with plenty of regional and national long-term growth potential. Very good benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Top management and owners are very obstinate in how they view employee compensations. You can't have a meaningful discussion about this because they will end the conversation. I'm glad this is a company that excels in the area of integrity in many areas. We need more companies like this. However, integrity falls apart when it comes to pay. After all, we live in a world where the object is to screw one another. Even from Christian pastors.The human resources manual states that C Spire Wireless does not discriminate on the basis of union affiliation. But, what would happen if everybody joined a union? They would get fired. This is doublespeak-integrity at its finest.I know so many people who used to work for C Spire Wireless (and some who still do) who constantly complain about the pay. I pray that one day these managers will see the light, and be transformed. I have confidence that one day these things will change for the better...You will be micromanaged, which bothers some people and is not such a big deal to others. You will be underpaid. Expect to hear ridiculous comments from upper management about how everybody in a department should be fired. It is laughable when they say these things, then they realize they are wrong.If you have good ideas to improve operations, management will often not care and this is missed growth potential, both for the company and the employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Ask yourself if what you are paying employees is right in the sight of God rather than pat yourself on the back because the pay is "competitive". Do the right thing and don't be so selfish about paying employees what they should be making. Find ways employees can receive substantial increases in pay by making big contributions to the organization. Most people receive low salaries, but the top 50 people receive very high salaries. Please be more open to bringing your salaries more in line with those of employees to send the message that you are not so far above them...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>CAE (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Account Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Great company to work for  as far as benefits, products and people to work with,</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management style or at least in my region.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Install the full version of SalesForce.com</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent Company to Work For”

</title><pros>Pros – SalaryBenefits (401K, ESOP, Insurance)Advancement OpportunitiesWork/Life Balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – Tuition Assistance/Reimbursement is not that great.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Offer better tuition assistance/reimbursement for those individuals wanting to pursue further education.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good company with good potential and good benefits.”

</title><pros>Pros – Fair expectationsClosed on Sundays and major holidays.Closes at 6:00 PM most stores.ESOP and vested after 6 years of service.Benefits package is ok.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bonus structures change consistently.Too much push for sales with not enough support from infrastructure in some areas.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company to work for!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Commission, Manager's attitude, Pay, Bonus Opportunities, Off Sundays</pros>
<cons>Cons – Uniform, Lot to learn, Computers not user friendly</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Offer more career opportunities beyond the Mississippi area</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Downhill fast”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefitsGuaranteed 40 hours a week</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management tends to be way too familiar with employees.  A few managers know where the line should be and act accordingly while the rest of them flirt way too much with that line.  The morale gets lower every year due to unreasonable goals and policies issued by those in corporate who are just looking at the numbers but are out of touch with the customer.  They put way too much faith in surveys and mystery shops, which are important but should not be the entire view of the employee that corporate gets.  There is no reason anyone should be as stressed out as their employees are 24/7 (which could explain the frat styled partying that takes place behind closed doors between some in  management and employees).....</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The good old boy system needs to die in this company....  Also, check up on your regional managers to ensure they aren't just goofing around and actually doing something....</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Market Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Great hours, no Sundays, always changing.  Compensation is good for managers.  benefits are great.  I am going to open up my own business with money earned on ESOP in less then 8 years.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Copy other people when making changes.Ever since name change they tried to make to many changes at once.under utilize important key staff members.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good benefits (insurance and 401k), but limited opp for growth and promotion”

</title><pros>Pros – Health Insurance401KStock OptionsPaid VacationsSick TimeChristmas BonousEmployee PCs are kept current</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor managementLimited opportunity for promotion and professional growthResistant to forward thinking employees ideas and suggestions</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Challenge or remove Directors and Managers that harbor/display any form of bias based on gender or race. Remove the open policy to not market to "urban" areas (look at "Bright Lights" )</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Start Job, but if you arent from MS you can forget advancement”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits,Pay, Free Cell Phone, Nice people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours, management is has favorites, working Saturdays</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You need to begin to micromanage the market managers and the ROM's. Bet you have no idea all that goes on behind closed doors.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>