<name>Toys R Us Canada Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Toys-R-Us-Canada-Reviews-E454243.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cashier Position Is not the best position”

</title><pros>Pros – You still feel like a kid being surrounding by toys and kids activities</pros>
<cons>Cons – - management pressures you into selling Warranty Plans (BPP) which customers don't like to buy due to extra cost (managers nag me and I feel so irritated)- have to sell batteries (if you don't sell a lot they'll bug you for that as well)- overall your hours are also based on you reaching the store goals (less plans and batteries less hours)- Management gets bonus for Plans employees sell- Cashier Position is not the best position (better to be a floor associate)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Give credits to cashiers who actually sell the plans (either bonus if they reach target goal or some sort of giftcard to the store)- Irritating us to keep selling the plans won't get us to sell but pissed off and not to sell</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“They take advantage of their works”

</title><pros>Pros – You get 15% off your purchases within store.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They don't recognize their hard works.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>World Sales Leader (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I hope you learn before too late”

</title><pros>Pros – Co-Workers, Kept up with all the new toys.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bosses stick together and do not know how to admit when wrong. The bosses  and employees that party together advance. Bring in new bosses who know nothing about receiving, working LRTs,  no people skills and can not do any of the paper work but can  tell you how it should be done(when have never done himself) after doing it myself for  many years. Very low pay after years of service.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn to listen if more then one person is telling you something about a boss, it is better then one  boss telling you all is good. The workers are the ones who speak the truth alot more then your managers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of opportunity for growth in hourly associate to ASM”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun, challenging, always changing, ability to be creative</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working weekends (but it is retail)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Empower your associates to produce better results and teamwork</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Meh”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with children is fun. I worked on the till which was challenging, but let me talk to people and I enjoy that</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management was a little slack. They were more like dictators. I was a seasonal worker and they didn't even tell me that my contract ended, just didnt post my name on the schedule...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more professional, you're not the children you're selling to.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>World Sales Leader (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awful management.”

</title><pros>Pros – Got to work with children and toys</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you hurt yourself at work, management yells at you</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be less cruel, you work in a toy store.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cashier during x-mas rush and the baby for six months.”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun people, great discount, early holds of new hot items</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unpredictable hours, targetting metrics not always indicative of performance (ie in Baby if you don't get your registry goal it is very bad, but consistently getting $1000+ sales don't mean anything for recognition)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>World Sales Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very nice company”

</title><pros>Pros – Very nice company good experience because it is not a rough work the company will make us very satisfied in benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Full time work and tiring work and bad in work,life balance, and cultural and values and a little bit bad in senior management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Good and nice company to work at but we must work and always focus on our work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The workplace is a very fun and friendly environment, very relaxed.”

</title><pros>Pros – Nothing was very strict, we had quite a bit of freedom with our clothing choices and the people I met there were very upbeat and positive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The after-hours clean up took at least 1 hour on regular days and 2 hours during the holiday season.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Electronic Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent Compensation, Good Management except director”

</title><pros>Pros – -Raise every year- Lots of opportunity for cross-training- Coworkers are great- Management up to assistant director has been great</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Director is horrible- Too much pressure on measurable items ( Buyer Protection Plans, batteries etc)- Poor scheduling and hours</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management has to be consistant with polices, directors need to be further evaluated. You must ease off the pressure off your cashiers when it comes to measurable items such as BPP's , they stress the employees out which creates unhappy employee which in turn affects the customer experience.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Service Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Depends on each store's management”

</title><pros>Pros – - flexible hours- raises each year- good management team- good coworkers- family-like working environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – - not enough communication between management- policies not clear enough- certain managers not backing up policy</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - more communication with each other and your employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Floor Person (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“only a number”

</title><pros>Pros – hires lots of students who need jobs</pros>
<cons>Cons – we have a problem with managers, we will ask them to do a correction, they tell us to call someone else even though they are beside us...what gives? They tell us to call asst manager since that is the order of protocall. I have worked here 24 years and it's only since we have the management that we have this problem. Morale in the store is very low. I wish things would go back to the way it was. We have lot of employees that have been with this store for alot of years, and we all feel the same way.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – treat your employees like you would want to be treated. Don't treat us like were stupid.</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Who'd have thought working for a toy company would be so miserable?”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with kids and toysMost of my co-workers were really great</pros>
<cons>Cons – You have to shove a million things down people's throats every transaction that no one wants or needs. Extended warranties (BBPs), overpriced batteries, charity stars (don't get me wrong, it's great they help children in need, but once you've harassed a customer about 3 other things they get really annoyed) and Air Miles. Management continuously tracks your percent in each one of these categories 3-4 times throughout your shift. If your percents aren't high enough (and factors such as a slow day are never accounted for) you get yelled at.Lack of proper training, I had no idea what I was doing for a few weeks, and getting help was difficult.Rude management. We had the district manager come into our store one day and yell at a girl on her very first shift for not knowing who he was. Needless to say she never came back again.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It's a toy store for pete's sake, lighten up on your employees!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Be prepared to be overwhelmed”

</title><pros>Pros – Team spirit is great, working with toys :)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Protection plans we have to offer are alot of pressure</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – nov-dec work 50-60hrs a week</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Electronic Department (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good employees, Poor Management”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with kids and toys are great.Some managers are pleasant to work with.Co-employees are also pleasant to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You can only work part time, even though you are working more that 40 hours a week. Therefore, there are no benefits.Also, management want to you sell sell sell things to individuals you know they don't need.Finally, sometimes managers demand too much from an employee.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It should be about the customer and kids...it's a kids store for crying out loud. Don't let it be about the money all the time...those are only short term sales for the shareholders, the longterm weath and relationship with the customer is more important.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Rather Not Say (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“While it 's still a fine place to work; new managements bottom line thinking makes bottom line results near impossible.”

</title><pros>Pros – Any body as long as they have the hours to pay their portion can join in the benefits program at different levels. Do the work learn the methods and moving up is very possible, including into H/O jobs at entry levels. Most stores have a very good family/team atmosphere and people seem to really care. You can learn skills that will transfer within the industry.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some stores are not run as close to SOP as they should be and so although moving up is possible, if you don't have the support of your management team ( or more specifcally your director) then you may be stuck.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You have some great employees and if you let them they may surprise you with how well they can increase sales. however it may forgo some of the other small things (BPP's, VITE) but the results might be worth it. Some out of the box front line thinking may kick start other things.  Look what "Undercover Boss" is showing other corp/executives. We are on the same team, a stronger company means job security.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing opportunity for growth, until you hit the ceiling, then growth turns to stress.”

</title><pros>Pros – The more you put into the job, the more you can get out of it. Management often rewards individuals who stand out. New Express system have has immense potential for both job/career advancement and employment in general.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The more you put into the job, the more you'll be asked to contribute on a regular basis; give an inch and they'll forever expect miles. Management is often swamped in extra responsibilities being placed upon them all the time. New positions are only being created at the bottom of the hierarchy / pyramid, over-working anyone off the ground (most those with seniority).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Financially, the business is headed in the right direction, however cutting too many corners is leaving many employees frustrated. The expansion model must be great for the offices that had to give the order, but no one executing it is seeing (or feeling) any compensation for the extra workload.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>