<name>Vinove Software & Services Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Vinove-Software-and-Services-Reviews-E455945.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good to start career”

</title><pros>Pros – They have a lots of projects for you to learn work in pressure</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is not good.. Company policy is not transparent</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior BD Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Has helped me to evolve as an professional”

</title><pros>Pros – Since the day I joined I have been given enough hand holding and mentoring by different seniors. Though I came from business development domain however my time with Vinove has exposed me to all together different gambit of the business perspective. I have become more focused and business oriented. The approach towards business and topped up with in depth analytic has in deed opened up new paradigm to me. Initial it made me uncomfortable to apprehend the approach adopted here. Even there was a point I thought to call it off however thanks to my friends who helped me to continue. Today I am thankful to the organization and the team for what I am.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is more data driven and process oriented organization. People feel initial hiccups to adopt to the processes however it is mandatory for everyone to graduate to next level in their respective career.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I feel more dedicated migration program should be adopted by the HR to make people transit to such process oriented organization. Mostly who come from small/mid organization where there is less emphasis on process would tend to feel uncomfortable.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Web Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working with Vinove has been an amazing experience & will always be the best.”

</title><pros>Pros – Facing new challenges everyday and sorting them out with a very motivated team has been great experience for me. If you are prepared to work hard and have a long term vision then the opportunities with Vinove are immense.  Culture is full of belongingness, transparency in processes & full of growth aspects.  From the start till end of journey with Vinove, I am sure you will be impressed with efficient and proficient professionals working with them likewise I have experienced the same.  Company has injected inspiration, confidence, speed & consistency of delivering best in me and definately in everyone associated with them at different levels.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Little behind on retention of good employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increase traning opportunities and scope to make employees more productive & this will lead in retaining good employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-22</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Right Place to Bring Best Out of You”

</title><pros>Pros – I have joined this organization 1 year back and the pattern of growth is visible.  Hunger to drive more out of me has been developed by my seniors.  Working experience to capture the market has played a motivator's role in my career path with Vinove till now.  Exposure of technical tools, client interaction, new frameworks to delivery has made me smart enough, I could not have been anywhere else.  Senior's boosting for trying new things, taking new risks & making job interesting is remarkable.Most important is keeping culture and giving importance to employees is very good by the Support Team.  Format of daily celebration to cherish special occasions like Employee's birthday, Year Completions and I must mention “Wedding Anniversary” is something I have witnessed & is awesome.  The way of introducing new arrival in the company & making them comfortable has helped in adopting new culture.  I must say, it's worth joining and working here at Vinove.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management's contact with junior staff should be open and strong, improvements than will experience tremendous growth.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give praise and criticism in the same way.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Development (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible”

</title><pros>Pros – you got to learn new things</pros>
<cons>Cons – middle finger for Human Resource Department</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be Punctual</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Lead - Operations (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to start career in the web industry & lead it uptill managerial position.”

</title><pros>Pros – Company's mission has helped me at larger extent to understand & learn the actual principles of the career development, taught me about work ethics and fundamentals of being a true professional.  Because of Company's experience in Global Market and worldwide technical expertise; approach towards employee's professional growth is commendable.Best practice is “Office is all empty for Teams latest by 6:30 P.M. Every day” & provide plentyful time to spend the day's remaining hours with family.Right place to create and make the Identity as a Professional.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not many but yet improvement always has scope.  Middle management need some more mentoring to guide the juniors hence their education should be on priority.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I am optimistic about the outlook for this company & would like Company to indroduce few employee benfit plans & more value for people which deserve the position and have given the soul to Company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you have Exp, don't ruin it with them”

</title><pros>Pros – Only good for freshers, definitely have lot to learn.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited knowledge curve, after certain time or project, nothing new, plus super extra work pressure. Even if you are passionate about your work, you dedicate everything still there will be lots of pressure.No personal life remains, no perks associated with your hard work, no one actually no one cares if you are hard worker and everybody tends to save his seat and try to send the ball from one's court to another. No one takes responsibility and thats the reason the person who is passionate gets the most pressure.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to understand the concerns of employees, need major upgrade in tech front specially leadership.Owner is a good leader but nether a visionary nor a person who can motivate anyone.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sales professional- STAY AWAY”

</title><pros>Pros – will give you 1-2 months to adapt their process and policies</pros>
<cons>Cons – you feel like working is vicious circle, where you have nothing to gain- both professionally and personally.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – STOP bulling your EX employees and listen to other staff member as company cannot grow with just DELIVERY HEAD and CEO</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-24</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“One of the Best Place to Work for”

</title><pros>Pros – - Enormous Learning Scope.- Hands on Exposure to new Technologies.- Enough Space to Perform.- No Work Place Politics.- Employee Friendly Environment.- Dynamic and Vibrant Work Culture.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Truly there is nothing as such which would stop an individual to grow and learn here as long as they prove there worth. No free riders are encouraged any where. However apart from being situated in Industrial area there is no downside. Though the location is well connected with Metro and Road.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Top management really cares for employees here.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>HTML Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good”

</title><pros>Pros – If you work in vinove as fresher so this is a good opportunity to learns..</pros>
<cons>Cons – Vinove Company in Industrial area so this is a not good area for IT Company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Respect Juniors</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>