<name>J. Ray McDermott Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/J-Ray-McDermott-Reviews-E4563.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2011-06-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very good company to work with!”

</title><pros>Pros – Multi talented workforceMulti culturalRelatively small company therefore everyone gets a good chance to grow within the organization</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes you feel overworked with not enough help available.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poorly managed Good company”

</title><pros>Pros – SmallEfficient ( once)Full serviceSeveral industry firsts</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too small to handle major projectsIncompetent leadership teamLost lots of good professionals4 years of poor performance</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be sincere and protect company's interest and not simply line your pockets</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“EPCI Offshore Construction”

</title><pros>Pros – A lot of opportunities for engineering jobs</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company needs to improve management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-02-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cost Estimate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The skinny on McDermott”

</title><pros>Pros – good job selections and the chance to work in exciting places.  the client list is great and there are exciting opportunities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the salaries could be better, but benefits are ok.  i have worked in better places, but i have also worked in worse places.  the use of cubicles is not to everybodys liking, but the we are coping for the moment.  I think they may be building a new building soon to help with all of this.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – upgrade your equipment and make it competitive with other companies out there</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-02-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>RIF (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Field workers need personal communication from upper management!”

</title><pros>Pros – J. Ray is a good company to work for if, your in the "In Crowd".  In the field front line management is great and works with the employees in the field.  Good compensation for employees usually and most of the employees in the field are friendly, competent, and hard workers</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management needs help.  There is hardly any communication between upper management and field supervision.  The only thing that is communicated is "negative" and not to many positives.  Most of the employees have the "fear" that they might be next to be fired or layed off.  It's a very "top down" company and field employees cannot make decisions on their own without worrying about repercussion from upper management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Senior management needs to communicate with the workers with face to face talking.... not messages, emails or anything else.  They need to take the time to meet with the workers and discuss any problems they may have, rather than decide without knowledge of what's really going on in the field!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-07-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – JRM offers a great salary and are great people to work for and with for the most part (there's always one or two in every company who are hard to work with).  For the most part, everyone works as a team no matter their position in the company or as a contractor.  Employees and contract employees are treated with respect.  It seems that, when hiring, how a person will fit in seems to be considered in addition to their qualifications to make sure everyone can work as a team.  I think this is a great company to work for and plan to stay a very long time!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Haven't found any yet after more than a year except that most positions are dependent upon projects.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-10</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Controls Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“University of Project Management”

</title><pros>Pros – Most of young talents have worked here. Many of them has gone to Oil and Gas company and became key personnels - effectively creating connection between contractor and company.One of the best bureaucracy of most EPC as well. Very well documented.They offer one of the best  retrenchment package I have seen from any industry.Good place to work as well as learning how to manage projects effectively.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Great at spotting talents but not good at retaining them.Some senior personnels are just good at talking - this is common organization mistake.Great salary package for fresh grads, but just average salary package for experience personnels.Dual management (yard and projects) mean more conflicts and less unity.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to manage the dual management things carefully.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Field Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall, great place to work.  And you will work, a lot.”

</title><pros>Pros – Very friendly work environment and people.  Almost family like, at least at overseas locations.Most more experienced co-workers and managers were happy to give advice and assistance.Good pay and benefits, although fairly normal for the industry.Plenty of company events/parties that promote camaraderie.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very little standard training, like learning to swim by being thrown into the deep end.  They are willing to send you to courses, but you have to ask for them.Sometimes hard to effect change, many things are done that way just because they always have been.  Again, being a little pushy can get it done.On shore work schedule was supposed to be 5 1/2 days a week, with one Saturday off a month.  That half day was always closer to a full day and almost no one took that Saturday off, even when there wasn't much work to be done.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Encourage a better work/life balance.  Everyone understands deadlines, but when there's not a pressing one, encourage people to take the available time off.Provide more job-specific training to new hires.  Especially new grads in entry level positions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Administrative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It made my life”

</title><pros>Pros – I got good knowledge from this company, Got learn more, Made me know various types of persons from different nations. It bought me closer to my work. It was like a family to me.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Well ups and downs are there I am still not aware as to why i was terminated? after working for 33 years at the end I was not even welcomed? WHY.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I still feel that Mcdermott should respect its workers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very disorganized, departments in the Dubai office needs to wake up and get their act together”

</title><pros>Pros – Global opportunities , market salaries and travel</pros>
<cons>Cons – Be proactive and not reactive.....huge political divide between global fleet employees  and regional office based employees.....you need to pay people based on talent and not on nationality</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pls look deeply at how some departments carry out their work</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – I haven't been with the company for too long, but so far I haven't come across anyone who wasn't friendly and knowledgeable.Good pay and benefits, as well.</pros>
<cons>Cons – None so far. There's the occasional period of low work load, and sometimes the day can drag on. But those cycles of fervor and languor are fairly normal, and I suppose this experience depends on the work area.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Subsea Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place for a few years to kick start.”

</title><pros>Pros – growthlearning opportunityzero taxcan go anywhere from here</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is gross difference between salaries of Asians vs.  People from Americas or EU (Graduate Engineers get more pay than Engineers of 5years experience).No work to life balance.Very rigorous work regime (you have to clock nearly 50 hrs per week).There is overtime shown on paper but it is manipulated in such way that you don’t get any extra money for that.Lot of abuse of HR policies for the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – be fair to all!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Project Management”

</title><pros>Pros – Good exposure to offshore hook up and commissioning</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much time offshore since no rotation policy</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Management (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice people but terrible management which is causing everybody to work in fear.”

</title><pros>Pros – Competitive pay package with comprehensive benefit package. International reputable contractor with a long history and track record.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Exceptional high turn over for new startersBully style managementFear cultureLack of trrust in their peopleGood old marine boys cultureLack of innovation</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management should realize the importance of people and using effective management styles to get the best out of the organization. Just applying fear does not work, neither using outdated Jack Welch practices and fire 10% of the people. Quality of leadership goes a long way, just promoting young guys will not give this company the reforms it needs to remain competitive.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good enough job”

</title><pros>Pros – Money, benifits, hours, 401k, stock options</pros>
<cons>Cons – Being away from home for extended periods of time,Frequent lay-offs, in general a lack of work to maintain a stable steady workforce</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire someone other than your brother in law, son, nephew,Hire local workers rather than as many forigners as possible In marine division.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Electrical Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“the worst mistake i made in my life, but  meet great people in the cities”

</title><pros>Pros – give relocation packageno growthvery politic</pros>
<cons>Cons – the worst place to start a careernot good for black or diversitydon't help w/ education growthLie companylook for them self only</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – start looking into the lower department</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Employer”

</title><pros>Pros – Global Opportunities for growth, exciting work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Cyclical nature of work, thats just the industry</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Its a well-run company, not a lot of advise to give. Need some opportunities for offshore visits so people get a full perspective of operations.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Management and peers, for the most part, are congenial and cooperative.Salaries seem competitiveWorking atmosphere is casual yet professional9/80 work schedule allowing for 3 day weekend every other week is great</pros>
<cons>Cons – Communication between departments needs to be improved.  Hard to do a job without necessary information or having to spend a lot of time trying to get information.  This could be due to the nature of the projects being on tight schedule leaving little time to think about who will need the information downstream.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Certainly the EPCI schedule is a major consideration when bidding but more consideration needs to be given when developing a schedule such as increasing manpower to meet the requirements.Please consider a 4/10 work week.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>