<name>Robert J. Semrad & Associates Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Robert-J-Semrad-and-Associates-Reviews-E465433.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-01-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible Upper Management”

</title><pros>Pros – The pay is ok depending on what your job title is, horrible for some, ok for others.  Depending on what office you work in, time off is ok.   The offices are nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No real benefits.  Management is horrible and no consistency.  Firm is built on greed.  No job security, turnover is the highest of anywhere I've ever seen.   Hours and work load is ridiculous for most.  it's basically a mill, not a law firm.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need consistency.  Need to build firm on rewarding good work and not just everything based on money.  Management needs to be more involved, most managers have no idea what's going on and don't care.  There is no follow-through to make it a better place to work for most people.  The managers have a few favorites and everyone else is treated poorly and neglected.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Paralegal (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“a nightmare”

</title><pros>Pros – That is a place for entry level people ONLY</pros>
<cons>Cons – They never pay you on time, the amount of work is just ridiculous. They just want to make tons of money without having enough employees to do the job. No benefits at all, you are entitle to one week vacation only, no direct deposit. I am going to keep is simple that place is a hot mess</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Show respect to your employees and understand that employees need their payment on time</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Starter Job: Big Firm Hours, Small Firm Pay”

</title><pros>Pros – It's the nicest bankruptcy mill in town. Seriously. The management seems to want to improve the quality of the firm's work and reputation.Other than that, it's actually a paying gig, and right now that's worth 2 stars all by itself. Also you'll be so busy that those 12 hour days will fly right by.Good place to start a career. If you aren't fired within 2 months, you will very likely be promoted or move on to a better job within a year.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Like I said, it's a mill. It's all about volume. And since you can do this sort of work only so quickly, the hours range from long to atrocious (including every other Saturday and at least until 8pm on Tuesdays). And even that wouldn't be too too bad, except the money doesn't match the hours.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – For the love of god, give people at least the option of taking Monday off if they work Saturdays. I bet the attrition rate would be cut in half with just this one change. And please recognize that this job is extremely taxing on a person, both mentally and emotionally.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>