<name>C. Wonder Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/C-Wonder-Reviews-E470445.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good idea for a new retail brand and new approach to customer service, but poorly executed.”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly customers, nicely arranged stores.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor management and it keeps changing with no explanations provided, why somebody left, and why somebody who's no way better was hired. Could be a fun place to work, if the management would know better what are they doing and would appreciate their hard working people.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get your act together. And communicate with people who actually sell your merchandise on a floor.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My experience at C Wonder has been disappointing.”

</title><pros>Pros – The pros of working at C Wonder is the employee discount and working with such great customers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Corporate is extremely unorganized which negatively effects the retailers. Management at retailers are extremely unprofessional.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Find more professional management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Department Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a wonderful place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – I love the people I work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I was very excited to join the C.Wonder team; they were just what I had been looking for: an innovative new company that could provide me lots of growth and opportunities. However, after only a few weeks, I knew I had made a mistake. There is no structure to the company whatsoever. It took me SIX MONTHS as a manager to get login information to tools I would need to correctly do my job. I watched person after person around me attempt to move to a higher position or to an entry level corporate position, only to be completely dismissed and not even be able to interview. (And these were employees that had been with the company since they STARTED.) As a previous commenter stated, they promise you the world when you interview/are onboarded, yet, you will never see any of the benefits of those promises. I didn't feel like I had anyone who was interested in my development and growth, whatsoever. Response time is a joke if you need to get corporate to get back to you on something. All the company is stressing is opening more and more new stores--which, of course, I understand--but perhaps you should have more structure and systems in place to help aid and better your CURRENT stores before you open new ones.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Things Have Gotten Worse Since My 1ST Review!”

</title><pros>Pros – The 40% sometimes 60% discount,  Amazing Coworkers (The original associates & managers, not the new ones)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Shady Shady business! C Wonder hired a new HR team along with new store, general & district managers. Since this happened, things have spun out of control. The new managers are pushy on customers and demanding of associates. I can literally never stand in one place for a moment without getting bombarded by at least 3 managers. I came to work last week and there were 6 managers on the floor at one time!!! The new HR team rolled out a new clause on the back of our availability forms that stated that if we needed to change our schedule for fall (ex. going back to school) that we would be "voluntarily resigning" if our schedule didn't meet the needs of the store. If we don't sign, we also get terminated in a month. They also never explained this to us and left employees to figure out the new terms themselves. This would mean that if the store fired us we would not be eligible for unemployment. The worst part is, many of the associates had just been hired a few months before this new contract and were promised that we could stay once school started however the store denies that. Some employees that fall under this new clause have been working at the company since the opening! In addition, all along the store has been hosting Open House events, hired tons of new employees and put them into our positions. To add insult to injury, they want us to train our new replacements! I cant put a number on how many times the new managers now come up to us associates and ask us "are you okay?" or "why are you upset today?" UM, MAYBE BECAUSE WE ARE RANDOMLY GETTING FIRED & WE NEED MONEY FOR SCHOOL! They also deny that we are getting fired & say that we are resigning. They also continue to push the sales goals on us even though i don't make commission & we are being terminated. I swear it takes everything in me not to lose my temper with those people while i work till the cut off date. I don't understand why they feel the need to be patronizing when they know how bad it is for the employees that are being let go. I could go on and on about all the terribly insulting things C Wonder has offered me but i really liked this company until things started changing for the worse. If the customers knew about this, they would be horrified  and wonder how the associates keep it together everyday while doomsday quickly approaches! Because we still deliver amazing service even though we are getting fired, our associates are class acts! Sucks that we all have to find new jobs. Your loss C Wonder!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Think about your employees. C wonder spends so much time trying to please its customers but never thinks about the people who deliver the service! Most of people that are in retail are students, firing all your students not only makes the company look bad but its unethical.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Department Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Many promises made, none kept!”

</title><pros>Pros – I love my co workers at the store. They are the reason I come to work everyday.</pros>
<cons>Cons – C wonder is a lie. They tell you everything you want to hear to make you stay. I was promised the world when I started and I'm still in the same place I was when I was hired. Problem is now, they hired all new corporate employees so you have to start fresh with people you don't know and don't know you. They don't believe on your abilities and for that anyone that has been with the company more than a few months will go unnoticed. I loved this company with all my heart but the feeling have since disappeared.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on your seasoned employees. We know this company like the back of our hands and would do anything to make it better. Ask us our opinions because without us at the store level, this company would be NOTHING!Side note: change the return policy. I know we are suppose to make the customer happy but because they beat their nylon tote against a rock doesn't mean I should have to give them a  new one because the strap is cracking. It's Not my problem that they got a hole in their shirt after wash and wear about 12 times/ I don't want to give them their money back.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unstable!”

</title><pros>Pros – Working at C. Wonder opened my eyes to taking school more seriously so that I don't end up in retail forever. Co-workers are friendly and outgoing. The store creates competitions that are fun and competitive.  I learned to deal with certain customers. The discount is good although the prices aren't that great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – High turn over rate. Nobody lasts. Rude customers with high demands and its all your fault in the end. Mpos system needs to taken care of, too slow and always freezing. Corporate needs to be friendly to those who work for them. Break room needs space and a table!  The music is terrible, same songs like clock work. It's a drag working with Motown music. And also very short staff</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat every employee with respect and be friendly. Get rid of Mpos system. Change the music!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Still new to job”

</title><pros>Pros – Positive culture among corporate leadership</pros>
<cons>Cons – Retail environment by nature provides little flexibility in schedule</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Think outside the box on how to provide more flexibility to employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>