<name>Getty Trust Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Getty-Trust-Reviews-E4713.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Maintenance Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ggkkk”

</title><pros>Pros – Good company, too much management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company hires and fires people according to how good their "Trust Fund" is doing. If there fund is doing good, your job is good. If the fund is doing bad in the stock market, they lay off people.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Management Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing environment, intellectually stimulating, but stagnant in key areas”

</title><pros>Pros – The setting, the art, diverse workforce. I worked at the GRI for nearly 9 years, almost straight out of college. I felt lucky to work in a department which allowed me to interact with the curators and art--a dream job for a long time. Also the GRI is a library and research center and so the exposure to rare and new books on architecture and art was a privilege.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Byzantine management structure that makes communication, direct action, any spontaneous problem solving difficult. Most distressing to more ambitious folks is that upward mobility rarely happens.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more innovative and don't sweat the details. Stop micro-managing everything.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Security Officer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Life at the Getty”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits and good pay. Beautiful place to work and some decent people. I would recommend students to work here because the Getty is very flexible to students and offers tuition reimburse.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hard to advance to other department if qualified, a lot of politics, and favoritism. Can be back breaking if you have to do a lot of standing. Depending on who you are and who you know your voice will not be heard.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Contract Administrator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cringe-Worthy”

</title><pros>Pros – Every other Friday off, the week between Christmas and New Years off, flexible hours, free gym, beautiful surroundings, high overall job satisfaction,</pros>
<cons>Cons – Procurement - terrible management (a case study in what not to do), low employee morale, micro management to the nth degree, sub par training,  HR and upper management turn a blind eye to years of complaints and high employee turnover</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get rid of the Procurement Manager</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Staff Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Snr Staff Assistant”

</title><pros>Pros – Have place to absorb you if you are good!! If your dept is merging, they will pick u up!!Every other off Friday, gym usage, vanpool benefits...good benefits!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – No where to go up....have to stick around in present job!! Merit increases minimal!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more open minded, promote from within.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Administrator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stay Away from Procurement, You'll Regret it, if You Don't !!”

</title><pros>Pros – Beautiful location,beautiful art, good benefits!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Stay far away from Procurement!!! It is a wasteland; HORRIFIC management, hostile work  environment, instability and miserable drone-like employees.  Not a place for a person with a pulse</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Lose the Procurement Department Management</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A valuable experience for me in a very unique organization”

</title><pros>Pros – A one-of-a-kind environment in a unique location.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Workforce reductions, job eliminations, and layoffs.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Staff Assistant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Snr Staff Assistant”

</title><pros>Pros – Good steay company, great health benefits!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – No room to grow upwards! Stuck in the position. Either leave or live!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more open to ideas!! Closed in the policies.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Visitor Services Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Pits”

</title><pros>Pros – Met some great co-workers who have remained friends. Pretty views, the art.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nowhere to go. Doesn't matter how many degrees you have or languages you speak- your initiative, hard work and suggestions at improvement are not rewarded and mine was even discouraged in a "you're rocking the boat" kind of way. Pay is low. Stagnant atmosphere. HR is a nightmare. Hierarchy is absurd with multiple levels of supervisors stumbling over each other.. Pay is laughable - you can make more at In n Out Burger.  Everyone was working overtime, all the time to make up for low pay. At first they offered benefits - that were taken away.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value and listen to your staff and pay them what they're worth.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I was proud to work there, interesting place, very good work-life balance.”

</title><pros>Pros – Every other Friday off, good benefits, good amount of PTO, free gym for employees, beautiful location, probably the best in LA, cultural/academic stimulation, diverse employees with interesting backgrounds, less stress compared to corporate world</pros>
<cons>Cons – politics, leadership is not always good about communicating with staff, very difficult to advance, minimal pay increases each year.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Staff Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Too bad they there is no room for growth”

</title><pros>Pros – low stress, kind people, academic environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – The president of the company was paid more than I would have made in 35 years and after 5 years I was yet to get a raise</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – reward hard work and innovation</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technician (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great non profit to work for.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits and free access to two of the best museums in the Los Angeles Area. Also the alternative work schedule is great. Parking is free.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No chance to move up or get promoted. Getting to work is tough unless you live in brentwood, because of the the location. Its off the busiest freeway in the world 405.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Incompetency within Trust Accounting ; no reward for hard work; TOO MUCH POWER within HR”

</title><pros>Pros – Supposedly, every other Friday off!  Not while I was there though, as I had to put in overtime and come in on my "off Fridays!"</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much politics, spying and backstabbing.  Accounting/payroll & G/L department have their share of low educated and/or incompetent members handling mid-to-high level management duties.  Payroll walks around like they own the place just because they print your checks for the work YOU put in.  It's few members hardly put in more than 3-4 hours of workday. Lazy slugs within Procurement department.  HR polices you, and calls you in for every asinine thing.   Not at all what I expected from a museum environment.  The environment is diseased at its core The place doesn't nurture; instead, it suffocates you!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You can't run the place like a mob organization ~ giving monetary rewards to the ones who slug away at their jobs ~ while others put in 110% and get no recognition at all.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Middle Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor performance in a toxic environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Views are good. Building is clean. Every second Friday off (although you make up for it by longer hours the other days). Lots of good people to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots of incompetence especially among the senior management of the museum, conservation, foundation, and research institutes. professional qualifications are considered far inferior to art history education. senior management is bloated and self-serving.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't be afraid of having honest outside audits and reviews of programs and organizational/ business matters. Consider a board of outsiders responsible for each institute and that has power of veto over director appointments and funding of major projects. Outside review is critical to success; without it, organizations survive with nepotism, oligarchy, and even tyranny.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Security Guest Relations Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – The pay starts out pretty decent! For a basic "minimum wage" job, the pay is above L.A. average.The people were extremely friendly, never had any bad encounters with other staff.Gorgeous place to work, every day I had an amazing view!Good schedules, every other weekend you had 3 days off.Discounts on food!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hours not good for part-time, but you eventually have the opportunity to move up to full-time.Tasks can be repetitive, but that's customer service, take it or leave it!Can't think of any major complaints!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“We could be doing great things.”

</title><pros>Pros – Beautiful location, great benefits, some brilliant people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – We're not saving lives but conserving art...let's have fun doing great work.  Cut through the non-profit political games.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your staff</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Museum Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Museum Associate”

</title><pros>Pros – Compensation is good off the bat for your position. Instead of starting small they start you according to the max your dept. can spend for your position or what it has for its fiscal budget which is usually divided up pretty fair. The grounds are unbelievable and the people that come through are really cool.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Its a world class museum run completely by really good Artists who don't really have any business management training. I work in Visitor Services and not one of the 15 managers,supervisors, leads, or assistants have any formal business management training. It used to be the perfect place to work until the recession. Morale is low now, they are not hiring at all in the many  museum sections besides the bookstore, and they are not promoting within in my very large dept. They have a record of hiring non-qualified / lost managers throughout the entire trust (which means both the Getty Center and Villa) and its a shame because this is the most prestigious museums you will ever see.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If I were to say one thing they need to do to better is only hire people with a combination of proven leadership skills with equal education completion in a business setting and not just artists who usually come in with  some emotional problems.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great organization, going through a rough time”

</title><pros>Pros – Beautiful campus, wonderful people to work with.  Benefits were nice and affordable.  Because most people never left the grounds during working hours, there was a lot of informal communication between the departments.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Several growing pains of a rather young organization.  Low moral among those who had been there for a long time and kept seeing their perks taken away.  Lots of layoffs even though their endowment is in the billions.  Made for a stressful atmosphere and a constant "who's next?" fear.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more transparent.  Let employees feel as if they have some sort of input when it comes to big decisions.  Be grateful for such a dedicated staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>One of the Minions (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The corrosive effect of money on a non-profit”

</title><pros>Pros – Being part of an organization that shares and cares for some of the great works of art in history.  You're helping to educate and bring art to the public.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bureaucracy, ethically-questionable senior staff promotions and salaries.  Bad managers promoting other bad managers based on the candidate's ambition rather than competency.  A PhD in Art History doesn't necessarily make someone a good manager.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do something because you should and not simply because you have the money to do so.  The Getty's money is its Achilles heel.  Trust your staff.  This distrust is causing very low morale - especially among junior staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>N/A Affraid of Senior Management Revenge (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Disfunctional asylum”

</title><pros>Pros – Stay away unless you cant find your place in the "normal" world. The Getty seems to be a good place for those that can't fit anywhere else. There's a few human resources with intense intellectual capital, but those are few and far between. Most others are parasites. And they will make sure you die the death of a thousand cuts.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's a dysfunctional asylum, everyone seems to be a veteran of either a mental institution or a sociopath farm. The politics are beyond any reasonable imagination. Since the Getty is a non-profit organization, employees don't really have to face a market driven force. Therefore, the lack of deadlines and market metrics is driving most of them to parasitic activities including huge ego trips and vendettas against those vastly more capable than themselves. This is  the embodiment of pettiness.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Change starts at home. Start showing the slightest trace of integrity and fairness and you'll be a much better manager and person.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-22</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Security Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Getty: A picture perfect place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly co-workers (except for the occasional run-in with a self-absorbed/important art snob staff), Great salary and benefits package (C'mon, who else covers contact lens'?!).  No need for a corner office, we have the best view of any workplace in L.A. (inside and outside!) , 24 hour employee fitness center,  easily accessible from all areas of L.A.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Occasional run-ins with self-absorbed/important art snob staff. Other than that...hmmm...oh yes, on the true downside, the breaks on my car need replaceing a bit more often due to driving down the hill all the time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You are doing an outstanding job of restoring the Getty Trust's reputation, after a very public airing of particularly dirty laundry left laying around the premesis by the previous administration.  Stay the course, the journey is far from over.  Perhaps, tell the occasional self-absorbed/important art snob staff members (they are few, but are around several corners) to lighten up and say hello once in a while.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“no two days are alike”

</title><pros>Pros – beautiful site, many opportunities to learn on the job, exposure to the arts, every other Friday off of work (paid); you have some control over your experience (responsibilities are there for those that want to learn). many resources at our disposal. the benefits are good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the pay leaves something to be desired and the pay structure isn't balanced. someone with 15 years of specialized experience shouldn't be making less than someone with a junior title and 5 years of work experience.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – it would be beneficial for moral if there were merrit based bonuses, above the standard 3% annual increases. unless fortunate enough to be hired when there were pensions,</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Can be a great place to work, depending on whom you work for”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart colleagues who are generous in sharing their knowledge, informal work environment, beautiful setting in Santa Monica mountains, every other Friday off.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Trust leadership does not have the confidence of employees and morale is shaky. Leadership under James Wood asked the programs to cut their budgets without making any concessions of their own, or taking full ownership of their decisions to lay off staff and restructure.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Share the sacrifice, show your employees that you value their contributions, eliminate the secrecy that has characterized the restructuring over the past several years. One thing I heard over and over was that there's a general attitude of "there are 20 other people waiting outside the door for your job if you don't want it" and unfortunately, I agree.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits and work schedule</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited advancement opportunities, would have like another level to strive for</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Consider a succession plan</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>