<name>P. Machibroda Engineering Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/P-Machibroda-Engineering-Reviews-E471810.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-02-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Laboratory Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I really learned a lot and got to move up within the company.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good experience in a wide range of different types of testing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Comminucation within the company could be increased.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK”

</title><pros>Pros – It was a good place start a career. Lots of opportunity to work on varying projects and different aspects of the project. Was treated very well by the company and was encouraged to take courses and seminars to further ones education and professional development. The senior engineers were always helpful when available.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Senior engineers were based in another office, thus sometimes weren't available when needed for advice. Lack of strong structured management led to a too loose of structure. Some employees knew what they could get away with and exploited it, resulting in others to shoulder the bulk of work load. Lack of focus and direction on how to grow and run business and offices were not treated equally.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire qualified people to run the different areas of the company. Invest in the resources and personnel needed to make the company stronger as a whole. Remember that this is an engineering company thus investment should focus on making the company stronger on this end first (taking risk on business end is part of the business). Create budgets and communicate a clear direction to employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>