<name>E Squared Communications Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/E-Squared-Communications-Reviews-E472605.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor Management. Low Pay.”

</title><pros>Pros – There are great people that work at E Squared. Also, the healthcare benefits are good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No room for growth. Very poorly staffed. No overtime pay. Salaries are very low (average $34,000 entry level salary with small raises) for the amount of work and responsibility that is expected of an entry level position. Processes are not up to date. Not much work-life balance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upper management should realize there are issues going on and actually address them. They seem to feel nothing and do nothing although 11 people have left in 2013 (so far) and negative opinions have been voiced.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Coordinator (Sorry Excuse for An Event Planner- Don't BE Fooled) (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You can tell that people are unhappy here but just go with the flow of things for fear of loosing their jobs.”

</title><pros>Pros – The pay is okay for what is expected of you. But there is no overtime just salary. So some nights you may be there until after dark, don't expect it to show on your pay.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everyone here will smile in your face but "throw you under the bus". There is no sense of ownership among the people here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Actually train people. Don't have subordinates train the new comers. Try having an actual training course. Take some ownership in your own short comings. Include ALL employees in updates of what is going on company-wide.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>