<name>Big W Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Big-W-Reviews-E473193.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Associate - Casual (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for a student, negotiable hours, not much room for training.”

</title><pros>Pros – Negotiable hours (casual)Good managementReasonable pay for a student</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not much opportunity for trainingNot many opportunities for promotion or new opportunities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“fun times, good environment to work in”

</title><pros>Pros – provides challenges and experiences require for future employment</pros>
<cons>Cons – less working hours, can be very demanding at times</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – work harder, with the purpose of improving the business even further</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Managing Optical Dispenser (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“awful”

</title><pros>Pros – close to home, supposedly flexible working hours, good salary</pros>
<cons>Cons – as manager, always working public holidays and sundays with no extra hourly rate or overtime, poor marketing meant business very slow to build, poor staff training</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting”

</title><pros>Pros – Working at BIG W provided me with a rich multicultural experience.  Lots of growth opportunities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes the routine gets dull and extremely boring.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Motivation sessions should be held for employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Department Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The big w brand.”

</title><pros>Pros – large company, good brand, reasonably secure.</pros>
<cons>Cons – work extremely hard for not very much money, and you will not be appreciated for your hard work, you are just another number.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – should learn to look after your good staff, so they will stay and actually treat them like human beings and not a number.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>