<name>Etisalat Software Solutions Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Etisalat-Software-Solutions-Reviews-E475362.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-12-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Software Consultant”

</title><pros>Pros – Except salary I didn't find anything good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No Work life balanceManagement is not at all good</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Test Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst Company to work for - No work life balance”

</title><pros>Pros – Sorry No Pros - But Nice people to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – No Training, No Growth, No Hike, No Internet, No Weekends, Worst work culture.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please concentrate on your work and maintain your and your teams work life balance.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Average Pay, Work Culture depends on individual team, high pressure”

</title><pros>Pros – Gives above average pay.If under a good manager, work-life balance is great!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Heavy Pressure.No process involved whatsoever.Very less flexibility.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Bring in processes.Give more flexibility.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company with best in-hand package and great hikes!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. People with designation of Architects and Manager have best life here.They get handsome salary(Best in the market) , great hikes and perfect work life balance. Even some paymasters can't match that package.2. Very long weekends and weekend sets in Thursday evening.Having a middle east client means Fri(no-work),Saturday and Sunday as Holiday.3. People are very friendly and ready to help peers.4. Great HR team, no layoffs even if you are not productive or don't work for years.5.  Inhouse Customer, so even if you miss deadlines by months  or deliver some buggy code, no one is going to blast you away.6. RMZ infinity is great place to work. Can enjoy the Bay area during lunch and evening snacks.7. Frequent travel to Dubai and Sarjah if you want to travel and make some good money.8. Quality Code base and product design which you won't find in any other COTS products from product development companies(Amdocs/Oracle BRM).9. Bonus in not a part of CTC, its over and above top of CTC ranging between 2 months basic salary to 5 months basic salary.10. Sodexho not a part of CTC and freely given.11. Retention bonus also offered to most of the employees and equals 4 months basic salary.12 . Work from home facility is available.13. Freshers/Junior employees can expect 100% hikes post apprisals.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Fixed working hours, even if you don't have much work you need to put in 40 hours each week.2. Once you get hang of the architecture, new requirements/projects get boring to implement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 1. Give good hikes to people at middle management.2. Keep up the good work.!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>