<name>NthDimenzion Solutions Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/NthDimenzion-Solutions-Reviews-E475353.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-31</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company for Freshers and Mid level to start with...”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. No timing2. No formals..3. This being small, Will get exposure to end to end in each project4.  High level of visibility to the work you have done5. Company in a residential area.. Good restaurants and all near by6. Will be interacting with End client even though we are not that experienced7. Competitive Salary8. There will not be a bench like situation. Will have projects all the time.9. When i had joined company size was 25 now its 40.. So growing10. Technically competent management</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. high level of visibility can create issues if you have done something wrong..:)2. Bus connectivity is less.3. On the other side of IT Hubs..4. Not inside a Business park5. Delivery time pressure6. LEads and Managers will have to work along with Managerial work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Good work.. will miss working with you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Did not enjoy working there.”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. You may get an house near your office as it is in a residential area.2. If you are a fresher u may learn, as ll get a lot of work. So good for freshers not for experienced.3. Some research is going on vedic maths, so if u wish u may participate.4. Your sibling employees are supportive.5. There are no timings.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. They don't appreciate talent.2. Higher management is non deserving.3. They believe in quantity not in quality.4. If you won't listen to your boss you are fired. Well you can be fired anytime even though you have given a lot to the company, and even after you have proven your self to be the best in them always.5. They don't keep there promises. Bonuses are not given every year.6. If you got fired for no reason you won't get your notice period money for sure. And no body is secure there.7. They harass you during Giving your final settlements.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Evaluate the environment during decisions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>