<name>Rheal Software Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Rheal-Software-Reviews-E487209.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-31</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Junior Programmer Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very good company for freshers and less experienced”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Very good environment.2. Hike in every 3,4,6 months based on performance.3. Co-operative colleagues and peers4. Good Exposure and learning.5. Boss is a very good, fair, friendly and a decent person.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Less leaves and very very less holidays.2. Less facilities like tea/coffee, very less celebration and events.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increase the number of leaves please and also add some more holidays. Only 1 holiday for diwali and no holiday even on Eid is a bit of an over-kill.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Programmer Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its awesome”

</title><pros>Pros – Good company to work for freshers only.Friendly environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bad appraisals. And Less opportunity to work on new technology</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management is awesome.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Programmer Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Rheal Software Review”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work culture and colleaguesAlmost no internal politicsGood Managers and Boss is really excellent and jollyGood for entry level candidates</pros>
<cons>Cons – No technical improvement scopeGood for the freshers or 1-2 years experience, you will be caught in the same routine work no new technologies to learn or no self development beyond certain level</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Programmer Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice for freshers”

</title><pros>Pros – You get good hands on , on all the technologies.Get increment after every 3-4 months !!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary increments are upto some limit.Limited growth in salary as well as technology</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Look at the industry standards of compensation.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Programmer Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“asas”

</title><pros>Pros – good working experience.senior management is good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – salary growth is restricted. good for 1-2 year experience.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – good working experience</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>