<name>Z-Wireless Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Z-Wireless-Reviews-E488519.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“review”

</title><pros>Pros – decent ammoutn of business walks through the door</pros>
<cons>Cons – no bennifits and no breaks on handsets</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – not every year is the same as the last</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“STAY AWAY!”

</title><pros>Pros – If you can"sell", you can make OK money at the busier locations.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No home life. Scheduling is often lasst minute and ALWAYS subject to change. There are "clicks" within and if you aren't part of that inner circle, doesn't matter how good you are, they will manufacture a resson to let you go. Poor store and middle management. No benefits, low hourly wage with often unattainable bonus structure.....</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Find people with real management skills. Provide access to benefits for front line employees. Create attanable sales goals and qit "raising the bar" when people start hitting their numbers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Wireless Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wireless Consultant”

</title><pros>Pros – Very friendly work environment. The customer can be told that they are not always right.</pros>
<cons>Cons – For how much money you as a sales rep bring to the computer your pay is absolute crap. 7% of your profit margin. When your manager makes as much from your sale as you do and he/she is still on the sales floor, He/She makes salary and they will only pay you $8 an hour. Oh yeah you have to wait 60 days before receiving your first commission check. And say the customer bough the top of the line device, you made maybe $100 dollars towards your profit margin and then they let their account go delinquint, you as the sales rep who sold the phone to a customer that you are not supposed to judge, now cost you $700 dollars negative in your profit margin. Ten charge back phones can cause you 50 phones of profit.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay your employees more and they might work harder to stay with your company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall it was a good experience and happy I was part of a good team.”

</title><pros>Pros – The rewards for doing well were nice. The experience for sales in general was good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The structure for which rewards were given was harsh. It seemed to be unfairly bias towards one aspect of selling. It made you want to not sell to certain people, and send them elsewhere.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus more on what certain people's strengths are and utilize those instead of forcing them to do something they are terrible at.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company to work for.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people and transparent structure.  If you have a question there is no BS.  They help you understand how, and help you, make more money.  benefits available!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Overtime pay is not available.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep growing.  You are a better company than most in the area.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Wireless Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not terrible, but there is better”

</title><pros>Pros – Z does insurance through Protectcell not Asurion. They have a good emphasis on customer service. They seem to have some good leadership in place at the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working for a retailer you make a lot less money. I felt like the company was pretty cheap. Pushing the most profitable phones with huge spiffs on cheaper phones and services. Not bad for a single person, or a part time job. Great actually for those situations probably. But providing for a wife or family you probably aren't going to get what you need here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Wireless Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wireless consultant”

</title><pros>Pros – Honestly the only pros are probably the hours of operations and the customers...when they're happy.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are a lot of issues with this company; prices are on average double the cost of the competition, terrible management including upper management. This company is growing itself out of business. They change their policies so much it's hard to keep up. They forced all employees to purchase branded expensive polos then within three months they changed the dress code to where we can't even wear the polos we spent money on.  Politics run high in this company if your friends with the right people you can get away with murder. Of course they expect us to charge customers fees that actual Verizon stores and other retailers don't charge. Their number one value is employees first however that's not the case at all. I've never worked for such a poorly ran company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Your horny store managers and district managers are running off amazing talent that could help grow your company</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work, but the atmosphere is a little crowded.”

</title><pros>Pros – You will never find a more closely knit group of employeesWhen business is good, everyone's got a good attitudeLots of down time while still getting paid (mostly due to lack of business)Somewhat flexible hours (as long as nobody else has to have a day off, typically you can have it)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everything is taken on a much too personal level (i.e. there is a lot of misinterpretation regarding the employer/friend line)There is very minimal constructive criticism with new or even senior employees (i.e. there are a lot of raised voices)The amount of profit the store has made in a day directly effects the way the employees are respected</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It's vital that a store is profitable; everyone understands this. The problem is that it isn't part-time employees' responsibility to handle marketing while being paid minimum wage. It needs to be kept in mind that while the employees here are all very close, that does not mean it is our store- the responsibility an owner or manager is by definition more demanding than that of a sales person.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“new to company so far so good”

</title><pros>Pros – new to company so far so good</pros>
<cons>Cons – new to company so far so good, communication hasn't been the greatest.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company needs to treat all employees better”

</title><pros>Pros – There are many rewards programs</pros>
<cons>Cons – No recognition. Lies about management. Unfair rewards</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>