<name>I-Flow Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/I-Flow-Reviews-E4881.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-03-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good People, I-Flow is a Medical Device Company, KCC is Consumer Products.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people, recognition for people when they do something that matters.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is a problem at the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get real about appropriate pay to attract and more importantly to retain employees.  The pay at I-Flow is below the area and industry.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“a Kimberly-Clark company in the midst of getting KC-ized”

</title><pros>Pros – multicultural workforce, nice people, lots of work to do</pros>
<cons>Cons – many new systems due to new KC systems, negative management at leadership level</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – For the GM, the negative approach of "it will not be like this next year..."  does not inspire, it does not provide a vision of where we will be, try a positive view or plan on losing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Mid-Mangement Role (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Competent and professional overall.”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice peopleGreat productTeam environmentOn par with regulations</pros>
<cons>Cons – Clock watchersSome dept heads are less than professional</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Should treat employees in a more professional manner.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“places to work”

</title><pros>Pros – the company has a good benefits package, lots of flexibility, and excellent resources to support product sales. management provides as much support as possible.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the cons of this job were...my  long term goals are not to be involved in medical sales. creating a target list and constantly revising is not my forte.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – there has to be a way to better communicate with hundreds of people all over the country. email, conference calls with tms.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>