<name>e-Procurement Technologies Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/e-Procurement-Technologies-Reviews-E490404.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-06-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Deputy Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent Team work”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Team Work2. Every member of the team is highly and well qualified</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Lack of Management policy</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not for those who want a good position as per experience”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. You will get chance to work some very good project and fresh development if you have good knowledge + experience.2. During your tenure you can get to learn a lot of new things with some highly qualified team mates.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. If you are working in old application(JSP-Servlet) then you won't learn anything and also won't get chance to work in other good projects until tell the management.2. You won't get reward even if you deserve. Only a few selected people gets this chance.3. To get a good position in company(TL, Module lead), you need to have a very good relation with existing TL and management and do any work provided to you without questions.4. Increment process is also not transparent.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 1. Please stand by the employee in their problems. Support them. Reward them if they deserve.2. Don't cheat the employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Executive In Sales & Marketing (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Back Office job & Spportive Staff.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Boss is not treated as their employees.Everyday they are giving pressure to the employees & not fair.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please do fair treatment with employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>