<name>Wealth-X Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Wealth-X-Reviews-E494231.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“hard work but rewarding”

</title><pros>Pros – the company is growing fast and looking to promote people, as well as international postings</pros>
<cons>Cons – startups can sometimes be confusing and lack formal structure that people want.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – the CEO needs to communicate more</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Les MisĂŠrables”

</title><pros>Pros – -Can listen to music in the office-Actual work performed as an Analyst is very interesting and insightful</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Management is inexperienced and lacks business acumen, at all levels-Wealth-X's Corporate Culture: employees are expendable because of the economy, so exploit them until they quite or find better opportunities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Exporting research to developing countries is not a long-term solution - clients will eventually notice the change in research quality</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very nice company”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly environment. For the company work is work.You have to be really committed to what you doing.Anyways your hard work will be paid.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long working hours for workers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat workers well, cause they deserve it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Internship opportunity”

</title><pros>Pros – High growth company that encourages innovative ideas. Close working opportunities with management team.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some work may be repetitive. Job role may not be so clearly defined (for interns).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Editor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cool company, poor management and career”

</title><pros>Pros – Somewhat interesting work. Keep up with current events and wealth trends of super rich people. The company product is interesting and useful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Dead end; no opportunity for career advancement, everyone who has managed to have been promoted are still listless and wandering losers. Company has terribly poor communication among its several international branches. Executive management is pretentious and behaves with an air superiority.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The wealth X product and intelligence is great, useful, and very valuable. So you should highly considering treating well and respective the analysts and editors who are doing all of the grunt work and 97% of the entirety of your operations.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Electronic sweatshop”

</title><pros>Pros – Very casual environment, flexible hours (you still need to work at least 10 hours a day to complete assignments).</pros>
<cons>Cons – No corporate culture whatsoever. Company tries to make a successful global appearance but in reality it is an electronic sweatshop with the biggest offices in India and China (shut down the New York Office).  Extremely underpaid, unhappy employes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dead end”

</title><pros>Pros – Get to set your own schedule and learn some new research techniques.  Little oversight, lots of people waste time at work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Start up environment (long hours, employees are always overworked, insultingly underpaid) minus the usual start up perks (no equity or incentive plans, no reasonable expectations of raises or promotions, company success is not tied to yours). Poor and inaccessible management structure with no attention payed to happiness or success of employees. Poor to non-existant corporate culture (most employees show up, work 10 hours without talking to anyone else, leave and go home to job-search).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create an incentive plan, pay attention to the success and happiness of employees, work proactively to create a good corporate culture. Most importantly, improve quality of employees hired. Do not get poor interns and outsourced labor just because its free or cheap. Ultimately, take long term view to building a start up instead of trying to improve the bottom line at lowest possible cost to get sold.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>