<name>CDAC Hyderabad Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/CDAC-Hyderabad-Reviews-E495200.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer - I (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“cdac”

</title><pros>Pros – good environment to work, new technology to learn is good</pros>
<cons>Cons – they send to teach for pg-diploma students</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – no</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Keep it as last option”

</title><pros>Pros – You will have a good learning experience in the early stages of your career, after 1 year you will realise you had been working on outdated technologies. Highly recommended to switch after 1 year else you may end up in spoiling your career.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In most of the teams no process model is followed, some TL's doesn't know what are the actual objective of the project also they possess poor management skills you will be asked to revert back after coding for 2-3 months.Management is not concerned about credibility of employee</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Kindly follow some process while doing any project also don't take employee for granted.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The worst organization in Hyderabad”

</title><pros>Pros – Nothing. Please don't spoil your career by joining in this company because the chances are you may be working under a person who doesn't know the technical stuff or he/she doesn't know even how to manage project</pros>
<cons>Cons – They expect some of the best talent to join their company but make them work on outdated technologies which have no standards.All the power is bestowed with team leads only. If the TL is not the fit candidate, then the only option for a new joinee is to leave the company.No proper HR policies. They are mere puppets.Lot of internal politics.If you have no project, then you are pushed into training department.No SDLC is followed. You are the client, developer,tester,architect,admin. If anything goes wrong then you are the only one to be seriously blamed.All the projects look like btech projects. They do not even qualify to be at enterprise level.Senior officers are present just to come to office,chitchat,read newspapers, do their personal work and leave office.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Nothing. Its the government organization!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If no other option only then only u go for this”

</title><pros>Pros – nothing to share it's true</pros>
<cons>Cons – Team leads dont know anythng.They dont work also.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Trainee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“trainee”

</title><pros>Pros – not good for professional growth</pros>
<cons>Cons – no professional growth but personally good environment</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – go for it</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to learn, not good place to earn”

</title><pros>Pros – good place to learn, one can learn many thin gin their own, full independence is given</pros>
<cons>Cons – No earnings, no commercial perspective</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – no proper project management</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good at early career stages, could definitely provide better knowledge than outside”

</title><pros>Pros – minimal bureaucray .work on some good technologies and can get different job rolescan also get to work on areas of your interest</pros>
<cons>Cons – salary revision is fixednot a good structure for long term career growthlacks interaction with outside world  ,in terms of using  technical expertise ,which could be problem in some cases</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – policy making is in wrong hands. Incompetent people are also sitting top in hierarchy. Some guys are chatter boxes and complete  nonsence</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>