<name>People Interactive Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/People-Interactive-Reviews-E497825.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good start for fresher”

</title><pros>Pros – will get to work on large scale website , coding standard is high and follow processes</pros>
<cons>Cons – it is software product based company , so most of the websites are all ready developed  , will not get chance to develop from scatch</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good enough....not bad”

</title><pros>Pros – every month they organize party,good environment,</pros>
<cons>Cons – work is limited to your designation</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Regional Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Company To Work For............”

</title><pros>Pros – Tere are many pros but I would like to mention a few like Brand Value,Culture,Job Satisfaction,Team,Compensations,Systems,</pros>
<cons>Cons – Would Not Like To Specify But They Need to Have Higher Transperency Levels.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Control Attrition/Increase Transperency/Invest More On Branding.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice company to work”

</title><pros>Pros – NIce work environment, HIgh traffic website, monthly parties</pros>
<cons>Cons – All the guju people at senior positions, thats not a con though as they are sweet  :D !!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>UI Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible work timing. Good coordination for wok.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing as down side, which I can mention.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – -</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sharpen your Skills”

</title><pros>Pros – There is a constant push to bring the best out of youVery dynamic approach towards marketingVery Stable and growing in leaps and bouncesFocused in learning every curve whether its up or down</pros>
<cons>Cons – MicromanagementSuccess should be rewardedBias doesn't take an organisation any where</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Find the once that are really talentedSwallow the Ego when you see the talentQualification has got nothing to do with talent</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-27</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Relation Advisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its well developed company, In this process we will get vry gud benefits”

</title><pros>Pros – Good environment, Friendly with all & we have good benefits to work here</pros>
<cons>Cons – I don't find that in this process.......</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Good managements...........</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>GM - Information Systems (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very Good ... Stable company ...”

</title><pros>Pros – Good company from career growth & stability point of view. Management is very understanding and encourage work / life balance. Also the encouraged by management is employee friendly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Teams work on stable technology and thus there are few chances to explore cutting edge technology. Newer technologies are adopted only when there is bandwidth to explore & implement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep it up with your good work !!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>User Interface Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good to work. But not too happening”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work environment. Flexible timing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Kinda dull for a dot com. People are friendly but reserved</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Neutral”

</title><pros>Pros – Good open learning platform. Pioneer in Mobile VAS industry</pros>
<cons>Cons – Need more focus on new emerging technologies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Relationship Advisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its a Good Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Becoz of its Good Salary Scales,Incentives,Supportive Managerial Staff.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No holidays,Target Stress,Long Timings etc</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They should allows some Holidays just like Diwali,Dussera etc.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Affiliate Online Marketing Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A healthy environment to work within for a fresher and better learning experience but lacks future.”

</title><pros>Pros – The senior positions here are more than eager to help you out with your queries and draw backs. the environment is lucrative enough for a fresher to learn and improve and also helps one to sync work life and personal life better. Punctuality is on the Lenient part as far as the performance is not bothered. Ample of ground events and exercises. Tests and learning camps.</pros>
<cons>Cons – slow and strenuous growth. Though annual appraisals and promotion are promised, they fail to satisfy in terms of remuneration. No uniformity in terms of appraisals and pseudo strategies with regards to performance assessment and employee satisfaction.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good job”

</title><pros>Pros – A good job  to work with at the start.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bad management. Good for people who can talk crap</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to improve</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working at People Interactive was fun , enjoyable and had a wonderful time learning and exploring new technologies”

</title><pros>Pros – The company portals have a market brand value / image.It promotes innovative thinking / solutions.The company has a employee friendly environment and HR works hard to promote team work and conducts stress busting , team building exercises.</pros>
<cons>Cons – For employees there is scope to grow up and learn up to a medium management level but anything beyond that its difficult since all the top spots are filled and occupied by long term employees.Although they provide a lot of tax saving schemes, it is difficult to get a good/satisfying pay hike.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The company could look to spawn off into a new vertical to allow some of the employees a new challenge and to explore new avenues of growth.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>TRAINEE SOFTWARE Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“till now is good currently going thru training”

</title><pros>Pros – stable job , using advance framework for php</pros>
<cons>Cons – its product development company so u r working on only one product</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – nothing</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager Online Marketing (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Satisfied”

</title><pros>Pros – Informal work environment & flexible attitudes</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of Recognition and bad paymasters</cons>
<advice-to-management> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>