<name>I Wish Lessons Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/I-Wish-Lessons-Reviews-E498059.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-08-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Human Resources Manager/Public Relations Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Beware of shaky financial strategy”

</title><pros>Pros – Great concept, talented coaches/event staff/corporate staff... fun events.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Financial structure of the company -overall- is shaky. Company doesn't have enough capital on reserve to pay employees' earned wages and relies on profits to cover costs. Not a solid foundation.CEO micromanages key employees, while ignoring the needs of others.Company rolled out nationally with shaky strategy to entrench in markets, result has been a lot of cancelled classes, a lot of angry customers. Do not envy the customer service team at all.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – CEO - rethink the decision to manage company finances and funding yourself. You're just not that good at it and really could benefit from outside help. The place you excel is in planning, creative and employee motivation - get someone to handle the money side and focus on your strengths, it will yield better results for the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Instructor/"Coach" (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Constantly unpaid, Very disorganized.”

</title><pros>Pros – The classes are fun to teach. Co-workers work close with each other and give great respect for one another.  Venues are very accommodating.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They do not pay their employees and if they do, the checks bounce.  Scheduling is a constant nightmare not only for the consumers but the employees too. (They once sent all the "students" to a completely different restaurant 30 minutes away from the right venue!)  They do not refund their consumers when applicable.  They(administration) do not have any knowledge of the product(s) they are teaching.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get out of Atlanta!  We don't want your kind of shady business practices here!  You are not welcome here!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Refusal to Pay Wages Earned”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible hoursWork remotelyGood concept for a company</pros>
<cons>Cons – THEY DO NOT PAY THEIR EMPLOYEESThere isn't much more to say than that. They are disorganized, dishonest, run by a highly incompetent CEO, and apt to put blame for their failings on your head.They provide a poor service, despite an excellent concept.They do not pay you on time, if at all.They will communicate with you, the employee, only as long as they think they can get away with not paying you etc.Once you start expressing disinterest in being "smoothed over" they will cease and desist all communications.They put you in extremely difficult positions that make it very difficult to do your job properly.Work here at your own risk. If you do, make sure to get EVERYTHING in writing and as detailed as possible.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay your employees and start offering better service.Also, poor customer service complaints are on YOUR head, CEO.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>