<name>U-Stor Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/U-Stor-Reviews-E501549.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-05-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Property Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Seems so promising and then you learn...”

</title><pros>Pros – -company offers decent bonus incentives-gave me the time off i requested when needed-95% freedom, no bosses around but twice a month or so-free apartment</pros>
<cons>Cons – -minimum wage-very, very heavily dependent on sales-4 hours of weekly marketing with horrific advice-management is extremely distant. If called- almost never answer-no health insurance or other important benefits-air conditioners/heaters in apartments are so weak that it is useless to use them (no hope for upgrade's either)-any maintenance or fixes are expected by you-company "cleans house" of its employees every so often-require 2 people to be hired at the same time and live together on=site(one works full time, other part time) and combined work either 6 days a week (if your lucky) or 7 days a week with one allowed day off a month (if approved).-expected to answer phone calls/ door knocks after hours (even if it's 2 am, otherwise customer complaints will bar you)-managers are allowed any time to enter your apartment-$400 pet fee each pet!-you're expected to weed-eat, leaf blow, snow plow, de-ice or any other preventative maintenance on the entirety of the storage facilities grounds-grounds are worn down and storage units are hard to sell because of the cruddy look-alarm system for units is ridiculously fidgety and unreliable. I spent many nights checking on "potential threats" out on the grounds and nothing was there because the alarm went off for no reason-management seems as though they are on a "team" and your the competitor-cockroaches in unitsI worked there for five months. In the beginning I was told I was doing amazing (I sold the most units several weeks in a row) but as winter hit and sales drop (no one wants to move in the winter) all of a sudden things go sour. They warned me to increase my sales which I told them I was doing my best and not even two weeks later (4 days after christmas!) My district manager came in and fired me and told me I had 7 days to move out of the apartment. With no job and no where to go I had to move back in with my parents. The managers had no remorse and cared nothing for me or my wife only about sales. Upper management comes every few months to tell you how you need to improve. I started there and the occupancy for units was 88.9%, When they fired me for lack of sales the facility was almost at 92%. I have never been treated so low or so much like trash as the day of my termination. I would never recommend working here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Build relationships and give useful advice on improving performance. DO TV OR RADIO ADVERTISING. The 80+ hours I spent marketing for the company (handing out fliers and other junk) never brought me a single customer! Not one! Spend the extra money and get it out there the right way! Check up on your facilities more often and make sure that you actually offer a way to retaliate yourself rather than just assuming the managers suddenly became comatose.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>