<name>XTB Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/XTB-Reviews-E502624.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-07-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Junior Account Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Junior Account Manager Intership”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice place to work in. Young and friendly team.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Many different task to be carried out, from phone calls to sending email to writing technical analysis.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Broker Assistant Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice start for a brokerage career”

</title><pros>Pros – learn more about financial markets; monitor their evolution; daily analysis and briefing sessions; build on sales skills; enhance self-confidence during telephone conversations</pros>
<cons>Cons – work gets boring after a while; training starts with the very basics; training is not so in-depth; knowledge acquired in intermediate level; just sales skills are utilized most of the time</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Portfolio Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“For a beginner its ok.”

</title><pros>Pros – The support and time given is good. Theres a scope for freshers as they can share there ideas. You dont have to be under pressure while working.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The approach should be more positive and a lot has to be done by the technical analyst in each and every currency pair and commodities.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get a better analyst or have four analyst working and focusing on different pairs and commodities and should be well aware of the present global scenario.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>