<name>J-Curve Technologies Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/J-Curve-Technologies-Reviews-E504608.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Support Level II (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Company that is always looking to improve and grow its model the right way.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great EnvironmentGreat PeopleEmployees are held accountableMonthly Raffles for the EmployeesManagement cares about their Employees401k available</pros>
<cons>Cons – no covered parkingBenefits could be bettertracking tools could be a little less user intensiveall and all not to many Cons</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the great attitude going. Keep the encouragement to your employees coming, and do not stop showing your employees recognitions for their hard work.Since these are all things the management does already, keep doing it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tech/Management/Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“J-Curve is a tech support center that really offers many bonuses that other support centers do not.”

</title><pros>Pros – J-Curve has a very unique business model that services many different technology related businesses. J-Curve is unique in that they manage their support cases by leveraging their techs across multiple accounts. This allows their technicians to really learn a variety of technical concepts but it also gives them a peek at how other businesses  and support centers operate behind the scenes.For a person who is motivated to learn and grow in every way possible to advance their career this is a really unique environment and can help them build a really good resume. There are many opportunities for employees of J-Curve to advance in several areas if they  are motivated and creative about how they approach the job. I worked at J-Curve for five years and was given the opportunity to build the foundation for my career post J-Curve.J-Curve takes a much more fair approach to the standard call center type model. Employees will not be subjected to schedules that change every week, will normally be ASKED to work holidays when needed as opposed to being forced, and will generally be treated like a person (when compared to how other support centers operate)During my time there the metrics and Quality assurance were based on doing the right things rather than just checking boxes on a binary report card.The management team at J-Curve was always "pulling in the same direction". While it may not have always been apparent at J-Curve we had some ideas of what was right for the company and no one member of the team was allowed to dictate course that didn't align itself with their direction.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I see some negative reviews here and this can be a negative position for people who are looking for the easy ride through a standard corporate environment. J-Curve is the kind of company where you will often have to roll up your sleeves and may not always be afforded all of the perks of working at a larger company.Sometimes at J-Curve things may be lost in the hustle and bustle of getting the job done and you may encounter a glass ceiling if you are not willing to be very proactive in showing what you can do or have trouble following the rules.Sometimes working in a small company like J-Curve can feel like you are running in a hamster wheel but from my experience this is common in smaller companies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't turn into a real call center. Figure out what you want to do and stick with it. Stay away from flavor of the week and march toward your vision. Don't waste time with knee jerk reactions to things outside your control, just keep moving forward.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Lead (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Complete lack of leadership”

</title><pros>Pros – - Magnificent stories and promises given about potential career development and a "Non-Call Center Call Center"-Charismatic CEO who appears to take genuine interest in your well-being</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Pay rate only significantly changes if promoted (.05 to 0.25 annual raises)- Promotes people into management positions and uses their lack of experience as reason not to pay sufficiently. As soon as individuals are able to excel at the job duties given, position is changed and lack of experience in new responsibilities are used as reason not to increase pay.- Will go long spans of time with crucial roles unfilled including HR(over 6 month gap in 2012), CFO, and Lower/Mid management positions. Management team reduced from 13 (1 Manager of Operations, 2 Supervisors, 8 team leads, 2 QA) to 4 (2 Supervisors, 2 Team Leads).within 18 months. Responsibilities redistributed with no increase to pay.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Seek employment elsewhere.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>VOIP Technical Support L1 (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“All their great leadership is gone”

</title><pros>Pros – beats unemployment and you can rely on getting paid when they said they will pay you</pros>
<cons>Cons – really bad hoursinstead of giving you actual raises they give you some small number, i got a 5 cent raise.....They fired all their great leaders to avoid having to pay them any type of salary raise on annual review dates, they decided to let them all go and promote more people, get thisreally lack communicationnot only will they get rid of people, they will also completely sabatoge that persons reputation by blaming everything that has happened on them, didn't get your review because so and so was let go, that's why we fired em, sorry!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – hear your people out, stop hiding behind "this is what's best for the company"</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>L1 VOIP (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“horrible place to work, and I used to work at 2wire”

</title><pros>Pros – They don't really care if you take long lunches, they are relaxed with days off and time off</pros>
<cons>Cons – if you used to the regular call center atmosphere this is exactly like it, I came here being promised a great work atmosphere but was met with the same sweatshop type job as I had at 2wire. They pay very small wages for the stuff they ask for, other places pay alot more. Stay away</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take better care of your customers, I felt bad how they went on about how much they make with all their customers do to charging alot more</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Tech (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“call center sweat shop paying poverty wages and wanting high end techs”

</title><pros>Pros – -The building is air conditioned-they don't whip you-you can be on break for hours without them noticing-don't care about quality as long as you answer calls-they never fire you no matter how late you are or how many absences lol</pros>
<cons>Cons – -they rip off their customers and lie constantly to them-poverty wages-poor leadership from CEO-NO leadership-smoke and mirrors culture, they talk a big up front but severely lack "the walk"-they promise high end techs to their customers but instead pay everyone minimum wage-absolutely 0 career oppurtunities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – find a new business model</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“J-Curve Technologies”

</title><pros>Pros – Some good emps - questionable business model - when customer out grows J-Curve's shared model they lose them to a real dedicated call center company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Needs a new CEO and CFO - No direction huge EGO!  - Super High turn-over!</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>