<name>Caliber Hunt - A Candidate Portal Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Caliber-Hunt-A-Candidate-Portal-Reviews-E504809.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-03-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Recruitment Head (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Right place for professionals with dedication and determination along with fun”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. Small enthusiastic crowd2. Business Module is entirely different from any kind of Recruitment related entity3. Every idea and individuality is  appreciated and valued4. Professionals are not considered as Robots5. CH - ACP appreciates individuals who do not just dream to succeed , instead work for it6. Believes strongly in team contribution rather than individual contribution7. Team is filled with Like-minded people which contributes to accomplishing assigned targets</pros>
<cons>Cons – Current office Location needs to be changed, as team mates time management gets affected at some point of time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to induce more work pressure along with maintaining the existing family atmosphere as there could always be a possibility of taking things for granted.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-01</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Content Management Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Place with right professional values and each individual given priority”

</title><pros>Pros – CH-ACP has a small team working efficiently with a single focus. Highly potential and right focus. CH-ACP believes in working together and wining together.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The office location need to be changed for better output.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Appreciate the family environment with serious work nature.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Freelancer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A most favorable organization for talents who are not appreciated ever”

</title><pros>Pros – CH - ACP is a company which aims to satisfy the demand of employees or common human being  rather than merely satisfying its business demand.Its a best place for employees of CH - ACP to learn and grow, as one gets the opportunity to increase knowledge from all levels</pros>
<cons>Cons – Due to location constraints, organization is not able to reach out to the right people who would appreciate and benefit from their services. Since its a new innovation, public would take time to know more about the organization</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to think on increasing the company brand value in the market, in-order to reach out to the public</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-31</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Operation Head (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A solid platform to professionals who would want to see a true recruiter within them”

</title><pros>Pros – For those who wish to grow its the best place with lot of challenges to accomplish and innovation to reach the height. Experience with CH - ACP built in a confidence within me and taught me never to say quit. In CH - ACP together with our team mates and clients we have proved that every problems comes with a solutions. The way we look towards or for solutions makes us different from the usual.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The business module is niche and new which brings in a lot of queries within public to basically understand how different CH - ACP is from any other recruitment related patterns.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It is essential to introduce a pattern which would educate the public about individual benefits they would experience through the business pattern (module) CH - ACP follows.The cause of Referral Program initiated by CH - ACP and its benefits extended to public needs to be educated and brought into action, in-order to withstand the actual cause of CH - ACP's existence (help a true candidate no longer experience the wrath of recession, frustration of unprofessional managers, unappreciative work culture, long wait of new employment, disruption for personal and professional peace).</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Recruiter (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Opportunity to learn about Recruitment”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity to learn about recruitment and different domains</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited employees to communicate and share</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its been quite magnificent, enjoying my role and responsibilities.”

</title><pros>Pros – Complete authority.Good ambience and crowd.Quite challenging.Company with good intention.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Its small organization just starting to grow.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>