<name>LINE-X Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/LINE-X-Reviews-E505509.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-09-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Proud to have been there.”

</title><pros>Pros – There is a real sense of committment to doing the job right at that place. They really care about the customers and take real pride in the work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It can get unexpectedly busy very quickly and have to stay late sometimes to make the customers and dealerships happy. Working with the new truck dealerships can be a double edged sword sometimes - nice to have the work, but they always want to go to the head of the line.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>District Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A nice stepping stone, but an adolescent company”

</title><pros>Pros – The people in the field are great and the franchises are interesting and keep you on your toes. If you work in Ops, the VP is good natured and fun. Once you earn respect, there is substantial autonomy. You get the day before or the day after Christmas off and the company phone is an iPhone.  Travel is fun at first and you rack up miles and points.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Under the new management, there are a lot of secrets and a lot of decisions made in a vacuum (I.e. without input from the functions that do the work). The CEO leads lofty and unsupported goals like wanting to grow 34% in a year but having no plan or real grounding on how to make it happen. Women and minorities are actively discriminated against and called bad things ever since the move of corporate from California to Alabama. The pay is not commensurate and it is varied across people of the same job (me 65, colleague 45k for the same job) and they're ok with that. Everyone is sacrificing long term stability for short term profitability to make the investment firm more money so they can sell soon, but they just bought a big company that left LINE-X cash poor and the employees suffer. I'm all for capitalism as long as its not unethical, but management consistently takes advantage. It's a good ol' boys club.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Focus on (honestly) doing right by the customer and your employees and the money will follow. Act inconsistently with your words and you will lose talented employees and franchisees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Like working for a dysfunctional family”

</title><pros>Pros – Relaxed atmosphere, family environment, people tend to be very friendly</pros>
<cons>Cons – Clique-ish leadership, highly disorganized, they don't always realize what they want or how to move forward with projects</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>