<name>C-Cubed Solutions Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/C-Cubed-Solutions-Reviews-E510445.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-01-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Support Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good to start”

</title><pros>Pros – Good to start your career.</pros>
<cons>Cons – After few years you will start feeling stagnant.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>MIS Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good to work in this company”

</title><pros>Pros – we can work without any pressure</pros>
<cons>Cons – everyone have only one problem to work in this company and that is our salary</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please increase agents salary and do the need full</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I had never thought I would fall in this mess!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Best for those who hate themselves and would like to undergo some torture.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sony USA's support is provided by C-cubed solutions(located in bangalore,INDIA). I worked over there for 4-5 months and the working conditions were like hell, so I left that blood sucking firm. They ask us to handle 3 chats at a time. EVEN IF ONE CUSTOMER NEEDS FULL ATTENTION.THey pay $180 a month. plus DLOPs (double loss of pay if taken a leave unexpectedly)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – My advice is: Better start to rear some cattle. This is the best thing your company can do</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Support (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good as first job and for gaining experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Environment, colleagues and experienced seniors</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor transport, food and management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please don't just ask the employees if they have  any problem... try to resolve them also...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Technical Support Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“bad”

</title><pros>Pros – bad management and bad environment no way to grow</pros>
<cons>Cons – every one there owner and senior like boss</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – make good management</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>SME (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company for a beginner”

</title><pros>Pros – Good support and salary in the class.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No proper management and facility</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Create SOPs and follow them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Content Writer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Till now no issues”

</title><pros>Pros – Comparatively high salary and 5 day a week work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – HR and admin department have bad communication and zero coordination with employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve the communications, be more clear in decision making.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior IT Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An elegantly flopped company with neither glue nor screws!”

</title><pros>Pros – Good for the freshers as they can will learn more with technical and troubleshooting knowledge.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not for the experience. Poor management and no scope of growth for the employee.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please do think the employee(s) as a family and provide the necessary benefits and equal opportunities so that they will remain loyal to the company. Hiring new inexperience candidates and  ignoring the experience ones will bring no good fortune for the company and the Business.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Quality Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company to gain  Experience and to know about the corporate world.”

</title><pros>Pros – The Best thing about the company is that it teaches a lot of things for the fresher who steps in to  the corporate world. Especially the Explore talent process is the best process were the work is fun, once you start making good sales you will be kings for yourself.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The only bad thing abt the company is it gives growth with good positions with no increment in the salary..!!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Should work on employes satisfaction so that attrition rate can be decreased.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>