<name>Deft Infosystems Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Deft-Infosystems-Reviews-E512352.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-12-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Team of  Young and Energetic Technocrats”

</title><pros>Pros – Good working Environment and no pressure you can feel like in other companies .Management respect ideas of individuals and implement them as per requirement .Job security and career growth is biggest  things for any employee .</pros>
<cons>Cons – Liberal behaviour of Management and no work pressure . Some time referral clients extend their work and we have to modify it again and again . company easily accept change request  .</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Proper Documentation to be provide and Change request form to be followed  . Start of the project all documentation to be done .</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Web Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Deft Infosystems pvt. ltd is a good platform for learning in the field of management or technology.”

</title><pros>Pros – Management is cooperative and understand work ethics.There is Proper guidance to juniors by seniors and healthy work environment.Innovative ideas are welcome and team work is promoted for overall development of organization.Employment satisfaction is there, with job security.Employee retention & engagement  is given as first preference so as to achieve organizational goal.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Here based on the time delivery of govt & non govt projects, flexibility of timing is reduced so as to make the employee focused about their associated projects.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>