<name>gen-E Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/gen-E-Reviews-E513957.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Potential and Growing Company with Experienced and Intelligent People”

</title><pros>Pros – - One of the strongest products in the market known as Resolve which continues to grow and develop into a industry changing software.- Amazing people and leadership and bringing in even more intelligent and hard working staff.- Start up feel and excitement to be part of a team that has much to conquer and a lot toprove.- Fast paced environment overall with good stress workload. Encourages employees to go beyond their comfort zone and challenges them to build their skill-sets.- Great resources on hand with great benefits and Monday breakfast</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Location is beautiful but a bit out of nowhere</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Great job, continue to assist in giving well specified tasks and obtainable expectations</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Development Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Business Development Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Co workers were good Products were solid</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of marketing focus Upper management think of themselves only</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Empower your employees to act on own</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great product, not such a great leadership culture.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good, friendly people.Product is top of industryGreat view of the Pacific Ocean in the San Clemente office.Few unnecessary meetings.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Culture feels sometimes like that of a 1990s tech company.No phones for non-managers.Company has a huge identity crisis with regards to whether it will be a tech company or a consulting services company.Not a place to innovate.Lots of pressure to complete tasks without solid design principles.  This causes issues downstream which would not have arisen with well planned execution.The culture favors those who avoid rocking the boat and are willing to accept mediocrity in execution.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Seems like you bit off more than you could chew in 2013 and maybe the layoffs in August were a good thing.  Hopefully, you'll find the right mix in 2014 and bring in the revenues.  And down the road, maybe top talent will again be drawn to gen-E.  Resolve is a great product, but poor business/engineering choices can ruin this company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worked in San Clemente, CA”

</title><pros>Pros – I didn't see any significant "pros" to working at gen-E. The leadership team doesn't know how to lead a decent team of professionals like they had. All of the truly professional staff have jumped their sinking ship.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I worked there for almost 2  years and quit. The hours are long, uncompensated, and the leadership team can't communicate or won't communicate. I was overworked and needed assistance which the CTO kept promising and NEVER intended to keep his promises. They don't care about their employees. They think most people are motivated by money and while that is true to a degree, we need much more than that. We need communication of expected tasks, inclusion in the work flow, really working together as a team, and kept promises. Stop criticizing the staff who have a different and perhaps more professional method of doing things. These things are business killers. The word about gen-E is out on the street. The recruiters who have approached have heard some real  horror stories about working.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – See Cons.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“All of the sizzle of a startup, fast moving and best product in the space, experience to back what they do.”

</title><pros>Pros – gen-E has been an evolving company.  It started as a consulting firm dealing exclusively with improving NOC operations through software, services, and application of best practices.  With that experience and delivery personal, they have evolved into a software company that carries the large experience and consulting practice but also has a transformational IT Process Automation solution that scales to support very large telecom customers, large financial services firms, and anyone looking to reduce the cost and improve the efficiency of IT Operations.  In many good ways, they are still "small" in the sense of nimble and responsive, but they also carry significant years of "experience" as well.  I have worked in the software business my entire career and have never been so excited or energized than when I have worked at gen-E.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Being small, you are sometimes expected to wear many hats.  Folks who have worked "in a box" for large companies may find discomfort in wearing many hats.  It takes a start up, can do mentality working for a firm like this.  Sometimes the hours can be long, the work can be bursty (slow days, then intense days) but the rewards are all there.  Senior leadership have a plan and direction, sometimes they do not articulate it to everyone.  But I have personally found that if you take the time to patiently explain a position and solution, they will always take in the information and consider it.  So patience is sometimes required as everyone is very busy.  I remain neutral on work life balance because it is a start up and up to each individual to "throttle" the work.  Everyone is understanding and accommodating as long as you get it done!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Think big, stay on course, continue to recognize and value your employees.  Together we will all make it happen as a team!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“All around awesome place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – I have a background in sales but not software sales. genE hired me in spite of a lack of software experience, and they have bent over backwards to get me up to speed. Because of that, doors are now open to me that were closed two years ago.Unlike lots of other sales jobs, at gen-E I have the ability to sell a product that I really believe in.The company is poised to become the leader in a huge market and we have a genuinely unique value proposition that none of our competitors can match.</pros>
<cons>Cons – genE is growing faster than it can hire. There is important work that needs doing that is going undone.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Product Management”

</title><pros>Pros – Their Resolve software product has potential.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nepotism pervades the leadership team.  Venture Capital firm is not actively involved or is not monitoring critical business metrics.  Intolerable employee turnover.  No "Open Door" management team policy.  Unable to attract and retain talent.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Let some else qualified lead this company.  Company needs seasoned Industry Professionals that know how to lead, motivate and attract talented personnel as well as inspire employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best company I've ever work for!”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are incredibly nice. Management is flexible and definitely shows caring and respect toward employees. The culture is great, people are provided a tremendous degree of automony and are really able to impact the business.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The culture is great if you're a self-starter. Those who don't show initiative and a willingness to ask questions won't do well at gen-E.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make a point to clearly communicate regularly the stragies, goals and objectives of the company, and let us know how we're doing against our plan. Spend a little more time with new hires, setting expectations and orienting them to the company and your department.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-10</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Growing Company, exciting time to join”

</title><pros>Pros – This company is rapidly growing in 2012, and anyone joining in the future has the opportunity to have a huge impact on their department and the future of the business. There isn't a ton of red tape restricting associates from making changes and introducing new ideas and processes. gen-E has a solid, innovative product, management is accessible and personable, compensation is fair in my opinion. The culture is in the process of being defined as the company transitions to the next level. I've worked for extremely large corporations and it's very refreshing and energizing to work at a company that is in growth mode and open to new perspectives.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As said above, the company is rapidly growing, and if you're not a self-starter with passion and excitement for what you do best, get out of the way! You won't do well here if you're someone just looking for a job instead of a career path and exciting chance to make an impact. Is that a con? Only for certain people.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to be open with your associates and maintain consistent communication. Keep up the good work, the new recruits coming in have been stellar and the existing backbone of the company is passionate about the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-27</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – I have been with gen-E for the past 3 years and have been extremely active in the incredible growth and progress that the company has made over the past few years.  We are in high growth mode and constantly looking for great, motivated and enthusiastic, and "top of their game" talent.  The associates here have incredible internal drive to succeed and excel and this makes it a very exciting work environment.  This is a great time to be a part of this company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The current environment is best suited to people that are self-motivated, know their jobs extremely well, and can hit the ground running.  There is not much room for those that like a neat task list of 'to do' items each day, but rather individuals that are constantly looking around for what needs to be done and how can I help.  The environment is great for the self-starters, maybe not for those awaiting direction.  Not sure that's a con, but rather a fit issue.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Share, communicate, stay involved and keep that small company feeling as we grown to number one!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Small, efficient company with some great employees”

</title><pros>Pros – Small company, great learning experience, exposure to many new and exciting technologies, work is done very quickly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The workplace is a little cold, and the quickness with which products are sent out take a toll on the employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employees could be better compensated.  Look at industry averages for salary, overtime, and bouses.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>