<name>B24 e Solutions Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/B24-e-Solutions-Reviews-E513124.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-01</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best Start-up to work with”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent work culture, supportive team members and management.Learning curve is excellent, so i will suggest this company to every fresher.</pros>
<cons>Cons – some minor issues with the finances, sure they are going to resolve with the market up-trends.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work......</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good environment for work”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of work and very cooperative environment with guidance and good structure for running projects and also good and talented staff in all segement</pros>
<cons>Cons – Less salary in terms of cash , CTC is good and have to work on weekends to meet timeline and no extra payment , salary delay sometimes</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Level of company has reached zero”

</title><pros>Pros – 2 year ago environment, project and teams were good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Now all seniors has left and only freshers are working in this company. Bad Management, facing crisis from last two year. Not clearing due of Ex Employee.Salary is 3 month late and also give partially.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No Advice ..............  they are not capable to do business and handle an IT Company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst One”

</title><pros>Pros – Only rental building is good</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary Issue form last 2 years.No one is responsible for employees.Management sucksCompany directors (as they are not concerned personal for any company matter, financial matter, Employ  Matter ) are hired by HR managers , So they can not involve in any company matter. LolNever join.. they only give you mental torcher. Because "they can give you salary once in 4 months, it's your problem, that you need food twice/ thrice in a day."</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you are not able to pay, not able to handle employees, close down your company. Don't play with future of your employees. Because of your employees, You are earning, Else you are no one.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best Experience with B24esolutions”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Team work and very supportive seniors and Team leaders</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary delay of 3 months from last 2 years</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – please cover up the financial crises .............else everythng is good</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“need to improver environment else every thing is good...”

</title><pros>Pros – had the good work to learn.</pros>
<cons>Cons – salary delay, lot if  work ,and missing the happy working mood</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – need  to improve the environment as now its not as it like  as before.  we need to work for employee comfert first so they can provide you better productivity.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Good environment at company, no time boundation here</pros>
<cons>Cons – last 3 months salary delay. but this is not big issue. some time every company has passed on financially recession.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please clear financially recession to our employee. at least you should discuss with us.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>