<name>Lifestyle International (UAE) Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Lifestyle-International-UAE-Reviews-E517425.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-07-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Research Project (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A company with excellent business growth and work culture.”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. One of the largest Departmental Stores in India growing with fast pace in terms of business.2. Customer friendly opportunities to shop all along the stores environment and brands positioning.3. Good with supply chain and inventory control across all stores.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. Need a lot of efforts to improve its private labels especially Fameforever & Code in ladies concept.2. Rather maintaining growth there need to be innovations a lot in terms of technology and category development with the same.3. Recruitment needs more smart conduct .</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management should do consolidation to innovated lifestyle technology to stand along with the top most companies standard. Its high time now to preserve brand equity for an upcoming generation to support with the evident nomenclature i.e., "LIFESTYLE".</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Very Good Working Environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Well Organized with Transparent policies and Good Growth Opportunities in very short span of time. . Healthy work environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – No Regularity in Following Standard Operating Procedures</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“work culture”

</title><pros>Pros – well written sopfriendly staff ,learning and developement is high,indepth product knowledge</pros>
<cons>Cons – growth chances are limited ,compensation is not compititve with the market</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – better focus in L & D, increase participation of the employee,</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sourcing Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company for work experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work environment and plenty of good work ethics. Employees are given good opportunities to learn about their field of work. A lot of exposure to different segments of retail industry. Seamless method of operating departments helps in gettng an insight into different work practices of the departments.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Scope of progress and career growth limited. The compensation and appraisals are also not very satisfactory. A lot of focus is laid on work experience rather on actual talent of an individual.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>