<name>A3Logics (I) Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/A3Logics-I-Reviews-E518567.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-08-28</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

““ A great company to stay””

</title><pros>Pros – It was one of the best organization in Jaipur, and nice place for work-Relaxed work environment, encourage you to take breaks</pros>
<cons>Cons – there are several things that i didn't liked in the organization. Internal politics and no appreciation for good work done.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make honest discussions with your employees more frequent</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome learning experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Awesome work cultureAmazing opportunities to learn</pros>
<cons>Cons – Require more facilities for employees</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please provide more facilities like good canteen etc to employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tech Lead (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast growing company”

</title><pros>Pros – Company is growing fast so you are also on high growth path. Senior Management is very accessible and cooperative for example CEO of the company personally knows most of the employees  so A3logics is good in taking care of their employees and are very considerate towards it's employees. A3logics have very good training program so you can switch to technologies you like e.g you will get the opportunity to switch to Java from testing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not enough emphasis on software architecture during development which is a very essential. Not enough expertise in product development.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start working on dynamic and modern technologies like python, rails, they should have increase their portfolio of technologies. Should focus on either product or services not both. Should develop domain expertise in the domain they want to workin.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>