<name>Metropolis Health Services (I) Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Metropolis-Health-Services-I-Reviews-E519636.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Operations Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Growing organisation with poor systems and management”

</title><pros>Pros – Fast growth,good expansion plan, cash rich,having good quality services</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor managemnt structure, decisions with two three top people, no delegation of work(TOP Heavy)Sometimes autocratic(POP n Mom style).Few old cronies calling shots not allowing to develop new leadership perticulary in operations dept.One of the top most head serving for more than 2 decades very much interfering in non related areas and taking credit for everything.Dues settlement for ex employees not done.done after long frustating follow up.Incentives bonus, increment etc not paid on time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Requesting to change to corporate management style, put more professional operations head.Improve employee compensation policies which will faster in terms of speed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Deputy Manager Marketing (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good job”

</title><pros>Pros – The company provide handful of opportunity for its employees to work, leadership is good. The quality of service company provide is top class.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is poor increment cycle, poor politics played within staff, the location of its office is not good. Some employees are in the company only because they are old.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Deputy Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“deputy manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Growing company, so a lot of things to do. If there is initiative you can undertake various activities to learn from. Good CXO level people who are open for intiatives</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very poor pay. Many decisions are based on gut feelings rather than brainstorming or looking up research based guidelines</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Lab Technician (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“challanging working style”

</title><pros>Pros – good quality reports for patient</pros>
<cons>Cons – management  is not so good</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – make neurtal decision and pick the able person</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Chief of Laboratory Services (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible, torture and only false promises.”

</title><pros>Pros – Nothing is good about this place.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everything is bad. suckers, dont value genuine people.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They should learn to value human beings and recognize the efforts put rather than trusting someone who talks flowery language. They should realize that they cannot run a healthcare organization without doctors, just by promoting non -technical people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>