<name>MPS Limited A Macmillan Company Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/MPS-Limited-A-Macmillan-Company-Reviews-E519671.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Rural company-good if you want a paycheck with no growth potential.”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a job in a small area. There is a sense of community within the lower level employees.  There is an odd tuition reimbursement program.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Prpmotions are rare and are given only when someone retires.  The working conditions are tolerable, but do not expect advancement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give employees an opportunity for professional development.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Freelance Copy Editor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Terrible.”

</title><pros>Pros – Just the foreign brand label.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The Indian counterparts are damaging the repute of the company. Possibly the worst editorial force in all of India. In addition, a senior management that turns vindictive and holds back release letters, black-lists employees, holds back freelance payment, divulges and openly discusses contract problems within counterparts, lies to employees, forces to overwork, does not train well, does not recognize efforts, and many more. There is nothing mentionable about the company save its foreign brand label.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Cannot teach professionals how to behave ethically.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Operation Executive (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A workplace like home”

</title><pros>Pros – The workplace is the amazing. no stress of work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary could be low for some.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Editor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“There were many corrupt people in the org when I was working there”

</title><pros>Pros – I found nothing positive in this org.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Corrupt higher management.Employees are treated like commodities.Aimless organization.They are denying to sign and process my Provident Fund forms.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There were many white elephants (senior management) earlier. They were sucking blood of the company and the employees. I don't know how it is now.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Trainee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“company salary process is very disappointing.”

</title><pros>Pros – working process of this company is good</pros>
<cons>Cons – MPS has years of experience working with all kinds of pagination requirements. Whether you’re looking for a fast and cost-effective XML workflow for your academic journals or database-driven typesetting for an encyclopedia, our skilled paginators will meet and exceed all your requirements.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – increase the salary scheme</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Publishing (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“12 yrs”

</title><pros>Pros – There are different type of publishers in this time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – We working from 12 years and in this time sell ADI make in disappear.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Superb atmosphere in this company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I enjoy working in MPS”

</title><pros>Pros – I have a lot of fun here developing my skills, building my career, and dealing with challenges. There are a lot of resources and connections waiting for you to utilize, as well as the opportunities to explore.</pros>
<cons>Cons – MPS is a big company so the pace might be slow sometimes.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make smart decisions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-29</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Director, Editorial Services (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Incompetent management, in it for personal gain only, will never move the company forward.”

</title><pros>Pros – If you go in with your eyes open and negotiate hard, you can probably do well financially.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You may need to scrub this off your resume or downplay it, as the company's reputation for poor quality and corruption may taint you. Turnover is very high below senior management, as hard work, honesty, client service, and high-quality performance are not valued, whereas personal loyalty (as opposed to company or client loyalty) is paramount.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>