<name>KocharTech Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/KocharTech-Reviews-E519486.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“best place to grow”

</title><pros>Pros – lots of opportunities. work life balance, career opportunities. Very good company to work with. Good work culture. Good work and life balance. Flexible timings.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Role and Responsibilities are not clearly defined</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Terrible”

</title><pros>Pros – Good place to learn technical knowledge on mobile trouble shooting</pros>
<cons>Cons – its a family oriented businesslot of bias in the system, bad pay masters.No Job security</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Planning needs to be effective</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>IT Department (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Kochar is a great company to work with.”

</title><pros>Pros – Kochar is a great company to work with. It offers variety of opportunities to the people who are aspiring for a bright future.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 6 days working in a week</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“About experience in Kochartech”

</title><pros>Pros – I have been working with this company from last 3 years. Kochar is having Excellent Work Culture, Supportive Seniors, Growth opportunities in job and all round development, Full of life and spirit. In company there are lots of activities to participate in. The work to complete during shift helps me with time management skills. Kochar is a good place to work and to improve my skills.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Formal dress is compulsory four day in office.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management is very good and satisfied.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Kochar is the best palce to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Kochar is the best palce to work. , Job Security. Salary is good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 6 days working in a week</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>IT-Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Experience at Kochar”

</title><pros>Pros – Its a great place to learn. Great place to start career with. Good work environment, Where u can work and have fun.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The quality of food in canteen should me more tasty.Management should be little more transparent.Salary needs to be matching industry standards.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more open and fair to fellow employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Experience while working in Kochar”

</title><pros>Pros – Kochar is growing organization and hence there is a lot to learn. The work environment is better than many other organizations.  Growth prospects for performers are good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – nothing a very nice company</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior SEO (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

““Good place to work if are want to innovate””

</title><pros>Pros – 1 ) Culture of innovation Opportunities and support to learn newer and relevant technologies.2) Fairly good salary.3) Good working environment.4) Nice HR policies.5) Internal job Opportunities is the best thing with in the organization</pros>
<cons>Cons – As per me there no Cons .</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Earlier had growth in professional career, but not now”

</title><pros>Pros – Experiments a;;owed but at your own riskthat's it</pros>
<cons>Cons – No senior supportNo work channelWorking simuntaneous in multiple project no time to even think, repetitive workless salaryno workflow</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – will give if they care</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My experience”

</title><pros>Pros – I have been working in this organization from last 2 years. This organization has given me ample of opportunities to grow. Internal job posting is the best part of this organization. I joined Kochar as a TSE but due to IJP I have been promoted as the Quality Evaluator in just one year. The working culture of this company is great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Formal is compulsory 4 days a week</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Experience at Kochar Infotech”

</title><pros>Pros – The best part of this organization is the training session that they conduct for their employees. I am working in this organization from last 2 years and I have attended many training sessions. These sessions have helped me to upgrade my skills and move towards the next level.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is nothing which brings Kochar back.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Demonster (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“not to share”

</title><pros>Pros – I was interested to work with kochar because kochar supports the other companies like airtel, idea, vodafone, for marketing and selling their products.</pros>
<cons>Cons – workload is to much no timetable for work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – please be truth.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review”

</title><pros>Pros – Kochar offers unrestricted learning ,immense growth opportunities and  engaging mentorship opportunities which is true of any dream organisation .</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing as such that we can think of currently</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Human Resource (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Experience with Kochar”

</title><pros>Pros – One of the best place for employees who want to have high on learnings and getting chance to work  on critical activities in short span of their tenure in organisation.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I dont think there is anything which brings kochar on back front..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would like to thank management for having employee oriented organisation in Amritsar and Ludhiana. would like to see some centres coming up in Punjab to provide more Opportunities in north India for professionals.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>TL WFM (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Handling WFM Activities for Location”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to WORK in learning</pros>
<cons>Cons – Localisation Languge barrier politics & etc</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>TSE (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its a Grate Learning Experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – Grate Work Environment, & Work Culture. The New Way of Possibility in GPRS technical problems.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Confusing & Poor Management. Some senior management trying to skip or ignore the problems......</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Discuss & Share the problems with all employees and then find the way to resolve it.Do not ignore it. or Do not Pass this to another department...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor quality of leadership and management.”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexibility of timings and the management is understanding.When the management is understanding employees have a smooth experience.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No proper hierarchy among the top management.Management is essentially very important as the organization depends on them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Should get more personnel who are qualified and can run the company in a systematic manner.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Field Support Engineer At Vodafone India Ltd (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best employer as my first company”

</title><pros>Pros – salary  on time , employment nature , Co workars ,</pros>
<cons>Cons – my company is best i hav seen ever ..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>