<name>Techno Q Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Techno-Q-Reviews-E525886.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-08-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“combines knowledge, experience, and passion to ensure that each project is delivered on time, on budget”

</title><pros>Pros – Qatar based Techno Q is an industry-leading systems integrator specializing in audiovisual, security, control, fire, lighting, IT, broadcast, and hospitality management system.the engineering consultants design customised solutions to provide cost-efficient and advanced technology featuring an easy-to-use human interface.</pros>
<cons>Cons – sorry i cant share this with you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>BMS Site Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Qatari Electronics Company”

</title><pros>Pros – very good company to start as a fresh graduate, gives good trainings.</pros>
<cons>Cons – alot of under pressure work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Managers should be given authorities</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Frustrating workplace”

</title><pros>Pros – ideal place to practice ISO procedures,well organised,medium sized organisation with good reputation that will post in your career.</pros>
<cons>Cons – blame culture all around ,Frustrating  atmosphere,management are very selective in rewarding and appreciation that give opposite results.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none of your employees has loyalty for the company. and if happen,you gave him many reasons not to be.TechnoQ procedures are too complicated that it will reduce productivity and not maintaining quality.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>