<name>V.Ships Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/V-Ships-Reviews-E526113.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting and special”

</title><pros>Pros – informal work relashionships, independence and diversity, appreciation for human factor</pros>
<cons>Cons – limited market, dependent on one client which restricts significantly the desicion making</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – not much they can do - maybe stand up for the comapny a littler more even at the risk of "upsetiing" the major client.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sailor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“it was awesom to work with v ships”

</title><pros>Pros – good relation ship between employer and employee</pros>
<cons>Cons – management level have some fluctuations</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – work with coordination and accept the suggestion of ur lower ones also</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-02</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>4th Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“one of the worlds largest company...”

</title><pros>Pros – good employ benefits ,good work culture , lots of ships so less waiting , and lots of company policies for the benefit of employs...</pros>
<cons>Cons – some ships are very old so lots of work for marine engineers , rest problems like hard life and staying away from families is a part of merchant navy  and allover the world it is same , but on the bright side " good compensation in terms of salaries "..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Second Officer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“So far, so good.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good promotion aspects and good safety culture.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management company, so superintendents prefer to provide cheap and substandard stores and spares to appease the owners and superiors.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – MLC compliant flag state vessels must be included in the fleet, and 24X7 internet facility  must be provided to crew.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Second Mate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“amazing experience working with the biggest manpower company in the world”

</title><pros>Pros – safety has always been their top concern,training the seafarer to global standards is one good point.</pros>
<cons>Cons – average salary compared to rest of the industry.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Chief Officer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good if not Excellent.Company.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Company to work with. Procedures and policies are established and followed. No shortcuts allowed.Easily one of the better companies to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Different parties are responsible of different departments. Multiplication of paper work involved. The industry itself is going through a downturn so You can not blame the Company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>