<name>Eye Q Vision Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Eye-Q-Vision-Reviews-E531102.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-08-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager- Supply Chain (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exploring journey...”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a Growing company, so there's a growth for individual as well. Learning atmosphere. One can get lot of things to explore.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's still not a fully structured organization. Processes are still getting streamlined. Lot of things are unstructured.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Streamlining is necessary.... Good that you are doing it....</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Patient Services (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Boardmembers just to passive aggressive”

</title><pros>Pros – Still. Maintains some what of a family atmosphere</pros>
<cons>Cons – Many of the employees perks have been cut back.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You need to re-sharpen your pencils</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Regional Business Head (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great learning experience as regional head, reporting directly to CEO”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity to handle P&L responsibility of a major region for the companyClose interpersonal relationship development - a key requirement for this roleHighly charged and energetic work environment where the week starts with a top management review and ends with a team review</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work-Life balance gets affected due to 6 day working week.Weak HR, delays in hiring replacements, talent retention is weakVery weak IT and systems - affects productivity</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Outsource HR and talent managementImplement a strong IT-based solution for daily reporting and financial modeling</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>