<name>Dorma India (P) Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Dorma-India-P-Reviews-E535961.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-08-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ok”

</title><pros>Pros – great exposure of market as there is huge range of products u can sell.</pros>
<cons>Cons – no personal growth (as far as designation is concerned) if u r in same company for long time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – take care of ppl associated with the company fir long as they are the real asset.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review on Management”

</title><pros>Pros – - Flexible work atmosphere at times- Nothing much to think of</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Poor Management- No proper structure, process defined- Too much partiality over selected people- No follow up on work & too much of internal politics involved- Proper hike, incentives was always a NO in the organization- Absolutely no job security, can be shown the doors anytime</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Kindly review the entire work flow- Haphazard processes hamper the work culture which needs to be checked</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>BDM (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't Join DORMA India”

</title><pros>Pros – * Good Parent company-German origins* Awesome brand name for moving on to another competitor</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots of it* Iyengar caste people will easily get job* Iyers next* Hindus predominently* Retarded organisational structure* High Office politics* Employees are treated differently</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Just learn something from the parent company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Regional Sales Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting place and interesting work environment. Professional management.”

</title><pros>Pros – Your efforts are recognized and rewarded. Basic amenities are provided for.Colleagues are generally cooperative,helpful and cooperative.Congenial place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too many reporting formats,which have to be filled in frequently.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Nothing gets done without follow up.</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>