<name>L and T Chiyoda Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/L-and-T-Chiyoda-Reviews-E550821.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-01-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Instrumentation Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A place where learning is given importance”

</title><pros>Pros – Cordial superiors and a great learning experience. Quality standards are one of the best in industry.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working freedom needs improvement and compensation offered is on the lower side compared to other engineering companies</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Rotating Equipment Engineer”

</title><pros>Pros – L&T is a very good place to learn. The nitty-grittys of any project, only Technical details, are learned very well at L&T. I was associated with L&T-Chiyoda for few years & with L&T later. It was a great place to learn.. (Acronym LTC sands for : Learning and Training Centre)Every Mechanical engineer shall be a part of L&T in his career.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A correction : "Every Mechanical engineer shall be a part of L&T in his career.... but only for a while..!!" The longer you stay with L&T, the more you get paralysed by its bureaucracy and lack of decision making. It's a great place to learn "meeting-room-tennis". People pass on the responsibilities and decision making things on each other so ridiculously, that after a few years, you start to realize, whether is this the L&T what people talk about !.. LTC or L&T or L&T-Chiyoda stands for Learn, get Trained & Change for a better job.. Do NOT STAY with L&T... L&T pays decently to trainees, but for equi-potential lateral joinees, L&T is a place next to hell.. So if you are employed with some organisation right now, and thinking to switch to LTC or L&T, you are gonna be PENALISED, severly.. (My Buoy..!!!) Good Luck..If you have a decent work ex (> 7 Years), and you join L&T, you would come to know, how orthodox or even Juvenile the thinking of L&Tites is...!! Decisions are still made by the grey-haired fellas, unaware of new management philosophies and hence the risk appetite is even below zero(Advice to people : Go to L&T, get trained AND GET MOVING...)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Advice to Senior Management – Larsen & Toubro might have never thought L&T to be what it is today.. A multi million dollar organization.. But to sustain it, is upto the management's decision and their ability to retain people, Unfortunately, this seems a fading possibility..</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>