<name>Pilot Flying J Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Pilot-Flying-J-Reviews-E5534.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager/Co Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good start to a career”

</title><pros>Pros – Move up on your own merit</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours, hard to balance hoe and work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Your folks have the answers, listen to them</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Definition of Corporate Moneygrubbing”

</title><pros>Pros – It's easy to understand this job if you realize that your only function is to make money for the corporate office.General Manager at my store is great, most employees work hard.  Those who don't don't last.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Wages, expectations, problem solving, accountability, big picture, morale.Everything is based on sales, not reality.  I work third shift as a Team Leader and as such my function is chief cook and bottle washer, scapegoat, and problem solver.  The company condescends to allow two employees on third shift and expects us to clean showers and restrooms, sweep and mop the whole store, take out trash from store and fuel islands (you know what's in the diesel trash cans), keep food in production, handle customer problems that are not our responsibility, stock the entire coffee bar, make six kinds of tea (only three of which sell), oh and WAIT ON CUSTOMERS.There is an Assistant General Manager in my region who is very stressful to work for and disrupts our work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop wasting time on minutiae such as cleaning Transflos 3 times a day, stacking condiments straight in the bins, deli opening and closing checklists and shower and restroom GI records.  Allow us to work more efficiently.Utilize the coffee hostess by allowing her to do more stocking and cleaning of the coffee/deli bar.  This takes the pressure off third shift having to have everything stocked for her.  It also takes the pressure off her by enabling her to have the coffee bar in spic and span condition for health department inspections and mystery shops. Don't put the onus of coffee sales solely on her.  Don't base mystery shops on her selling but the condition of the coffee/deli area and the products in that area.  She is under a microscope and you are putting too much pressure and responsibility on her.Quit emphasizing that you expect clean restrooms.  The overhead "courtesy check" announcements and signage enable customers to make mean comments accusing us of not doing our job just because we can't check that every customer has flushed the toilet and not used the last of the toilet paper and paper towels.  When customers smear excrement on the bathroom walls and write expletives in it, (yes they do, more often than you would be willing to admit, and it usually consists of disparaging comments about the company) that is behavior that has been encouraged as mockery of the announcements and signs.  Put restrooms on the diesel islands with trash cans for disposal of empty urine jugs after they have been flushed down the urinals.  Since you expect us to handle biohazardous waste, provide us protection.Allow enough hours of payroll to have more people on staff.  One more maintenance person, one more deli employee, and one more cashier on first and second shift would still have work to do but we could do it better with less pressure.  On the rare occasion there are three trained people on third shift, we work hard through the shift but we are able to get everything done without the pressure of knowing that we are letting the coffee hostess, maintenance, and deli employees down by not getting everything done.  If you really cared what the customers think, they tell us all the time we are working too hard.  They see that, but they understandably expect the restrooms to be cleaner, a greater variety of food, and the diesel pumps not to vapor lock three or more times a night.  The good employees know what needs to be done and do our best to get it done.  We could amaze you and the customers with what we can do with adequate staffing.  We don't need the knowledge that we are going to get in trouble for not completing our jobs because it's physically impossible to do so.  It's a constant headache and hot poker to the gut.  It is inevitable that people call off or don't show from time to time.  Having more people on the schedule and more hours available for more personnel on the payroll would enable us to pick up the slack and/or have more people to call in.Quit covering your asses by making us lie and say we had all our breaks when we sign our time cards each week and threatening to fire us if we don't take them.  You don't allow us enough people to do even the minimum of what you expect.  We have to work through our breaks just to do the bare minimum that keeps the company running.When minimum wage increases result in higher wages for minimum wage employees, give commensurate increases to all other hourly employees.  Pay us for what you expect out of us.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A waste of time.”

</title><pros>Pros – I can't think of any.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Realize that from the start you will be lied to by the recruiter...Google them and see what legal trouble they are in. There is no work family balance. You become a stocker, merchandiser, checker, maintenance etc...Very little time to truely manage.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start over....but then again you will still have Jimmy (unless he gets what it looks like he will get...prison time). There is no hope as the problem is apparently the owner! I was told not to mention issues with Jimmy as he oks the payroll!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Always got my hours and a little overtime.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No pay raise, even after giving you unofficial promotion, meaning more work without the pay. A lot of favoritism, along with seniority, Only the General managers favorites were scheduled Monday thru Friday 7 to 3 or 4. One was being paid to train new employees and she never trained me or anyone the year I was there because I did the training or people in 2nd or 3rd shift would train. I got fired for a cash shortage on a day I didn't use the register, the week before management called me into question me on why I reported them to district manager, next week im fired. Company had a problem with not giving lunches and would edit time so we wont get paid and they wont be in trouble. I can go on.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Fire management and and start fresh.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Co Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Fast paced environment, great company!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low labor hours, hard to balance work and home.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You can never ask enough questions</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Maintenance (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Low pay”

</title><pros>Pros – Some great people to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is bad for the stuff we have to do/clean shower bathrooms, propane,fix pumps,move trucks , do other peoples jobs because there to lazy and ask you to do it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do your job stop texting in the back room and go help out and make sure work is getting done.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Management style is to find fault, rather than to find anything positive, public humilation is an everyday occurance”

</title><pros>Pros – The drivers and the general public that you get to interact with every day, are just wonderful. It sometimes seems that the whole world will pass thru the doors eventually</pros>
<cons>Cons – Allways run short staffed, medical is the worst I have had.  Don't bother to call the hotline to report abuse all they do is send in the managers best friend, the Regional manager who has a financial interest in keeping things as is.  Moral is poor.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Maybe a regonal HR person who has no financial gain, could spend times visiting the stores and getting to know what is going on at the hourly employee level.  Currently any corporate visites are limited to the management who have put on thier best face for the visit.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Shift Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Shift Leader”

</title><pros>Pros – They are ok. Life could be better there</pros>
<cons>Cons – No time to rest. Expect to much.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay more money for all the hard work that we freaking do for you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“General Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – They pay to move you to another city. Easy to get hired with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not great pay, a lot of hours, terrible insurance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Maintenance (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“One hard,long, work day.....”

</title><pros>Pros – While the pay and benefits are NOT pros in this company, the lessons in life are. While your body is busy being tortured with labor and stress,take this time to reflect on what is good in your life. We are put on this Earth for a reason and for me working at this company is it. When a customer comes up to me and says: "You're working way too hard", I think to myself: " wow good job!". Our purpose is not always clear in life, but for me there are people out there that recognize what we are going through.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Ignorance. Plain and simple. Even the management has it at times. Other times there are just overbearing simpletons who it seems would rather ruin your day than try to make it a bit easier.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Same as other reviews, try a better wage for dedicated,hardworking employees. And maybe fake a bit of concern for people's struggles in life. We all have things we are going through at this company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Maintenance Team Member (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Better jobs exist.”

</title><pros>Pros – -Good work experience. You really can learn a lot while on the job.-Fellow employees are some of the nicest people I've ever met.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Poor pay. The way I see it, if you want to pay your employees minimum wage, then expect that type of work.-There is no balance for your personal life/poor scheduling.-You're basically on call 24/7.-Constant visits from corporate, who are always there to complain about something and not offer any assistance on how it should be fixed. These are also the days your managers work you the hardest.-Training is less than sufficient. The videos tell you a lot of information you'll never use (for maintenance, that is). I was shown how to clean showers. Everything else was up to me to learn through trial and error.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get your act together. Talk to your employees more. My managers only speak with me when they want more work done on top of what I'm doing. Come out of the office for more than 5 minutes every hour; You might actually know what's going on in the store. You want superhuman efforts? Maybe the payroll should reflect that. Also, 1 maintenance guy isn't enough for a full shift. You're working people to death for little compensation. That's why so many employees leave for better working conditions. I certainly have much more to say, but won't for the time being.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good place”

</title><pros>Pros – great people, great food, great deals</pros>
<cons>Cons – no cons, nothing, nada, this is a great place :)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – no advice</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing experience for recent college graduates”

</title><pros>Pros – Amazing travel experience and learning opportunity for recent college graduates, all expense paid opportunity to travel to different parts of the country.  The locations varies.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unorganized management, management in C-Stores need to spend more time training employees rather than hanging bags of candies. They try to use technologies but doesn't always work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a salaried position.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Well basically every other aspect of the job.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You should take better care of your employees and managers.  At least pretend you care.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Coffee Host (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not Family Friendly”

</title><pros>Pros – The other employees tend to be friendly. Benefits are offered for both full time and part time employees. Good part time job for young adults and college students.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Employees get overworked and are rarely recognized for this. Pay is minimal at best and raises are difficult in coming. Management does not deal well with being incorrect and have a hard time providing flexibility for their employees. Not worth becoming a full time employee as it is not very family friends.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Flexibility and appreciation for employees would improve work place morale and employee satisfaction.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Retail/Stock Service (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An Endurance Test, But One to Grow On...”

</title><pros>Pros – A very fast-paced learning experience. Work objectives were easy enough... I never had any major problems scheduling around my classes while attending college...Much respect to some of the general managers I had, who were mostly even-tempered and helpful through their own workload... I was able to work as little or as long of a work week as necessary...It was certainly a job - and an endeavor to grow on, which brings me to my next point...</pros>
<cons>Cons – You're essentially doing the work of a Walmart employee, a custodian, as well as a cashier for a glamorous minimum wage. The transactions a team member processes deal with food, fuel, grocery, merchandise, and tobacco. If you work during the day, you're guaranteed to get a steady to constant flow of customers, and during the rare time periods where you're not assisting people you're involved with cleaning the counter and the deli/coffee section. I realize that professional drivers carry out a job considered by many to be in a most dubious category, but a lot of the kind of people that stopped in at this store were representatives of the downside of mankind. As a team member, you're putting in a remarkable effort at keeping things rolling and attempting to meet the needs of these people to total indifference, or even humiliation when something would go wrong with the erroneous P.O.S. systems or when one customer would be in a particularly rude mood. Not to mention that I felt like the company would be setting up team members for this kind of backlash with their methods of pricing. I stuck it out being a team member here, and my good will ultimately got me through the toils of this customer service position.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – This is a fast-paced, complex work environment that you're throwing team members into. If you're going to expect a superhuman effort from each employee, don't pay a joke of a wage. Sooner or later, the more solid workers will find better opportunities at much better companies.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Travel Center Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Say goodbye to your life...belongs to pilot”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay is goodStore team is good</pros>
<cons>Cons – Perfection is expected each day.No realistic payroll to work with.Above level management has no appreciation for team.Your boss is worried about his boss not drivers.No work life balance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Jimmy get in tune with your people at the store.  New hires above store level not realistic.  How is it possible you have lost more than 50% of your gm?  No need for company to struggle as it is...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-20</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pilot, no love for anyone”

</title><pros>Pros – It was close to my home, that is all, nothing else positive to say</pros>
<cons>Cons – No love for anyone, at least 75% of the customers are angry when they arrive and PILOT does little to appease that, over charging for everything from showers, to soda pop.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – pay the low level folks a little more...hire more people so that the building can always be clean.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-27</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefit and pay. Great employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – Do see some nasty stuff</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Mid Level Management (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“In all seriousness, Pilot Corp Office may be the most demanding company in USA in management level positions”

</title><pros>Pros – Great pay and benefits.Almost everyone is friendly and pleasant to work with.You feel at home working there pretty fast.If you can be successful working here, you can't help but feel like an allstar.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very little toleration of anything but perfectionIf you screw up even slightly once, your job could easily be in jeopardy. Screw up twice, heads roll with no hesitation.  I've seen this happen one too many times.In a management position at corporate which are all salaried (not hourly) positions, if you're not putting in around 60 hours/week, you likely won't make it there very long.  Plus you're automatically considered a slacker. 40 hours a week is not the norm and quite frankly unacceptable there.Get ready cause you have to live and breathe Pilot.  And if you're not loyal, forget it.  This is a very tightknit company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-28</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If your looking for a career, keep looking!”

</title><pros>Pros – There are always many job opportunities. They have great tools for management to utilize. It is very fast paced.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The reason they have continuous openings is that this company runs too tight on payroll. They burn out their employees. Management seldom has time to utilize any tools available to them. It is a study in continual crisis management. Their unwillingness to address pay necessitates hiring those that will leave shortly. Definitley not a good career stop for most. There is no family/work life balance regardless of what your told while interviewing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have exit interviews done by HR. Look to upgrade your staff by upgrading your pay! You can't attract great people with your wage scale.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Management (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Read all about it Ethics not wanted”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with customers both trucker and gas were the best part of the job.  You had the opportunity to get to know them on a personal basis and they became part of your Pilot Flying J family</pros>
<cons>Cons – Ethics were not appreciated.  Policies in place were totally disregarded some that could be a liability for the company in the future.  What you are reading in the press about Pilot Flying J is a global issue not just limited to the headquarters in Knoxville.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Caashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Cashier /stocking/Diesel & Gas Desk”

</title><pros>Pros – All shifts available but seniority does get their pick first.   They are good to work with you as far as needing off for any reason.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Don't take care of their employees very good.  You have to stand of your whole shift.   You get 10 minutes breaks and half hour lunch breaks.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to watch your tapes more.  You could sure learn a lot.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>QA Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great to work with schedules”

</title><pros>Pros – Worked well with my schooling, great hours,</pros>
<cons>Cons – Mass layoffs so flying J is no more</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Store Director”

</title><pros>Pros – Great People to work with, Bonus is nearly guaranteed. 5 year bonus as part of profit share which could easily be 6 figures</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long days, Dealing with Truck drivers who urinate in bottles and poop in bags and throw them where ever. High Stress!!! Always being yelled at and being pulled in all directions. Do more with less each and every year. Average store has 18,500 customers a week and we operate 24/7 on 500 hours do the math 12-13 hour days 6 days a week is the normal environment. Non stop visits from HQ people that say what is wrong but, don't step up to help.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You make 0.18$ per gallon of diesel spend some on hourly wages and more payroll to drive customer service which is what you preach. Back it up and quit lining your pockets to buy a football team</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Co-Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you like running all day and never getting anyting done, then this is the job for you.”

</title><pros>Pros – I enjoyed building rapport with the customers and employees, but you get that in any retail setting.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Like the rest of the retail world, salary means you work a lot of hours. I did average about 50 most of the time, but some weeks were 60-70. The pay is not great- I made a lot more at Walgreens for the same position. The corporate support system is not that good. The computers are always having some kind of problem- some issues go on for months without being addressed.  We had 30 year old  gas pumps that the techs had problems finding parts for. They were constantly messing up and it frustrated the customers. It was frustrating listening to the complaining from the customers when it wasn't our fault. The employees' pay was pitiful. This led to high turnover. They cut hours during the winter, so everyone had to get used to making less money during this season. Not really fair in my opinion</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – For this business model to work, you have to have good people and keep them. $8 an hour gives you no chance of doing this.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK company if your standards are low”

</title><pros>Pros – Meet some real good people</pros>
<cons>Cons – They milk you for everything so Jimmy Haslem (Owner) can go by a NFL team (Cleveland Browns).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Spread the wealth, we make you so much money..... give some back to your leaders.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“upper management”

</title><pros>Pros – challenging, If you make it here any where else should be a piece of cake</pros>
<cons>Cons – if you cant EXTREME MULTI TASK you cant work for this company</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Can you do what you ask your employees to do? Have you?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“do yourself a favor and stay away”

</title><pros>Pros – i really do not have anything positive to say about this company</pros>
<cons>Cons – very low wages, over worked, extremely poor store management, they hire managers that do not have common sense, no benefits, constant changing schedules, no loyalty to their employees, express your opinion you will be fired</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – pay attention to the employees in the store because if it wasn't for them you wouldn't have a job</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pilot Flying J is a great place to work and you get to work with likewise great people”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible ScheduleFamily First MentalityGreat PayGood EquipmentBig Company seems like Small CompanyGood Benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – Little interaction with managementNo advancementNot a lot of time off</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take a little more interest in day to day activities so that employees know how they are doing and where they can improve.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company with Great Benefits”

</title><pros>Pros – I've been with them for 11 years and I can't imagine working anywhere else.  I'm a retail guy and I must say there is no beter retail job.  The benefits are very good and the salary is very competitive to big box retailers.  If you like not killing yourself on holidays and black Fridays then you need to come work for us.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is a 24 hour operation and call offs happen.  You need to be willing to take care of business when duty calls</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Low Level Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worse place I've ever worked, very degrading”

</title><pros>Pros – Managers talk down to you in front of other employees and customers, they have a no facial hair policy but my female RGM has a beard. The list goes on.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Crap management training they tell you about imortant things but never teach you. no job shadowingbenefits are crazy expensive @ 129.00 per week.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Speed of service is important but so is quality of service. Customers don't want to be rushed anymore than they want to be delayed.Passive aggressive actions by upper management creates a hostile work environment. Hence the actions by the opening RGM at store #596 and when I said something to her manager I was let go.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Retail Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This company has left me with a bitter taste in my mouth that has slowly began to erode the lining in my stomach.”

</title><pros>Pros – I've made 2 very good friends while working for this company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Since our company was taken over, workers that have been employed for years have suddenly become seen as incompetent and obsolete.  Pay raises are almost nonexistent, and promotions go to the worst possible employees, who, by the way, receive very little training.  The worst part is, former full time employees are stripped of their hours, forced to work only 3 or 4 days, but the company keeps hiring new employees, intentionally reducing the number of hours available for each employee.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – We have 2 general managers at our store, but somehow our store is among the worst managed i've ever seen.  The problem is that both GMs are so concerned that the other might receive a moment of recognition that the other does not, or that one may get a smile from corporate management that the other misses, that they cannot manage effectively.  Our night shift team is a mess, and coming from one who has had the task of managing that shift, I can honestly say it is not the fault of the lower management team.  They can only do so much with what they are given, but they carry the blame if anything goes wrong.  It does not take a genius to figure out that with 2 GMs, one should always be available to work nights.  This will avoid any uneducated finger pointing when something is not done because it is very easy to blame someone else for their perceived shortcomings when you have never tried to work their position.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“First 15 years were good - then all down hill after the recession.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good pay as a General Manager...decent benefits...Years ago they cared about you as a person and respected family values.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Life/Work balance very poor...Micromanage you to death...It was all about suggestive selling the last 3-4 years...When times are tough you cant pinch dollars out of every customer - they only lightened up on the staff because of customer comments on facebook and via corp website.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop driving all year experienced staff out the door just to save money...drop the promote from within since you dont...stop being so greedy...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Fuel Driver (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company to drive for”

</title><pros>Pros – Regular hoursGood benefitsStable company</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay slightly lower than average</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good not Great”

</title><pros>Pros – Good retirement plan, competitive salaries, great structure to the company.  Pilot is well organized and run fairly well by many good managers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A few managers are not very flexible in adapting to new ways of doing things.  24 hour facilities so management schedules vary greatly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This company is very fast paced and I loved it!”

</title><pros>Pros – The pros for this company is the variety of duties you perform. I love how fast paced it is and you never have down time where you're standing around with nothing to do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Numerous drivers hitting on you. If you can't take a joke don't work here. Management switches all the time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be friendly, it goes a long way. Especially since your truck drivers would like conversation since they are on the road all the time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Better Than the Majority”

</title><pros>Pros – Paid vacation for full-time employees no matter what job type.Medical, dental, vision, even life insurance benefits available within first year of employment, full or part-time.Mandatory breaks (two 10 minute paid breaks, one 30 minute non-paid lunch).Company perfectly willing to pay you if you're actually willing to work.True opportunity for advancement in the purest sense (start as Cashier, promoted to Team Lead, Shift Lead, Store Manager, General Manager, District Manager, etc.).Perfect chance to meet people from every state, every country, and every walk of life. Literally. Great job if you like people and know multiple languages.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very high volume (Truckers always drive), very quick paced (Truckers have deadlines), combined with radio chatter in one ear and customer chatter in the other means for relatively high stress.Company's strive for perfection, while admirable, and usually achievable, can sometimes be downright bothersome, especially during peak hours and days and months (1 week before Thanksgiving Day to 3 days after New Years is MURDER).Customers can sometimes be outright mean at times.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Maintenance (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Low wages, unreasonable expectations”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits for part time employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hourly wages are low, and work load is high for maintenance personnel.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get some real expectations for your employees, we're not robots.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Employees treated with total disrespect”

</title><pros>Pros – The only pros for me with this job are..my fellow employees...meeting new people daily..and having a job.The pay is not sufficient for what is expected of employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – My supervisor at the Haw River Flying J speaks to all employees with total disrespect..ex.screaming,yelling,cursing,.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Corporate needs to speak to all employees about their experiences with management at this location...9 employees walking out in less than 6 months should speak volumns.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A waste of time”

</title><pros>Pros – Honestly there's really not to many good things to say about this workplace</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working here you really have to watch your hours on your pay stud because they are good for paying people the wrong amount of money, the managers talk down to you if your not in good with them, and they are the cause of 90% of the gossip which is sad, be prepared to be in a popularity contest, since the over turn is so high and people can get moved up in the company there's alot of backstabbing, I know some reviews say that you can get moved up quickly but in reality the regular employee get paid the same amount as the shift leader 7.25, so your not getting a pay raise your just getting more hours and demands, through my experience the employees are more rude then the customers, which is ironic bc you will get rude customers as well, the training is horrible and the demand is extremely high so expect to have to learn things on your own, which causes alot of tension at the job, you have to front face all your bills in your drawer, write on all your voids and suspended transactions what happened, clean showers and bathrroms bc maintenance always need help or sometimes aren't there, call and activate checks and people credit cards ect. sometimes working a 8 hour shift as the only cashier, now ask yourself do u want to go through all that for little pay, another thing is that pilot is not flexible and there student reinbursement is not up to par, if you ask for time off they tell you the week of if you can get the time off or not, after asking two or more weeks in advacnce bc they don't have to approve your time off and they schedule weekly, for the student reinbursement you have to be full time worker for over a year and have a certain amount of hours & gpa, and you still might not get any reinbursment which makes it impossible to achieve, they would let credit collecters or any one garnish your checks, the health benefits only apply to you if your breathing pilot flying j, bottom line if your trying to support a family off this company it would be a waste of time, p:s if your in Indiana and want to work at pilot beware bc there are some prejudice people who work there, just for the heads up</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The training is horrible for all the information that ya'll require the employees to learn, the managers and shift leaders are extremely rude and cut throat, I read some reviews and they said the same thing, pfj need to be more aware who's running there store and stop giving the position to just anybody, being rude to your workers is not a good look esp for 7.25</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-02</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Like being in the military without the benefits”

</title><pros>Pros – Customers are great the co workers are cool</pros>
<cons>Cons – You do as they say or you would wish you had. Your hours get cut you be lucky if you can go to the bathroom.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to treat your employees with respect. You will acomplish more. Need to get out the office and help your staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Terrible, empty promises, treated like dirt”

</title><pros>Pros – Semi decent pay, paid holidays</pros>
<cons>Cons – Way too much responsibility, with too little pay, talked to and spoken to like a child</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Respect your employees! Show them that you care!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Completely incompetent upper management.”

</title><pros>Pros – I've met a few cool people while working here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Almost everything. Horrible pay, uneducated hiring, etc. I could write an entire book about this but the gist of it is that the upper management is lazy and incompetent , and they don't seem to care. If any concern is brought up with them they very obviously tune out and just wait for their turn to speak., and ignore everything said to them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Step out of your locked office for more than two minutes per shift and learn how to do your jobs. Or just quit and let someone with an IQ above 12 have the position, at least they would probably be able to create a schedule correctly.Smoking an entire pack of cigarettes while you're on the clock is not a good way to lead by example.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Chaotic and Horrible”

</title><pros>Pros – Able to earn promotionsMeet a lot of different peopleFast PacedThat's it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Worst Management imaginableNo respect for employee'sPoor communication between employee's and managementOverall just a terrible company</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Respect your employee's more, and learn how to do your job and take care of customer's needs better.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Restaurant General Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“They do what they say they will”

</title><pros>Pros – I was told that if I was successful at my first assignment they would move me out west and they did. You always know where you stand. There aren't any surprises. The 401k match is good and I'm looking forward to my Partners in Profit pay out. This is a family business that became big, but still has the family business mentality. Senior management know me by name, and some even know and care about my family. The first time I met Jimmy Haslam, after six months of employment at a training session in Knoxville, he asked me how my wife, son, and horse were adapting to our new home. He has thousands of employees, yet he knew that about me. My direct supervisors know and care very much about my family, interest, and my career. They are insightful and compassionate.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 168 hours a week of operations can be a challenge at first, however once your team is developed life is good.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do not lose the family business mentality no matter how big the company get's. Continue the focus on health and wellness. These things matter.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Regional Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A family ran business that has sports atmosphere making you want to excel in your position to help the TEAM be the best.”

</title><pros>Pros – Pilot Flying J allows me to have a positive impact on several team members from the person with there first job in the industry all the way to the person that's looking for a quickly growing career.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's a job that has both mental and physical challenges which some individuals aren't used to being held accountable for there performance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep pushing forward towards the Driver Driven culture as we're in this business to take care of customers, and keep rewarding those that have the biggest impact on customer service.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier, Maintenance, Coffee Host (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It started out great but all went downhill fast.”

</title><pros>Pros – Job keeps you busy.Some coworkers are nice.The occasional manager is honest and kind.Pay raises are ok most of the time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Promised promotions that you never receive.Worker's compensation claims are handled poorly.  Don't hear back about them for almost a month.Talked down to by senior management.Made to feel obligated to work almost to death even after a serious life-threatening illness.Management is the cause of much of the gossip and drama in the store.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be fair and honest.Do not promise what you will not deliver.Give promotions and raises to those that deserve it and not  your favorites who constantly call out or cause storewide drama.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fast paced, technical cash register work.”

</title><pros>Pros – You develope  good money handling skills very quickly do to the amout of cash handeled. Training is adiquite for the position.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Your expected schedule can sometimes be over bearing and some employees are not in it for the team, just for a pay check.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Better compensasion and benifts would be ideal, the work can be demanding and tricky at times. Would like to be promomted more quickly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to grow”

</title><pros>Pros – Can move up quickly or stay where you are at it is completely up to you. The upper management team will support you as long as you can do what is right and work hard</pros>
<cons>Cons – Like any public work place you have good and bad interactions with customers. And some team members like having drama not a good thing</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – My advice is keep doing what you are doing I am very happy with the company and I hope the company is just as happy as me</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier/Shift Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is an emotional rollercoaster!!!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible SchedulePaid HolidaysExcellent Health Benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – No pay increasePressure to Sale Items with no CommissionSelfish Management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – To put so much stress on GMs that cause problems with employeesStop showing favoritism.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I try to make the best of it but wish I could change many things..”

</title><pros>Pros – There are opportunities for advancement if you have the qualifications & are willing to live & breathe your work & put it before anything else.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Minimal to 0 communication or feedback between management & employees. The place is much like a factory which expects its employees to be workaholics & not be compensated fairly for it.  Overtime is not tolerated & somehow disappears if you end up going hrs. Employees are underpaid compared and not compensated fairly for # of yrs worked. Management makes no time to make sure their employees are fully trained but yet excepts them to perform to superior standards.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make sure your employees are treated with respect & properly trained.  Don't except them to be comfortable on their own without having adequate, structured, & hands on training.  There is a reason why employees filter out like water.  Give praise & recognition when deserved..not just criticism.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Pay IS No Good Get Same As Cashiers (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“pay is no good for maintenance”

</title><pros>Pros – im in maintenance and we all work together, some great people there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – pay really sucks, maintenance does way to much to get paid same as cashiers that pretty much stand there, and maintenance is running every where is sucks</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – pay maintenance more im not the only one thats mad about what we get, that or dont ask us to do alot.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Proud to say I work at Pilot!”

</title><pros>Pros – This is a company that cares about its employees. I look forward to coming in every day and I have a sense of pride when I tell others about my job at Pilot.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I wish we got a discount on gas</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work !”

</title><pros>Pros – job security, family oriented , open door policy...you know PFJ are in for the long haulFor the most part the people here are truely nice and not just putting up a front.  Pilot is a growing company</pros>
<cons>Cons – some times you work your butt off and it doesn't show when review time comes around.  I do think that it would be nice to get a raise by how well you do instead of just a percentage</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – pay better for job well done.... acknowledge the little guys more</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Programmer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fine”

</title><pros>Pros – The company is very stable.Pay is decent for the area.I think the benefits are good (never had them until I came here though).Very easy to get time off if you need it.And unlike my last job, management has a good sense of humor here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I could make at least 50% more money at almost any other company in the area, but this is only my second job in the IT field.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Human Resources Administrator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for a resume builder”

</title><pros>Pros – Very family oriented. I love the people I work with.  It is like a loud, italian family.Management will not mind if you have to take some time off as long as it is an unpaid leave.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Corporate office positions are being compared with retail positions. I started with $10.50/hour. In the retail world that's outstanding. There is only one problem - corporate and retail is not the same and should not be bundled together to drive up the statistics.Pilot has always run on a low budget, understaffed and paid the very minimum. Only those that have a direct impact on sales (besides the senior mamagement; regional managers and sales reps) are being compensated well. That is how Pilot has managed being so succesfull - work the minimum paid employees into the ground and reward the managers who are able to have their employees produce high yields for the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 1/ Make your choices in management wisely.I know supervisors that barely have a high school education and there is a lot that they need to learn. Sharing the details of your very private life with your subordinates and then DEMANDING respect, not the best career building ground...Some highly compensated employees have been with Pilot for a long time, not sure how they managed to fly under the radar for so long... Perhaps because they advise us to aim for a 7 in the scale of 1 to 10. Apparently mediocracy have been working for them...2/ Increase the rate of pay for hourly employees instead of giving them access to a ridiculous health coverage that in the long run does not benefit the employees since it leaves them with pre existing conditions if they seek coverage elsewere .  This change could help reduce turn over, which would lead to increased productivity within the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Travel Center Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“They own you”

</title><pros>Pros – The pay is good and that is it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They own you 12 to 16 hours a day.Your job is at risk every day and they will tell you this.Take a pitcher of your familyto work because that is the only way you will see them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They could care less.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Great Place to Work”

</title><pros>Pros – Steady HoursDeli and at some locations, restaurant discountsGood communication from management</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most of the time you are doing 2 or more tasks at onceCustomers aften come in by the busloadsCustomers sometimes get rude and angry over company policies</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give more recognition, performance reviews, and pay raises!Please staff accordingly for holidays and busy hours</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Shift Leader (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pilot was the worst place I have ever worked.”

</title><pros>Pros – Before the merger Flying J was a wonderful company to work for. Good pay, friendly people, and caring management. Post merger was the polar opposite.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working 60 hours a week and only getting paid for 40 even though I was in an hourly position and should have gotten overtime pay. Working day in and day out for 5 years and when I finally crack under the pressure and leave the company, they don't even have the decency to pay the vacation time I was owed for 5 years of loyal service.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take pride in your stores as far as cleanliness. Treat the professional drivers with more respect(coffee is one of your most profitable items, you can afford to give away a cup with a fill up). Stop assuming that your employees are all thieves. If you treat them with a little respect and show some gratitude for the job they do everyday maybe they wouldn't turn their heads and ignore when someone is stealing something. Stop using the Loundsberry tests to replace competent interviewing for hiring new employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not good at all”

</title><pros>Pros – Dealing with people is hard, but he coworkers are friendly.  I have worked here for 17 years and love every minute of it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lots of hours, but no overtime to be found.  Benefits are good but take long to get enrolled.  It is what it is.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make employee relations more friendly. Improve the speed of the cash register.  Work harder to improve your relations with customers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>CASHIE (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OKAY JOB EXPERIENCE”

</title><pros>Pros – THE SCHEDULES ARE FLEXIBLE. Management works with time off requests. location is good. Workday is busy and goes by fast.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The salary is minimal. The employees are not interested in performing their jobs well due to lack of salary. Management does not keep personal oinformation confidential.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Maintenance (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not Good”

</title><pros>Pros – Much to do,never boring.Get to meet a lot of different people.Good hours to work.Management is not breathing down your neck.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management will shave time off your time card to save themselves.Management never does anything to take care of any problem.Never a pay raise.Management never says thank you or you're doing a good job.Hours and pay gets cut so you loose your benefits.Store management makes up their own policy and when it does not work,you get blamed.Stores are always dirty.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pilot has grown to big to fast.It can no longer govern themselves properly.I doubt very seriously if upper management at the corp. office knows what goes on in their stores.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“co- workers were great but mangement  had favorites”

</title><pros>Pros – Great food, part time hours,fun co workers,</pros>
<cons>Cons – was hired as a server but was put to work in the back of the house which means no tips less pay ;(</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I can understand why you went out of business</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-31</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Close to home, good deli</pros>
<cons>Cons – A lot of favortism, woman are not valued and are paid less than a man in the same position, no communication between departments.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need flexibility with job share, need PTO, communication.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Having a not so great day the Pilot way!”

</title><pros>Pros – Good opportunity for a beginner in management...has the potential to remain competitive for that experience level with pay.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is disappointing to those with extensive experience who have earned good money before-50-90k. There are tons of janitorial duties driven daily all the way to your level as the manager.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Good Luck and Hang On! You will work a lot with barely any coverage and you will often be called in to work when others call off...don't wworry though, you can take those hours for the team as you will be salary based anyway...go YOU!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Hostess (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Easy Job”

</title><pros>Pros – Great PayYou always had something to doEmployee Discount (25%)You got to be a taste Tester for new food!</pros>
<cons>Cons – The managment were very disrespectfulThey didn't care to help much, but sat aroundThey would tell you to do one thing but yell at you because you weren't doing the other(because clearly I don't think you can wash tables on one side and snap your fingers and be at the register on the other side)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Your a manager actually do your job and not sit in the office and talk on your cell phone</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-29</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sandwich Artist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst Job I've Ever Had”

</title><pros>Pros – Location, Opportunity for advancement, Travel Center management rocks,</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too much work for one person, you'll work by your self a lot, managers play favorites, discount sucks, can't get time off, will work more or less than you want, everyone is a drama queen</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Figure out whats going on at Subway. They've got things all messed up</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-03</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Most dont but I like it”

</title><pros>Pros – Diverse, large company.  Great opportunity for learning. 401k match and Christmas bonus are pretty good for salary employees, not so good for hourly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You work for a company that runs 24 hours a day.  Depending on the job, that requires you to be available all the time</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Communication between departments may be lacking.  Work (workers) may be redundant, because two employees in different departments are doing the same job</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Fuel Desk Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“only work here as last resort”

</title><pros>Pros – unable to make any recommendations</pros>
<cons>Cons – 80% of the staff is manager in name.  20% of the staff complete the assigned work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – assign duties to be copulated by the managers.  when giving the title of manager they assume the work completion is not their responsibility</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Server (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“dissaprove of the way things are ran and emplyees are treated .”

</title><pros>Pros – there are no pros at this point .</pros>
<cons>Cons – i have been on the server team of ta for 14years they care less about there employees . when the sales are down the guest count is down  the food over priced and the labor out the roof what are there solutions put more servers on and cut the money to nothing . when you have a complant they dont care . and after 14 years you tell them things have to change or you have to get another job to pay your bills all they say is we will miss you . they refuse to change anything for the good of there Staff .</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – you want to know why you are loosen money and long time emplyees and dedicated costumers the emplyees arnt being listened to and dont matter by there management .</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good stepping stone”

</title><pros>Pros – Large corporation with corporate guidelines and support.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not very good at internal support and promotions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More support and recognition for dedicated workers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier/Team Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people at my location, not a big fan of corporatism though”

</title><pros>Pros – The team I work on is made up of a bunch of great people. Of course, there is always one or two people who can be annoying or jerks, but overall the work environment is great. The truth about the truckers is that 98% of them are great to interact with. It's that 2% that some people focus on and they forget about all the nice ones. I'm in school studying economics, so its nice having all the different varietys of people who have such different perspectives on the state of the nation to ask questions to. Working at a truck stop/convenience store, you get to talk a lot of politics/public policy/economics with people, so I love that apect of it as well. Most of the customers I get are really cool people, and the 2% that are pissed off or bitter about something, I just remind myself that it's nothing personal and move on.</pros>
<cons>Cons – To be fair I came to work here with a lot of experience, but the training was abysmal. I had to learn pretty much everything here on my own. A lot of trial and error is involved and it can get frustrating. I also wish the labor wasn't so tight. It's really annoying being called so often to come and work for someone when I've already planned my week ahead of time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – A greater emphasis on training is needed. Obviously, the labor issue and the training issue are inter-related. I know Pilot is making insane amounts of profit right now. Invest some of that into training please.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A place to grow, so you can move on to a better organization”

</title><pros>Pros – Every position is capable of being notice3d and moving the needle.Work is fast paced and expectations are high.Good work is acknowledged with a significant bonus.The people are friendly</pros>
<cons>Cons – Top management is not people oriented to any degreeTop management is more interested in doing new deals than sticking to its knitting</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to get it right next time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Abominable Employee Relations”

</title><pros>Pros – Fellow employees at this center are, in the majority, very likable, and out customer base of truckers were fantastic people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In this 24-hour truck stop we had 12 lower level employees and 4 supervisor/managers, yet no management was available. It was common for the 2 cashiers on duty (usually one) to have their registers locked up and 20 or more people backed up in line, simply because a manager would not come out of the office to clear the problems. Training was non-existant. Employees are not allowed to verify their start tills. Breaks are clocked out for, but worked. Customer service is never a priority. Management gossips about management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire some management. This particular store is on its 6th general manager in 4 years.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Prepare To Be Sucked Dry And Spit Out”

</title><pros>Pros – Active job with many different facets to keep you busy.Good job stability for crew members who can show up to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Ridiculous labor standards.Incredible favoratism from upper management.What have you done for me lately means in the last week.A great manager is someone who works more hours than anyone else.Pathetic, almost non-existant training hours available to develop crew.A "human resources" department that exists to defend upper managements whims.Politics, politics, politics...brown nosers please apply.A company culture that could care less about the employees outside life and if they burn out...well there are always more desperate people out there to use up!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Realize that there is a reason you had around 150 first year managers last year, and it is not the great opportunities the company offers.  Ask yourself why 98% (literally) of your current management staff has been with the company less than ten years, and 80% less than five years.  It was not always like this, what has changed in the last five years to cause such incredible turnover.  My answer is insane labor standards, little to no accurate feedback from overworked regional managers, and upper management who only wants to hear what they want to hear.  How can you ever get any accurate information when all of your GM's are scared to say anything except what you want to hear?  I have seen several long term managers be labled lazy complainers for bringing up issues, and could tell hours of stories of horrible labor situations managers have been put in.  If every customer complaint about labor that was directed to local level management came directly to you, I think things would change quickly.  But hey, even the complaints about staffing that DO reach you are labled the GM's fault so maybe it wouldn't make a difference.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Data Center Technician Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Flying J, a good place to intern in Ogden Utah”

</title><pros>Pros – For an interm possition in ogden utah, it is a great place to work.  they were very flexible with scheduling and letting you work when you want to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I believe that the health benefits weren't very good for the full time employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to create an atmosphere where honesty is welcomed and embraced.  I think everyone plays the blame game a lot which creats an incentive to push on your mistakes onto others.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a long term employeer”

</title><pros>Pros – There is nothing great or nice about working for Pilot, they promote ASM that have no leadership qualities  There is nothing great or nice about working for Pilot, they promote ASM that have no leadership qualitiesThere is nothing great or nice about working for Pilot, they promote ASM that have no leadership qualities</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is nothing great or nice about working for Pilot, they promote ASM that have no leadership qualitiesThere is nothing great or nice about working for Pilot, they promote ASM that have no leadership qualities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There is nothing great or nice about working for Pilot, they promote ASM that have no leadership qualities, look for more professional managers, not uneducated individuals that are just promotable</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Management (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Chance for advancement and more work with no additional pay.”

</title><pros>Pros – The location is great.  Opportunity for advancement is good and most co-workers are friendly.  Flexibility with schedule.  Flying J provides free passes for mass transit.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are multiple divisions and companies within Flying J, but many employees have NO idea what other departments or divisions do. There is little to no training, or orientation for new employees. The communication between the different companies under Flying J’s umbrella is appalling, it’s like they are competitors.  You work for an oil conglomerate, so the better you do the more you help pollute the Earth.  There is little research and development for alternative energy; or..... maybe there is, and I just don’t work for that department.  Compensation is poor and the benefits are probably some of the worst in the country.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Reprimand employees with bad work ethic.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Shift Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“People should be promoted by abilities not likeableness”

</title><pros>Pros – the insurance was the best reason to work here. They are changing that as of the new year so it will no longer be obtainable by hourly employees.I havent had any trouble getting time off for my family when i needed it but others have.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management makes promotions depending on who they like not the ability of the employeePeople in same positions are treated differently</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Walk in hourly shoes before you try to run a store. Dont ask employee to do what you yourself are not willing to do.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-25</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work, but not great.”

</title><pros>Pros – There are great opportunities for personal growth and learning at Flying J.  Some managers give the ability to take ownership of your work and job.  If working in the right department, there is great bonus potential!</pros>
<cons>Cons – They have less than competive pay for the industry.  They require really long hours.  Upper management isn't really people oreinted.  Their health benefits are really expensive.  It is hard to earn vacation (zero in your first year).  There is a lack of parking at HQ.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay your people better to keep your them happier.  Expand the parking facility at HQ.  Continue to reward good work with bonus and other perks.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Shift Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you don't mind low pay with ever increasing demands on your limited time, This is the job for you.”

</title><pros>Pros – Working with the public can be an enjoyable experience until you have to take on all the responsibility placed on you for corporate's bad decisions.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This company sets you up for failure. Store hours are constantly being cut back, but the expectations remain. Through the winter months especially, employees are expected to do the same work with up to 100 less hours available.Training for store management is non existent. The store is allowed 30 hours a week for three weeks of training, but they are never given the opportunity to learn what they need to know, and then  held accountable for not knowing what they weren't trained for.Store management is instructed to "make sure that no one gets any overtime." Including deducting actual hours worked to make sure the employee will receive absolutely no overtime pay.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start treating your employees like human beings and not cattle in a feed yard</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work”

</title><pros>Pros – The deli pizza is amazing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management works too much with near same pay as non-managment (whom get no hours).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay the people who do their job consistently, more.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Travel Center Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Asks alot with little rewards”

</title><pros>Pros – Clean Stores. Numerous locations. Bonus</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not alot of teamwork. Focused on results at the expense of employee morale.  Employees just a tool- Not appreciated</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Lets remember who got you to where your owner could purchase the Browns-the employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Flying J Management GM's and up”

</title><pros>Pros – Work is enjoyable, pay ok, benefits are ok</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper Management needs some training , GM's and RM's  don't communicate or lie to employees,doesn't seem like they know their job, will ignore you or belittle you if you disagree with them.They will yell at you in front of customers or won't even talk to you for days. They don't schedule enough staff for busy days but will make sure when they work they have more than enough staff on hand. Very disorganized or lost...You would think when they have a mass exodus of staff they would investiate why.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get some training on how to handle people, follow hierarchy of reporting, don't bypass managers or belittle managers in front of staff. Don't hold grudges and learn to communicate to your staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Retail Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Business, Very nice concept but poor management”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun work environment, Lot of things to learn for retail business management, Tremendous opportunity to capture highway business.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor management, Slow response to market change, probably due to old and tired senior management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get out of your comfort zone, think big and think new,</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Co-Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Positive”

</title><pros>Pros – Weekly Pay, Better Inventory System</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours, staff turn over and not much staff appreciation</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need more locations in BC</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Crew (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A very stressful atmosphere to work in.”

</title><pros>Pros – On Travel Center Side the hours are decent, the job is not hard.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There's no guidance, people get away with anything, there isn't any follow thru or punishment if tasks are not performed properly. Important things don't get done and it falls upon the next person.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Managers be more responsible for there shifts tasks, and crew can't leave until they are finished with them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“NEVER A DULL MOMENT”

</title><pros>Pros – Fast paced, never a boring moment, If you are willing to forget about your personal life you can advance further</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor upper management that in turn creates less than ideal working environment. Never enough employees to cover shift, therefor store complaints rise. Employees not paid enough for the work that is expected</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Out with the old and in with the new is not always better when you have a valuable employee what you may save in wages you lose elsewhere</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-25</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“pilot is a good positive place to work!!!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – I like working for pilot, one of the best companies that I have ever worked for!! I have been promoted fast and have had alot of opportunities for advancement. It helps if you are an outgoing person and put forth effort to help out in anyway that you can. overall i think that if you try you can go far with this company. it doesn't hurt that they are expanding rapidly and need QUALITY people to fill the positions. the stores tend to be run well and upper managment atleast in my zone are very down to earth and make up feel like part of the pilot family</pros>
<cons>Cons – one of the main downsides that i see is that if you want to advance u need to be willing to go where they will send you.  If you are not able to be flexible in relocation then you have to wait for some of the upper TC management at the local store  to get promoted, quit or get let go. you have to also have to  flexible as to when you will work. for the most part as a cashier or maintanance person there is not a set time that you will work every day.  they tend to hire more people than are needed so the hours that you are given are not always what you need. but if you play the game and do a good job they will take care of you for the most part.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I think that do to the fact that we are expanding, we are bringing on some people that really are not a good fit for what we want. I work in a training store so I see alot of the new trainees, some of them tend to think that they are above learning the "grass roots" stuff because they are going to be running a store. I think that you are on the right track with the changes that you have made to the focus of taking care of the driver, and not making the cashiers try to push candy,cigarettes and other things on the customers. I think that it will really hurt the overall bottom line but it is the right thing to do</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is an exhausting place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Co workers try to have fun, but we rarely have more than 30 seconds to chat.Management works as hard as we do.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You can almost count on working two or three shifts every week.  Almost always need one more cashier than they are willing to pay.  Nothing gets cleaned well or often enough because they keep cutting payroll to up profitsCustomers complain constantly about long lines and pump key pads never working.Help desk is so overworked that after 20 minutes of being on hold waiting for them we often hang up and send the customer away with nothing.Grave shift cashiers work all alone quite a bit of the night.  No lunch, no break, no restroom break.Gaps in maintenance on weekend nights so bathrooms, garbage and showers are a total mess when day shift comes in and people complain all night about the mess</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Up payroll.  We would love to keep counters clean and coffee pots filled and fresh.  We would love to clean roller grill every day instead of when we have time.  We would love to give friendly service instead of "Can I get you anything else thanks, next please.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun employees, Horrible Company”

</title><pros>Pros – I enjoyed the people I worked with - they made long shifts filled with rude customers at least somewhat entertaining.There are a couple of shift-leaders and managers who keep the job from being totally disastrous, so as long as you're working their shifts, it's not that bad.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Rude customersFaulty equipment - our computers crash a few times a day - we're on the hold with our help desk every few hours at leastPumps that never work properlyCheapest company I've ever worked for - they're constantly trying to squeeze every dollar possible out of their employees and clientsCompletely disorganizedDon't expect to get paid for all the hours you work - they're constantly trying to stiff you hours here and there, read your pay stubs properly so they don't screw you over!Incompetent head office - they're completely oblivious to all the problems goingZero communication - they will put in place changes without telling you and then reprimand you for not following the "new" rulesTotal disrespect - you are not an employee, you are a slave; they bully you into submission and use threats to get their way</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop treating your employees like garbage, and actually invest your money into improving the company instead of getting every penny possible off of your loyal customers. Clients have been leaving our store in droves since there are so many local alternatives. The turnover is crazy high, with at least 2 or 3 employees quitting every week (we've had 11 quit in the last two weeks (including myself) - that's half our workforce!) Learn how to run a business, you cheap, lazy idiots.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Outstanding”

</title><pros>Pros – If you "consistently" work hard, produce results and improve, you will be rewarded</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work a lot of hours.  Sometimes hard to balance between work and family</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to provide updates to the employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Travel Center General Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I will never work for another company!!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – PFJ, is a family driven!!!!</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you are not wiling to work hard you need not apply proformance driven mangers are the key to individual growth with PFJ.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Retail Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It started out great, but now it is just hell to work here.”

</title><pros>Pros – good paygood benefitsstandardized computer based training for associates.</pros>
<cons>Cons – long hours, unappreciative upper management, penny pinching to the max.  lack of concern for a balance between family life and work life by above store management.  Flexible? you might want to carry a pic of your family with you to see them.  low pay for associates and that makes retention very difficult at store level.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increase pay to a living wage.  Quit pinching pennies.  This is a family owned company, remember that your employees have families to.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Under appreciated”

</title><pros>Pros – Meeting different drivers from all over the world daily.Liberal management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management doesn't care about the problems in the store.People are promoted for the wrong reasons.Hard work is not a matter of importance.Knowledge of products and services are not appreciated.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take a second and take a look at what happens in your store. Pay attention to what employees know, and don't know. Train people properly. Give credit to those who care about the business and their work. Positive reinforcement is a great management technique.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“extremely demanding”

</title><pros>Pros – Never boring, great  benefits, you get to meet a great deal of customers</pros>
<cons>Cons – A very tens atmosphere, you will get a corporate visit every week</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – it is okay to let your gm run the store, there is no needed to do weekly visits just to come around and criticized</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“always a bundle of joy”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits, team work, good listeners</pros>
<cons>Cons – open 24 hours, you bounce around the schedule</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – keep up the good work</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Maintenance (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its a job....its better than no job.  But the company can afford to pay its hourly people better.”

</title><pros>Pros – I have a set schedule.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The payscale is horrible.  16 year old at McDonalds start off making the same pay as Pilot offers its new employees.  I havent even gotten my review, or a raise....both are way overdue.  Pilot is a slave driver.  "Pilot...one law away from not having to pay its employees."</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is a difficult work environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – The family that owns the company cares about the employees and the pay is very competitive in the industry, It is a stable employment due to the nature of the environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The management is poor and as a manager, you can expect to work 60hrs or more a week without overtime pay.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The management at the retail level is not very good and they often get the job not based on experience but who they know.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not the best”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly down to earth managers, flexible hours, pay is not unreasonable considering, meet interesting people on both sides of the counter</pros>
<cons>Cons – Employees are treated as potential thieves,  raises are unheard of, the up selling and 2-fer goals are unrealistic in this time where no one has extra money, employee hours are constantly cut and then the next week we would be short-handed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try not looking for the negative all the time and try to encourage....negative re-enforcement has never worked...relax the witch hunt</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“One Big Family”

</title><pros>Pros – It was the family atmosphere of Pilot Flying J that won me over. The company is family-run, and the culture is very family-oriented. My managers and supervisors have been extremely patient & flexible regarding my schedule & my special-needs child. Working for this company, I feel more like I'm just a part of a big family that is all working together, and I really like that feeling.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Like any large family, communication is an issue, and the larger we grow, the more of an opportunity that becomes. If we could improve our communication, especially from corporate to the field, we might do a better job of cultivating the "family" attitude more uniformly at the store level.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to "do the right thing" for employees and your people. Maintain the family-oriented attitude that has carried Pilot for so many years. It works, and it's what I love most about working here.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-01</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's a Career at Pilot... Not Just a Job!”

</title><pros>Pros – It's just such a solid company, and because of that stability, hard working employees have the chance to grow with the company. And with all of the growth Pilot Flying J has experienced over the past year, my future feels very secure here. If you come to work and do your job well, then you are rewarded for your performance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There are downsides to every company, of course. The rapid growth of a company always causes some extra work for the employees, but it's worth the extra effort on my part. And PFJ rewards loyalty.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the communication going. Mr. Haslam has always been great about communicating his vision & goals for the company. We need to hear that on a regular basis. It keeps us going in the right direction!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Shift Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Large company looking to save every penny possible....”

</title><pros>Pros – paid vacation and team member rewards</pros>
<cons>Cons – unstable management and chain of command</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – stop being so cheap, take care/pride in your stores.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overworked with long hours and inconsistent time off.”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent pay scale and bonus program</pros>
<cons>Cons – Up to 16hr days expected of on site management teams without added compensation or additional time off.24/7 operation created an around the clock availability necessity which was not reasonable.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Ensure proper structure of management schedules to allow for proper and legal work time frames.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Shift Leader (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Be Prepared to be treated like an idiot”

</title><pros>Pros – I must say that I was promoted almost immediately upon being hired. There is a lot to do and time passes rather quickly. Great for a person with a busy body and no degree.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I was talked down to continually even though I was much more intelligent and held greater education than most of my managers. Also, the customer complain to you about how they hate the company all day, and its hard to disagree.Employees are treated like thieves and not given any respect. I had managed for a few years in a much busier work place and they treated me like I was an idiot.The pay was atrocious, every other place would offer much more than 8.50 dollars an hour to management level employees.Also, I was required to work extremely random schedules. Often I would work 4 over night shifts and 2 day shifts a week. This destroyed any normal sleeping schedule I could muster. I was sick and sleep deprived all the time.There is also an atmosphere of backstabbing. Basically, trying to rat people out gets you praise, nothing monetarily speaking though.Overall, if you are an intelligent person who holds a degree don't even think about taking this job, I did it because I had to, but I'd rather have started my own business or worked else.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat your employees with respect and compensate them fairly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Regional Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No time spent to develop me. I believe it was my spervisor though others have had lots of time spent with.”

</title><pros>Pros – Over load of information to run your business. Great benefits but costly.  if you travel you are well taken care of on the road</pros>
<cons>Cons – Came from merger. More worried about several psychological profiles. Little time spent with to be developed. Spent 3 hours with my supervisor in 6 month time span.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Follow on time spent with new managers. 70 percent of the people that came over from other company failed. Impossible for that many successful people to be poor performers. Training was truly next to none and made people feel incompetant when those that have been in system for years were the peroformers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Governed by greed!”

</title><pros>Pros – Growth organization.Reasonable pay.If you want to be in the truck stop business there aren't many choices and this is the largest.Profitable company with no danger of going out-of-business</pros>
<cons>Cons – Really unfair to the rank and file. For the money they make, the benefits should be much better.Nobody will ever retire from there. They get rid of people before they vest in profit sharing plans.They don't encourage new thinking. You have to suck up to the boss t to get ahead and the management team realizes that. So they just kick the dog to get ahead.The company portrays itself as  such great and generous people.  Nothing could be farther form the truth. They are cold-blooded to the core and don't care about people. Their generosity to charities is based on what is good for the name and business.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Move away from a family business and bring in new blood. Don't completely fixate on grinding people down to make you a fortune. Ironically, this could even make you more!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>CO Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A learning experience with a twist!”

</title><pros>Pros – As Flying J before it became Pilot run was a great company to work for. But, now it is very different in the sense that you are expected to work 55 to 60 hrs. per week no matter what every week. And you are only scheduled for 47.50; the same reason I had to get out of my last Management position.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Now that it is Pilot run they are replacing all levels of management with "Pilot" managers everywhere. So beware if you are looking at their ladder to climb!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Companies such as Pilot wonder why employee's have very little respect for them and the theft rate, vandalism rates are high. Because, employee's are not treated with respect and they are treated as "machines" .</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Was cheated out of Profit sharing! Fired within a few days of payout! worked there for years!”

</title><pros>Pros – The pay is great! However, the pay is not worth the work you will put in. It averages out that your employees, if they worked the same amount of hours, would probably make more than you! You work right in the middle of the day so anything in the morning is cut off , and you wont get home til late because you're not allowed to leave, even if you come in 3 hours early because you scheduled yourself in bluecube so you will have to stay unti it is scheduled to leave... so you wont get home til the kids are in bed. So you will have no family life whatsoever! It used to be a family run business and they cared about you and your family, but now it has turned into a money grubbing business that stretches every dollar out of you even if they are killing you!</pros>
<cons>Cons – They will work you to death! If company is coming you may have to work both of your days off, spend 18 hours there while the company is there, yet you cannot take off a slow day because you've already put in your hours plus and you are exhausted! You are expected to work your schedule in spite of wether or not you've worked your days off! If you have a family DONT work here!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – When I first started working for Pilot, they cared about their managers! I remember a time when you were treated like a human and not a work horse. Now, they expect you to stretch yourself so thin that you are no longer able to function. You are away from your family way too much and if somebody is coming expect to work nonstop for a couple of days before, because what they expect of you wont be done because you are more worried about customers in stead of the mondane things, you get to them, but they are not most important. Then once the company comes, expect to be at the store until your scheduled to time to leave, doesn't matter if you've camped out there, came in 4 hours early because company was coming, worked all your days off, and are exhausted and about to fall over. Most companies allow their GM's and RM's to have some authority and understand that they are the ones who go through most of the stress and work very hard... and shouldn't be measured by a time clock! A GM should be measured for job performance not bluecube! I remember a time when we would get visits and my Regional would see the hard work, and after the company would leave he would say "go ahead and go on home! You deserve it!"  that sort of thing is impossible now! they watch you like a hawk thinking you are "pirating time"! It's not pirating time if you have worked your hind end off all week and need rest! It's not wrong to leave work 15 minutes early because you came in  4 hours early to handle a call in. But you will get fired if you work different that your bluecube schedule!I would not advise working for this company now! If you would have ask me that question a couple of years back I would have went all out about what a great company this is and how much Jimmy loves his people! I don't think that way anymore! I think the dollar has gone to his head and a once great company that was proud of how it treated it's managers now has lost it's foothold in morals!My hourly employees were treated much better than GMs or RGMs. If they got mad at you because you documented them for being late several times or whatever, they would call the hotline on you, then you would get in trouble! But you were doing your job! GMs would get nothing in a Christmas bonus... but hourly employees received a small gift card! I don't think a bonus that you earn should compensate for a Christmas bonus!If you don't have a family, don't mind working your days off and continuing on with the rest of your work schedule... being called on to the hotline over stupid things... working not for your money but for far beyond your capabilities...then this is the job for you!Sure it pays very well! I made very good money! But it wasn't worth the time I lost from my children! I would get home at 9:30 or 10pm at night  and sometimes past midnight, my kids would be asleep and my spouse would be asleep. They would get up far before me because I was exhausted. I would get up, go to work and do it all over again... that's on the times I did go home! Quite a few times I had to pull all day and all nighters because if you can't find someone to replace a call in... you are stuck! And if I did get a day off I was so exhausted from working nonstop and rarely even gettng time to eat. Because when you are on salary with Pilot, you ensure your hourly employees get a lunch and ten minute breaks, you also are a moral person so you ensure your Co-managers get a lunch break and a smoke break if needed...but you are stuck without eating quite a few times! Because Pilot doesn't have a program in place to ensure their GMs get a break! They do not believe their GM's are human I guess! Work like a horse and not eat or sit down!! They have these slots in bluecube that shows breaks for everyone, even salaray managers, but ask any Pilot GM or RGM if they get a lunch break or a ten minute break! They are lucky to sit down for two seconds! Labor is so tight you have to make up the difference plus ensure everything else is done! Pilot is no longer morally right!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Co-Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Warning-Think Twice”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent salary and benefits. Nothing else</pros>
<cons>Cons – Terrible work/home life balance...terrible hours...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none-stick it..</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“pilot travel not what it claims to be”

</title><pros>Pros – good pay, training good, get to eat at a discount</pros>
<cons>Cons – you have to live there to be paid that good salary you are getting, no life other than work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – get real. people have families, church, friends. lot more to life than working my butt off for you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Happy at Pilot”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice company to work for.</pros>
<cons>Cons – not a lot of team members so call outs are a big issues.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be consices</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good work environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunities to work on interesting projects.Great people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – High turn over.  The company has not had the best insurance benefits.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More communication would be helpful.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“tough place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Small family atmosphere at store</pros>
<cons>Cons – Be prepared to work 60+ hours a week.  Not by choice, but becasue of payroll constraints.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Law of diminishing returns....Sooner or later, you have to put payroll back into the store to get the job done as expected....</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Something to consider...”

</title><pros>Pros – Available opportunity to advance within the company.  Once  you understand all the processes involved the business is all about maintaining standards.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If your not interested in marriage or personal life, this is the job for you.  Work schedules will vary from 50-70 hrs a week being the high end.  Nothing less than 50 as this is a standard for ALL salaried employees NO EXCEPTIONS!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Not much to say here.  A leader is there to train, guide, and motivate in the right path for success.  Lets make sure this is 100 across the board.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“wow!”

</title><pros>Pros – the best reason to work at pilot travel center is that it is a job and right now those are hard to find</pros>
<cons>Cons – you bust your hump, available for any hours, dont ever call off  and the fact that you cant force people to buy 2 packs of smokes and your no longer worth thier time as an employee if you dont mind being treated like dirt and constantly haveing your job threatened this is the place for you,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – treat your employees with respect  instead of beating them down and then saying thats still not good enough, even better try working in the conditions you created</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Shift Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pilot is a very strong company financially. Work hard and you will grow with the company”

</title><pros>Pros – variety of things to do. not bored</pros>
<cons>Cons – shifts change all the time. hard to plan things</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – n/a</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-10-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“some good some bad”

</title><pros>Pros – great entertainment if your into laughing at grumpy people all day.  fast paced so the time goes by quickly. they do have a 1-800 number for employees to call for issues their having. GM has every weekend off (only a pro if your a GM). Insurance available. 1/2 off at subway (up to $4.00)</pros>
<cons>Cons – bad hours for shift leaders, some weeks they do all three shifts 1st, 2nd & 3rds. raises are few and far between. not enough employees, if someone calls in your shift is gonna be bad because there's no one else to call to come in. TOO MUCH POLITICS.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – hold all employees to the same standards. promote by work performance and ability not likeability. listen when people tell you others are stealing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-09-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No life outside of work.Hourly employees get only two holidays Managers none.No personal days,”

</title><pros>Pros – The experience of learning many sides of a full service restaurant.Testing your strenth , weakness and abilties for every kind of food service.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Schedules done the day before you work.Reviews done only when you beg.Restaurant side is never on the same playing field as the C-Store.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They spend so much time worring their employees are takiing from them and never seeing how much they give of themselves.They should have been watchiing the top people before they went bankrupt.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It used to be great.”

</title><pros>Pros – None within the last three years.  10 years ago it was a great place to work.  We were proud of our stores then.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Quality of Life was not in favor of the employee.  Money has been taken out of the stores' payroll and gained elsewhere.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give more back to the communities where your stores exist; not just in Knoxville or the University of TN.  Make more store level employees full time and pay them what they are worth.  Your turnover will be much lower.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Center Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pilot's a terrible place for center managers”

</title><pros>Pros – Best reason for working for Pilot is that it does give you experience in working with retail.  Many times it's the only real opportunity for work in some areas of the country Pilot services</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours.   Upper management (regional and up) are made up of people who would not be able to successfully run a center as they are asking it to be run.  Manager's 3 year turnover expectation (Pilot expect to burn out it's managers and turn them over every 3 years).  Move up or out culture (4 years).  A CEO who has a terrible god complex.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – quit burning out your center managers so you can maximize your dollars.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>