<name>C Lazy U Ranch Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/C-Lazy-U-Ranch-Reviews-E560502.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-07-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Bartender (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Work hard to play hard.”

</title><pros>Pros – ~Beautiful surroundings/ sunsets!!~Staff are young and active.~Policies are somewhat lenient... We get to lay by the pool, play on the beach volleyball, basketball, and tennis courts.~ Don't have to pay for food or housing.~ Get a van to take us to play soccer on Mondays and the theatre/bowling on Fridays.</pros>
<cons>Cons – ~Gossip spreads fast. If you do something stupid everyone will find out within a few days.~If it's your first year working here you will probably get stuck living in Bunk House or Sunrise which are dorm like living situations. Its only for a few months though.~Not very many staff horseback rides.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There needs to be better communication between upper and lower management to let employees know what is going on in the upcoming week.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Gossipy High School like Atmosphere”

</title><pros>Pros – Free food and housingGreat way to meet new people and gain connectionsNice wagesBeautiful settingLaid back atmosphere</pros>
<cons>Cons – Guests are very 'snooty' and talk down to employeesPoor communication of rules in the work environmentStrong favoritism towards certain employeesManagement does not stand behind employeesStaff food is terrible</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management needs to stand behind their employees more. It is hard to enforce the rules when guests don't feel the need to listen to employees. In order for employees to best serve guests, the employees need to be happy!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>