<name>M*Modal Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/M-Modal-Reviews-E560438.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tech Support (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great WFH not so great company”

</title><pros>Pros – work from home...that is it</pros>
<cons>Cons – company shipped most positions overseas. MT's were not paid properly at times didn't receive paychecks on pay dates. Seemed to be layoffs every year</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – should consider holding on to loyal employees in the U.S. India techs doesn't seem to care very much at all about the person on the other end of the line, huge language barrier</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist/Editor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My Opinion”

</title><pros>Pros – Working from home. Good benefits. Great experience with supervisors. Excellent platform. Great if you like editing speech recognition.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unrealistic production vs quality expectations. Poor pay. Frustrating speech recognition that does not seem to learn. Too many accounts/account specifics to increase production. Apparently most work is off-shored to India, with only the most particular accounts staying in the US once the account is "trained" by US transcriptionists for speech recognition.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the work in the USA. Offer better pay.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good people and interesting work”

</title><pros>Pros – There are a multitude of problems to solve, and the development groups operate with a relaxed schedule, trusting their employees to come in for enough hours to get the work done. Corporate culture is excellent with quarterly catered lunches to discuss what the company is up to, monthly afterwork parties, and a general feeling camaraderie.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It will often be more than a 40 hour work week, and success among the developers is sink or swim. You are given ample resources to learn speech technology, but my experience is that there's not a lot of feedback as to whether or not you're meeting the standards until about a year in. Also, the company is experiencing a bit of growing pains between the merger with Medquist and outgrowing the bounds of the office, so the company now is not quite the same as it was a year or two ago.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Decide whether the company operates as a startup or as a larger corporate structure. As it is, the line is straddled, causing some confusion among the ranks. There's also some friction between the levels of management about how much work to do innovating versus work to fix holes with contradictory orders on either side. I do like how transparent the company is about where we stand in the business market and what the planned features are for the future.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Culture and compensation”

</title><pros>Pros – The people in the Franklin, Tennessee office were wonderful people to work with.  The company had fair salary wages for most roles within the organization.</pros>
<cons>Cons – M*Modal is the consolidation of several smaller medical transcription companies.  The integration of platforms and employee cultures was very difficult to complete.  Therefore, there were many silos within the organization.  Lots of changes in executive management over past few years.  Employee benefits were not great.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Low side of mediocre”

</title><pros>Pros – Got to work from home. Fellow employees are great to work with. Pay for supervisory and support staff is not bad.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 10 years and nearly as many CEO's; none of whom made any positive contribution. Transcription and support staff jobs are being outsourced to India. Technical issues go unresolved, until clients start complaining, then manual measures get put in place, sometimes for years. "Pay no attention to that man behind the curtain."American transcriptionists (the people that actually earn the money) are getting shafted buy low pay and long hours.Even the Indian workers are starting to complain about working conditions and low pay.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management would not know what to do with good advice.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This once great ship is sinking fast.”

</title><pros>Pros – The office is decent - if you like open office spaces.  Dress is very casual.  Don't have to pay for parking.  Benefits are decent.  They have quarterly catered lunches and "unofficial" gatherings at the office with snacks and beverages.  Relaxed atmosphere.  A few gems of good people within certain groups.  Some bright individuals work here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – M*Modal WAS ONCE a GREAT place to work.  Over 4 years I've watched it grow from a cool start up that was revolutionizing healthcare to a top heavy corporation that just wants to sell products.  Unfortunately, now it is a sinking ship.  Employees just keep wondering when and what the next bomb is going to be.Overall:- Too many company wide changes over the past 3 years (mergers/acquisitions, sales to PE firms, multiple CEOs, restructuring).- A lot of investing of engineering resources into a product, Catalyst, that has no sales!Not enough engineering resources into products that are making money.- IT and QA, is just awful.- Core engineering has no leadership and hence no direction.  Releases are constantly delayed, products recalled and back patched.  And as a result our products are immature.- Core engineering still operates like a startup - they don't follow good engineering processes and the products show it.- Management and accountability is a joke here.  You'd be lucky to find 3 effective managers in the entire Pittsburgh office.- You never know how your performance is going to be evaluated from year to year and no one is accountable for their actions.-Some people come and go as they please and at times not even their managers know where they are, nor do they care.-Inter-team communication is nonexistent.-There is zero room for advancement because of the flat structure.  Essentially, you get more work and hope you get a new title which reflects it and possibly a mediocre raise.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start by cutting the fat.  Get rid of the cancerous egos that exist within the organization which do nothing to help it.  Make people accountable for their actions.  Set achievable product and sales goals.  Lastly...pray.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“They took a job I loved for 25 years and my it so very stressful!”

</title><pros>Pros – Being able to work from home is the only pro</pros>
<cons>Cons – I had worked as a MT for 25 years in January. Of course started off with one company and they kept merging until eventually it was Medquist and then MModal. Who works for a company for 25 years and earns half of what they use to.  I am a good MT, I would not have been able to do it for 25 years if I was not, but MModal terminated me on Wednesday.  I was moved into a new region early in the year and an entirely new platform. I was given 2 weeks to learn it and after that the harassment started. I was not meeting their standards. First slow down, then you are not producing enough. They never took into consideration I had to learn everything new after 24 years. I had myself in such a panic I actually got sick and ended up in the hospital from complicated stomach ailment and had surgery in August, and stress was part of the reason.  I knew they were trying to get me to quit but I refused to quit, and Wednesday I got a call from my supervisor that I was terminated.  I found out recently that MModal is downsizing and sending most of their work off shore.  So we have other countries typing up our medical records. I find it despicable. I was wounded after I was terminated but today I feel free. Its not the company I use to work for and not worth getting sick over.  Im close to retirement age at this point, not sure what I am going to do, but for now I feel at peace.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start caring about your employees as human beings. Sending work off shore is not helping America!!  So many skilled people in America.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very Depressing.”

</title><pros>Pros – None that I can think of, other than you never have to face the horrible management people who treat you like dirt.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Where do I start?  They expect a 99.5% quality rating on your work.  There is no human being who can be almost perfect all the time, especially when dictating for foreign doctors whose English is terrible.  The formats and programs are constantly changing.  Just when you learn one and think you have it down, they change it on you, so slow you down.  Their goal is to not let you make too much money.  After 10+ years of putting up with this, I was terminated by phone call with no notice.  The positive thing is I make more on unemployment than I did working for this company, since the last 2 years I only made about $35.00 per week.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You will end up with no customers because the quality of the work coming from India is bad.  You will lose your company.  Karma....</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcription/Editor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“So ddd”

</title><pros>Pros – Truly cannot think of any</pros>
<cons>Cons – Fired without notice (I believe because I "made too much money;" was grandfathered in at a relatively high line count and they did not want to continue paying anyone more than a pittance.They are in the process of trying to send most work to IndiaYou are lucky if you make more than minimum wageYou are set up to fail so they can "justify" the pay cutsThere are many more; these are just a few</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-02</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Radiology Transcriptionist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Just got fired”

</title><pros>Pros – Working at home and even that isn't all that positive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I am the Radiology transcriptionist who worked for M*Modal for 3 years and wrote a review here a month ago.  I had been given warnings to get my report count up and I did so the warnings were canceled/no longer in effect.  Then it fell below their requirement and I was summarily fired with no other warnings given out.  The previous warnings did not say anything about having to keep my line count always at the minimum and it is reasonable to assume there may be pay periods where the count may fall below yet that was not taken into consideration at all.  This company does not realize we are flesh and blood people and will have our awful times, they see us as just numbers (easy to do when you never meet the people face to face).  They had been trying to force me and others out ever since they bought the company we worked for before them.  I was always able to meet their demands and then some while my former co-workers were steadily disappearing until they made their requirements so high that your average transcriptionist like me cannot keep up.  Then, to top it all off, I was told I had to contact IT to let them know I was fired and get return labels for their equipment.  So, they expect newly fired employees to continue to behave like an employee and do a job that should be done by their former supervisor or HR.  Very unhealthy antagonistic do whatever we want you to do even though its not your job and still keep up your counts or else attitude from management.  Then there are certain people in the IT department who, once they find out they are dealing with a woman, treat you like you are stupid because you asked them to repeat themselves due to their heavy accent.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start treating your transcriptionists like skilled workers instead of sweatshop workers.  I actually celebrated getting fired instead of being all depressed and angry about it, now what does that tell you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>MTE (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Treats Employees Like Dirt”

</title><pros>Pros – The only pro is working from home, and maybe if you get a good direct supervisor</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay per line, constantly increasing expectations, very little recognition.  Also, work may dry up on one account and you will then be sent to another team where you have to learn new accounts, which then slows you down, but you are accorded very little time to get your speed back up.  I was bounced approximately 5 times in the space of a year.  Ended up making minimum wage for most of that time.  Lots of editing, which only pays half as much as straight transcription.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to "the little people" who make your company the money it brags about.  You could not "delight" your clients if the MTs did not slave in the background.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exploitation of American workers to advance corporate VR development. and offshoring jobs”

</title><pros>Pros – In concept, companies which hire remote employees allow talented, highly trained professionals to work at home and sustain the quality of family life.  The original companies absorbed by MModal offered just that work environment and ethic. Through major mergers and acquisitions MModal became a corporate leader and sacrificed the very employees who enabled them to advance, selling in 2012 for 1.1 billion to an investment arm of J.P. Morgan Chase.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Medical transcriptionists hired by MModal  must work an established schedule, yet are compensated only for production.  Time worked that does not actually produce a key stroke, is not compensated.  Computer and internet downtime are not compensated.  Company does not guarantee sufficient work to enable employee to work entire shift.  A corporate decision earlier this year terminated hundreds of employees without warning to compensate for work now being done either offshore ofrby a scaled down voice recognition work force paid at approximately 50% of the transcriptionist line rate.  Ironically, it was these very same terminated employees who had perfected the voice recognition systems and trained the offshore employees who replaced them.  Additionally, top down management in more recent years became hostile and abusive.  Rules kept changing and were inconsistently applied by middle management with little or no accountability.  Indeed, the only accountability was a 24/7 accuracy rate of 99% required of the medical transcriptionist, the computation of which was never clear to the worker.  It is believed when efforts to force employees to quit failed, management had no other recourse but to terminate the top tier employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Consider the quality of life of the American worker, the accuracy and timeliness of medical documentation, the privacy of patient records, and the unjustified imbalance of executive salaries to just over minimum wage for an extremely talented, dedicated, and professional group of workers.  The only shame is that these workers did not organize a union to protect their interests before your management sacrificed theirs.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Master Medical Editor/MT (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't Even Bother to Apply”

</title><pros>Pros – Even working from home is not worth it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This company treats its employees like dirt in order to "delight" it's clients.  They consistently show that they are unconcerned for those who keep them alive in the marketplace.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start actually reading the answers that come back in your annual poll and do something about them.  Or better yet, just treat your employees as well as you treat your clients...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-31</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist/Editor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst employer ever”

</title><pros>Pros – There are no pros for this company!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Fired over the phone without notice.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Show some professionalism!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist/Editor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The epitome of corporate greed”

</title><pros>Pros – The only pro is working from home.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This company is proud of the fact that it is sending US jobs to India and the Philippines.  US transcriptionists/editors are held to a ridiculous quality requirement while taking a substantial cut in pay.  "Work harder for less money" is the message to faithful long-term employees.  No raises EVER, just pay and benefit cuts.  Coinciding with "expanding their global operations" (offshoring), they have laid numerous US employees off without any advance notice, just a phone call informing them they're no longer needed and are out of a job, effective immediately.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Quit lining your own pockets and pay the ones who make this company a success a livable wage!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Terminated, job abolished, after 10 years”

</title><pros>Pros – None that I can think of.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slave wages, about $35 per week lately, work dried up, jobs sent to India.  Managers treat workers horribly.  Very low morale.  Every email communication has threats of termination.  Just terminated without cause, told job was being taken over by full-timers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat your employees with some dignity or your company will go under.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Master Medical Editor/MT (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Been here 2 years, its a job!”

</title><pros>Pros – I get to work from home and be with my family</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay is low - could improve there</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-02</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist and Editor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The worst of the worst”

</title><pros>Pros – The only pro is the benefit of working at home.  I can't think of 20 words of anything positive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay, terrible speech recognition software to deal with, little to no opportunity for advancement in a totally dead end job.  This was the hell-hole formerly known as MedQuist, famous for stealing from their employees and their clients at the same time, and I think they have figured a way to steal from their workers legally now, because I barely make enough to get by.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You can advise them all you want, they don't listen whatsoever to their workers, unless perhaps it is those in Bangalore or the Philippines.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Master Medical Editor/MT (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Twenty-five plus years....for what?”

</title><pros>Pros – The only pro at this point is the ability to work at home.  Funny, this section requires a 20 word minimum, but I could truly not come up with 20 positive words for M Modal.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Cons – Not enough room here to list them all, but by the end of my time with the company I was making less than when I started. Corporate philosophy seemed to always be to throw a Band-Aid on a hemorrhage rather than really do the work necessary to prevent situations. People were placed in positions for which they had virtually no training or qualifications due to the constant restructuring; no matter how hard they tried, round pegs could not fit in square holes. Some of the managers were actually former clerks with virtually no medical transcription training or knowledge whatsoever! Yet they were the ones telling MTs and MMEs how to do their jobs. Virtually all the people I knew who took professional pride in their work are no longer with this company. Loyalty, integrity and hard work grew to mean nothing. It all came down to playing the game just right. Talk about "big brother" watching. It is a shame that a company we were once proud to be a part of is now an industry joke.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Why bother?  At one point, I actually witnessed them model the entire operations based on the poorest performing region!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Quality Improvement Specialist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Beware”

</title><pros>Pros – I got to work from home and be with my kids.  The one and only pro.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No sense of being a team.  Managers/supervisors constantly changing.  No positive feedback.  Always made to feel that I was too slow.  Pay cut after pay cut, and finally laid off 30 minutes before I was supposed to go on vacation with my family.  More and more work being sent overseas, leaving American workers unemployed and unemployable.  Quality of transcription subpar because transcriptionists have to rush to be able to keep up with line requirements.  Overall, a very bad experience.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay your American workers what they're worth, and stop sending work overseas just to save a buck.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist/Editor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Below minimum wage pay; horrible benefits; horrible management”

</title><pros>Pros – There are absolutely no pros about this company!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay, management, benefits, must use PTO if you are out sick, horrible morale, no positive feedback, employees are treated as inferior, work weekends and screwed up hours. Be prepared to be constantly berated and audited daily.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Higher pay wages, better supervisors with some form of humanity about them. Employees should not be forced into using their hard earned PTO if they are sick or have an emergency.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>MTE (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible company, no pay raise, just pay cuts in over 20 years.”

</title><pros>Pros – Can't think of any, used to be flexibility, but that is gone.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unrealistic expectations.  The powers that be need to be on Undercover Boss to understand  and feel what they expect.  If you work in California your benefits are different than if you work in a "right to work state."</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Realize we don't like to be treated like we are working in the 21st century sweat shops.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist/Editor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I have really tried to stick it out, but it's just not working.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good insurance benefits, good trainers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They do not pay well.  Not enough work, constantly running out for months now.  Very inflexible on shift scheduling.  No paid hoidays unless you use vacation time.  I've chosen to use my PTO for those days I run out of work, which is at least 3 out of 5 days a week.  Plus, and I may be wrong in this opinion, but it seems they really cater to their global team more than their US employees.  If you visit their Facebook page, they clearly post in favor of their overseas employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – When your US employees are constantly running out of work yet you're still outsourcing overseas, there's a problem.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist/Editor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst place I have ever worked in my life!”

</title><pros>Pros – Insurance is comparatively cheap, and working from home saves you money and time spent commuting.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I don't even know where to begin, but they are completely unscrupulous and predatory toward their own employees.  When you work at home, you are isolated from fellow employees, a fact they use to undermine your confidence (oh, geez, nobody else is having that problem, etc.) and keep you in the dark about company policies, management's agenda and even your own pay rate!  I have worked 5 places in my life and was promoted at the 2 hospitals I worked at as an MT before my job was outsourced to M*Modal in 2009, so I know I'm no slouch, but have never experienced such utter undeserved disdain from an employer in my life.  I won't even go into the compensation or lack there of.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Wouldn't waste my breath.  There's no hope for anyone who would do to their employees what I have seen done by the management here.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-02</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist/Editor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stay away from this company!”

</title><pros>Pros – It's great to be able to work at home and the pay was always on time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Punitive QA policies that take money out of your pocket for things that aren't your fault, poor communication from management, ran out of work all the time and had to go on partial unemployment, pay cuts, constant changing of client profiles.  You don't know the names of any of your coworkers and cannot contact them.  The company expects you to work in a complete vacuum.  No chance for advancement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Bring back bonuses, bring back full pay for editing reports (they currently pay 40% less your normal line rate for this privilege), supervisors need to be more sensitive to employees and more approachable.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>MTE (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No matter what they change their name to, it is still the same horrible company.”

</title><pros>Pros – Working from home; good IT support; supplied most equipment needed; had a few decent CCMs that really tried to make a difference, but always ended up quitting; once a great company to work for until sent home to work but in reality, up until 2008.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay cut in half; no communication unless it was negative; accounts taken away if you made too much money and given the "bottom of the barrel" accounts; people in positions without having experience; treated as a number; life made miserable if you voiced opinion or concern that was not receptive so in turn, certain CCM would do everything opposite of your needs to the point of interfering with caring for family, etc.  As mentioned by another employee - run!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – CCMs and supervisors should be experienced and not use their position as a weapon; respect and pay those who allow you to live the lifestyle you do.  This company is where it is because of the MTs, as are your bonuses and high yearly salaries.  Keep up the greed, outsourcing, disrespect, accepting low standards of work, etc., I can assure you that one day you too will be living paycheck-to-paycheck because of one little word - karma!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>MT/ME (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor pay for MT/ME”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits are okay as long as you are a full-time employee.  Not having to commute to work every day is a real plus.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay cuts, poor communication from supervising manager, everything is on a need-to-know basis and we are usually the last ones to find out anything, which doesn't make one feel they work for a company that is ethical.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay your MT/ME staff a living wage!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“M*Modal used to be about improving healthcare but now is about selling products and making money.”

</title><pros>Pros – The founders of the technology company (Michael, Juergen, and Detlef) are amazing people.  They are bright, talented, driven individuals who don't forget their roots.  The Pittsburgh office is filled with a number of talented teams and individuals.  The Pittsburgh office maintains a fun and relaxed atmosphere - casual dress, parties, flex time, etc.  You have the opportunity to work with cutting edge technology and some really talented resources.    Some nice perks, free Keurig, fresh fruit, monthly luncheons.  Overall, was once a GREAT technology company focused on making a difference in healthcare and clinical documentation, now is an OK technology company focused on making and selling products.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No real career opportunities.  Once you get a job, plan on being there for a while.  R&D needs to seriously refine their development, release processes.  They still develop like a start-up, but try to deliver like an established corporation.  Simply not scalable.  Since the merger with MedQuist, we have become very top heavy with senior management.  People seem to get hired based on who they know, not what they know or can deliver.  Becoming a typical good old boy network like many other large corporations.  Senior Management is more focused on selling products and gaining market share, rather than improving healthcare, improving doctor's experiences, and improving service to our customers.  The vision seems to have shifted and I no longer feel like I am working for a company that is making a real difference in the world - I might as well be working for any consumer engineering company.  Senior management wastes a lot of money early in the year, then pinches pennies at the end of the year to cut costs and boost profits.  Benefits have gone down after the merger.  Compensation has gone done after the merger - at least for anyone who is not management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop trying to be Nua-pple.  Remember what made M*Modal so successful and get back to it.  Practice what you preach.  Be strict with your spending all year, just not at the end when you missed your numbers.  Improve your development and release processes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Transcriptionist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This company treats employees horribly.”

</title><pros>Pros – Get to work from home.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Constant threats of termination in just about every email communication, phone meeting.  Very bad for morale.  Don't they realize if they treated their employees good, we would produce better quality work?  None of the employees care anymore.  We are just holding on until they go under and we can get our unemployment.  Can't wait to see that day come!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat American employees with dignity and respect.  Give us realistic sick leave, instead of 3 lousy days!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcription (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Mmodal - just like your old fortune 500 company”

</title><pros>Pros – Pays on time, benefits, ever growing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Right hand doesn't know what the left is doing, like most big companies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Walk the talk.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Everchanging, each day is different”

</title><pros>Pros – Work from home, no traffic</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay, low pay, low pay</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Human Resources Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sr. HR Executive with experience in HR Generalist, Recruitment and Training and Development”

</title><pros>Pros – Had good experience working with Leaders of the company directly</pros>
<cons>Cons – No growth and salary is not satisfactory</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Lead (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor”

</title><pros>Pros – Good till it was in AKR Tech Park.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unprofessional, same language speakers given preference by people in management, one manager handling different departments (production vs quality) and preference shown to one team handled by manager to look good in management books.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Instill professionalism in managers and teach them to walk the talk.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was good company to work until it was in AKR Teck Park.”

</title><pros>Pros – Very nice interior infrastructure and neatness.  Salary wise it is good company for those who perform well.</pros>
<cons>Cons – New office posses bad and limited infrastructure and</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Human Resources Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“learned a Lot”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Work Life Balance, More Learning, Increasing Responsibility, Good Infrastructure, IT enabled</pros>
<cons>Cons – Internal Politics, Authority Misuse, Work Culture, Invisible Matters, Break Link between Higher and Lower Authority</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please give authority to those who themselves are not discriminating the others by their nativity and language</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible company to work, near to hell”

</title><pros>Pros – Good collegaues, good team, good place to lean.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No leadership, managers are worst.  Managers trouble MTs by deducting salary or not giving the salary at all.   Sometimes even salary is not given if target line count is not reached.  Mangers have ego problems.  MT tools never work.  line counts are such that they are never reached.  I have been working here for more than 5 years, but for the past 2 years have experienced horrible management.  My salary was not given for 2 months in the last year and now for the past 1 month kept on hold because I did not reach the target line count.  Line count counted by the management is always less than what the MTs count.  This company is closer to hell.  Never recommend anyone this company.  Loans are offered and in return ask for blank cheques.  If MTs raise their voice they are kept as non-direct and are given horrible files.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please be kind to MTs.  Because of MTs managers are growing up.  Don't harass MTs.  Managers are very rude and have ego problems.  I would have mentioned the names, but it is far better if Management find those people.  MT tools never work and in return line count is never reached, because line count is never reach salary is kept on hold.  Stop troubling MTs.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“overall satisfactory to work with”

</title><pros>Pros – gained good team work experience</pros>
<cons>Cons – no stable policy, keeps changing</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Quality (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Healthscribe, Max Healthscribe, Spheris, Mmodal...what next?”

</title><pros>Pros – 1.  Flexibility ( work from home option)2.  Made a brand name as Healthscribe...still people sticking around because of that</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1.  Bad payment and incentive policies of recent.2.  Bad managers...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You could get more employees from anywhere but you can't substitute that for experience in this field...but you guys have different ideas I suppose.  Myopic ideas rule...that is the whole point!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“waste company - bangalore AKR tech park”

</title><pros>Pros – I attended 5 rounds of interview (4 technical, 1 HR) , they took all the details like salary slips, revision letter and two weeks later they informed i got selected but they did not send any offer letter, after a month they gave feedback saying i refused to work in some technology they asked in interview which is false info. Everyone's target is to get offer on all the interviews we attend. If thats the case they would have rejected in technical round or HR round, why they have to inform me i got selected then giving feedback like this. Not only to me it happend some guys who attended interview along with me. This is happend in dec 2012 in AKR tech park, bangalore office.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Think 100 times before attending interview.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Reveal the interview result only if you are ready to give offer letter. once committed please dont say stupid reason to avoid the candidate.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – laid-back culture, flexible dress code, good work-life balance, diverse talents, competitive pay, unstressful environment,  very friendly employees, founders of the original M*Modal (the Pittsburgh office) are very smart, modest, and encouraging</pros>
<cons>Cons – not that many, but maybe the unpredicative future due to all the mergers and  acquisitions in the last year?Also, it could get frustrating getting people on the same page!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Make sure you keep the cool culture you created in the Pittsburgh office and spread it among the rest of the company!- Always remember and help everyone in the company to remember that the ultimate goal is to make an impact in healthcare rather than making $$$- Improve the communication channels among the different teams and help every employee no matter what role they play to see the big picture!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Medical Transcriptionist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I hate this job every waking moment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Absolutely nothing positive to say about this company.  They treat American employees horribly, while providing workers in India with FAMILY health care, including ELDERLY PARENTS, free transportation to and from work, free meals.  It is shameful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The only one I can think of is working in my home.  Other than that, nothing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat American employees with dignity and respect and pay us a salary we can live on.  We hate you and will continue to do a lousy job in the hopes of sabotaging this company.  When this company goes down, we will all be laughing because you deserve nothing but contempt.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lack of transparency is an issue.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good team work though not everyone is open.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Transparency is not up to the mark.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More transparency required.  Need to have more friendly policies.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Joining here is like you are committing a suicide.”

</title><pros>Pros – All is well when the company name is CBay, Everything has gotten worst and worst when the name has been changed to MModal.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Feeling shame to be a part of this company, which is not having a job security for even a single employee.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat employees like human beings, not like machines.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Junior QA (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Friendly environment in office.”

</title><pros>Pros – salary on time and good management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – only one weekly off for night shift.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>MT3 (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very tough to be loyal and concerned about what is getting produced.”

</title><pros>Pros – I can work from home.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Terrible pay rates. Terrible paid time off benefits.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give us a living wage!  Give us REAL time off besides the 7 national holidays.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>