<name>Ideal Insurance Brokers Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Ideal-Insurance-Brokers-Reviews-E561802.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Computer Operator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worked as a computer operator and web designer. I had fun”

</title><pros>Pros – There was prompt payment of salary while i worked at Ideal Insurance Brokers. The company was constantly opened to great business ideas and opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – The Salary was very low and wasn't improving even over the years and after several openings. I think it had a lot to do with the management policies of the company which had a lot to do with the ideals of the business owners</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – My advice to the Management is that they should bump up the salary structure</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Risk Managet (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not an Ideal company to work with”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Exposure as the company is small.Various Opportunities as Insurance industry is growing in India</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low compensationPoor work culture</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Risk Officer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Has been a great place for learning insurance at large.for immense exposure, this is a right place to start with.”

</title><pros>Pros – From top level to bottom, all are so co-operative.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes it become tough to manage all things all together.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Should provide more compensation.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>