<name>E-Nopi Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/E-Nopi-Reviews-E561640.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-07-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Math Tutor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Having fun while you work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible schedule; you can work anytime!Have fun while working; the children are energetic and playful. It's like "Kids Say the Darnest Things!"</pros>
<cons>Cons – The children can be very noisy and playful at times, making it a little frustrating to keep your composure.Not all of the children will follow rules or directions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Teacher (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good stepping-stone job, but little room for creativity, poor management”

</title><pros>Pros – -I was lucky enough to have great coworkers.-Flexible schedule-Provides great opportunity for developing your skills in talking to parents-Curriculum is provided</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Directors weren't very understanding of teachers' needs; they were very often in for the money more so than the teachers' and students' needs.-No benefits-No room for creativity-You will need to be able to work with various age groups at the same time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Rewarding experience with children”

</title><pros>Pros – rewarding experience working with kids, very few hours each week so it's easy to balance between work and personal life, great curriculum and program, good practice multitasking</pros>
<cons>Cons – few hours, lack of opportunities for teachers to collaborate and discuss each child's progress, sometimes you end up doing more than just tutoring (since it's a small company, you might tutor, grade, administer a diagnostic test all at once)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It would be great if there was more communication between the directors and higher-ups because the way the director trained me is the complete opposite of how the assistant director says that things should be done.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>