<name>G BY Guess Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/G-BY-Guess-Reviews-E565635.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Co Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great company”

</title><pros>Pros – fun environment and great company to work for</pros>
<cons>Cons – Didnt like the store manger and associates fight over sales.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-30</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A new disorganized company”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun product and people to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Disorganized. Things changed on a regular basis</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Co Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company to grow”

</title><pros>Pros – if you want to move up in retail, this is a great company to do so. Pays well, you have vacation time and benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – You could be overwork at timesneed to work weekend and holidays</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – it's easy to communicate with upper management</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Design (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bad!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits and you get gret discount for your clothes.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management treat you like slaves. You need to work really long hours including weekends. There is no support from management and too much micro managing. You are under constant pressure that your job is not secure</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees and trust their judgement. They know what they are doing</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Store To Work At”

</title><pros>Pros – DiscountsMeet New PeopleLearn Fashion Trends and more.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper ManagementHours are crazyCompany doesn't try to help.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get better managers</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“G by guess”

</title><pros>Pros – Great customers, can have fun with them and build relationships. Concept and design are fun and unique.</pros>
<cons>Cons – None that I can think of.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I love it here!”

</title><pros>Pros – 40% employee discount.Great managers and co-workers.Pretty cute clothes,purses,shoes,sandals etc.Every once in a while employees get 50% discount in all the regular clothes.I love working here all the time nice environment!Nice club music and loud (costumers hardly hear us when we greet them.LOL!)We have walkie -talkie to communicate.Which is so cool!The SALES section is already 50% but you get additional 50% off.Really cheap!</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Associates schedule is base on how much we sell in a day,weeks and in a month.-Associates are very competitive and steal your costumer even though they've seen you that you are  helping that person.They don't even care or bother to ask who help her/him first,but because they just want the sell for themselves.-A lot of costumers don't even need our help because they got it or they are just browsing around..Sometimes they just leave because it kinda annoys them that we follow them all the time and ask them the "Are you finding everything okay!" Again and again!-At the cash register.The cashier will ask the costumer,"Did anybody helped you today?" and if she said, she did/he did then the sale goes to your sell credit.(we have to tell them our name so that they will know who helped costumers).Overall if you want to work here and get hired just provide great costumer service and have fun with it.=)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lukewarm”

</title><pros>Pros – The great thing about working there was the discount. You can use it at G, Guess, Marciano, Guess Kids, and Factory. Flexible hours. You can listen to music all day and meet great people. The best thing is the employee bonus days: 50% off anything. Includes red marked down items.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You don't get paid anything at all. Just minimum wage. No matter how long you've been with the company..... you may even see a 10 cent raise during your time there. There's really no room for moving up the career ladder if you live in a city other than the headquarters. Requires you to work hours on holidays...You have to meet daily and weekly sales goals so it can get mighty competitive and ugly on the sales floor. This is how you get your hours. By the way you don't even get commission. They require you to wear G By Guess clothes to work and dont really like it if you wear the other brands. The G clothes are very poor quality, expensive and ill-fitting. If you are a high schooler the clothes may be suited for you, but not young adults. Very tacky and bedazzled. Managers show favoritism to employees that sell the most. Overall, its a headache. High turnover.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat the employees with more respect. After all they are the driving force to bring in the all the money to keep your job and meet all the monthly, quarterly and yearly goals. They do a lot of work to not even be paid that much.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>