<name>Arthur J. Gallagher & Co. Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Arthur-J-Gallagher-and-Co-Reviews-E57.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Easy interview”

</title><pros>Pros – Learn about selling insurance. Meet upper management</pros>
<cons>Cons – Easy material. Tend to get lost in the mix</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-31</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Producer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nepotism at its finest”

</title><pros>Pros – Hard to think of any</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not sure how a publicly traded company could have so much nepotism.  Only way to get anywhere here is if your last name starts with a G and ends with an R.  You do have a chance if your a cousin, but if your reading this and looking for advice, your probably not a Family member.  Intern program is a joke, more of the same nepotism.  One of these days Wall Street will figure this out. Perhaps then something will change.  Good employees are leaving rapidly and morale is at an all time low. Ask them they did an employee survey that shows those results. The Gallagher way they talk about is not the document they claim.  The Gallagher way is to take advantage of good hard working employees and reward the family with big pay while they do nothing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work in hiring and promoting family. Before long only family will work for the company and nothing will get done. Start hiring and promoting qualified employees and the company might grow into the national company it could be.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good people and good company, poor industry”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are excellent.  Everyone there is willing to help. In the Los Angeles Office you are slowly worked into the producer role, allowing you to learn the business over a number of years.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The insurance industry is not super stimulating and the industry as a whole is very complacent.  Very few, if any, MBAs.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Arthur J. Gallagher Summer Internship Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – - Access to upper level management- On-the-job learning experience- Access to client meetings- Weekly presentations to management and other interns</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Cold-calling- Doesn't seem like a great job starting out of college</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work to incorporate 1st year full-time employees in the consultative sales process, to attract other young people to work for the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Summer Sales Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great experience and internship”

</title><pros>Pros – Access to executives and senior experiences</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some tedious duties and tasks</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Understaffed, overworked”

</title><pros>Pros – Time flexibility, close to food places</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor management, unethical behavior/manner, unhelpful</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to employees and take steps to make work a better environment</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Accounts Receivable Specialist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to learn!”

</title><pros>Pros – Worked with you on flexibility of what you could work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Definitely a lot miscommunication that was unnecessary.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Receptionist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company with great benefits..high stress...heavy work load....”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits..opportunity for further education</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very heavy work load, high stress..not a good environment to work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You might want replace the humans with robots..</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Trade Payables Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very stressful work environment with little help and training. Lot of employee turnover in trade payables department.”

</title><pros>Pros – Clean offices, great parking, and some great co-workers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too many systems to learn, very little training time and no written procedures to do your job. Management in trade payables department tell you do not worry about learning the job but get on you and throw you under the bus if things do not get done.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees when they tell you that they need help. Also get some written procedures and give your new employees more training to do their assigned jobs.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Extern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exterrn”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people, interesting industry with huge growth!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Could pay more just like every job.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“All about what your last name is”

</title><pros>Pros – Some really people to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Health-care is invasive to keep a low deductible. Must track daily exercise and report it online. Unless you're related to someone or bring a book of business with there's no room for advancement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire people who are not relatives</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Producer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent place. Great resources, poor compensation structure.”

</title><pros>Pros – Large organization, good resources. Good people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor payment structure compared to smaller brokers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Loosen expectations in the margin.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Accounts Payables (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bad Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Generally coworkers are nice and helpful</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management has no idea what is going on.Company fires people all the time and has a high turnover rate.Company makes lots of money but feels it should continue to outsource work to India and shrink department size. Overwhelming amounts of work for employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn to care about your employees before the company can not function.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stay away!”

</title><pros>Pros – Global reach. We had good coffee in our office.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Just about everything else. Advice if you are considering going to work for these people: Don't. If you're like I was, you've probably read a mix of good and bad about AJG, but the bad is really bad. And if you're like me, you think the bad is probably just rare exceptions in certain areas. And like me, you would be dead wrong. These people will promise you the world, then throw you under the bus if it suits them. This is a very fragmented organization, so all the resources they have will likely not be made available to you, even though they'll tell you otherwise. Don't just walk away. RUN!!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I won't waste my time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great organization, culture, and opportunity within this growing company”

</title><pros>Pros – Ever challenging and full of opportunities to perform.  This company allows you to make your own impact but gives you the resources to be able to meet and exceed objectives.  Although, there is the appearance of rigid hierarchy, you can speak with most levels of the organization as if all were peers.  There is quite a bit of nepotism but they make everyone earn their wings.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Medical Benefits are not the greatest and stock purchase could be at greater discount</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep up the good work and the stick to your growth strategy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Summer Sales Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I had a positive experience at Arthur J. Gallagher.”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun work environment. Very good internship</pros>
<cons>Cons – Selling employee health benefits -- boring stuff</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More structure</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was a good job from responsiblity angle”

</title><pros>Pros – Gvies Good learning opportunity with out matching pay. good for sales folks</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor HR , Does not care about work balance or employee's ultimate well being</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Internal Audit Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“internal audit intern”

</title><pros>Pros – learned a ton about the internal audit process, got involved in a lot of audits and was able to complete a walkthrough audit of corporate tax alone</pros>
<cons>Cons – since my inexperience, my ability to add a lot of value to audits was limited</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Full of opportunity”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunities for growth within the company</pros>
<cons>Cons – High expectations of client teams</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great chance to expand professionally”

</title><pros>Pros – The program was well organized. Senior brokers are more than happy to spend time with you and show you the ropes.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you didn't feel comfortable confronting the senior brokers, then you were left without things to do. Have to be proactive.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep offering the internship.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Network Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“High Stress, long hours and very caustic work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Not a lot of positives that I saw from my tenure at AJG.</pros>
<cons>Cons – High stress. Understaffed. Favoritism to certain team members.  NO TEAM structure. Managers are required to work as engineers and can not manage the teams way they should. The team that I was a part of was one of the most dysfunctional teams that I've had the displeasure to work with in the 20 years I've been in IT.   Work from home non existent for Operations folks...</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Adjust staffing levels. Acknowledge employee contributions and SKILLS. Allow work from home for ALL team members, not just the chosen few.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Intern”

</title><pros>Pros – Great supporting cast, Above average pay, Great hospitality, Numerous areas for growth and development, Hands on experience, Never sitting at a desk bored/doing nothing</pros>
<cons>Cons – You have to work in all areas, regardless if you're interested or not</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Prepare to work long hours for lower industry pay and little recognition.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people that are in the same boat and most are willing to help you however they can.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay, long hours, very little appreciation for what is expected of you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Wake up and show appreciation for the employees that go the extra mile day in and day out. A raise more than every three or four years, a little something at Christmas, acknowledgement.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior IT Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great work life balance, but not a place for innovation”

</title><pros>Pros – -I was fortunate to have an amazing manager that gets it (need for processes, empowers employees, doing the right thing, not overloading employees).-There is plenty of work and opportunity to wear many hats.-Hours are very reasonable. Work from home Fridays.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -The business is a stale environment. Innovation is stifled and not an exciting place to be.-Fundamental issues with senior leadership team's view of technology.  Historically, the company spends only 30% compared to what companies of comparable size spend in IT.  The new CIO of AJG indicated that the senior leadership team see's their industry as a "relationship" business and does not see how technology can be their competitive edge "yet". Good news is that the CIO has an action plan and made it his goal to convince the senior leadership team to invest more in IT and use it as a competitive advantage.  There are signs of improvement. The company has hired a lot of new smart people over the last year to assess the industry and create a Roadmap for IT.   However, was surprised that this wasn't already in place since the company has been around for 50 years..-The lack of understanding Account managers have of how clients can benefit from analytics and how to proactively foresee their clients need results in non-innovative requirements and dull BI development.-The underinvestment in IT has resulted in the company running sort of between a startup and a semi-mature company.   Very limited IT governance processes, no enterprise architecture group, no architecture reviews or standards for infrastructure. No processes in the group I was in, but have implemented standards and processes since then.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – -There is a lot of value technology can bring you. Maximize this potential.-Develop a client management strategy where you are a strategic partner, not just order takers.-Hire new account managers and/or train the account managers to be a strategic partner, not just an order taker.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Compensation Needs Improvement”

</title><pros>Pros – Very professional atmosphere, but that is about it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Overworked, underpaid and very limited opportunities for promotions</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-01</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great summer internship experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Very good work culture overall. I loved working there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I think the business is hard to get into. Definitely need to be a people person.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Underwriting Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Low pay & a lot of stress”

</title><pros>Pros – Some of my co-workers are still friends today. Usually not a problem to take a day off. Chairs were comfortable. Could listen to music at my desk. Nature of the work was interesting and kept me around a lot longer after losing faith in advancement & management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Favoritism & male chauvinism run rampant. Pay raises & bonuses frozen for years, yet company brags about how much revenue they are pulling in. Obvious outsourcing to India will ultimately replace some jobs in the future. Strong leadership is lacking. Training is lacking.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Care about your employees. It really isn't that hard. Don't hype how well the company is doing fiscally then turn around and claim it isn't in the budget to give raises to people who work very hard to keep those wheels turning for you. Make advancement opportunities available for everyone who qualifies, not just friends of senior management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-28</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Gallagher Benefit Services Summer Intern”

</title><pros>Pros – Tremendous culture and work environment.  Upper-level management is very much involved with employees/interns and always willing to offer advice and assistance.  Exceptional opportunity to gain sales training as a college student and a heavy emphasis is placed on increasing the interns professionalism and value as a future member of the workforce.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Industry that demands significant training before an employee would be able to tackle problems on their own</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to stay involved with the internship program and develop young talent that will eventually lead AJG to further success in the marketplace.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Contractor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Beware”

</title><pros>Pros – Company has workout/fitness center and a nice, but pricy cafe.</pros>
<cons>Cons – All of my managers were from Arthur Anderson, and we all know what the management did to that company.  Positions were 'created' for Arthur Anderson friends.  Gallagher is not a bad company to work for, but someone should be watching who's hiring employees.My manager fired me because I couldn't complete a project that she knew nothing about.  She was with AJG for only 2 months before I started and I could tell she didn't know what she was talking about and that I would be the 'scapegoat' when she couldn't meet the timeline.Nice to know I was right about that!!!!  It's weird getting that sense when you first meet your boss.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please watch that not too many people from Arthur Anderson are hired.  Also, be sure that projects are given the correct timeline. AND Gallagher Family........ watch out for those Arthur Anderson people, they brought down one company and after working with them....yours could be next.  One more thing Mr.Gallagher, you know that book "The Gallagher Way"?  The Arthur Anderson people made fun of it for an hour during one of my meetings.........</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – people that work there are great to work withgood culture, my superior was one of the best I've worked for, very easy going.</pros>
<cons>Cons – benefits could be better (especially the health insurance, which is self funded)commissions are also not very competitivelots of gallaghers in the corporate office (nepotism)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I just wish you had more options for Health Insurance, and were more quick to recognize those that work hard.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“One of the best jobs in my career to date!”

</title><pros>Pros – Outstanding people in my division; interesting work; best boss I've ever had the pleasure working for; great benefits package (except leave policy)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited opportunity for career advancement; not a very flexible leave policy for working parents</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Consider revising your leave policy;  The Gallagher Family emphasized the importance of family, but doesn't demonstrate this in their time away from work policy.  A working parent is likely to have more than 2 occurances of absence per year to care for sick children.  This doesn't make us a bad employee!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Risk Management & Brokerage Services Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I had an excellent experience at Arthur Gallagher. The summer intern program was invaluable and really taught me a lot.”

</title><pros>Pros – great people, thriving environment, good work and life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – insurance is not the most exciting field</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – keep doing what you're doing</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Executive (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My experience has been fulfilling”

</title><pros>Pros – There is a large room for advancement</pros>
<cons>Cons – Inter office competition can become hostile</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Commercial Account Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to learn, dead stop for growth.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great flexibility in terms of what you want exposure to. You can work on a number of different types of insurance lines without any problem from the company structure (unlike the Aons and Marshs that only allow you to have exposure to just 1 line of business). You can really learn a lot and expand your knowledge here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you're looking to build a technical career during the launch phase (1-4 years), this place is not a good start.  Very limiting on your growth potential. The company structure is too defragmented by offices and as a result is a counter-incentive to working with each other across offices or regions, in effect limiting your growth opportunities, exposure, and recognitions to just your office.  For a global brokerage, you're still getting the same experience you could get at a localized single office brokerage, but with nationwide corporate protocols that further restrain your role.No payscale with constraining by-office budgeting will limit you from getting any sort of raise to once every 5 years. Consistently excellent performance has merited a raise for some as "early" as once every 3 years.  Only decent growth potential are for the producers. Company culture is not keen on promoting from within and believes that technical roles and expertise can always be found from hiring externally, and it does help keep employee costs down.Also very easy to get complacent and lost within the beat of your office, and I've witnessed this keep some stuck in their role for 10-20 years without really growing much at all.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Restructure the business model, office structure, budgeting structures. Find a new way to operate that will be enabling for office-to-office, region-to-region interaction. Think "virtual" teams.  Offer pay-scales or a career track to entry level employees to make them feel like they are growing somewhere. Especially with Gen Y, very likely to move after 2 years. It's hard to grow talent from bottom up and expect them to stay in the company for 20-30 years, traditional methods are not efficient anymore.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Gallagher Way is a thing of the past”

</title><pros>Pros – Most employees believe in a good work/life balanceCompetitive salaries</pros>
<cons>Cons – Benefits package lags peersRampant nepotismCorporate cowardice is commonplace</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Lead by example, stop hiring friends and family.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Executive (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Arthur Gallagher is fine however, DO NOT WORK AT BROKERS PROFESSIONALS (MEDIA, PA)”

</title><pros>Pros – Arthur Gallagher is a reputable company with a stable reputation.  Most of the company is very professional.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Arthur Gallagher must ensure that its corporate culture is reflected in all small companies it takes over.  For example, the Media, PA office is a revolving door and quite frankly, a joke.  The employees and work environment is abusive and not condusive to the mission and goals of the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Close the Media, PA office.  Cost too much money to operate and the office is a lawsuit waiting to happen.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was a gread internships, and i was able to capture some real world experience from it.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people to work with, good hours-solid 40 hours a week, supervisors give you important projects unlike many internships. Sold Company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Alot of free time which in turns leads you to be bored alot, the starting of the internship was a little slow, but things picked up.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It has been a positive experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – AJG has given me the opportunity to explore different avenues of the claims industry.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The duplication of work efforts.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst claims job I ever had!”

</title><pros>Pros – In the beginning the people that I worked with were terrific. Once a new manager took over this changed.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay, absurd work loads, unprofessional, lack of appreciation, absence of senior management input, constant projects generated by requirements of perfection, lack of respect for management team knowledge and experience</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Senior Management/Home Office should be more involved with what happens in the branch offices - take a look at the turnover and reasons for this. Be more accessible to branch office staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very positive experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexibility, and Resources available to production</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of dedicated niche teams</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Grow the formalized niche teams</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“family ran”

</title><pros>Pros – internship programcompany reputationloyalty to employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – M/A as opposed to organic growthfamily ranleadership is gained by last name rather purely by performanceglass ceiling</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – hire motivation, train talent</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Professional Organization”

</title><pros>Pros – Life work balance, opportunity for advancement, great skillset</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of communication is an issue</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They could be more collaborative when introducing new concepts, programs or directives to employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Summer Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review of Summer Internship”

</title><pros>Pros – They are very dedicated to their internship program, I was given lots of responisbilty and was allowed to participate in client visits and presentations.  Very up and coming industry, lots of room for future advancement.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes boring material, Health care is a constantly changing industry that takes constant dedication.  With the changing Health care climate there is opportunity for people to come in and tkae control of the industry.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Gallagher should continue to expand their internship program in order to find young talent.  It offers them a good way of training their interns at a reduced rate compared to a full-time employee.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I Will Post A More Extensive Review Later”

</title><pros>Pros – Shared values and strong ethical practice</pros>
<cons>Cons – Corporate to Acquisition Partner communication & Execution could be improved</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – TBD --- ---- ----- ------ -------</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Owner's incentive is to run out the clock after becoming a Merger Partner”

</title><pros>Pros – Large database of resources and education tools.Gallagher grows primarily through acquiring small businesses. The takeover of a small company is pretty transparent to the small company's employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Medical Benefits are embarrassing. There are 9,000 employees all over the nation - number of different medical plans to choose from? One. That one plan - $600 IN NETWORK deductible and 80% Coinsurance IN NETWORK after that. One employee had a baby costing $8,000 out-of-pocket.If you work for a small company that gets acquired by Gallagher, the incentive is for the owners of the small company (now employees of Gallagher) to manage a certain level of growth and profitability for 3 years until they get another payout after 36 months. It's possible for the mindset of the small business owners to change from entrepreneurial visionaries to corporate tools handing out Gallagher edicts as employee morale decreases by the month.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Mandate the newly acquired companies to train the newly acquired employees in all of Gallagher's numerous resources.Have more professional people present the Webinars. Most of them are embarrassingly bad; the speakers sound like lightweights.Make the newly acquired companies' owners stay for 5 years before a payout. 3 years is too short and it's too easy for the owners to run out the clock. With a 5-year mentality, the owners that sold out are more apt to think longer term.There is of course a benchmark for revenue growth and/or profitability for the owners to meet during their 3-year buyout contract, but make sure there are employee retention benchmarks as well. The small company I work for lost two high-level employees after 1 year and significant clients (revenue) to go with it. We just lost three more mid-level employees after 2 years. The company Gallagher bought is not even close to what they are going to end up with.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Meritocracy; good feedback from management; nimble company.  Hard work was usually recognized verbally and, situation permitting, with compensation.  Good opportunities for growth.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Could be long hours; still some growing pains</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Overall, a good experience.  Company offered some flexibility to take your career in some different directions.  Sales drive decisions but that's to be expected in a consulting group.  Very ethical group.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-31</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unfair but good place to gain experience”

</title><pros>Pros – A great place to learn working under pressure. This place will give you a lot of opportunities to work on challenging tasks. It is a great place to build experience. Think of this place as a boot camp where you can learn important working skills. Working here will give you a great answer to the interview question, "How do you handle working under pressure?"</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unfair management and very poor communication from management. It may be frustrating to work here because management seems incompetent and at times dishonest. Don't expect to stay here as a lifetime career. You need to speak up and stand up for your rights. It seems management does not value integrity.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat employees fairly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Claims Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Long hours with no light at the end of the tunnel.”

</title><pros>Pros – There are nice co-workers to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The management has exceptions that are not obtainable.  Home Office has way too many in house requirements for reports.  They have a report that they run  every Tuesday.  The management wants to be sure that the reports are perfect.  If so, they feel that they are meeting the goals that they are doing well.   In the meantime the examiners can't keep up with work that is not on the weekly report and management does not offer any solution.  It is "Fly under the raider" attitude.  Everything else can go unattended.  The client is not getting "A" service as they claim.  The attitude towards working extra hours is expected in order to keep up with extremely heavy work flow.  Told that with more work comes job security.  Employee's can't voice their concerns about not being able to service the clients according to best practices.  If you voice your concerns, you get brushed off by stating that everyone should be happy to have jobs with todays economy.  They do not meet best practices.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to the employees with concerns.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent place to work...”

</title><pros>Pros – The management made all the difference in the world. You are expected to pull your work load and get the job done, but they acknowledged your hard and made sure you were compensated. They also treated the employee's to perks for a job well done. i.e. ice cream socials, bbq cookoffs, flex hours. They also offered EXCELLENT training programs so you had the tools to do your job...</pros>
<cons>Cons – The work can get demanding and sometimes weekends are necessary. The turn over has become a problem as well.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start hiring new management since the best just left.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company out of the 70's”

</title><pros>Pros – My office is very generous with time off, however the company as a whole is not.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In my office there is no room for growth and very little training.  The benefits are horrible - our medical plan is absolutely outrageous.  The company is very disconnected as a whole in that there are so many different brokerages that do different things yet they try to make us all fit into a mold.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve employee benefits and thinka bout the policies you are putting into place.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Process Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good for starter but too much of politics”

</title><pros>Pros – 70% of the staff is beautiful girls.no dress code.rotational shift so you get a chance to experience all.pay good for overtime infact best in the market.</pros>
<cons>Cons – too much politics.beautiful girls get a advance over hardworking employee.if you can make the manager happy with girls stuffs u get promotion and trasitions within a year no matter ur talented or not.talent and hardwork doesnt pay at all but polishing butter to tl willno sick leave direct lopthey dont pay a day for 550 rs but cut that as 1 day lop.canteen suck no option available....</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – pay attention to work not beauty of girls.have a dress code for girls after all it a place to work not show off.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Systems Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not good...... No proper management”

</title><pros>Pros – I don't see any pros</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. No proper Higher Management2. No clear goal</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-16</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Human Resources (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“As the company grow u can grow”

</title><pros>Pros – Growth opportunitiesGood teamFlexible way of doing</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low sal,10 days of Earned leaves  per yr</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have automated systems</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Accounts Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Learning Curve is Always high.”

</title><pros>Pros – Best place to work, in start your career as a fresher.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low Salary & lack of Incentives.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dysfunctional Organization”

</title><pros>Pros – Well known name in insurance industry which helps to attract some potential clients but little do they know what is happening behind the scenes.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Dysfunctional & inept management group especially in the San Francisco Bay Area.Constant reorganizations and sometimes it's never communicated to you who you are reporting to.Turnover issues...valuable producers and other employees leaving to pursue better opportunities.No formal compensation program; employee pay varies greatly within same positions and management is aware of the discrepancies and does nothing to address it.Benefits program is sorely lacking, not competitive in the industry, and in particular, the Bay Area.Many employee will leave once the employment market improves.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You (Itasca) are choosing to ignore the problems and eventually it will catch up to you!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Network Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good placeto work”

</title><pros>Pros – More lesure which u never get in any other company</pros>
<cons>Cons – No much exposure to expertise in any field</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – it sucks</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Benefit Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Benefits Consultant”

</title><pros>Pros – They provided a good surrounding for young inexperienced consultants</pros>
<cons>Cons – Had to attend a lot of unecessary conference calls</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – n/a</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very sketchy”

</title><pros>Pros – decent benefits, lots of training when wanted</pros>
<cons>Cons – Infested with nepotism at all levels.  Don't plan on moving up in this company</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't bother, it strictly a top down management style</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was a love/hate relationship”

</title><pros>Pros – Was a great place to work at the local level, management was great to work with and would back you up when needed.  Certain offices went out of their way to make sure you were doing well.  Benefits like vision and dental did improve over time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If your not one of the cronies or a family member of management then don't expect to get promoted.  Corporate level management is bad at communication, nothing like a unexpected phone call to let you know your working 40 hours instead of 35 at no pay increase for the increased hours.  They expect certain things of you even if you have no idea or have not had adequate training on the matter.  Had several opportunities for other jobs but wanted to stay for loyalty to the company.  In the end if your direct management does not like you, no matter how much you do to improve or show more effort they will force you out.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Your subordinates know more than you think and are a valuable asset, treat  them right and you might not have a high turn over rate and more loyal employees not being burned out.  Be consistent, if an employee is presented with new responsibilities with no training and comes to you with many questions on procedures, but then in their review state how often you were bugged by them with questions only to have the next year state how they didn't come to you for questions is irresponsible.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good working experience with staff; Office President not as much”

</title><pros>Pros – Good opportunity for young producers, very good selection of support company wide to enhance an atmosphere of cross selling and success.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The president of our office was considerably difficult to work with, often times demeaning. Sometimes the message from the corporate office did not meld with the objectives of individual offices.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“friendly people”

</title><pros>Pros – the people are friendly, success driven culture, ability to work in many different industries, work life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – hard to be promoted, strong family bonds for promotions, not a lot of direction, no employee reviews, lack of communication</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Account Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Neutral environment, horrible benefits package, outsourcing to India.”

</title><pros>Pros – Solid agency with strong client base. Multiple offices with strong relationship with carriers. Competitive salary compared to agencies in the area.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Medical benefits and paid time off are not up to par. AJG is trending towards outsourcing work to India. Management in my office was practically non-existent.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Reward your employees with a better benefits package. Keep the work in the US rather than outsourcing to India.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Vice President -- Broker (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor use of technology, hard to find resources, fractured culture but it helps you be entrepreneurial”

</title><pros>Pros – Very entrepreneurial.  You can build your own network in and out of the company so long as you sail with the fleet.  Allows you to focus and build your expertise.  Pay is on par is not slightly above industry average.  Good mix of work and life balance given to employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Fragmented culture due to growth by acquisition.  Sometimes seems like you're working at a franchise but yet nothing is standardized - systems, procedures etc.  Benefits are terrible.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve benefits - they are abysmal and embarrassing for a company that provides benefits consulting to other entities.  Don't rave to employees about outsourcing work to India to free up their time to focus on core competencies - while at the same time you are planning/doing layoffs.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company Culture”

</title><pros>Pros – The company has a great corporate culture that enables all of it's employees to be happy with their job. The management is always willing to assist you with any needs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The only problem that I had with my experience with Gallagher is: They acquire so many companies that its hard to keep up with all the changes in the office makeup.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing what your doing. You make everyone in the company feel important and your doing it in a way that the other insurance companies are not.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Has Ups and Downs”

</title><pros>Pros – The flexibility and work/life balance varies by office but in my office it is amazing.  Tons of flexibilty in hours and you can do your job without being micromanaged.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The medical and dental benefits are not very good.  The company doesn't seem to have much organization at headquarters.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give your employees better medical  and dental benefits!  The fact that a 10,000 life company has only 1 medical plan and the dental plan does not pay 100% for preventitive is beyond me - especially since half the company is benefit consulting!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work but could be more competitive with salary and especially the benefits program.”

</title><pros>Pros – Very strong and functional managment team within regional and branch offices however, cannot access HQ in Itasca since I've had little interaction. Local management very good at recognizing and acknowledging employee contributions.  Level of knowldege and expertise of insurance industry very solid.</pros>
<cons>Cons – For a compnay of it's size in a few areas Gallagher lags in accessing and developing competitive salaries and benefit plans.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Would suggest instituting some type of company internal surveys to gauge how employees perceive the organization, i.e., to get feedback from bottom up.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>