<name>K-Bobs Steakhouse Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/K-Bobs-Steakhouse-Reviews-E571812.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Executive Chef-corporate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good steaks, excellent salad buffet,   good stocked bar..”

</title><pros>Pros – Good corporate management, owner is very passionate about good and fresh food. Old style with a new flair. Food is well worth the coast.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No many to bi honest, maybe new employees should be trained a little longer,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more seafood combinations.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>General Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Long hours hard work no appreciation.”

</title><pros>Pros – Honestly there are not too many. Free food while you are working. Other than that there is not much to say.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They say they are all about family, the fact is that they could care less about your family. When the owner of the company tells you that he does not care about your day to day opperational problems that the bottom line is all that matters then what more do I need to say. If you feel like being chewed up, spit out, and tossed in the dumpster then by all means apply.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn how to run a food service company, Run it in a consistant manner. Learn how to deal with people both the public and your staff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Waitress (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Well maintained an opererated franchice as long as not in a small town”

</title><pros>Pros – great managers when ran in a larger community</pros>
<cons>Cons – family ran an operated as well as freinds of family</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Server (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“nothing good to say about food or employer”

</title><pros>Pros – At first it was decent money but after a while of locals either not liking the food or management, or both, the business slowed down conciderably.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the management has not a clue as how to run a company, between not taking care of employees and not giving the time off you requested for important matters ever. nor checking up on customers and being rude to them. the place has a terrible reputation and for a small town that spells closing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn how to do your job properly</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>