<name>Triple R Child Care Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Triple-R-Child-Care-Reviews-E578734.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-08-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Loving environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun environment. Nice people. Wonderful job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lower pay. but all child care is low pay</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Teacher/Aid (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“They don't take care of and retain their good employees, cronyism rampant.”

</title><pros>Pros – Adequate starting wage with regular reviews and opportunity for increases.Relationships that you build with children and parents.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Fundamentally flawed management methods when dealing with staff. The manager(s) operate with a "scorched earth" approach to everything. As a very skilled and qualified (adult) childcare professional, I've never been spoken down to and made to feel like I was "in trouble" as much since I was a child in school who had to answer to a principal. The truth is that I ran my room exceptionally well and with a true sense of affection and compassion for the children while many others were simply there to punch the clock. Nobody would ever know though since the only time a manager would stop by was just to peek their head and and FIND something to take an issue with and be gone the next minute.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Realize that the people in those classrooms working with the children are the ones doing the work that IS the actual work of your business. Maybe even get involved with that side of the operation every once in a while if for no other reason than to know who your good people are. A happy employee is a good employee. Treat the ones you hire with the respect and dignity that you show to your 10 year plus employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>