<name>HP GeBOC (Global e-Business Operations Center) Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/HP-GeBOC-Global-e-Business-Operations-Center-Reviews-E588182.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Training Lead (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very transparent and employee friendly company”

</title><pros>Pros – I have worked for so many companies but HP really stands out for its transparent way of working and "open door policy". I have great regards for HP as the Management makes all efforts to truely live up to the company values. Great learning exposure and oppurtunities for people for internal mobility (IJP's). This is a great company for begginners as well as for people who want to retire in the same company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not a very good pay master.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Your the best!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Smart Quote Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's a good place to start your career”

</title><pros>Pros – Young and energetic employees, dynamic environment with lots of changes and opportunities. If you show ambition and put in some hard work you can get ahead pretty fast.Also, the work environment is relaxed, mangers are flexible with regards to taking time off (there is no need to give advance notice, if you let your manager know one or two days ahead is enough).Another pro is the possibility of working from home a few days a month up to one or two days a week depending on the team you're working in.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Because it's a young environment and some of the managers get promoted form within the company you might get a young and inexperienced manger who appraises based on personal relations or tries to steer you in the direction they want you to go instead of trying to help you find your own way.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get more involved with the operations, with the people that do the actual work and ask for their feedback and opinions. Also, ask them for feedback on their manager (the open doors policy is there, but most of the employees wont come to you by their own. You need to go ask them).And take action after you've got the feedback</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Lifecycle Marketing Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“HP GeBoC: A good place to work at but sometimes not challenging enough”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexibility to choose role and plan your workGreat work-life balanceOpen systems and communication</pros>
<cons>Cons – The role can become too operational sometimesHP's growth might affect future hikes in individual salaryTry to give challenging work to each individual</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You should have a 360 degree feedback system where reportee's feedback actually affects the reporting manager's annual rating. Manager can play favourite sometimes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ok”

</title><pros>Pros – flexible hours, working from home</pros>
<cons>Cons – no motivation, no salary raise</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Lifecycle Marketing Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice experience, but can be better”

</title><pros>Pros – Ability to be a part of exciting projects, if you are willing to stretch.True flexi-timings. Ability to take vacation as needed.Most people are polite and helpful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Review process can be more fair.Manager has disproportionate influence on ratings and can play favouritesExcessive culture of time-pass. Many people do not work hard enough and take advantage of the fair culture of the company</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please execute strategies faster. The re-org took too long to happen and people were paralyzed for a good 6 months</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Smart Quote Specialist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Smart Quote Specialist”

</title><pros>Pros – Stable, pretty well paid, somewhat laid back job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not creative or challenging, unfair management, extremely bureaucratic company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – In my team's case, there were some serious HR situations. Almost half the team left because of the somehow abusive management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>