<name>R House Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/R-House-Reviews-E593415.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-31</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>CCW Mentor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great kids, horrible management. Prepare to be treated just like the residents.”

</title><pros>Pros – The kids. Only reason. Like someone else stated, you CAN make a difference. Sure they will push, and try you, and stress you out, but any job working with underprivileged or at risk youth will wield the same.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The "upper management". The directors, site managers, lack of consistency when coming down the chain of command. Being treated like, and talked to like we were also in the program. Belittling. Hard overworked with inadequate pay and no real breaks at work. Hardly any backup or support when needed. Constant overturn of employees. Employees being fired for "breaking rules" that were constantly changing or being altered to fit current moods. Have met a couple new employees (summer 2013) who said that because of a complete overhaul of Directors and people running the organization that to them it seemed to be getting better. When talking to old employees, they were still leaving, still unhappy.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If there is some at the end of the year - Update Policy and Procedure. Form clear lines for children and staff and stick with it. Abide by those policies and don't alter them or leave them open for interpretation so they can be used against others at will. I'm not even an employee who was fired or got written up but I still saw it happening. Talk to your employees. Part of what lost you all the old good ones was lack of communication during a critical period with lots of changes. Also.. don't send your bulldog to yell at employees at 6 o'clock in the morning. Yelling at staff is disrespectful.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>CCW Mentor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You can make a difference in a kids life, but you must endure the company”

</title><pros>Pros – As a mentor for R House you can actually make a difference in a kids life.  4 days work, 3 days off.  Team atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay is not good.  R House does not treat their employees well.  There is little job security.  They are always hiring and likewise always firing.  Managment, was at times, very unprofessional and would treat their employees as residents instead of employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat your employees with respect.  Let them know the rules so they don't have to worry about getting fired.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Site Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Dysfunctional leadership - beware!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great mission, the kids can be wonderful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Zero communication, the ED does not run the organization, the HR director does. I am not a disgruntled  former employee, but just attempting to be honest. The leadership here is in need of an overhaul. People have stuck around too long and the organization does not appear to be sustainable. Folks need to retire, move on and make room for some creative leaders.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – See above</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>