<name>Embitel Technologies Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Embitel-Technologies-Reviews-E595700.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-05-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its a harmony of work-personal life”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Salary, Employee friendly Management, Will value your work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing in general, but all the above mentioned will depend up on the team and manager you are in to.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Please avoid this ...”

</title><pros>Pros – -Short term u get hike</pros>
<cons>Cons – -No projects-Short Sightedness of management-No job security (as soon as requirement ends they fire)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – -Look for long term image of company and not short term ..-Industry is made of people only so don't spoil companies image by biased policies.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great work environment and amazing learning experience”

</title><pros>Pros – It is one of the fastest growing company.Great work culture and environment.Be your own lead</pros>
<cons>Cons – Need to expand more aggressively and increase visibility.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-08</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Technical lead”

</title><pros>Pros – work culture and values, passionate talent pool, learning opportunities (depends), compensation in par with industry standards(for experienced professionals)</pros>
<cons>Cons – learning opportunities depend on new projects since it is a small organization</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-14</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Aspiring Engineers Never join this company”

</title><pros>Pros – Even I cant think of anything like others in the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1. They treat you well when you want to join.2. They never give a written confirmation all rules are told by mouth.3. Company has no set of rules/policy.4 . No matter how color-ful is the offer, never join this company.5. Mails are never answered in a written format.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Change</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok, not the better place to wrok”

</title><pros>Pros – policies will change person to person and time to time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not feeling comfortable working with them</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be a company and maintain professionalism.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>4</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This is body shopping company, where the company consider the employee as use and throw”

</title><pros>Pros – Till now we are getting salary on time till we have job with them</pros>
<cons>Cons – I was associated with Embitel more than 2 years. I felt the company lack ethics in dealing the employees during harder time. Company recruited highly skilled professional from big companies by offering falls commitments. Recently company sent termination letter to all the employees at the client site with a notice period(dated end of project date at client site).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – As a service based company we should value to employees since we are the key person who bring revenue for the company. Don't make employees use and throw. The higher management should make amend policy where the employee can take up issue with higher management rather than keeping a single manager as a contact point.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Embitel Technologies (I) Bangalore”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Work Life Balance in here</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not a best place for entry level candidates</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>