<name>E*TRADE Financial Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/E-TRADE-Financial-Reviews-E6005.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Operations Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Has potential to be better”

</title><pros>Pros – the company's focus on innovation and technology are commendable.</pros>
<cons>Cons – opportunities for moving up with in the company are obscure/non-existent. could improve in employee work life balance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – investing in  your employees current success at Etrade should be enhanced by offering on going training workshops and engagement between management and employee.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Financial Service Rep”

</title><pros>Pros – Everthing abou them is great</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing that I have noticed</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Had the BEST co-workers but the WORST management!”

</title><pros>Pros – E*TRADE was a wonderful place to work because of the people that you get to work with each day. Some of the best in the business and you can learn a lot in the short time you will likely stay.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management is the worst as they have no idea what really goes on day to day to keep the customers happy. They have the worst methods of internal promotion and some of the highest turnover I have ever seen because almost every job there is a dead end.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Less management (upper and senior) and more internal promotion.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Invaluable experience below market pay”

</title><pros>Pros – There are many learning opportunities and you have the ability to obtain various securities licenses.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As an analyst, pay is below market rates.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Compensate employees better to retain talent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Back Office Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Challenging and rewarding, even during stressful time”

</title><pros>Pros – Management, at the time, my teammates were the BEST, and support for employees was great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Went thru 4 mergers in less than 7 years.  Having to lay off great people was emotional and then had to hire staff within 3 to 4 months.  Very senior management was unapproachable and not receptive to suggestions from any level beneath them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Look at the cons and work on them in the future.  Some associates, NOT ON YOUR LEVEL, have ideas that could work.  Try being an UNDERCOVER BOSS and sit on the jobs that you are making decisions on WITHOUT truly knowing the process.  You might learn a lot....</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-05</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E*TRADE promotes a great team atmosphere!”

</title><pros>Pros – Team atmosphere, OT opportunities, Growth potential, CEO is focused on Customer Service first.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some areas of the processing systems seem more difficult to our clients than it should be.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to promote growth in careers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-25</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of opportunity”

</title><pros>Pros – Room to move up and to other locations</pros>
<cons>Cons – Great for entry level candidates</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Learned a lot, but hated working here”

</title><pros>Pros – Got licensed, learned a lot about numerous financial instruments and how they function.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Training for 7/63 was great, but after that they just kinda throw you in the deep end on the phones. Really would have benefited from some on the job training, but even their 'incubator' wasn't really training. Maybe our group of hires was too big for them to properly train everyone on systems.   This job is basically a phone sales position. So much stress is put on getting leads for their financial consultants. Etrade's platforms (for their customers) are so easy to use, which meant someone only called in when something was wrong, or the customers were not smart enough to figure out how to navigate a website. This caused for very stressful/uncomfortable conversations. One of the happiest days of my life was the day I quit working here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a terribly bad place to work at”

</title><pros>Pros – They have streamlined internal standards and processes for application software development.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Extremely high workload; Limited opportunities if you'd like to stay abreast on the latest tools. Poor work-life balance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent Customer Service Job”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent benefits, pay, and training.  At 5:00, you can leave and forget about your job (in a good way).</pros>
<cons>Cons – Aside from "licensed stockbroker" sounding important, just another customer service job in a call center.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I realize a call center job is a call center job, but there's no reason why management couldn't treat it like more than that.  In general, FSRs are relatively well educated, and management could treat them more like professionals than like mere phone jockeys.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Financial Services Rep”

</title><pros>Pros – Good suite of products and services for entry and mid level investors.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Back office operations completes work on their own timeline with no communications.  No coaching from management - only directives.  Senior Leadership not approachable.  No clear direction for the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Develop a strategic direction for the company, then develop a matching pay plan and coach your way to success.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst People Ever!”

</title><pros>Pros – You can steal from people (if you are into that) Well, really you are forced into it, so if you work CSR for etrade you are going to be lying to customers frequently.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You are forced to steal from people. If you speak fluent english you are going to have a hard time finding someone to talk with or making friends.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop stealing from people. You are all crooks and thieves! Give some help when employees ask for it! Stop focusing on stealing from customers and focus on customer service!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“IF YOU GET HIRED AS AN ASSOCIATE FSR, PASS YOUR EXAMS AND GET OUT AS SOON AS YOU CAN!”

</title><pros>Pros – Licensing. Period. It's "free", and they pay you while you are in training. As the title says, get hired as an Associate FSR. It's great coming out of college, or wanting to start a career in finance. START being the keyword.Paul Idzik is great! Structure, streamline, may trickle down. But I doubt it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you have morals, do not attempt to work there. If you are creative and know how to motivate, do not fill out an application. If you have potential to be great, you will intimidate your superiors and your Life @ E*TRADE will become a living hell. And if you aren't broken, imagine some place worse than hell.HR is a joke.FSRs and Sr. FSRs are licensed stockbrokers and all we do is sit there and pray that we can meet our quota each week by bringing in money for lazy Financial Consultants who don't do anything but wait for us to put in a lead. We do 75% of the selling and don't get any compensation for it. Bring in 20+ million a quarter and hand the phone off to an un-enthused FC--absolutely no compensation.FSRs and Sr. FSRs who have been working there for 2 years or less know more than managers and senior managers who have been working there for at least decade or more. It does not mix to be a pleasant experience.It's sad when you are told that you have to stifle your innovation and knowledge so not to outshine your aloof and incompetent current manager and future manager to keep your job and to climb the political career ladder at E*TRADE because the dumber you are the more valuable you are to management. Middle management from Senior Managers to Directors aren't creative enough nor know what the FSRs and Sr. FSRs actually go through in order to make processes better. Customer Service Senior Managers do not value the FSRs nor Sr. FSRs. We stayed tethered to a phone and computer screen for 8,10-15 hours a day (sometimes more because of understaffing) but they are quick to forget they made us STOCK BROKERS. They promote who they control instead of promoting people who can actually contribute to our new CEOs vision.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – When you see talent, don't stifle it and don't discourage it, and definitely don't steal it. Bolster it. Have a backbone. Be that one to step up and show upper level management who you've heard about or who you have on your team. Realize that you have people who hold titles lower than yours who are studying competitors in school and know how to implement processes for cheaper.For Senior Management in LOBs other than CS: Know that you are dealing with people who are a decade or more younger than you and can learn what you require in that internal job posting quicker than you could yourself and more quickly than you can find an external hire, if given the opportunity because they want the chance. Don't brush them to the side.Appreciate your minions, they can contribute and can bring your stock options from being underwater.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Analyst”

</title><pros>Pros – Progressive. They are always looking forward and into the future with their products. They are highly competitive in the market.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Tons of red tape  and management issues. It's hard to move up or cross train. Many people stay in the same position for years.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value you employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Place to get started”

</title><pros>Pros – This is a great place to get your 7 and 63, heck even more. paid training for 7 & 63 can't be beat. Plenty of overtime if you need extra cash. Overall i learned so much coming out of college and there aren't many opportunities in this area of finance in Atlanta at the moment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation for lead generation can be boosted.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good product company to work in”

</title><pros>Pros – Process drivenTechnologically in the forefrontWork life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – Education and rich experience is sometimes underweighedNot sure why some folks not with rich experience and education are in the higher level</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Looking for job at E*trade?”

</title><pros>Pros – The company uses cutting edge and open source technologies.Company provides good work environment and focus on framework based development approach to improve productivity.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company growth does not seem to be impressive for some time and seems to be in the process of changing that by reorganizing and focusing again.Not sure how long it would take to get back into high growth mode.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unlimited comp for sales on the FC side”

</title><pros>Pros – Unlimited comp for sales on the FC side I love it it makes me very motivated to work hard.I am happy my manager gives me the space to sell to the right clients. The clients that want and need advice. Many need advice but just do not want it so you need to sift thru to find someone that "gets" that putting all their money in a 12 cent gold mining stock will most likely not help them reach retirement with a good size nest egg.Given 200mm book to work with huge opportunity but can hurt you.A get the job done culture!</pros>
<cons>Cons – *Operations and TOA are way understaffed should have 30-50 people full time. E*TRADE could bring in an additional 10-25% or more in assets and retention if they refined this area in particular.* There should be a positive small revenue share on your practice/book that exceeds threshold or* Threshold feels more like a "steal take"*UMA needs a bond manager yesterday.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Look at how other discounters execute operations and TOA then copy what they do well.I am not sure is Paul is wanting to grow us or sell us? I prefer grow there is an enormous opportunity to grab more market share from TD and Schwab.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Etrade death”

</title><pros>Pros – Mirror test hire meaning if you can fog a mirror with your breath you're hired from what I observe of uneducated simple people in Sandy, UT</pros>
<cons>Cons – Truly mean and manipulative staff who leave you to customers with limited training. After working with larger brokerages it is mesmerizing to see how gullible management is to the slightest concerns. Run... Don't walk from this seeming opportunity.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get some life experience.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stuck behind the pack”

</title><pros>Pros – Work culture is generally pretty laid back - very dependant on your branch manager.There is a lot of "low hanging fruit" b/c ETRADE customers are not accustomed to having a FC, if you position yourself properly you can gain a lot of credibility with clients.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Equivalent to horse and buggy in terms of investment and sales capability - lack fixed income options in UMA, no to hardly any I shares, not able to speak to ETF's to client's.  Your ability to talk to clients is limited to as if you have no licenses or experience with investments.  Company does not value experience, accredations or investment knowledge of FC's.While the comp plan is supposedly "open ended", your threshold is subject to where your branch is located, with better locations having to produce WAY more.  Unfortunately they don't do the same distinguishment with base salary, so your base is the same no matter what location you are in... still can't figure this out, but it makes meeting your day to day bills very difficult if you live in a good location.  Also you are paid out a full 2 months after the end of the quarter making cash flow managment very difficult.  If you miss a bonus you won't be paid for a full 6 months, base is not enough to support you through this time.No addtional benefits to speak of - 2.5% match on 401(k) employee contribution of 5%, NO stock purchase plan (despite being one of the largest ESPP providers), very little to no reimbursement of educational or accrediations, no reason to stay long term leading to high levels of attrition.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Senior Management that was all recently replaced - what are you doing?  Communicate with us, give us some hope, inspire us, right now it's so silent it makes us wonder what in the world is going on.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Product Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Young and dynamic company with endless opportunities for the brave and ambitious”

</title><pros>Pros – Many opportunites to grow whithin. One can start at the bottom and with hard work and the right attitude can easily move up to more rewarding positions.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation could be better. This industry requires talented people to innovate and stay ahead of the curve. Pay seems lower compared to other companies</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the culture as it is and design fairer compensation package throughout the organization. Identify key personnel that keeps the business running and the compensate them based on merit.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Company but needs improvement in several areas”

</title><pros>Pros – Hardworking staff, dedicated workforce, Get it done attitude among employees is the backbone of E*TRADE's technology domain. The business and technology teams work hand in hand to deliver award winning products</pros>
<cons>Cons – No work/life balance in this company. Promotions and raises are tough to come by regardless the amount of quality time and effort you put in your job or deliver outstanding results.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work towards employee retention and creating a better work environment for your employees. Acknowledge the hard work and dedication of your employees by appropriately compensating them for their hard work and result oriented work</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Software Engineer”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly environment, lots of personal time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not too much room for career development</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>New Accounts Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Employer”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Culture, Was able to advance but it took a year and a half</pros>
<cons>Cons – uncertain future, new management team</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Network Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A pretty good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Pays decent, mostly flexible, an overall pretty good place to work. Not necessarily a lifetime opportunity, but definitely a great place to lead to better opportunities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is full of real 'jerk' type of personalities. They almost seem to reward the 'barker screamer' type over actual competence. Which leads to many departments being run by barking idiots over actual competent people. If you have any real talent, most likely, you won't stay here long-term. A good place as a launching pad for talented people, then take your talents to a better place.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I had an amazing tenure at E*TRADE. Lots of opportunities to work with amazing people and projects.”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible work schedule, and depending on your team, the opportunity to work on good, visible projects.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Constantly changing. They had more than 6 CEO's and numerous changes in their "vision" and management. If you can't weather the storm and you're not aligned with the right people, your screwed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get your act together. E*TRADE has the roots to make a great company but the revolving door of CEO's and upper management are the company's own enemy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“its a bumpy ride”

</title><pros>Pros – Good environment, good work life balance, good locations, good benefits... All in all its a good place to stay for a small duration</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is no vision and no planning... things keep changing every now and then and keep loosing focus</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-27</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not so extraordinary!”

</title><pros>Pros – 1) Good place to pick up your security licenses and learn about the stock market, financial services, and obtain some customer service call center experience.2) Promotions are based on the buddy system rather than skills and abilities. Backstabbing is encouraged and rewarded, so if you are good at kissing up to management, good at beating down your coworkers and covering your backside, this is a great to work!</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1) Company too cheap to hire enough employees to cover the daily call volume and too cheap to provide smooth operating computer systems for optimum job performance.2) Customer Service employees are micro-managed to the max through a Command Center, customer service management uses negative reinforcement rather than positive reinforcement to motivate employees resulting in low morale and high turnover.3) Most feedback from customer service managers is "not provided" in a timely manner resulting in minor problems/infractions becoming more numerous and more serious than they need to be.4) Customer service work procedures and expectations are constantly changing or flip-flopping back and forth without notice or warning ... what was okay yesterday, may not be okay today, but could be okay again to tomorrow (very confusing & contradictory).5) New employees and/or employees filling new positions are not supported or provided with sufficient customer service training to get their jobs done without a lot of hand holding.6) Objective employee feedback and constructive criticism regarding work processes and/or management style is frowned upon. Honesty and being outspoken is not a plus or conducive  to job security.7) Employees who fail to find a place in the buddy system are setup for failure and termination.8) Older employees on the higher end of the pay scale with mucho vacation days are driven off or put out to pasture, while younger employees with less pay, less vacation days, and less experience are retained.9) Appears to be a lot of age biasness and religious biasness in the hiring process, promotion process and in employee retention process.10) Company struggling to find and hold on to a stable CEO and survive their subprime problems. Not a stable work environment for anyone looking for fair treatment and job security.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 1) Take some courses in management and human relations.2) Start treating your employees with the dignity and the respect they deserve.3) Stop harboring ill-will over all the little things (keep your egos in check) and provide your employees with more positive feedback and a well deserved pat on the back.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Leader (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An honest assessment of E*TRADE...”

</title><pros>Pros – Work/life balance, some of the products</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay, ESPP (or lack thereof), the people (can you say "C"-team?), management (old regime that is), culture, environment</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Although most of the culprits have seemingly been flushed out, there are a few very, very unqualified Director's and VP's. Plus, too many good people have been lost lately because the ineffective placed blame at the bottom.. until it trickled back up that is. Kudos to the new CEO for recognizing...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unskilled, uncaring management”

</title><pros>Pros – No micro-management in some locations...a problem in others</pros>
<cons>Cons – Uncaring, unskilled, self serving management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Begin thinking of employees as other than a necessary evil</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Staff Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was a great experience working in Financial domain”

</title><pros>Pros – It was good to learn and have working in Financial domain</pros>
<cons>Cons – Constant changing of management has lost so many talented resources</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to gain experience and knowledge</pros>
<cons>Cons – No work/life balance, Not much room for growth depending on the department, classic Corporate America,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need more flexibility for employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior IT Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall good, but not the greatest”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work life balance and overall flexible hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of good management; lack of direction</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get back on track;  have a solid business strategy</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was a circus.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people with good intentions and resilience in the face of futility.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Disorganized, backward project development process and poorly managed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Support your personnel, don't bully them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall a good company to learn about financial service industry”

</title><pros>Pros – People are smart, supportive and dedicated to their work; culture, always try to excel, innovate and fast paced; in both banking and brokerage business, and not too big/bureaucratic</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too many upper management turnarounds in recent years</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Figure out a strategy and find the right people and stick with them</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to learn about the financial services/brokerage business”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay you to get your Series 7 and Series 63 license, benefits are very good, starting pay is decent.  Learn a good deal about the financial world in a short amount of time, very applicable if you move to another financial job. All my managers but one were great people to work with, and always there to help. You get a 10% pay increase for working any hours past 5 pm, and any time on the weekends.  Business casual dress.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You are monitored on everything you do, from taking exactly a 15 min break, to "unscheduled" bathroom breaks.  You phone and computer are tied together and you must "code" you phone to what you are doing, so they now what you are doing all the time.  Job can get very monotonous and repetitive.  Can be easy to get burnt out.  E*trade is open 24/7, so you if you get stuck on the night shift, it can be a while before you get back to regular hours.  You have to try to get "leads" for the company (7-10 a week) and you don't get any additional pay for going the extra mile and getting them.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Ease up on the 24/7 monitoring,  would be nice to get a little compensation for leads.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-14</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Mean, Rude, Arrogant and Obnoxious Culture”

</title><pros>Pros – Salary and benefits aren't bad. The staff is great! The company seems to be getting its act together from a profitability point of view.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most managers from director on up to senior management are some of the meanest people I have worked with anywhere. Extreme micro-management combined with arrogant, unappreciative managers has lead to low morale and some turnover. In spite of decent salaries, the raises are quite terrible. Senior management does not seem to have any vision for the future which makes for further complacency.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It's quite clear that management has given up. There is no vision and no innovation. Instead of pretending that the company has a future, just admit that the company is just doing enough to sell.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Operations Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Operations analyst”

</title><pros>Pros – National corp discounts, relaxed dress code, work from home, approves expense reports quickly, out of the office outings were great. Very flexible on taking vacations during the year.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management does not listen, no advancement, long hours, HR dept is caught in between. Addressed internal issues to HR and they finally address them after 6 months...that's way too long! I was promised a review after 60 days and it didn't take place until I pushed it and by that time to was 6 months.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees concerns...more people would stick around</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Credit Administration (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E*trade is good or bad.. it all depends who you worked for in the company”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible work hours but not the same for all employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salary and no room for growth even if you work there for years and your responsibilities increase they refuse to pay you as you deserve to.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You need to consider all employees and not only the brown noses. in the credit administration department it's noticed that in order to grow you have to be part of the click and if you are not or have had differences with one of the "star" managers you can kiss goodbye to growth.. promotion, good bonuses, and raises. Management in that department needs to be reviewed.  Just my thought....</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of changes”

</title><pros>Pros – Good pay and benefits, work and life balance is fantastic.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No loyalty to employees, they will use and lose you. Company politics drive or stifle programs depending on who your buddies are.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You must communicate to your teams, make them feel valued.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Culture, executive team made work life hard”

</title><pros>Pros – Hard working, proud employees. Underdog mentality led to trying to achieve a greater good for the company. Benefits were competitive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Executive team turnover. Bad balance sheet management effected everybody. Young sales organization did not have the resources or training to effectively manage sales force.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Operations Specialist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great culture and work life balance”

</title><pros>Pros – Laid back and low pressure environment. Management very accommodating of adjusting work schedules and time off. Adjustable work schedules as long as you put in 8 hours and get work done. Pay is OK taking into consideration nature of work. Management really looks out for employees. Co-workers were all very friendly and approachable. Collegial work atmosphere among different departments.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work can be routine and unexciting. Layoffs can be rampant especially in Operations. Can get stuck in mediocre position for long time with little pay increases and not much advancement opportunities due to business climates. Low turnover and staff cutbacks which reduces growth opportunities.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Principal Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stable company? No more”

</title><pros>Pros – - Good work/life balance- Friendly colleages</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Management generally  lacks  management skills, fail to inspire employees.  Middle managers have not changed for 10 years so no opportunities for other to advance.- Good people finally start leaving after recent massive layoff.  Moral has been low for a long time.- Too much processes</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value human asset. Don't view them as disposable resources.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Run from this place. The culture will eat your soul.”

</title><pros>Pros – OK benefits, nothing special. Cafeteria in building. Nice location in midtown. Company sounds cool on a resume.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Never experienced such a hostile work environment in all of my career.  Culture of every man for himself and zero accountability. Peter Principle in full effect here. Majority of employees find themselves in the middle of the "blame game", having to constantly defend themselves from verbally abusive coworkers.  Some of these known repeat offenders are completely out of control. HR mentality seems to encourage this behavior. People with real skill and talent will never be rewarded at this company.  Morale is low, heads are down, and people avoid eye contact. Stress is high, tension is thick, and good people jump ship at the first opportunity.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Longevity does not equate to capability. The whole of the executive suite is a nightmare to deal with- from the laughably incompetent secretaries to the disconnected executives who clearly only care about their paychecks. This trickle down effect sets the tone for the rest of the office, and is unfortunately making the company a very unpleasant place to work.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“it's ok overall in all the area.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people with the ok pay.</pros>
<cons>Cons – for the management keep changing</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“What a Joke, avoid this company at all costs!”

</title><pros>Pros – decent pay and benefits for the jobvacation starts to accrue from the first day</pros>
<cons>Cons – everything about the jobyou're not a broker you are a customer service repyou will never work for a more micromanaged company in your life, guaranteed!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – what management?</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-06</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E*Trade Manila call center”

</title><pros>Pros – strong emphasis on technology, latest trading technologies, advanced trading platform, global trading.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of accountability and disconnectedness of operations in Manilla. Inability to contact operations directly to jointly resolve escalated problems. Strong emphasis on cost savings through brokers in Manilla who frequently misunderstand words in English. Clients only get to speak with Americans once they become frustrated with Manilla reps.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat employees with more respect. Randomly demanding mandatory overtime on weekends or other inconvenient times puts demands on employees that are worth more than just being paid overtime pay. Trying to motivate employees to do more work for free by calling work a "game" insults employee intelligence as employees are there to make a living and do not work to play games. More incentives are needed for additional work requirements as this is not a cost savings strategy.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Administrator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is a "hot mess" right now - avoid.”

</title><pros>Pros – Reasonable hours, lack of any deadlines.  New CEO is at least trying to break through the walls that protect those who refuse to embrace change and prevent innovation.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Entire senior management group has left (note this could be seen as a pro, but  it remains to be seen.)  Remaining managers have dug in like the battle of the Somme.  Very little chance to grow or learn new technologies.  Most good employees have left and those that remain are shell-shocked.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep on pushing change.  It may have to go all the way to the lowest levels of management before the job is done.  Bring in new blood at all levels of management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-24</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Staff Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Since I've started things have gone down hill.  First there were few development projects.  Now there are hardly any,”

</title><pros>Pros – -nice team members to work with-good compensation</pros>
<cons>Cons – -no flexible work hours-no work from home-cube walls are short-director and VP are inconsiderate-no good projects are coming-I am not being used to my full potential</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Motivate your employees to want to be here by giving interesting projects and flexible work hours.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent Place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Benefits, Great People, Decent Compensation</pros>
<cons>Cons – Technology side of the organization is declining</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Senior developer”

</title><pros>Pros – Good work /life balance, decent salaries and bonus, good team and nice place to work.Latest technologies to learn and grow.</pros>
<cons>Cons – sometimes requires 24/7 support.no more work from home allowed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please improve perfomance review system.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Broker/Customer Service (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You need the right position”

</title><pros>Pros – There are some advancement opportunities.  The pay is competitive but will likely be on the lower than average range.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you're stuck in the wrong position (customer service), you will hate life.  If that's you, apply to any/all openings you qualify for and hope that some hiring manager saves you.  Otherwise, it'll wreck your psyche.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Ease up on the csr.  The job is hell and you're not exactly paying a premium to attract the best talent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great learning experience to help the next company”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management has everyone a bit confused.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – People really do want to exceed here. You need to let them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“senior software engineer”

</title><pros>Pros – Goood balance of work and personal life.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very bad compensation. 20% below market average.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A company in turmoil”

</title><pros>Pros – Salary is competitive, good benefits package</pros>
<cons>Cons – With the new CEO, the company is in a huge state of flux.  Multiple top level executives were given their walking papers and serious reorg is in the works.  They are still digging themselves out of a huge sinkhole due to the loan crisis and are expected to cut 100 million dollars in expenses this year.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – GET IT TOGETHER or SELL</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Relationship Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Satisfied employee but company is not growing”

</title><pros>Pros – rewards top producing employees, lots of time off for employees been there for 5+ years</pros>
<cons>Cons – limited growth potential for someone with an MBA who is not willing to move</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to start...”

</title><pros>Pros – Very flexible and don't expect muchWilling to train and educate</pros>
<cons>Cons – No upward mobilityVery top heavy</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you paid a bit more you'd attract better talent</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good first job”

</title><pros>Pros – Etrade will train you to get your Series 7 brokers license. If you are not opposed to moving around there is some ooportunity for advancement. The company is small and earning potential is limited. It is good company to get some experience and go somewhere else to use it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No real up earning potential because of company size and corporate structure. Company is top heavy with management and is not taken seriously by serious investors. You always get the feeling the company is about to sold or is on the market for a buyer.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make up you mind what you want to be, either an investment firm providing solid investment advice or a cheap gimmicky discount broker.</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Operations Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A review of ETade Financial Corporation”

</title><pros>Pros – Its a great enviornment to work in. Finance company with a internet attitude. Started as a temp and quickly became a permanent employee.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company is not making it marks. It seems as if everyday someone else has been let go.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Needs the right people to make this place right”

</title><pros>Pros – can't find any pros here</pros>
<cons>Cons – Advancement only is you know someone</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Mid management is clueless</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-17</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Branch Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E*TRADE Financial”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Culture.  New CEO.  Great Brand.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Cleaning up the bank side balance sheet</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Too much Politics”

</title><pros>Pros – Can get to know about Finance - Stocks, Trading</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible Asian work culture, politics, stressful work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Managers need management skill as well as technical skill.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Relationship Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Relationship Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to get some experience and then move on. People are generally nice to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Systems systems systems. For a company that prides itself on technology ETrade has more system issues than any company I've ever seen. Embarassing plain and simple.Some managers are severly unqualified and lack graduate degrees. Promotions are based on friendship and not merit in many departments. Professionalism is not exactly the strong suit.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get a clue</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Staff Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company in maintainence mode”

</title><pros>Pros – - Relaxed work environment- Good work life balance- No hectic schedules</pros>
<cons>Cons – - No new products- Maintenance of  existing products- Least recognition for good work done- Benefits are ok- Green Card processing is very slow and bad (nothing more can be expected since the company is in cost cutting mode)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - New products and new idea should be brought in.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Get a start here, but don't get too comfortable.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good place for a young person starting out in the securities industry to get licensed and learn a few things. They pay for your licensing. You don't really have to take your work home with you.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low pay. It's a call center. Low employee morale. Every second of your day is micromanaged. Rude customers.  Promotions are actually just lateral moves to other departments doing the same thing.  Company touts promoting from within but sought after positions are filled outside.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – De-emphasize the "CE" requirement. Many excellent reps do not receive the recognition they should because they choose to not abuse the referral system like other reps.  Being able to "put on over" on management with inflated referral leads shouldn't be rewarded. Top referral performers are the least likely to allow others to observe their habits for a reason.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Experience in short-term but dead end road”

</title><pros>Pros – Makes it easy to get acclimated with the market  and a range of investments. Benefits are great. Good place to get a series 7 as they have  a good training program but most moves within the company after that are lateral.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very micro managed. Because of this, it is difficult to create relationships within the workplace. Most employees show up and leave with very little interaction. It is luck of the draw to get off work and most people end up taking PTO days in the middle of the week because Mondays and Fridays are the busiest days. New hires typically are stuck on an off hour shift that may include nights and weekends.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep a CEO longer than 6 months that can implement a strategy to be more successful.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Corporate Services is a short-term job”

</title><pros>Pros – Fine place to spend 3-4 years but not a place for a long-term career.  Good experience in corporate services to take to another company.  Great experience in equity compensation but usually you must move away from Atlanta to find another job in the equity comp field.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management won't developing employees, management always hires from the outside, raises are not regular but come every 3-4 years.  Client services is overworked, client management is underworked and overpaid, and product management is underappreciated which results in incredibly high turnover.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop the regular cycle of building up and pulling back.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Information Technology Worker (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a bad place to work if you're in the IT department”

</title><pros>Pros – Good life work balance; sane work hours and the company management does a nice job of providing team-building events and fosters an overall sense of good spirit.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Working with other teams can be difficult; not the most challenging job I've had in my career.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Break through some of the silos and get teams to communicate and work together more cooperatively.  Challenge the status quo and don't just settle for "business as usual."</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Stock Broker (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Benets but Horrible Job”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits and work life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – Call center environment, everyone hates their job.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make an effort to improve the work environment and employee morale. Please telling employees how poorly the company is doing to scare them into working harder.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Everyone is an island, little opportunity to grow”

</title><pros>Pros – They hand out titles like lollipops and E*TRADE looks good on a resume.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They hook you in the position with a higher than normal salary and promises of bonsuses, raises and promotions. Opinion throughout the company is that these are never delivered on. Good jobs go to outside hires. Very poorly managed from senior managers on up. Extreme micro management. Policies within the company don't communicate to each other.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Back off. Let your employees do what they were hired for without constant check ins.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Everyone is an island, little opportunity to grow”

</title><pros>Pros – They hand out titles like lollipops and E*TRADE looks good on a resume.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They hook you in the position with a higher than normal salary and promises of bonsuses, raises and promotions. Opinion throughout the company is that these are never delivered on. Good jobs go to outside hires. Very poorly managed from senior managers on up. Extreme micro management. Policies within the company don't communicate to each other.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Back off. Let your employees do what they were hired for without constant check ins.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-31</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Program Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Senior program manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Good tech team to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor management team, not much career growth</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not place to build your career”

</title><pros>Pros – Work colleagues keep day fun</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management makes salaries on performance of reps. Since products are sub par management continues to squeeze blood from stones which makes job difficult</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Call Center Environment--Micromanagement to the Extreme”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits are decent. You get paid time and a half for overtime because everyone except managers are hourly. It's a good place to get licensed and start out, but not a good place for a career.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Wow, where do I start? Very hard to get time off. Micromangement at its finest. Pay is not great for the industry. There is not much upward movement--only lateral movement. They say there are tons of ways you can go but there's not, just different teams within customer service and a call center.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Financial Services Representative”

</title><pros>Pros – Physical location is close to the freeway. The doors are open when you get to work.  Most of the managers could fog up a mirror.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In four years time, my hourly pay has increased about 7%.  My health insurance costs for identical coverage has increased by over 36%! I actually take home less now than when I started because Etrade now takes so much more out of my check for health insurance. At the same time the fomer CEO Steve Frieburg saw his base pay go form 1 million to over 3 million the second year.  The managers were all managers with companies that Etrade bougtht before the collaterized mortgage fiasco. Only 1 manager is actually a manager due to a promotion . 4 of our managers, including a top level executive, came to Etrade from Fidelity because they got laid off at Fidelity. Etrade was NOT their first choice for employment and it shows. Management FORBIDS any direct communication with the CEO. It is MANDATORY that ALL employee to CEO communicaiton be perused by immedate management first. Etrade stock has never been valued at more that 1/2 of what TD Ameritrade trades for.  After working at Etrade it is easy to see why. This company could spoil an erotic dream!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Tread your employees like the valuable resources they are. Do not assume that a 75% turnover rate every four years is normal! Train your managers to motivate and not terrorize!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-08</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Arlington, VA”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting work and manageable hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – Flexible work arrangements are not available. Very odd for such a new company with their store front on the web! Face time is everything. Working Mothers beware!401k match is very low compared to any other companies I have worked for. The company tries to save costs by outsourcing functions to India and constantly looks for more jobs to export. They’re very proud of the success of  this which is sad because we should keep as many positions in the US as possible. I’m embarrassed by this practice. Very little opportunity for growth and they actually demote people – who does that? Some managers have constant turn over and instead of fixing the problem they continue to just hire new staff.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Many of those have been with the company over 10 years which is a HUGE  issue. Very much an old boys club attitude since they have been here so long. It would be better to get some fresh talent with innovative ideas who put employees first instead of the bottom line.  Let each group decide how they should be structured and their workload  instead of micro managing everything – manage the big picture!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Review of E TRADE FInancial”

</title><pros>Pros – *During my time, benefits such as health insurance, vision, and dental were good.*Ability to learn markets</pros>
<cons>Cons – *If you begin on the telephone, difficult to transition to a different sector of company*Raises non existent during my time there.*Salaries weren't the greatest</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Investment Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Don't waste your time”

</title><pros>Pros – Can't think of any...  Good location.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Ineffective leadership from Senior level down to the sales manager.  This company has no sales leadership from what I can see.  My experience was  the managers I interacted with were constantly in CYA mode.  No one inspires anyone here with few exceptions.  Sales meetings are a combination of information dump and beat downs.  Training is 'one and done'.  Individual goals do not match overall corporate messaging and direction.  My manager regularly sent chastising e-mails - singling one employee out to the entire team.  My sales manager would single out people in ALL CAPS TO EVERYONE.  Hellooo.. HR, are you reading this??</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire sales leaders versus sales managers.  Inspire your teams to greatness - not beat downs.  Stop telling your teams 'what'; start showing them 'how'.  (I suspect that most sales managers are clueless about the how component).  Have your sales managers share a good idea to help Consultants succeed.  This place is mostly void of solid talent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It has been a decent company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – The best reasons to work for E*TRADE for me are benefits the compensation could be better. I feel the medical and dental insurances are superior. There are also other benefits such as 5% 401k matching and tuition reimbursement</pros>
<cons>Cons – The downside is the micro management on the lower service teams. It is more of a political game when it comes to promotion. Several individuals come to this company with years of experience and I feel they are belittled to fit the call center mode.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Really show your appreciation through the bonuses.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>QA Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall it's a good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Good team and there's a ton of knowledge to be learned.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Non-traditional hours, work/life balance can be difficult, work may become repetitive and dull</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Director (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“DBA at etrade”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Company, nice place to work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing as of now to say</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great learning experience tech and finance combined”

</title><pros>Pros – Technologically advanced and opportunity to learn</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of leadership and talent retention</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall pretty good”

</title><pros>Pros – Good ManagersGood work/life balanceGood base salary and earnings potentialRelaxed work environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Operational side is still a work in progress, not on the same page with sales. Can be more difficult for customers to open and transfer accounts, compared to larger firms.Commission plan changes often, consultants now get charged back for giving customers promotions, if customer moves from stock to cash, and you will get charged back if clients moves money out, causing wild swings in bonus.I feel like this job has more Pros than Cons compared with other jobs I've had.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Overall I’ve been happy with management, they give you space and offer help when needed. It would be nice if we could get more help with service issues and just focus more of our time on sales.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Auditor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Good team and there's a ton of knowledge to be learned.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Nothing negative about working here.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company to learn experiences in the Brokerage Industry”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits and the vacation request process is easy to manage. Casual work environment. Expect to wear slacks and shirts. E*TRADE will train & pay for your Series 7 & 63. Good place to learn call-center experiences, brokerage industry experiences, stock-plan, retirements accounts.  6 months to apply for promotion.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Expect to work with non-traditional hours when you first start. Sat & Sun can be your workday. Your manager, depending on who, can be a micromanager. The company will expect you to "sale" leads to Financial Consultants, or Active Trader Consultants, but reward you very little in compensation. Along with compensation, it should be higher. E*TRADE will expect you to do a lot.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Compensate associates more for the works they do.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work, although work/life balance can be a challenge.”

</title><pros>Pros – Exciting, dynamic, and challenging place to work.  Worked with a lot of smart, intelligent, motivated people.  You will be rewarded when taking on additional responsibilities while continuing to perform at a high level.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work/life balance can be a bit difficult at times.  I definitely felt that people who knew how to play the game, but were by no means all-stars, were unfairly rewarded and promoted over smarter, harder working, higher performing employees who were less socially savvy.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Senior Project Management”

</title><pros>Pros – The life-work balance is great.  Everyone is focused on business while in the office then go home.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Financial services in general isn't a growth industry at the moment so opportunities are limited.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take more risks with current technology and embrace ideas that may not yield big ROI in the near term but can differentiate us from the competition going forward.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Active Trader Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E*TRADE is a decent place to work, but as with any company has its pros and cons.”

</title><pros>Pros – The atmosphere is great, the people are great, generally pretty good to work with. The benefits are second to none.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The commissions bonus program, lacks transparency and tends to leave you wonderig if it is set up to benefit you or the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Competitive, but not quite polished”

</title><pros>Pros – Strong on trading technology and the range of investment products available to its customers.  Seeks to compete in a very competitive environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company is still young and its processes and policies are not complete.  Compare to competitor firms, where I've also worked, representative tools and support is highly lacking.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Service Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work to learn the industry from the ground up”

</title><pros>Pros – Internal Advancement are dependent upon PerformanceKnowledgeable Upper ManagementGreat Company CultureExtremely Flexible with work schedule</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work may become repetitive and dullI cannot complain, things have been great for the past 9 months</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing what you are currently doing!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“FSR”

</title><pros>Pros – I had very friendly co-workers and managers.  The work enviroment is really good. Overall,  I would recommend this company to friends looking for a job out of college.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay was low and they were constantly thinking of ways to save money. They need to pay a more competitive salary compared to other financial companies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to start but don't stay long”

</title><pros>Pros – -Paid training for series 7/63 license-Decent pay for a recent college grad-Will learn a lot about the industry</pros>
<cons>Cons – This position is extremely micromanaged.  They have a computer system that tracks everything you do, down to the second.  If you clock in one minute late or stay on a call too long you'll hear about it immediately. The job became extremely stressful do to management constantly on your back about CE (leads).  The morale here is very low do to the fact that the job gets very redundant.  There is no opportunity for growth.  Promotions are viewed as lateral movement so there is little pay increase.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you have no other cohice”

</title><pros>Pros – Paid training to get licensedBenefits are pretty good</pros>
<cons>Cons – Just a call center.  Managers like to micro manage.  No real room for growth just lateral movements.  If you really want to move up here you would have to be in it for the long haul and spend five plus years to move up.  The monotony of a call center can get to individuals and company doesn't</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Just OK, could be a lot better”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay to receive your Series 7 & 63.Employees generally get along well with each other.Benefits are pretty good, especially vision.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management makes constant changes without notifying the employees that actually do the job or use the systems.Growth potential is no longer as available as it used to be. Moves to other departments are all viewed as lateral so there is little pay increase. Promotions now only come when someone else leaves the company.Most managers can't be trusted and seem to have their own interests at heart always.Pay is low and employee morale is extremely low.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make a better effort to listen to employee suggestions and involve the people who actually use your systems in the decision making process for upgrades and improvements. Your employees make your company move. Find better ways to take care of them and make them feel appreciated because that is a main reason some of the brightest and best employees move on from this company so fast and morale remains so low. Contrary to belief, the customer is NOT always right and should have some sort of accountability for them as well. Many employees have been blamed for difficult customers who have no basis for their attitudes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Business Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great opportunities for advancement, but liquidity issue hamper new strategic initiatives.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great opportunities to take on additional responsibilities and learn new functional areas.  Prior to 2007 the firm was in many interesting markets outside of the US which provided dynamic roles in IT, Operations and Marketing.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work life balance is difficult, and employees are often unrewarded for working 60 - 80 hour work weeks when there are challenging situations.  Several departments have significantly lower workload than some key areas.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Long hours and poor support”

</title><pros>Pros – The people I worked with directly were great and care about the company.Communication is getting better.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Good old boys clubShort sighted, need better balance between quarterly profits and long-term goalsPoor management of employee satisfaction</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't just survey employees on satisfaction, hold management accountable for retention and satisfaction goals.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-01</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work!”

</title><pros>Pros – You don't take the job home with you, training is good, people are great, and management is very easy to work with and like able.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You don't make much money.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give employees more ways to increase their pay.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place for NCAs. Not for middle level people”

</title><pros>Pros – Beginners have tons of things to learn. Great technologies are available to explore. All open source at work. Its a great technology company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The etrade has too many managers and there is no growth potential for this company in the current world. The middle layer of employees are struggling.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Too many rules at work. Not a good idea to have a time based work enviornment at a software concern.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-21</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I have loved working at Etrade”

</title><pros>Pros – There are lots of opportunites for growth at Etrade, and the management is great for helping their employees succeed.  Promotions are based on performance, not tenure which I really like.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 401k does not match very much.  Health insurance is okay but not the best.  Company is not as big as others, so growth is slower than other places.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The management at Etrade is great and very helpful.  If you are a good employee, they will help you succeed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good place to start, not a lot of room for movement”

</title><pros>Pros – benefits, professional culture, good entry-level job</pros>
<cons>Cons – micro-managing, not a lot of room for growth, when you do bad, you know about it.  when you do well, you are not rewarded.  a lot of 'who you know' politicing.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you want to get licensed, get in and get out”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits, they have different schedules than the 9-5 so that may appeal to some people. You can get licensed and they train you to pass the test.</pros>
<cons>Cons – My shift changed without my notice. I felt like management lacked respect for employees, which didn't motivate me to want to work there.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Respect the FSRs they are the ones dealing with the customers. If you think you see the same thing over and over again, tell people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Boring, dead-end job”

</title><pros>Pros – Overtime available which is nice to make extra money</pros>
<cons>Cons – Zero career path, can't really get higher than manager.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It is what it is</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My experience at E*TRADE has been rewarding with advancement opportunities in to management and above average benefits.”

</title><pros>Pros – Fair pay stucture.Benefits from day one.Pleasant work enviornment</pros>
<cons>Cons – After mid management advancement limited.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – be better at coaching and mentoring subordinates</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is fine company to work with.”

</title><pros>Pros – It is right size company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work location is not flexible.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Fair and transparent are needed</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Educational but going no where”

</title><pros>Pros – To get licensed and learn about the securities industry.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Benefits, ok.  Opportunities, very limited.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-27</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Database Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Etrade, great people.”

</title><pros>Pros – The people are passionate, close knit, and have an immense sense of ownership.  The immediate management listens well to the employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – growth ads bureaucracy.   This isn't a fault of the company per say but the reality of SOX.   Also due to size, innovation has suffered.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Improve communication with the employee base.  Take risks with development, not with revenue. shut up and listen to the middle and lower tiers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The place for a predictable, dead-end, service job.”

</title><pros>Pros – Customers are relatively happy versus a big bank.  But seriously, the big banks are VERY incompetent so how hard can it be???  Some good technology but poor hardware to back it up.  You can pick up some more brokerage licenses vs. a typical bank.  They haven't bounced a paycheck yet.  Smaller size means the company is more responsive but not responsive enough versus its even smaller, niche rivals.  A competent, all-around retail broker.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No room for advancement.  No feeling of a future at this place.  No feeling of accomplishment.  Everyone is replaceable.  Development of unique skills and/or strengths is not encouraged.  I'm basically here to collect a weak paycheck; nothing more, and that really leaves you feeling like you're wasting your time.  Darn, I'm bored!  Constant concerns over bankruptcy, takeover, are they gonna shut down my office?, is my job gonna be shipped to Manila?, etc.  But seriously, what can you do in this terrible economy???  I've seen some very capable people move on.  Shabby offices.  Decrepit furniture and 10-year old computers.  Most of us gather on the weekend to drink and show-up bleary-eyed on Monday morning to start all over again.  Is that really any way to end a week???  Numb the pain.  Tax season is the pits and is one of the biggest reasons people quit.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Your employees are bored!  You re-hash the same old stuff and claim its new to your customers!  They are smarter than that!  The baby ads are getting lame.  Time for something new.  You have no idea of the repressed talent at your fingertips that could be doing so much more.  Harness it!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Security Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – - Great teamwork within the group.- Excellent manager who watches out for his employees.- Interesting technology and projects.- Great sense of pride in work.- Great benefits and opportunity to grow your career.- Rewards are available for those who work hard and earn it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -  The position is not your typical Security Engineering role.   More like Security Tools.  Not network heavy like most Security Engineering teams.-  Upper level management throws projects around or stalls/squashes projects randomly- Lots of politics on larger "Charged" projects that lead to dead-ends or delay/partial implementation.- No long term security vision from upper management.  More plugging the gaps to cover.- No backup engineer for your projects.   That means there is no on-call schedule, you are on-call for your stuff always.  *I mention this as a con because it's not the norm.  I personally like this better than on-call schedules and instills a sense of "eating your own dog food"-  Management commonly give Production and development much higher priority than Security.  Consistently feel like you there because they could not get rid of you (like life insurance.  No one want's to pay it, but they do)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Develop a long term plan for Security at E*TRADE.- Place a higher emphasis on Security with projects and peers.- Highlight the great benefits E*TRADE has.  Many employees do not realize how good they are.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Operations Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“n/a”

</title><pros>Pros – location, schedule, people, experience, benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – no room for advancement and little time off</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – stop micro managing</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stay away from the System Engineering team”

</title><pros>Pros – Technology wise, Etrade does try to stay on top of current trend and you will learn quite a bit especially in the open source market.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The biggest issue at Etrade (Menlo) and the reason for so many people leaving the company lately (or about to leave) is the management team.   None of the leaders have a clue on how to manage people.  They are very driven people with their own agenda and care less about how the people they manage feel.  They are borderline unprofessional people with no sympathy for others.  They will drive you down until you quit without remorse if they don't like you, and there is nothing HR can do about it because nobody wants to stand up to them.  Those so call "leaders" have been with the company for years, have build an awful reputation, and manage based on fear and reprisal.  I have to admit that those people are technically competent and should probably be Architects, but definitely not people manager.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Lead, Customer Service (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great place to start in the industry”

</title><pros>Pros – great place to start in the industry, get your licenses, and get the general process of how a brokerage house works. young management with some experience enables you to learn with them and see errors that you hopefully wont make when you become a manager somewhere else</pros>
<cons>Cons – related to the above issue with young management. Complete lack of mentoring. You are on your own to learn the ropes of the industry. inexperienced and uneducated. Not too many places for advancement once you learn the basis.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – not much as it seems this is a great strategy to keep people that would otherwise not be employed to their current level anywhere else. This creates a high attrition rate in that these managers with no education or experience know this is a good place to stay and from which to retire. CEO is too new to decide how he's doing but so far he's done a good job.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Innovative, good tech team”

</title><pros>Pros – Great technology. Great place to work if you seek new challenges.  Flexibility.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours.  Pay not great</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay more.  I liked working there but was offered more money outside</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people, great benefits, great work environment, overall a great place to be!”

</title><pros>Pros – The people at E*Trade are great, everyone is very professional yet easy to talk to and approachable.  Managers have a very good relationship with employees.  Employee appreciation is demonstrated often, and there are programs and events that demonstrate upper management is committed to a good work/life balance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Downsides include internal communication of company direction and intiatives, and odd shift hours for some employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Etrade is headed in the right direction, keep up the good work!  Overall a great place to be</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall my experience at Etrade was terrible because of management”

</title><pros>Pros – The company provides alot of training and courses to educate yourself.  We had access to many videos and investment courses, and the company website is very informative for both clients and employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Office politics play a big role in determining promotions and the work environment is very strict for Financial Services Representatives.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Etrade management should focus on promoting individuals that do a great job and not promote individuals based on politics or personal relationships.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Lead, Customer Service (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Determination and communication will get you far within the company - ask how you can get ahead and you just might!”

</title><pros>Pros – Young company - their youth makes them more aggressive at implementing new technologies and providing new products for the customers.Growing company - though the economic downturn has had it's toll on many companies, E*TRADE is still focused on growth. They constantly promote expanding their customer base by offering new products and undertaking more business partnerships.Fast paced - there's always something new and different happening. You may find that you're in customer service but working on other projects and working with other departments.Potential for career development - though costs can be an issue if you speak with management about improving your skills if it's a plus for the company you may get what you ask for.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Young management - not that age makes you a more skilled manager, but a manager or team lead with 1 or 2 years of work experience in total, even with a degree, doesn't have all the skills needed to lead a group (especially when more than the half the group is older than them).Lack of focus on core functionality - new features are great for the customer, but sometimes the drive to put out new features overshadows the necessities of correcting systems that are long overdue for a fix.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More performance evaluations - a once a month/quarter/year evaluation isn't good enough for most people. Going over stats also isn't entirely giving a representative a good evaluation either.Honesty - not that you can tell your representatives everything, but for major issues it's better to let your workers know the situation than to wait until the last minute and create confusion and mistrust.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I don't see a long term career opportunity at E*TRADE.”

</title><pros>Pros – They did paid me to get my series 7 & 63. The vacation time is good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay is really bad. They are all about the negative and you are never told about the positive. Can you say Micro-Managers that get really excited about their name tag and "power".If you are licensed then stay away. If you don't have your license, leave after you get it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Not everything is a metric and a number. If you didn't focus on each individuals number, those individuals might actually spend time to work with other departments to get things done. There is too much turnover, I am tired of being one of the few people that can actually get something done, because everyone else is too new or too stupid.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Auditor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You learn very fast to get out of the way of the train.”

</title><pros>Pros – The innovative culture gives you opportunities to continue with the process improvement. Internal transfers can broaden your work experiences and strengthen customer focus.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The work place environment overly depends on competition, which reduces cooperation amongst varying departments and ranks. Also, employees are constantly in the dark, there are too many secrets.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Motivate your employees with better incentives/rewards, you can start by adopting best practices from 10 companies Best Places to Work. Stop managing people by fear, otherwise it will continue to drive away your best talent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor incestuous place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Some leadership good, flexible about work/life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – Horrible promotional process.  very poor segmentation to clients.  Horrific offshoring experiences</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – wake up and sell already!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-17</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A Ok place to start out!”

</title><pros>Pros – Get your Series Licenses, observe how clients are riding this market and learning from them.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Service request that are not processed in a timely fashion and some clients complaining about  our Manila Call center.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to the clients concern about Manila reps.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok to work for some time. Not a great place to grow.”

</title><pros>Pros – Creative. Small world.Strong in web technology.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow growth.Lack of visibility to smart work.Immature process</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value IQ and education and utilize such talent</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ETRADE isnt what it used to be but it's still alive, surprisingly.”

</title><pros>Pros – There's a lot to learn at ETRADE, even for seasoned developers. I was impressed with the length of time most of the team members had been there, 6-10+ years. Some people have been there since the old glory days of ETRADE.</pros>
<cons>Cons – In my perspective the overall technology culture at ETRADE is hampered by poor team interconnectivity and low socialization. It seemed that groups of people tended to associate primarily within their own team, or within their own culture. Not unlike a lot of other companies, but this is clearly a weakness. I would have liked to see more of a team building effort, especially at times when morale had been low. My perception of the environment is that it is extremely competitive due to the lack of trust outside of cliques.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I believe team building across cultural boundaries is sorely needed. Trust and transparency is a must. Secrets and whispering behind people's backs only adds to the division. Focus on integrating new talented developers within the ranks of the seasoned heroes of yore.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“If you have a degree, then leave.”

</title><pros>Pros – benefits, short hours, time off.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The job itself. Customers. Customers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do something about the wait times.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Okay place to get started”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits, Knowledge gained about trading.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Micro Management could be reduced significantly.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more consistent.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Easy job.  Decent pay.  Little bit boring and one dimensional.”

</title><pros>Pros – By far the benefits are the best part of the job.  3 weeks paid vacation, 1 week sick paid vacation off the bat.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The work can be boring for somebody looking for excitement from their job.  Very monotonous schedules... which can be your friend at times, and depressing other times.  Soft selling is part of the job description but no compensation/bonus comes from it.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management was fine.  Can't ask for much more.  Good people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good for entry level”

</title><pros>Pros – entry level get series 7 and 63 licenses.  good training.  good experience in customer service.  great if you are looking to get into sales.  opportunity for future licenses (series 4, 24, ect.).  good stepping stone (currently looking for another job)</pros>
<cons>Cons – micromanagement.  breaks, lunch and start time are recorded to the second.  compensation is low.  will take years to earn decent living at FSR level.  you potential ceiling will end at being either sales RM or a manager.  creates a lot of turnover.  currently looking for another job after 3 years, which is usually the case (which isn't a necessarily a con)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – manager should stick up for their reps more.  be more of an advocate.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative In Call Center (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Call center experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Young managers indicate the ability for in house advancement.  Relatively high end phone center job which required experience in financial services (as well as Series 7 registration).  Still there are occasions for the unreasonable calls from customers who blame you for some mistake they have made. Company did make an effort to provide some outlets from the stress of making calls with a nice break area with  TV, wii and ping pong tables.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Young managers often are not experienced in managing people.  Tend to be too defensive and rely to too heavily on call statistics.  Senior management seldom on site. Relatively low compensation considering the skills and knowledge required for this job.  However due to cost pressures, firm was moving toward lower cost call centers in other parts of the country and overseas.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Senior management should consider the quality as well as the quantity of calls handled by CSR in the call centers. Should look at the example of Zappo to see how a call center should be managed.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-19</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Lead (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E*TRADE Securities”

</title><pros>Pros – The bonus structure rewards performance. Salary is consistent with industry standards. There are opportunities for advancement. It is an innovative company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – For a company that espouses technology and innovation, some departments are archaic, with processes that require manual calculations froth with human errors.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep technolgy in the forefront not only in the active trader brokerage business but for all business units.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Etrade”

</title><pros>Pros – Laid back work environment.  Great people to work with. Good to work in an innovative and entrepreneurial style work environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay is not good at all.  There is not much room for advancement.  The company is trying to turn things around</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give employees more assistance in advancing their careers.  Base more of the salary on performance and pay more for performance</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E*TRADE good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – - They are good about giving you time off when needed- It is possible to move positions within different departments fairly easily- Good employee benefits</pros>
<cons>Cons – - You are on the phone all day long listening to other people's problems which can be kind of stressful- Micro management to the point where every second of your day must be accounted for</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Less micro management of employee's time - trust that your employees are going to do their job efficiently- More incentive for sales</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Operations Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to learn”

</title><pros>Pros – Relaxed environment allows you to balance personal life and work. If you put forth the extra effort, you will have select oppurtunities for advancement.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Little communication from top down. Low pay creates high turnover. Often becomes a case of being well liked vs. skilled. Lack of redunency at some positions means working odd hours from time to time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay your team a little more and watch the talent level increase.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“FSR”

</title><pros>Pros – This is an inbound call center--not very glamorous work, but the company knows this is a realatively lousy job and doesn't try to sugar-coat it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – constant turn over between etrade, morgan stanley, wells, and fidelity.  if you want a promotion, you have to walk across the street to another firm.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get a handle of the revolving door between Wells, ETrade, Morgan Stanley and Fidelity.  Create a career path for advancement</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Staff Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“a waste of time”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits are okay, policies are fine, work tools are not bad, knowledge sharing system is good, working remotely or from home facilities are okay.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation is bad, managers lack some skills like communication skills, annual raises suck, no innovation or creativity encouragement, limited vision.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay employees well</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-05</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Broker (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is what you make of it.”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity to get Series 7, 63, and Series 24 licensing with company paid for training.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low Salary, Telephone call center environment very oppressive (if you go to the bathroom too much your manager will say something). Very rude and unknowledgable clients at the entry level.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat the people that are in the call center as important to the company because they are the first line of contact with your clients. Get rid of the Manila, Phillipines call center, just because it's cheaper does not mean it's better. By the time clients went through the ordeal of dealing with the Manila representatives they were so upset it was difficult to deal with them.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Licensed trader on Elite Services Team”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity to become securities licensed. Learn a bit about the markets, it pays fairly well for a call center environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You're in a call center environement. You're also dealing withe peoples money in  a market sensitive environment. You need to have thick skina and an ability to work under pressure, fixing problems while someone is waiting right in your earset.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Call center environments are difficult places to provice advancement. It is a horizontal structure with a manager and his/her reps. Not a lot of room for moving up, though there are many opportunities to move sideways.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Equity Compensation Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Satisfying work, poor management.”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunities to grow. (To a point)Good benefits.Multiple departments to consider. (Though a lack of layers of growth within them.)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor management structure.Status quo is maintained.Favoritism displayed in wreckless manner.Upper management exists at other sites, lack true visibility to what goes on.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Valuable employees will move on to other opportunities if not presented with any. Limited perception of those with value has hurt several departments. Sandy location needs more support, better leadership and leadership opportunities.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Accountant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work if you have the personality for it”

</title><pros>Pros – The enviroment is very steady.  You get to meet a lot of smart people who are not necessary on the super aggressive competitive mode in life.  The culture is very loose and relax.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unfortunately the culture is very relax, to the point there was no real structure to career growth, training, reasonable promotions.  It is a place where if you do not say anything, they do nothing for you, if you say a lot they MIGHT satisfy your needs.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please pay people what they are worth, recognize their efforts through promotions, especially with new graduates.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type> Financial Service Representative  (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Etrade”

</title><pros>Pros – Pretty relaxed environment. They have been getting a lot less relaxed as of late, especially with the economy in bad condition.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They don't pay very well and haven't given raises in over three years to anyone in the company unless promoted.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay your employees what they are worth or they will be unhappy and look for another job while getting paid at yours.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Elite Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Big name company, good market share within the industry.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is a disaster. They change policies and rules every week, they change rules Monday, and fire people the next day. They cut people off who have been with the company for a while tosave money, and promote new people without pay raises. They micromanage workers so bad, watch everything you say, everything you do. The company really gets on you about what you spend 1 minute on; you are their prostitute. People at the company are so scared they if they will be fired the next day, they fire people like it's nothing, one small mistakes, you are out.The pay is so low, you will not believe series 7 brokers with exeperience only get paid that little. The amount is disgraceful. Not much room for promotion, they treat you like 5 years old, judge you, the worst company I ever worked for.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop trying to micromanage people, care about the current employees and take care of them, and stop hiring new people to cover fired people. Empower employee instead of enslaving them. Stop firing people over little things, making reports on everything to watch employees is ridiculous. Pay the people right, the brokers really do alot of work, it's barely above minimum wage.People who not get on phones should not make rules or change policies, they don't know anything about it.The back office outsourcing is a disaster. TOA department needs to be more efficient. You are losing so many customers over TOA not running efficiently, too many headaches for people who are trying to BRING the money to etrade. All your mismanagement flaws are directed to your brokers, without anything valid to say to customers made by the management. Genie balance program is horrible, customers should not have to call in to fix balances on their accounts.Pay your brokers more, people in mainstreet, and Elite.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Get the experience and move on.”

</title><pros>Pros – -Well known company to use as a stepping stone for experience in the financial industry.-Front line employees make the work environment friendly and creative.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -Promotions most time awarded by how well you are liked rather than the quality of your work.-Constant feeling of job insecurity (which is verbalized by management).-Lack of respect from management towards front line employees.-Employees must spend just as much time protecting their position as they do performing their required duties.-Disproportionate percentage of minorities in management.- There is no in house contact for employees to go confidentially when they have problems with management.  HR seems to be in a position to protect Etrade regardless of the truth in the allegations regarding the behavior of their management team.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Departmental management should be required to go through management training. Management must recognize that it is important to respect all employees equally.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-17</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Relationship Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not the worst place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – The compensation was good. Decent base salary with good bonus opportunties. You work normal hours, Monday through friday nine to five no saturdays. Fairly low stress.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The systems are horrible as is the back office. The requests you send on behalf of your customers will take for ever to get done. Micro management that you can't believe. Almost no chance of moving up in the company. Forget about raises. Constantly changing goals and focus points.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Have a more clearly defined job description for the role with more defined goals and focuses. Stop the micromanagement, improve the operations of the company, and update your systems.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E*TRADE Financial - General View”

</title><pros>Pros – E*TRADE was once a small fish in a big pond.  Now with its bank, international presence, large customer base and national and global recognition it is a big player in its space.  The firm can continue to grow one the bank puts its issues to rest.  great company, with the need to have a change in upper mgmt (CEO and CFO) to get it back to a place where customers and employees and shareholders are smiling and believing that the firm is on a growth pattern once again.</pros>
<cons>Cons – right now like many other firms E*TRADE is contracting and going on a holding pattern on growth.  It is cost cutting certain infastructures that will only need to be built back up again during the growth period.  If should really look to cut our of certain businesses and high $ exec comp.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – every copmany has a CEO, CFO, and COO to take it to a certain point then move on...Kristos had his time....Mitch made his mark, Layton did his share...now lets get a CEO who can build the trust of the ranks and instill the same vigor and enthusiam that the firm once had...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-10-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Senior Developer”

</title><pros>Pros – Good career growth with many opportunities to work with many different technologies. Compensation is OK, maybe a little lower than competition.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very fast paced and stressful environment. Very high turnover rate with most of their developers overseas. Management does not balance personal life with work.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work on communication, many of the departments are very fragmented and difficult to coordinate to get any work done. Compensation could be better.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-10-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Lead (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“man battle stations!”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Environment, opportunity to advance, flexible time off. In general the people you worked with were willing to help, managers tired their best.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No bonus, stock price is still really low, they really blew it 2 years ago and have not really recovered. The 401k match was 2% when they were doing well 3 years ago... It really makes you think when the executives used to talk about their huge profit ratio, but they only matched 2%</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – At the road show don't talk about your huge profit ratio when the compensation is lower than your competitors. Offer more defined career paths.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-10-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good place to gain experience”

</title><pros>Pros – access to trading platform and cheap commission trades, sponsorship for securities licenses that are pretty much desired, fun younge environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – phone software program called blue pumpkin tracks all phone activity and tells you when you can take a break, go to the bathroom do emails</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – give employees more time to take care of customer problems rather than have to always be available to take calls</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-07-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Stock Broker (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not bad, Not great”

</title><pros>Pros – Love being in the financial industry and loved the corporate culture.  Everything was very laid back and the work day went by quickly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Everything was very deceiving at making the most money for the company and customers were not of top importance which was hard.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Not much.  It's a tough industry.  I liked my job and the pay was fine.  It would be nice to get a little more vacation though.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-06-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Gone but not forgotten”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunity for growth and advancement based on your skills. Recognition of a job well done. Atmosphere, work environment, and peers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor communication between upper management and everyone else. Unwillingness to assist employees in the balance of their professional/ personal life.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Communicate better with employees. Spport employees more in the desire to grown and advance within the organization. Treat employees with respect.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-06-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Staff Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E*Trade technology.”

</title><pros>Pros – New technology, many projects, brilliant people to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – .Proprietary stuff..No proper guidelines about promotions, and role definition. A junior  will do same work  or more then a senior, but all this does not count in review/promotions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more transparent about the management style.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-06-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Why Bother?”

</title><pros>Pros – Commission schedule was good, but I've heard has gotten worse since I left.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They don't listen to the right feedback. They wear blinders to the reps advice and continue in what they think is best, but clearly has not turned out to be best.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay more attention to your reps, not just formal feedback where they are nervous but on the floor where they speak their minds.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-05-31</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E*Trade Financial is a joke.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good technology.  If you are in the architecture group it'll be great because u get to explore and learn different technologies..do your trial and errors etc...otherwise if u end up just doing dev work, do it for 2 yrs and u don't learn anymore except kissing up and BS-ing</pros>
<cons>Cons – Product Mgrs @ETFC from Customer Service! One know the buzz words and kiss-ups to move up the corp ladder.Don't even know how to trade except simple equity orders.Don't have a clue what brokerage is or even what the competitiion is doing.Business side emp most are a joke.Salary is horrible compare to other companies.The only way to move up is the kiss the right 'S'.They try to act professional but all they know is just buzz words.They are just plain sales people who lies</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Leaders @ETFC?MOre like Followers IMO.  You kiss the right person and hope for a promotion. You scratch my back and I'll scratch yours.One person I knew got a promotion in 6 months fresh out of college! and then 5 months later promoted to mgr (he started as a software engr).He didn't do much except kissed the right butt.Barely chk in any code but still able to move up.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>UNIX Administrator (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Needs more smiles.”

</title><pros>Pros – The size of the company means there's less overhead to be bogged down with. There is opportunity to get stuff done and work on interesting projects.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The atmosphere and morale is pretty low. People crowd around the TV showing CNBC whenever the stock takes a dive.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try to boost morale somehow at the company</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Product Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not for everyone, but great for certain types”

</title><pros>Pros – At E*TRADE, almost anyone can have the opportunity to take the lead on an initiative, whether initiated by others or their own.  You can quickly go up a learning curve and develop new skills.  It's fairly easy to get a cross-functional education and transition to work in different roles and departments.  You have the opportunity to work on industry-leading creative, innovative products and services.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Most of E*TRADE works at an extremely fast pace and can be a very chaotic environment that often leads to unecessary mistakes.  Smoe may not appreciate the effect of this on the user experience. This can also lead to inconsistent rewards and recognition for employees, and can be too agressive a culture for some.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay closer attention to and reward more fairly the many talented individual contributors who build and maintain the exceptional products and service</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-03-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Stock Broker (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a bad company”

</title><pros>Pros – Great flexibility with your  schedule, several shifts are offered.  The benifits this company offers are great, including 4 weeks of paid time off from day one which is much higher than the industry standard. The salary is not bad, but is is not enough to keep you from looking for another job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the company is constantly being investigated for some sort of legal issue such as interpositioning in trades and things of that nature. Also they are starting to heavily rely upon call center reps based in the Philipines who don't know the first thing about the brokerage industry, or english for that matter.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire domestic workers!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Miserable Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Fast paced environment.  Get to speak to people of different backgrounds and learn new things on a daily basis.  Alllows you to keep up with the investment world and relay that information to investors.  Opportunity to educate investors and prospects on self directed investing. You get to trade in your own accounts at the employee discount rate, which isn't bad.  Hard to find many positives, cause there were very few for me.  Colleagues are fun to work with and make it a little bit easier to get through the day.  Trading systems were very good and easy to use for me.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Entirely too many calls on daily basis.  100 plus calls a day with the majority of them coming from somebody that has trouble with the English language and they are upset about something.  Company and team leads and managers are too controlling. Something screws up on a daily basis.  Whether it's the website or trading systems or anything else you can think of, there's a good chance it will be broken when you get to work or before you leave.  The company is being ran in to the ground and they expect you to work "mandatory" "voluntary" overtime to help explain this to the customers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Sell the company or merge with TD or Schwab.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Stock Plans Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Etrade is the best brokerage job to get started in the industry.”

</title><pros>Pros – Etrade is a great place if you like to just show up and do your job and not get hassled by your boss. People that are senior to you are excellent and actually care about their employees. As long as you do what you are supposed to then they stay out of your business completely.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is basically nowhere to go as far as advancement goes. You start there making 40K and you could work there for 25 years and make 45 or 55K max. It's a GREAT job for a student or someone that is just breaking in the industry. Just don't go in there with the idea that you are going to grab the world by the tail because Etrade is not the place to accomplish that.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – None, management is very fair. My boss was a "no bs" type of guy but he was great at giving all of his employees plenty of space. All the other managers are similar.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Services Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I recommend their services, but not employment.”

</title><pros>Pros – It's a good business model (mortgage issues aside) and has great products and services. The website and cash management services are user-friendly and generally problem-free. The pace of development and technology make it an exciting place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Employees are treated as disposable. There is no focus on health or wellness, and employees who ask for modified schedules to care for their family are frequently denied. The HR department serves only to police the employees and deliver bad news.The constantly revolving leadership team makes for frequent changes to priorities and goals.There are different standards for every department, with the "less valuable" areas receiving very little in the way of perks or moral boosters.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Your employees are your best asset. Treat them with respect. Retain the successful leaders, and eliminate those who get caught up in the power struggle and inter-departmental politics.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Operations Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice place to learn and advance your career...not for too long though”

</title><pros>Pros – Great learning opportunity, great benefits package, awesome brokerage platform, good marketing by the company.  ETRADE (Arlington) is also VERY involved in the community, e.g. homeless out-reach programs, elementary school visits, toys for tots around the holidays etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Senior management can be aloof and disinterested, instant messaging seems to be the only way to communicate with co-workers.  Stock price cant seem to break the $2 mark.  Nervous about the economy and if ETRADE will react accordingly. Lots of customer service are out-sourced to Manilla.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take more time to learn about the "little people" that work under you, help us develop our career by introducing us to new tasks.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-01-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Operations Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“a review”

</title><pros>Pros – a great place to get experience, it forces you to adapt to changing situations</pros>
<cons>Cons – management was always reacting to problems (and badly) instead of anticipating them.  Too many legacy systems, and too many changes, then unchanges</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't ever, ever, let the ETBank people run the company again</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-12-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok Company to work for if you are not ambitious.”

</title><pros>Pros – large stable organization and there is a lot of work; it being an financial services company, its not going to run out of projects but the downside is that it is not a technical orgnanization hence, you may get stuck with legacy apps and maintenance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – one can get pigeon holed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get to know your employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-11-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Relationship Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good management at local level, but not a ton of opportunity for advancement.”

</title><pros>Pros – The bonus was good when reasonable targets were set by senior management, and it was a fun atmosphere most of the time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very hard to get things done because of the way things are set up.  While there are some good people in the back office, it's generally just gets in the way of getting things done.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide a more clear career path.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-11-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company to START a career if we pull through the market turmoil”

</title><pros>Pros – Get your series 7 and 63 while being paid a competitive salaryUpward advancement availableLaid back enviroment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Uncertinity of where the company is headedMay be bought out or worse in the near futureVERY unprof. at times</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The employees of ETrade depend on you to lead us through this mess, dont turn your backs on us like the last management team. Focus on keeping E-Trade a float and PLEASE dont sell us off or let us go bankrupt like a few other competitors in the industry.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Will not feel like you work in a smooth running environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – Camaraderie.  Some good opportunities for advancement.  Closure of several offices means more work for associates who remain, good if you don't mind working OT, not so good if you're susceptible to burnout.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Will sometimes hire from outside rather than promote from within.  Some in management are clueless.  Used to be a good place to get a start in finance but now they're only hiring experienced and licensed brokers.  Always get the feeling that you're expendable and not appreciated.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Understand that front line associates are integral to your business.  Should maybe start recognizing that fact.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to get experience but not a place for a long term career”

</title><pros>Pros – Creative compnay and a great place to get in on the ground floor to get industry experience. ETRADE offers excellent opportunities for people to get their foot in the door of the financial services industry. You will even get the opportunity to move around to different areas.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This is a fast moving company and there is allot of turnover, reorganization, and offshoring. Couple this with the history of unstable financial stability and you will rarely if ever feel job security.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing what you're doing. Strip it down and get it ready for sale. But in the meantime make sure you are not making empty promises or misleading employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Product Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E*TRADE is an innovative company that has a strong culture yet wrought with many opportunities for job growth.”

</title><pros>Pros – The best reasons to work for E*TRADE is that firstly there are a lot of opportunities to work on many different projects and initiatives. There are many different initiatives the company undertakes. Thus opportunities generally seek you out first. Secondly, if you like to get things done, E*TRADE has a culture of getting big projects done in very little time. That can be exciting on the one hand and challenging on the other. Lastly, the company is huge on innovation. The company thrives very much on coming up with new products and tools to improve the experience of all our customers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As with any company there are certainly some downsides with working at E*TRADE. The first is that there is always a lack of human resources. Given that the company is always trying to keep costs down this is the biggest challenge especially when the company has so many big ambitions. On the one hand it means that there are a lot of opportunities. On the other hand it becomes a challenge to get everything done. The second is that with any financial company, there are a lot of regulatory procedures that must be adhered to. These can certainly get in the way of completing projects in a timely manner.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Despite the troubles in the industry, continue to seek opportunities to invest.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun, dynamic company to work for, but not an easy place to be due to turmoil and uncertainty.”

</title><pros>Pros – Fun culture, dynamic business.  Lots of opportunities to learn about various retail financial services.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Balance sheet is a wreck due to the HELOC assets.  It will be awhile before it is put back together, and when it is, my opinion is that it will be sold to a competitor.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Clean up the balance sheet.  It will be tough to attract and retain talented people otherwise.  Those that remain will do so because they are unemployable elsewhere or scared of the current economy.  Not the people you need to turn the company around.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Operations Analyst (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Life at E*Trade from the line level employee's view.”

</title><pros>Pros – There is constant change happening at E*Trade so there will always be new and challenging things for the motivated employee.  Since the company is small and in a constant state of change there are ample opportunities to shape your own role and take on additional challenges and responsibilities.  The workplace is an EXTREMELY liberal company and the dress code is a very relaxed business casual.  Discrimination is almost non-existent at E*Trade so you can be pretty well assured that you will be welcomed no matter who you are.  The Arlington, VA office is in a great location just 4 miles West of DC in one of the most diverse areas of the nation.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company is caught in the midst of the credit crunch. There have been multiple layoffs as well as a recent hiring and promotion freeze. It can be difficult working at a company where there may or may not be a future for you. Senior management very rarely promotes from within the ranks which is due in part to the total lack of a development program. To succeed at E*Trade you have to be a truly self motivated go-getter willing to take on additional tasks as well as the established power structure. New executive level management does not communicate at all past the executive level. Directors down to the line level employees are complete in the dark in regards to the company‘s financial direction and stability.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do more to retain valued employees.  E*Trade does a poor job of developing talent from within the ranks.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“To live and die at E*trade”

</title><pros>Pros – Etrade is a great place to begin a career in Finance.  Getting you feet wet is mandatory from day one.  They do take great care in training you properly for the position and provide ample time and training for getting all necessary licenses.  Once all licenses have been acquired, further training is given to further improve your job performance.  Also, self training in other fields and topics within the financial field is encouraged.  Being originally a dot com company, the work atmosphere was fairly relaxed but was changing considerably when I left.  The casual dress attire at work was still in place and definitely made for a more comfortable work environment.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The long hours required.  Overtime is generally mandatory.  The minimum standards and quotas needed to be met at work was strictly monitored and can be extremely overbearing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Cultivate the employees more.  The work environment and the constant need to meet your "numbers" was stressful and numbing.  This pressure seemed to come from the top since most supervisors I knew were also under the same kind of stress.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-07-20</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>FSR, Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E*TRADE flexible overall, but get a good manager.  Great place for a student, but may not be a full time career”

</title><pros>Pros – E*TRADE is a very mellow and easy going employer.  However, how easy going depends on your Manager.  Some managers look the other way while others are very strict and to the point.  Additionally, they give you a month to study for the series 7 and they pay you while you are doing it.  They have excellent study guides for passing this difficult test.  They do not ask for a specific length of time after they pay for you passing the 7.  So you may use E*TRADE to get it and go somewhere else that pays more</pros>
<cons>Cons – In customer service you always see the worse things that happen, that being said they do seem to lose a plethora of paperwork and can be slow to correct their mistakes.  Their pay is somewhat on the low side and they can be slow to give raises.  But their ability to work with families and busy students makes this easy to overlook</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to what the employees want.  It will not do any good to make rules that will drive employees away</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-07-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great talent, technology and very motivated  people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Balance sheet aspect, timing is not good as financial industries are going through downward spiral and ET is not exception.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employee retention, motivation and vision for company going forward will be the key for success for ET and management must look into these.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good company to work for with some occasional Back office operational hiccups.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good company to work for. Technology and innovation focused. Just needs a little work in the Operations departments and the programs we use to help customers need to stop crashing or being incredibly slow at random times during the day. Aside from that there is a lot of good to be said about the company and I do enjoy working there (I'm lucky to have a great manager, too).</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some of the supervisors working in the Operations department kill me sometimes. There are some great ones and others that I cannot believe have not been let go yet. They defy all logic and common sense. I wish they had the customer in mind back there instead of doing whatever the heck they try not to do. I'd give anything to put some of the supervisors back there on the phones for just one week (their direct reports do a better job than them honestly).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Fix Genie. Fix Operations. Fix VISA card and checkbook issues. 'Nuff said.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Paralegal (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working at E*TRADE”

</title><pros>Pros – Interesting work, growth potential of the company, good people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management decisions are sometimes made without complete understanding of the details of the daily workings.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – see above.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-07-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good to get your license but no growth”

</title><pros>Pros – easy to get foot in the door and some good employees. easy to get your licenses. good employees discounts on broker services and bank rates with high interest.</pros>
<cons>Cons – no growth; bad management and communication. management treats employees like children, and there is no attention paid to suggestions for improvement. not proactive in solving problems and would rather sweep them under the rug; people more concerned with covering themselves and office politics rather than improving the firm.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more transparency with employees and invest more in competent service</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E*TRADE is a good place to work but a little unorganized”

</title><pros>Pros – E*TRADE is a very fast-paced environment where employees learn to multi-task and utilize a variety of resources to complete the task at hand.  Opportunities for professional development are plentiful.  Employees have an opportunity to learn many different software applications.  The environment also provides very much information to employees about the goings-on in the stock market.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is inconsistent.  Constantly changing managers results in starting/stopping of projects and confused employees.  The company also has multiple locations throughout the U.S. and resources have been juggled between those sites over the years.  I think employees in some of the current locations are probably scared that their location will be closed.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Choose a path and stick to it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Do not work for Etrade”

</title><pros>Pros – They paid to get my series 7, 63</pros>
<cons>Cons – Constant layoffs, little opportunity for advancement, very poor training on company procedures. No raises in over a year, miserable employee morale, having to deal with outsourced representatives from Manilla, no community involvement to speak of, no accountablity for clients isssues, performance reviews are only held once a year, incompetent mangement with extremely poor communication skills. The monotony of dealing with the same rediculous call transfers that are totally unecessay from incompetent morons with no understanding of the brokerage industry, or company policies and procedures. Losing your job with very little notice or assitance finding employment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They suck, and ran the company into the ground due to poor investment decisions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Service Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“honest”

</title><pros>Pros – experience, and the have a good software for trading</pros>
<cons>Cons – this is an environment were it's who you know and hang out with rather then performance</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – the feedback i get is very vague i was only told what i did wrong and never what the issue was and what to do to improve in the eye of the company</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fun Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – friendly working environment.family oriented.has a lot of community related activities.curricular activities for employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – don't value employee so much.not a lot of incentives</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-28</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fantastic experience.. u guys need to look out for this one”

</title><pros>Pros – Timely food and salary  IQ/Skills/Personality  work space environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – very strict officers.. might be bugging at times.. never mind the compensation was good so just survuved there</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place to think & execute ideas</pros>
<cons>Cons – Too many managers to report to at the same time!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Variable compensation; Overall experience largely dependent on location and manager”

</title><pros>Pros – The product spectrum is expanding, and as consultants, we have quite a bit of flexibilty and control over what we present to clients and how. Some of the folks on the sales distribution team are great and really focus their resources on helping FC's succeed.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - The comp plan changes frequently. The newest change makes it difficult to gauge how your bonus is progressing throughout the quarter if you have clients who are active traders (despite the fact that all that trading actually makes E*TRADE money).- While it's nice that you're given a book of business to start with, it's extremely difficult to remove clients from your book who don't belong there. You may end up with people who have no contact info, who have no desire to speak with you, or who don't live locally (if you're in a branch),.- Some branch managers seem great to work with, others can be micro-managers or number crunchers who aren't very helpful in their role to foster sales growth. Some branches work well together, others may have FC's who rarely interact with one another.- If you don't have an operations person in your branch, then be prepared to waste some time here and there on service issues or paperwork.- Some of the leads we get are complete garbage, yet you're still hounded by management if you don't properly attempt them several times and prove that you've exhausted all avenues to uncover business. I'd rather focus on actual opportunities than satisfy some arbitrary requirement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-04</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Credit admin”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible place to work at...</pros>
<cons>Cons – they take advantage of people and make them work hard but don't pay them the money worth their job</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – No comments</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Awesome atmosphere, highly intelligent co-workers, and competitive pay”

</title><pros>Pros – o Great people to work with, great atmosphere, and very subtle politics among management people (one that is not obvious and weighing on the rank-and-file workers).o Competitive salary.o Fair performance appraisal, which may result in a bonus.o Night and day shift jobs.</pros>
<cons>Cons – o Holidays are US-based; work still ongoing on Philippine holidays (but I guess that's a Pro for the double pay!).o Management doesn't seem to want to keep their agents with the company (little to no agent retention).o Management seems to want to maximize an agent for all their worth and not look into increasing their pay.o Benefits are standard but nothing extra to make you want to stay with the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You guys might want to improve on your agent retention. E*TRADE is not just a "stepping stone" company. You might want to have agents work there until retirement. Loyal agents build goodwill for the company and touch your clients in a profound way. And please look into better employee benefits and aligning their pay to their workload.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Really strong technology company”

</title><pros>Pros – E*Trade has one of the strongest technology teams I have seen. It has a great working environment and many of the people have been with E*Trade for a number of years. This makes them very knowledgeable in what they do and that makes things so much easier</pros>
<cons>Cons – The only issue with E*Trade is stability of the company. You hear so many rumors of it getting acquired or not having a rosy future, you feel like you are on an unstable platform that may topple any minute.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company has moved to hard sales. Not the E*TRADE I once knew....”

</title><pros>Pros – For the work required the pay is pretty good.  I have generally had a good experience with the people I work with...they generally do not hire the kind of person one normally associates with a brokerage firm (slicked hair, angry etc).  Good base pay. I have made many, many friends who I will always be in contact with. Local Management has always been good to me.They are very good about not requiring late hours, weekend work etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The comp plan for sales associates is the worst thing that has ever been excreted out of a human mind. Its very core is designed to cost you money at every turn. Client dies?  Likely you will lose money. Client buys a house? You lose money.  Client sells Mutual Funds? You lose money. And don't confuse this with a loss of retention or some hypothetical loss of continuing payments.  You literally are charged from your bonus dollar for dollar. In other words, everything you sell will one day come back to cost you just as much, if not more (if it's value went up), than you were paid to sell it in the first place. Thousands of dollars a quarter will disappear due to things you have 0 control over. I won't go into too much detail, but I will say that when this plan was introduced to me I scoffed at the hypothetical losses I saw coming.Unfortunately they are not hypothetical anymore.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They live in their own world. I won't bother.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-31</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“weighed down by poor management”

</title><pros>Pros – great benefits, most people are easy to work with. work/life balance is great.</pros>
<cons>Cons – management is poor and mired by favoritism. senior management has their pets who get promoted every year while high producing employees are passed over every year. there is a culture of saying no. projects have 17 rounds of approvals, and everyone is looking to say no.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – get fresh talent from outside the company. too many internal hirings leads to an army of yes-men.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Fast pace, great learning environment for new to the financial service industry</pros>
<cons>Cons – long hours, temp worker layoffs</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-06</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Trade (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tips for assessing and reported this company”

</title><pros>Pros – I support the high-income jobs and support the places near the place of residence for more than a remote factor I support the diverse functions and not just one function</pros>
<cons>Cons – I hate the lack of diversity of languages ??and the lack of training courses for short periods</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – My advice is as follows: on the company to evolve and expand dramatically and fast at the same time and this happens to increase, especially the basic languages ??such as Arabic and ... Etc. Second, targeting people with popular on Facebook and advertising for this company Thirdly targeting their pockets full of people and people with influence locally and internationally, as people living in the Persian Gulf are the focal point for many companies that have become rich and globalI would advise to also target people from the countries of its currency cheap, because they would receive a wage high value and will work hard</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Limited advancement in uncertain economy plaques company.”

</title><pros>Pros – Good pay and benefits, God work schedules</pros>
<cons>Cons – Doom and gloom at line level employees, hard to motivate without incentives.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give management tools to help morale.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-29</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Margins Department (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is an overall ok place to work for.”

</title><pros>Pros – Relaxing environment, good place to work if u like screwing over customers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company hires very inexperienced people that have no business working in the financial field. I worked in the margins department and  managers and supervisors are really incompetent and have really screwed over clients because they really don't know what they are doing.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – hire smarter people that have skills talent in the financial industry, don't just hire them because they have a degree.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-15</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good place to start but not to grow”

</title><pros>Pros – lots of leads, good tools</pros>
<cons>Cons – changing comp plan, no wealth transfer focus</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Little guidance and training, but generally satisfactory.”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent pay, incentives to perform.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of structure and guidance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – See cons.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Opportunity but pay is not sufficient”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunities abound and able to learn a new job without experience</pros>
<cons>Cons – Work hard but pay is not in line with level of work</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ok place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – very good at keeping prdn systems running, despite all the best efforts of the entire company to hose it (unintentional ofcourse).</pros>
<cons>Cons – no respect for people.  old timers are taking the company for a ride.  way behind on technological advances, major decision making powers are centered within a few individuals/groups, who have least concern about company good, majorly looking to add buzzwords to their skills, resulting in half-cooked efforts.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management needs to trust new talent from outside instead of few favorite people being promoted, irrespective of their capability or skills.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tremendous work, horrible pay.”

</title><pros>Pros – E*TRADE Financial, also known as Microsoft of the East, has many areas that can be improved upon.  From a heavy dependence on excel, to disconnected systems, employees are faced with using multiple applications to do 1 of their many job functions.  With this, there are many opportunities to take initiative and improve processes and technologies.  At one point, the company produced an employee survey, providing employees a voice about their work experience.</pros>
<cons>Cons – E*TRADE Financial does not pay its employees competitive salaries.  The lowest score the company received from the above mentioned survey was salary satisfaction (Arlington location, at least).  Upper management chalked that up to "all companies have low employee salary satisfaction".  The company has taken no initiative to correct, nor improve the situation.  While there are several opportunities to improve the company's processes and technologies, employees are not competitively compensated for it.  E*TRADE Financial does give good bonuses, but they are not for a job well done, it's used to justify the low salary.  Upper management has often threatened to to reduce bonus pay out and has never made it a guarantee, like salary.  Many employees have been known to work hard, accomplish improvements, then leave the company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Leadership should not be afraid to challenge the status quo and adjust salaries to keep the talented and valuable.  Do the salary research.  Look at your employee's experience and what they can do to improve the core businesses.  If employees are good at their jobs, the company should be able to cut excess spending on unused contractor work (for example).  Employee salary increases in the balance sheet and income statement, coupled with decreases in certain operational spending is a sign that the company is relying on its employees - valuating the talented and positioning itself to retain the best employee workforce.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Desktop Support (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Learned a lot.”

</title><pros>Pros – Etrade is a very large and well respected US business!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sadly, due to the recession they have no longer have a UK operation.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Staff Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“So so”

</title><pros>Pros – Reasonable work hours and stressNice office with great river view</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor managementNo exciting projectsLots of bureaucracyBelow market compensation</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“one terrible place on the earth”

</title><pros>Pros – lots of open source technologya few good toolsconstantly trying to reduce the overhead towards technology - like the whole site is running on tools of no dollar spent.</pros>
<cons>Cons – there is a lots of gang and groupism at the management level. The management hat is misused to throw away people that dont fall in line with management especially teams like build and release. Demonstrates completely unprofessional and unethical practices. Unfortunately, senior management is deaf to complaints because you cannot cross over the barrier. The bonus and salary hike stays with a few individuals that are whims and fancies to local management. This place is a great example of atrocity and bureaucracy in IT industry. The people that are sincere, are treated like commodities. You have to work on public holidays because the guys running the management feel, they own your personal life. Since the whole thing operates like a solid ring, there is no way, you can get in and do something professional. This place should be inspected by Department of Labor for fair practices</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – not much to say as enough has been said in the cons section. Someone higher up, should really come down and investigate the site before DOL looks at it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-31</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good time”

</title><pros>Pros – great experience, work related technologies are always being explored for new or innovative ways of doing things.</pros>
<cons>Cons – hard to get promoted to senior management levels. Often will hire in management rather than promote from within.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Call Center”

</title><pros>Pros – They will pay you while you train to get your seven and sixty-three license. Paid days off for market holidays.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Call Center environment. Be prepared to feel like you have no control and you are constantly micromanaged. You are not a broker at this place, you are a glorified phone monkey.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – While it is constantly preached to help the client, currently the only thing that matters is identifying clients that have additional assets to bring in.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An educational opportunity that provide valueable experience to carry to a new job.”

</title><pros>Pros – E*Trade was a very polite and respectful place to work, I was happy to be there each day, the pace varied depending on the market conditions/tax season, but it was generally pleasant.</pros>
<cons>Cons – lack of opportunity for advancement from service to a more strategic role.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide more opportunity for movement, lateral or vertical.  The FSR role felt disconnected from the rest of the staff, as if it was undeserving of the respect that a operations role might get.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good place to work as a junior engineer”

</title><pros>Pros – you will learn a lot of  new stuff at the first couple of years.  generally rewards come to people working hard.</pros>
<cons>Cons – sometimes people prefer finger-pointing when the issues come up instead of working together to resolve it.  also the salary level is under industry average.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – reduce the process that make production cycle inefficient.  also should promote people inside company during group reorg instead of bringing new people in.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-23</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Relationship Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Damage Control”

</title><pros>Pros – Managers are typically young since there is a great deal of attrition of employees. Could be a good place to work if you quickly wanted to rise to a branch manager position just to get some experience. Good for entry level. Decent trade platform, and sales technology (salesforce).</pros>
<cons>Cons – Terrible communication to employees, in every aspect, which is carried over to clients.Low compensation, high pressure - compared to industry. Constant damage control, and mixed messages. Long hours are normal in industry, but at ETFC the extra effort doesn't translate to much higher pay. Company often raise sales goals unrealistically high so as not to pay out bonuses. Company has been in financial trouble and getting bad press since 2007.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Communicate better with employees, they understand the company has landed on tough times. But the poor communication does not instill much loyalty, and hence leads to very high attrition and low quality of employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Constantly Experimenting/Screwing with Sales”

</title><pros>Pros – E*TRADE offers a base salary with slightly below average benefits.  You will work 8am to 5pm with optional overtime to increase your bonus and no need to take your work home.  It's pretty hard to get fired in most offices unless you do something dumb or are lazy for an extended period of time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They are constantly experimenting and end up screwing over the consultants in Sales.  They just changed the compensation plan this year and it looks like more than 30% of consultants are getting no bonus for last quarter.  I was in the top 20% and my bonus was only $10k for the whole quarter.  Many people that are in the top 10% just got lucky with one big lead. Don’t plan to make much more than $65k a year unless you are pretty darn good.  If you are amazing you might barely break $100k.  Also the 401k match is an awful 2.5% and they give no salary raises at all, no matter how tenured or good you are.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – If you want to retain top talent don't take away their leads.  Asked your "sales distribution team" or any consultant who hasn't been told by their regional manager to keep their mouth shut; the leads are gone.  The best leads are new accounts, rollovers, and TOAs in, not because those leads are easy money, but because money getting moved in to E*TRADE is the most receptive to advice (mutual funds, MIP, and UMA).  If you want consultants to sell advice don't take away their best leads.Even more importantly, don't take away the best leads and double the number of consultants at the same time.  We are sitting in an office with twice as many people as we had a year ago and none of us have any leads to call and all of us are starting to simmer.  The best of us will be taking jobs at TD, Fidelity, and Schwab in the next year if this crap doesn't change and you will be left with the new people and the underperformers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Improving; Management is working on improving employee satisfaction.”

</title><pros>Pros – Blend of technology and finance industries has potential for diverse career paths. The employee bank account has no charges for ATM withdrawals from any ATM nationally.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company is quite inward looking; slow to pick up industry standards on the technology side, tending more toward in-house innovations. While this has served the company well historically, it  limits the potential for employee growth</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Continue to invest in people (training) to drive innovation. Provide opportunities for employees to visit other departments in order to see the impact their work makes to the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Learned a lot but very little room for growth from position”

</title><pros>Pros – Gained good experienceTraining was excellentColleauges were great</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay was not competive with similar positionsManagement very hands on - leaves no room for autonomy</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Change the entire model to be more in line with competitors and pay more</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Lead (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unrewarding”

</title><pros>Pros – You receive paid training for Series 7 and 63. They have a higher than average pass rate. The last 5 classes have had 100 percent pass rate.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You will receive no feed back what so ever regarding your performance unless you are a phone rep and you screw up.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – REWARD the people who are running your teams!! Bringing in treats to meetings doesnt cut it. You have already lost how many leads? And you refuse to do anything about them leaving.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-05-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good to start you work, but no long term career growth”

</title><pros>Pros – have chance to use new and emergent technology</pros>
<cons>Cons – promotion is hard, quite often they are not base on performance</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – talented ppl are leaving , do something to stop it</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-04-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – room for advancement and promotion opportunities</pros>
<cons>Cons – long hours and frantic pacerude customers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Mediocre at best and silo'ed”

</title><pros>Pros – Most managers at E*TRADE allow some flexible scheduling to balance work-life commitments.  A good employee can easily skate through without much effort.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The employees at E*TRADE are mediocre.Most of the people have worked at the company way too long.Leadership is poor.The pay is toward the bottom of its peers.Projects take too long to complete.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – E*TRADE needs to change and innovate.  The VP ranks really need to be assessed and renewed.  Steven really needs to implement the changes he announced shortly after he arrived.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-03</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's a job...”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits, being asked about the E*TRADE baby when you tell people where it is that you work. Not much else at all.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Promotions and recognition are hard to come by.  Very stressful work environment with constant unreasonable timelines.  Pay is not as good as comparable companies.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to start off to gain some experience but would not recommend for long haul”

</title><pros>Pros – E*trade has a strong culture of innovation and being an industry leader in technology. It has navigated the credit crisis very well and has survived which cannot be said for many larger firms. It has conducted a stellar turnaround and emerged a stronger firm than from where it stood 3 years ago. The people are committed and proud of what they do. There is a culture of ownership and creativity. It is a very good place to learn the business and grow your wings.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The salary structure at E*Trade is significantly below industry standards. Most people make significantly less than they're counterparts at bigger firms.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep doing what you're doing but do not forget that there are several areas where the company can grow and those are being overlooked</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Training Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Started great, but when the stock went from $18 a share to less than $1, the atmosphere was pretty bleak!”

</title><pros>Pros – good people. cooperative. flexible work schedule. nice balance of personal and professional life.</pros>
<cons>Cons – lack of strong management.. a pervasive lack of professionalism.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – promote quality employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Generic”

</title><pros>Pros – Encourage growth and creativity.  The work environment and culture is relaxed, professional and encouraging.  I havent encountered a single instance where I was worried or apprehensive. I could find support in my colleagues and also my manager.</pros>
<cons>Cons – One thing I noticed at the at the particular office I worked was "too much flexibility" in timing. Some folks too the word "flexibility" literally.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I would recommend to encourage more. Ask if the employee wants to do more than whats assigned. Be it new certification or training.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Etrade should definitely be the last option”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefitsFriendly co-workersSocial eventsOpen door policyCan be promoted based on performanceSeveral differenct shifts to choose from</pros>
<cons>Cons – Micro managementfeel like a roboteverything is monitorednothing rewarding about the actual jobhave to deal with rude customers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give employees more room to be creative.  Everything should not be so structured.  If employees were given a little but more breathing room, maybe there wouldn't be such high turnover.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This company does not know what it is doing. Except perhaps looking to sell it to someone else. Not a customer friendly”

</title><pros>Pros – People know the name and commercials.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Little chance for real growth. Very inside boys club have to make friends with others to get some where. And the next "step" is a dead end too, often with no salary bump.Not a customer friendly.Everything is based on "metrics" often with no relation to real efficiency or performance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – They will not care or listen. Very disrespectful to employees and customers. it should stop at some point.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Services Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Salary / Compensation”

</title><pros>Pros – compared to any other call center in manila, somehow you will earn much more working with this company. but work loads is superb, stressful and exhausting and you will end comparing your salary with your counterpart in the US.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1000 pesos per month for your meal allowance? guess it's not enough. my previous work provide 3500 for meal and transpo (jp morgan chase). no hazard pay as well</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – you're really gettin most out of us, doing outbound, inbound, correspondence at the same time. doing back up with other departments but giving us no compensation at all. no quarter/semi annual bonus. annual bonus depends on employee stat but i am not sure if senior managers here are qualified at all. no teambuildings sponsored by the company. no retirement accounts either.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E*TRADE is a good place to learn”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice physical work environments. No weekends. Decent benefits. Not overly difficult. Don't ask for too much.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Variable compensation package is impossible to discern where you should emphasize. It is so complicated nobody it has no impact on productivity. They don't treat people with a whole lot of respect. Very negative environment-always looking for metrics to punish you with rather than reward.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop looking for ways to punish.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-19</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Team Lead, Customer Service (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Supervisory”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy work, flexible hours, opportunities to grow.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow to progress upwards in management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more noticing that our product managers make more bad changes than good changes.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok place to work, not great, not bad”

</title><pros>Pros – Company has flexible working schedule to meet personal issues.  It also has pretty comprehensive benefits package compared to some of the other companies.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Senior management lacks communication with employees.  Some people seem to advance because of their ties with upper management instead of their performance.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to have more open communication with employee and reward those who are deserving instead of people who just have connections with upper management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Relationship Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“AN OK PLACE TO WORK.”

</title><pros>Pros – This is an innovative company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Other tha the trading platforms, other area are archaic.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Each department should be able to take calls for their areas of expertise.  Some RM's cannot explain margin calls- and they can't transfer complicated margin issues to specialists. Use the Fidelity Investments model where each department specialists are thoroughly trained, take calls relating to their areas of expertise. This improves customer satisfaction .</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-10</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good for getting your licenses and learning about the market, that's IT!”

</title><pros>Pros – In Alpharetta, you get sponsored for the Series 7 and 63. Get those licenses and then you're free to go anywhere else in the country and make money. You also get to learn a lot about the market. Also by looking at customers accounts and your calls with them, you see what NOT to do! They are good about letting you take time off EXCEPT for during tax season which is Jan til Apr 15. Sometimes it's not even busy and they say no.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Eliminate the "Command Center." It's a room built in Alpharetta, GA with the sole purpose of micromanaging call center reps. If a rep isn't back on the phone promptly after a phone call, then the Command Center questions the manager of the rep, then the manager questions the Team Lead, then the Team Lead questions the rep. Meanwhile the rep could be busy trying to solve a problem for a customer.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get rid of that whole "Command Center". It's such a joke. Get rid of reps in Manila except to do simple password resets or operations where they don't interact with customers. The customers don't like outsourcing, especially in this economic climate. Also many of the reps in Manila are kind but they are very robotic, sticking totally the script and lacking emotion.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-27</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Benefits”

</title><pros>Pros – The benefits package was excellent compared to other companies I've worked for in the past.  The balance between work and home life is a definate plus.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The opportunities for career advancement are only good if you start out at a higher management level.  Salary is on the low end vs competitors.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Promotions and salary adjustments should be based more on merit rather than tenure.  A lot of employees have left due to lack of career advancement.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unless you bake cookies and feed everyone at work- you won't get anywhere.”

</title><pros>Pros – Semi Stable job, personal trading is limited but not as limited as outside companies, good hours, i would consider outside offers before looking here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No pay increase for over 3 years, bonuses are low, management makes sure you know you are replaceable. Many of my peers hate there job and just stay because of a poor job market.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Review your long term Sr. Managers and above, its club to them and they not only show no respect to anyone below them but they show no respect to each other.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-12-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fair organzation when it comes to promotion”

</title><pros>Pros – Freedom, roll up your sleve attitude, ability to really make a change and have an impact, overall competence of senior management</pros>
<cons>Cons – matrix organization leading to lack of decision taking, need for a bigger and more ambitious vision for the product, lack of customer centricity</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – think global, act local</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>