<name>I-TECH Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/I-TECH-Reviews-E605334.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-02-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate Director (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great opportunity to work internationally”

</title><pros>Pros – Talented team members who are passionate</pros>
<cons>Cons – Senior management are not sensitive to mid management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Respect your employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Amazing colleagues, disappointing changes”

</title><pros>Pros – So many of the program staff here are amazing people. They are hardworking and have substantial experience in international health and development. The work can be very interesting and fulfilling.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I-TECH threw out the baby with the bathwater. The organization is beginning to feel the results of some poor leadership/management decisions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I'd put advice here, but you wouldn't follow it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Management has less experience than staff”

</title><pros>Pros – The work at I-TECH is stimulating and there are many opportunities to work with people around the globe and feel that you are making a difference.</pros>
<cons>Cons – After a process of re-organization that devalued the skills of the technical staff, a new hierarchical country-based management structure was put into place.  This did not reflect skills or years of experience in global health.  In fact, the director has little direct experience in global health.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Find a way to honor and value your technical staff that have the experience and skills that keep this organization running.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>