<name>C-Life Group Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/C-Life-Group-Reviews-E610907.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Modern Day Mac Slave (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“You Can't Polish A Turd...”

</title><pros>Pros – PRO 1: The artists are good talented people but are hindered under Manager's (A.M.) witch-like management methods.PRO 2: Having an hour for lunch to get away from her tyrannical character.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The Manager (A.M.) is one of the worst managers to crawl on this earth. She runs her division in a very draconian fashion, not to mention she has no couth when dealing with her staff. She offers nothing but empty commitments & has the worst spelling EVER! it's easier to decipher Egyptian hieroglyphs - A toddler can spell better than she can.The president is just as ignorant for keeping her on board & he should be ashamed of himself.AVOID WORKING FOR C-LIFE LIKE THE PLAGUE!!!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get rid of the Manager (A.M.)</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“service to a dictatorship”

</title><pros>Pros – Free tshirts, jewish holidays off, great artists at work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – This would be an ideal job for an artist except for the underhanded and malicious ways management treats its artists. Yes, i would strongly not recommend anybody i know to work here. Unless they where desperate enough to go thru the verbal and email abuse. Remembering that their opinion doesn't matter. Like myself and others you always felt like  you where going to be FIRED, an awkward feeling of uncertainty. I guess i could go on about one particular person who is the LAW in this place and carries herself to be above it all. My advice to her is that every porcelain doll eventually BREAKS, very cold, spiteful and will treat you just like a tool. BEWARE!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn how to build a team by becoming a better leader. Management is very hard and difficult to approach.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Computer Monkey (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not at all what I expected.”

</title><pros>Pros – Free T-Shirts, office job, nothing else I can think of.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There was no upward mobility. Basically a computer monkey job. You will have no real creative input in the design of their clothing. Most of what is involved is the placement already created, licensed artwork. Extremely low pay with extremely cramped working space. I was completely misled on my interview and left a secure job for what I thought was a better opportunity. I can partly blame my own inexperience for this.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't be rude and condescending to your employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>