<name>E la Carte Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/E-la-Carte-Reviews-E611146.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-03-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wonderful startup!”

</title><pros>Pros – ELC has the things I find most important: work and life balance, full autonomy, opportunity to learn new skill sets, supportive management, active voice in decision making process, etc.Some other cool perks that definitely matter:-daily lunch is provided-100% of health benefits paid-choose your own computer / reimbursement for device you may already have-bike credit / reimbursement to encourage healthy lifestyle-flexible schedules - option to work from home  and control your work load-open vacation policyIn this type of company environment, I'm much more satisfied and productive (even while working less hours) than I was at my prior employer.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Would like to see the company HQ in SF.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-25</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Company is flailing”

</title><pros>Pros – Company made a cool bet.Bet is not working out.Might still be sold to a restaurant chain, so we may become part of applebees</pros>
<cons>Cons – ceo and executive team treat employees very very very badlylot of turnover</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – employees are not easy to replacevalue them</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-05</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Really cool idea. Not a good place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – - Small startup is appealing- Cool idea that could become industry standard- Some really good people</pros>
<cons>Cons – - CEO & executive team show overall lack of respect for employees- Unbalanced workload- Low compensation (unfulfilled promises for raises/rewards)- Expensive sub-par benefits</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to employees. Ask questions, solicit feedback, find pressure points, and actually care what they say, and do something about it.Same goes for customers; don't try to sell them what you think they want. Listen to what they actually want, and if we can't deliver it, be honest about it.Communicate openly. Be transparent like you say you are.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-29</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“fun and always changing”

</title><pros>Pros – great people, amazing product, lots of variety and responsibility in work, growing rapidly, freedom and results-oriented culture</pros>
<cons>Cons – typical startup stuff, no deal breakers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Marketing”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart and ambitious people, good product concept,</pros>
<cons>Cons – Imbalanced life - worklimited potential to grow</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>