<name>Park 'N Fly Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Park-N-Fly-Reviews-E612195.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Shuttle Driver (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Drive clients to and from parking lot”

</title><pros>Pros – Meeting numerous people from all works of life</pros>
<cons>Cons – Dangerous driving in airport requires extreme defensive driving</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor leadership, poor direction, treats employees poorly”

</title><pros>Pros – Some very loyal and dedicated people at HQ and lots.  Many have stuck around for years.  Lots of potential both technologically and operationally.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The highest level of leadership are lacking in leadership capabilities.  They do not understand the industry very well.  They focus on ideas that have no positive impact on the company.  They lack integrity - they hide their contractor hires from the owners by telling contractors not to come to work on days that the owners are in town.  They cut hours at the lots, decreasing operational capabilities, while hiring additional personnel at the headquarters office.  They treat employees poorly.  Executives consistently email and talk with employees in a threatening and derogatory tone - Often using profanity....  Could easily be considered a hostile work environment.  Financially, the company usually doesn't meet budget under the current leadership.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Relieve yourself.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Operationally defunct!”

</title><pros>Pros – Corporate staff are very nice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Weak operational leadership. COO is actually Director-level of Ops - guess she likes titles. Heavy focus on marketing and customer surveys. Lack of parking industry experience by leadership team to be a real player long-term.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Time the busses! Simple - but effective.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>