<name>M & M's World Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/M-and-M-s-World-Reviews-E614446.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great if you need a fun job while studying”

</title><pros>Pros – If you're looking for a light hearted job with good pay considering it's retail this is a top choice.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Progression into leadership roles are mainly subjected to who you know in management roles or suck up to, rather than credentials.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat everyone the same and you will see more productivity.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK”

</title><pros>Pros – Good salary & benefits at all levels, bonuses can be generous.  Paid weekly.  Lively sales floor environment, good location.</pros>
<cons>Cons – "Cronyism" and blame culture in senior management.Poor communication, competition encouraged over teamwork.Poor performers aren't dealt with, personality valued over contribution.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Lead by example.  Managers should practise what they preach with five principles and ways of working.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“M&M World London not what you think”

</title><pros>Pros – Salary, Benifits, American Management, size</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lazy Upper Management, Favouritism, do not follow the 5 principles that that they preach, Bad atmosphere, backstabbing, if the management dont like you they make you life hell untill you leave or they find a way to fire you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – support everyone not just your favourites</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>