<name>Mark P. Finlay Architects Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Mark-P-Finlay-Architects-Reviews-E625870.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-10-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Young designers beware”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Brand name recongnition in Fairfield County architecture sceneHigh end projects where every detail is addressed.  Construction Document sets are very good.Pays overtime (I think this is CT state law though)</pros>
<cons>Cons – You are merely a pawn here.  Do not be fooled.  The upper management does not care about you at all.  You are a cog, an interchangeable part that has no real worth.  There is no encouragement, support, or incentive for I.D.P. or A.R.E. certification.  In fact, it is kind of a taboo subject to bring up.  Probably because they know they will have to pay you more money once you get licensed.  Annual employee reviews are non-existent.  This is surely to avoid raises also.  The vacation time is pathetically low.  Interest in improving technology and software are non-existent.   Pay is low and will remain low.  This is an actual quote by the President/CEO: "You are all really lucky to be working here for one of the best firms in the world.  There are a lot of people out there that want your job and are willing to do it for less."   Notice that there is a big revolving door at the firm.  People get fed up and then leave for greener pastures.  The staff remains very young and cheap.  That seems to be the business model.  Unfortunately, the projects suffer as a result.   The overall morale is very low.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Might want to start by treating people as if their ideas and input actually matter rather than just a worker drone.  It's tough to want to work hard for someone who you know does not respect you.  A simple thank you for coming in over the weekend or staying late to finish up a last minute change goes a long way.  It's sad that this is too difficult for upper management to muster.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>