<name>C-Net Systems Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/C-Net-Systems-Reviews-E645744.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-12-21</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>IT Professional (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Terrible owner, no room for growth, bad company securities, no benefits”

</title><pros>Pros – 1) The only benefit to this job was that it gave me IT experience to GET OUT and get a better job.</pros>
<cons>Cons – 1) The owner of the company hires in technicians at minimum wage.2) The owner makes promises of raises but always falls through. When you attempt to discuss it with him he abandons the conversation.3) There is no room for growth at all.4) There are no benefits or compensation for hard work.5) I am a security professional; this company stores all client information in a non-encrypted environment in plaintext files.6) The owner will set you aside a project to do with no real end goals. When he comes back to you asking for results it's next to impossible to give him a report as he never laid out what he wanted in the first place.7) The owner tries to setup a "team environment" and even asks for suggestions on how to improve the company. But, when you offer suggestions he'll get mad at you; one suggestion that I made ended with the owner in an out-burst screaming "I have 20 years of experience; I don't need your suggestions!"8) I drafted the companies entire IT security policy. The sad thing was it was a put on for the biggest client; none of the actual policies were enforced.9) The owner of the company called me on my day off (mind you I had taken my girlfriend out for her birthday) yelling and raging at me on the phone because of project he had setup for me to do that he never told me to. These kind of issues occur ALL the time at C-Net; the owner assigns you a project but never communicates that project to you; and then blames you for it flopping when you had no clue you were even assigned to a project!10) When I left two others followed.11) Owner is very greedy, company makes very good profits but owner barely shells out anything for his employees. This explains why the company's growth has stagnated.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – 1) The owner needs to stop setting up false pretenses of mobility.2) The owner is asking for suggestions on improvement; he should then act like a civilized human-being an accept or deny them rather than take them as a personal attack.3) Management needs to secure all of their clients assets and take IT security seriously.4) The owner needs to provide benefits, health-care coverage, and a competitive salary.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>