<name>G-Stage Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/G-Stage-Reviews-E648018.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-03-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Administrative Assistant”

</title><pros>Pros – Provided catered meals for workers, everyday of the week.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No communication between management and co-workers. Co-workers were extremely disrespectful and immature, yet management never even attempted to intervene. No benefits.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need better communication and adaptability skills.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Key Operations (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible company to work for. You wont go anywhere but out the door.”

</title><pros>Pros – Music is awesome. Clothes are adorable. Girls that you work with are great. If you just want a part time job and can afford to spend your money on the clothes, I guess this is the place for you. You do get 10% off, that's it. If you get on the managers good side you'll have fun and be given great hours, but at the expense of the rest of the crew hating on you. I was able to move up quick and then out as fast as I could get another job opportunity.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is Terrible. They range from the micromanaging spectrum or unable to control their employees. Upper management is despicable. Don't think about asking for certain days off. And if management doesn't like you or the way you work you will get hours cut, giving you the hint to quit. Training is not up to par. You are basically thrown on the floor and told to sink or swim. So if you are not familiar in the sales environment this is not the place to start. NONE of the clothes are USA made. we get all the clothes shipped from Asia, I know because it smells like its been on a boat And the owner is a penny pinching tyrant He watches the cameras EVERY DAY and if he sees something he does not like he will call into the store and YELL at you. Yes, I was yelled at twice. They don't hire a cleaning crew, YOU are the cleaning crew. If there were stains made by customers we were to wash all garments in the back BATHROOM and put them back on the floor. This company treats its employees like dirt. It sees them as replaceable objects, so if you have a problem they wont change, they'd rather get rid of you and keep with the program. There is no room for advancement. Trust me, you hear that yes they have great opportunities and you can do this and this. WRONG. Yes, you can go from sales, to cashier, to key holder, to assistant MAYBE. VERY FEW have gone higher. The pay sucks. You have to think about it. Your working with 20 or so other girls. They ALL want to move up. there are probably only 2 Lead cashiers, and based on seniority, is how you move up. But luckily for some, the high turnover rate and constant firing or quitting of employees you might get to move up. The turnover rate is so bad, that they recycle name badges from old employees and just put a sticker over with your name. Remember this is a Korean owned and operated business. It is very strict, very demanding, and very rude. Honestly if you have never worked for Koreans, your in for a treat.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Maybe if you valued your associates more you wouldn't have such a high turnover rate. If you get into this company at the corporate level I guess you might be better off. There is no room</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Positive”

</title><pros>Pros – Friendly enviroment to work in</pros>
<cons>Cons – not enough hours to acheive</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – be on top of your game</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>