<name>John W. Danforth Co. Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/John-W-Danforth-Co-Reviews-E649288.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-29</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Intern Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – * Not having to sit at a desk all the time* Learned many people skills - especially when I dealt with other contractors* Supervisor was fun and energetic, while helping me to learn varied skills* Company always trying to do better</pros>
<cons>Cons – * Nothing bad to say about this employer* Only thing I have to say, but it is not actually a con, is that they are in somewhat of a business freeze right now due to the economic conditions of our country - which means no hiring for new jobs</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-07</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Big private local company that makes employees feel as if they are disposable”

</title><pros>Pros – Well established company that has a big market share in the western new york area. A good stepping stone for new college graduates looking to get into the industry because they know they can pay you under fair market value.  Always opportunities to learn new things. Good first job for a couple years, then move on.  The benefits here are about average with any company this size, but the compensation is much to be desired.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some coworkers are personal brown nosers to upper management just to get ahead at your expense, you will find out who they are rather quickly. Due to this inter-company gossip culture, it can be used advantageously and allows one to find out many things that the uppers don't want the outer circle to know. Dealings behind the scene occur regularly. You will put 50+ hours a week in and not be compensated appropriately. You can be compensated more elsewhere with 1/2 the headaches if you have the experience. If your not part of a select inner circle, you don't matter. If you make too much money at your position and they can find a cheaper replacement, they will. Almost no company loyalty. A great majority of employees have been with the company less than 5 years should speak for itself. Long term future is reserved for the select inner circle, it almost doesn't matter how well your job performance is, unless you brown nose.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The  gruff fist pounding - "your lucky to have a job and be grateful for that" speech is not effective at motivating employees. It does quite the opposite and creates employee resentment. We work hard to make your millions and it is you who should be grateful. There are a lot of current employees that are unsatisfied due to this approach that are looking to go elsewhere or start a business to take your market share. Do your business a favor and reevaluate your current approach on motivating employees. Upper management micro-manages and creates too much "busy work", it is great to have continual improvement, but not at the expense of supervising jobs and bringing in revenue. Keep project management easy, not a 7 page "to do" list.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>