<name>J. Fitzgerald Group Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/J-Fitzgerald-Group-Reviews-E651889.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-11-10</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Communications Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great People. Fun Agency. Great Work.”

</title><pros>Pros – The office is very fun and creative, and filled with talented, and interesting people. The pub in the basement and the terrace overlooking the famous Erie Canal makes this office very unique. The owners are very passionate about doing great work and growing their business in the right directions.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Reputation of being small, but their trying to fix that.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Look Elsewhere”

</title><pros>Pros – Beautiful building on the canal, a pub in the basement, kind colleagues, bright atmosphere, plenty of parking, overall safe area in quaint town.</pros>
<cons>Cons – While at this firm, I observed unprofessional behavior, such as chronic negativity and emotional outbursts by leadership. Often, employees were on edge, under a controlling management style. Employees were fired with no mention to staff, several employees were distressed and unhappy. Intolerance was shown as was disregard for individual needs/styles. Many employees resigned. Once an employee left the company, they were shunned. Despite the large size of the building, employees were seat-assigned (and moved when told to, without regard to whether they wanted to) back-to-back in small open areas with no privacy, while larger spaces went unoccupied. And the whole "game room" you see on the website? That's just for show. Benefits were minimal.Raised voices, upset ranting and outbursts were supposed to be "nothing to worry about", "you get used to it", and "it's just the way they are." Not in my world.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – First: walk and talk slower. This will lead you to a calmer sense and professional demeanor. Don't approach people when you're angry or upset. Stop. Think. Then speak. Then listen.You've forgotten the golden rule. It is said that you can't change what you don't acknowledge.Start by recognizing that for one, you have an employee retention problem and discover the reason. It is not that you just haven't formed the "right" team yet, you've allowed good, talented, creative and hard-working people to leave, without asking for the truth: why did they leave?Here are some observations: they were not treated professionally, belittled, micromanaged, not treated with dignity, and saw no way of resolving these issues. Here is the scenario: they rationalized the first time, forgave the second time, made excuses the next time, and eventually saw the repetitious pattern of negative behavior and decided this was a poor investment of time in their career.Try to understand the root cause of the above and seek help and advice for improvement.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>