<name>K-Rain Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/K-Rain-Reviews-E651186.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-26</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Management (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unprofessional and disorganized.  Poor leadership, and future unclear.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great location to work, close to beaches.  Nice weather all year round.  Some corporate employees are nice, professional and helpful.  Talented and dedicated middle  & executive management.   Salary is competitive and benefits are good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Family owned business with poor-to-nonexistent leadership.  Future plans for growth totally unclear.  The majority of long-time employees are unhelpful or provide obstacles to improvement initiatives and block competing ideas.  Pro-activity, professionalism and planning is often met with ridicule, as chaos is the preferred method of operation.  Bullying happens frequently and is tolerated by ownership.   Aging infrastructure, with very little investment in facilities and employees.  Frequent pay cuts, including a default to a 4-day workweek when sales targets are not met.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good start-up, but not a long term career builder.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great office location, near Palm Beach, Florida. Extremely talented and motivated professionals, from top-management to production.  Limited but top of the line quality products. High moral family standards. Good people with good working habits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Small family owned company with a very informal management style.  Poor leadership and unclear future growth plans. Reduced or non-existing outside sales team.  Non innovative manufacturer, invests little on product development or new technology. Has eliminated over the past 4 years all US manufacturing and assembly jobs, transferring 100% of the production to Dominican Republic Extremely prone to propose 4 day work weeks to reduce costs, damaging employee moral. No bonus package offered, as well as no matching 401K compensation by employer.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>