<name>Charles H. Wright Museum Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Charles-H-Wright-Museum-Reviews-E656750.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great collections and a good workforce; however, management misses opportunities to shine.”

</title><pros>Pros – The Wright Museum is accomplishing a great deal of its mission - to educate and inspire its community. The museum has great collections, exhibitions, events, tours, and educational programming. Its staff reaches out to surrounding cultural organizations and is constantly striving to be relevant to its patrons and community. The building is beautiful and facility rentals are booming.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Because of the financial health of the city, the museum has lost a great deal of its economic base and must sometimes suffer reductions in its ability to serve. This means that its deserving workers cannot be properly remunerated or seek professional development and advancement in their fields. Great workers move on, remaining workers shoulder extra work, and the museum increasingly depends upon volunteers and interns. Institutional memory and continuity are at stake. There is not enough emphasis on black voices of community and internal routine and procedure.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work with and know every employee, volunteer, and intern and his or her job. Create more efficient workflows that actually follow the manuals; and if there are no manuals or procedures, collaborate with affected departments to create the best possible procedures.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-02</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Information Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The Wright Museum has great potential and could be a star in Detroit's crown.”

</title><pros>Pros – The collections are wonderful, as are the staff and the Detroit community that uses the collections and come to see the exhibitions and enjoy the programming.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Worries over funding and continued employment steal the joy. More directed advertising and collaboration needed within the Southeast Michigan area.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more open to staff and community's ideas, and start a community announcement page on the website.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>