<name>Hi-P International Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Hi-P-International-Reviews-E660366.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Mechanical Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Moderate career advancement, little benefits”

</title><pros>Pros – Exposure to mobile device technology, high end customers</pros>
<cons>Cons – No career advancement, uncertain direction of company and future</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to listen more to all level of employees, strengthen the HR team</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Project Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good pay, but no life”

</title><pros>Pros – The company, especially in manufacturing subsidiary, pay high bonus during good time.</pros>
<cons>Cons – There is no life balance in the company. 50% of your job is out of the job description.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please change the company culture especially in grading the performance.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bad and stringy company”

</title><pros>Pros – Can't find much about the pros</pros>
<cons>Cons – Stringy. bad culture, bad people</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be more generous</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Listed Company, Family Feel”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy access to top management and generally good positioning in market.  Employee culture (staff to staff) is generally good and salaries are competitive.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Complex politics centered on gaining the trust and ear of top management.  Although Company is listed, it is run like a family run enterprise.  Sales and Operations don't gel together. Constant change of management team means staff are disillusioned most of the time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep top management and get a better lot of managers.  Stop listening to only a few people.  set up a real top class management team and let go of the reins.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>