<name>Richard D. Hatch & Associates Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Richard-D-Hatch-and-Associates-Reviews-E660636.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-02-14</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall not a bad place to work, good boss, no chance for growth.”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice mild mannered boss with vast knowledge of antiques and collectibles, that was freely shared. Great learning experience. Stayed in nice hotels and usually ate at nice restaurants. Normally quiet environment. Met and interacted with any and all people. Fair and honest dealings by owner, good integrity.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If the definition of insanity is doing the same thing over and over again and expecting different results, this is the place. Very little freedom or input in decision making concerning betterment of the company. Difficult to build trust. Micro-managing to the extreme. One salary adjustment in almost 5 years, although much better profitability was obvious. Owner seemed to care more about the 'thrill of the hunt' and acquiring 'things' than taking care of hardworking, trustworthy, knowledgeable  and caring employees. Continuing education was available, as long as it didn't interfere with the opportunity to make more money, or get more 'stuff'. No recognition for going above and beyond on a consistant basis (e.g. working several weeks in a row with no days off), and certainly no 'extra' reward in your paycheck, no matter if you worked 50, 60 or even 70 hours per week. As stated, good guy but a terrible manager, with quite possibly a hoarding problem.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take better care of your people! Not only listen to good ideas by your employees, but integrate, take action, see if the ideas work better for yourself before dismissing. Better recognition and reward.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>