<name>D-Link Systems Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/D-Link-Systems-Reviews-E666355.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall a good experience”

</title><pros>Pros – They value hard workThey are larger and more stable than you might thinkCo-workers are friendly, helpful, and very knowledgeable</pros>
<cons>Cons – Need a path for advancementRaises don't happen</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide a path for advancement for existing employees instead of looking outside</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“D-Link Systems -  Driving via Rear View Mirror”

</title><pros>Pros – Great peopleGood TechnologyGreat PotentialCould be innovativeCould be a market leader</pros>
<cons>Cons – Does not want to changeBad HabitsLeads with priceShip it and fix it later mentalityWill not listen to their people</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop and fix the problemsShip quality productsMake sure their is a large enough marketIts not the price - It's the product</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to grow your career”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people, talented technical staff</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay is low to moderate,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Upgrade pay to reflect what the competition is offering.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Mismanagement costs the market”

</title><pros>Pros – Many good people to work with. Opportunities to learn how business works in a very competitive market in all aspects. Part of global company with fundamentals.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The management team missed the direction (couple times) and lost the market share, and they didn't listen. The internal communication across department and/or head quarters sometimes not too good.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop putting the head in the sand.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>