<name>D-Star Engineering Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/D-Star-Engineering-Reviews-E671632.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Creative environment beyond anything.”

</title><pros>Pros – D-Star Engineering Company is a “missing link” in the corporate America. If you ever wonder where the brilliant designs come from, this is the place. You will not experience ridged time schedules and prompt observed milestones in such a place and many engineers are uncomfortable with that.I find it to be a privilege to be working at D-Star Engineering. This company is promoting creativity and development way more than any other company I worked for. Normally you find a “development” project to be nothing more than a repeat of what was done before. Here, ideas are many times wild and frequently ends in a dead-end, but that is how the great inventions were created.At D-Star you are free to develop things your way. The boss is a promoter of free thinking and creative solutions. It is the same spirit that made USA what is was during the 20th century. We see today a decline in the US business due to the doldrums among developers and designers. Risk-taking is a bad word. Not so at D-Star.If you want to work in a place there brilliance and creativity is appreciated, D-Star is the place for you.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Can be depressing when things don't work out as expected. You work long hours to end up with nothing or something that doesn't work as expected.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I think adhering to time schedules a little more would enhance the operation. We sometimes work too much on the small details.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-16</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Waste of potential”

</title><pros>Pros – Possibility of fulfilling work, pleasant and competent co-workers, flexible hours, fruit baskets abundant</pros>
<cons>Cons – Employees are used as scapegoats when projects fail even though they possess no authority or decision-making responsibilities whatsoever.  Complex problems are watered down and in-depth analysis is eschewed in favor of 0th order, one dimensional spreadsheet calculations.  Occasionally valid analysis is outsourced to contractors only to have the results discarded if they do not validate a priori expectations.  A potential employee would be wise to research public documents, perhaps sbir.gov, and ask management about the success and outcomes of each project during a job interview.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn from your critics.  Not everything is a personal attack.  We all know Einstein's definition of insanity.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-25</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“D-Star is a poor company to work for.”

</title><pros>Pros – Work is interesting, co-workers are great,  boss is not.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The owner of D-Star Engineering is a micromanager, manipulative, and his management style is passive aggressive.  He makes all the decisions and then will blame you when they don't work.  You will get fired, laid off, or you will quit on your own.  Do not work for this company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your people.  You don't know everything and it shows.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>