<name>Radix Engenharia e Software Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Radix-Engenharia-e-Software-Reviews-E678982.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-04-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great place to work, but still with much to learn”

</title><pros>Pros – -lots of extra activities organized by the employer-chance to grow professionally, because the company is small-many challenges-since it won the prize of "Best Place to Work in Rio de Janeiro", it is getting a good reputation</pros>
<cons>Cons – -no profit sharing since the company is still beginning to grow-inexperienced people are getting management positions</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Implement promotion on merit as soon as possible. It isn't motivating to work a lot and earn as much as someone who works very little.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very nice place to work but can be frustrating.”

</title><pros>Pros – The best of working here is you get to participate in many different projects and learn a lot. It's a very dynamic and exciting enviroment. You also have flexible hours and people are very friendly.</pros>
<cons>Cons – For me, the greatest con is that no matter how hard you work, you don't get bonuses for this and there is a lot of people that does not work as hard and get paid more that you do just for beeing here for longer, or for being older (which is even worse). It is very frustrating and desmotivating.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You should really take meritocracy serious and stop being so tolerante to people that does not do a good job. This is frustrating for people who work hard and does not get rewarded for that.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>