<name>Wiley X Sunglasses Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Wiley-X-Sunglasses-Reviews-E680079.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-16</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company”

</title><pros>Pros – Owners willing to listen to employees for suggestions and ideas. Good pay scale</pros>
<cons>Cons – Dependent on government work for domestic business</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get more training for sales staff</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-11</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company”

</title><pros>Pros – I disagree with the person above.  I don't know what department they worked in but I don't feel unappreciated or not trusted nor do I know of anyone who feels that way.  I think it's a good place to work and everyone seems happy there, and that is a nice environment to be in.</pros>
<cons>Cons – None.  I think a poor attitude will get you poor results.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Executive (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Like being on a hamster wheel, always on edge and never felt appreciated.”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits and able to leave the job at work</pros>
<cons>Cons – Micro managed too much, small company family ran, management won't delegate. Mistrust in the employees. Lack of brand name; has a tough time competing against the more well-known brands. Success in firm entirely dependent on who you know and how long you been there.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Recommendation is to stop selling your souls</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>