<name>Babies R Us Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Babies-R-Us-Reviews-E683121.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-22</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great part time job. Enjoyed chatting with the babies and their grandma's”

</title><pros>Pros – Enjoyed helping all the grandmothers shopping for their grand children.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay was not the greatest.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Employee discount should be more than 10%</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-30</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It was a cool job”

</title><pros>Pros – The customers are great people!</pros>
<cons>Cons – The hours aren't that great.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Unrealistic work loads”

</title><pros>Pros – Great work atmosphere - fulfilling work - ability to learn alot both in retail and about things necessary for babies</pros>
<cons>Cons – Crazy heavy work load - high expectations - no room to grow in company - long shifts - need to do research on items sold in stores on own time to be able to sell them -</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Avoid giving employees more than one task from different managers, expecting them all to be accomplished.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-09</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“not a pleasant experience”

</title><pros>Pros – made a lot of good friends within the year that I was there.</pros>
<cons>Cons – pay was horrible, customers were even worse.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I loved working there.”

</title><pros>Pros – People I worked with were amazing</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay was not great.. Raises once a year.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-16</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“very nice”

</title><pros>Pros – nice people and helpful co-workers</pros>
<cons>Cons – less hours and less money</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – balance in sales and hours</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-22</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Department Supervisor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“department supervisor”

</title><pros>Pros – Providing customer service for pregnant women and new mothers, most of whom are very happy and excited and you get to share that joy, as well as your experience and advice.  Co-workers were great, hard working, and friendly people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Completely unrealistic work load  expectations,unreasonably high goals for loyalty cards, credit cards, protection plans etc, and as a department supervisor, I was not only held accountable for my own goals, but those of all team members durring my "GSL" shift which was a 2 hour, twice a day shift where you walked around the store, "motivating" team members to push the protection plans, loyalty cards etc. Management was rude to the point of unprofessional.  The store I worked in was brand new, after the 1st year of being open, there was 100% turnover.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The customer is actually turned off by the many pushy questions at check out, seriously, NO ONE needs a protection plan for a dvd.  When you have 100% turn over in one year, take that as a sign you are doing something wrong.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Typical retail work”

</title><pros>Pros – My co workers were very friendly, the job itself was pretty easy, just your typical retail job. Everyone was very understanding.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The air didn't work very well and it was a hot summer, other than that it was a good place to work at.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poow work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Good discount, can be used on discontinued items</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long hours, poor training, lack of leadership</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-31</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Babies R' Us is a decent place to work if your staring off. Pretty easy work, working truck can get tiring at times.”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy work when not working truck. Friendly atmosphere.</pros>
<cons>Cons – $8.00 an hr with 10-25 cent raises. No recognition, Managers play favorites when it comes down to new positions opening, no more than 30hrs a week. Hard labor when working truck hence bad pay for whats expected in a short amount of time.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Managers get 40hrs a week, not fair to others who been there for years and only get 32. at least 10.00hr for people working truck its technically warehouse work. working hard and waking up at 4am.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-18</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Price Sign Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Price Sign Coordinator”

</title><pros>Pros – Staff is very friendly and make you feel like part of an extended family.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Managers are very knit-picky but yet they don't know a lot about the store themselves. They have really high expectations and will write you up for the littlest mistakes. Getting a promotion is a waste of time. They will just set you up to fail.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – TRAIN PROPERLY. Don't expect to get a 100% from your employees after showing them the very basic parts of their job.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company for the most part”

</title><pros>Pros – Typical retail career opportunity, able to adjust your shift according to your personl needs (children)...but you need to work weekends and a couple nights a week.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No hours allowed at X-mas season...you will be assisting in TRU. hard to keep moral upTraining is terrible- mostly self lead</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Can be political...DM's need to be SM's before promoted to the DM position</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Terrific WISH I never LEFT!”

</title><pros>Pros – Management knew everything and my store manager was always willing to help out. I got promoted 3 times with in 2 years.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I ended up being asked if I wanted to work at the local toys r us store.... I should've stayed at Babies R Us.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Perhaps you should hire more management like those at babies r us for the rest of the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Baby Registry Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“The corporation itself has good values and employee support but they need better trained management.”

</title><pros>Pros – The company usually does a good job of filtering employees.  They also provide employees with great product knowledge and encourage (require) monthly tests to make sure everyone is up-to-date with the products they encounter during their workday.</pros>
<cons>Cons – While the company offers a decent benefits package for full time employees, the salaries (I feel) were not correspondent with work performance.  Also, a lot of the management (at least at the location where I worked) was incompetent.  They made it obvious who their favorites were and used their power and bias to help the employees they prefer.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – There needs to be a better management training system in place and the people chosen for management positions should be considered more closely.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-31</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Registry Consultant/Cashier (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Best job yet :)”

</title><pros>Pros – -Very friendly co workers and staff. Work around babies. Fun job. Great managers. Laidback but with a backbone. Get to see the new moms come in</pros>
<cons>Cons – None! I honestly love my job.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – We should get paid more but it is what it is</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Baby Registry”

</title><pros>Pros – None that I can think of</pros>
<cons>Cons – Learn on your own no help from management or coworkers. Throw you in and expect you to know.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Train your employees and maybe you wont have so much turnover</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Cashier/Back of House (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall a good place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Where I work we are like family.There are a lot of cute babies and we get too watch them grow up.Team members help one another and compliment one anothers work performance to the managers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – If you aren't a supervisor you don't work full-time. Some of us work only 15 hours a week, some even less. The pay could be better, especially if you have worked there for several years.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – For upper management get out of the office and spend at least a month working, actual work on the floor as a cashier as a part-time associate would and see how things go.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>