<name>E-View 360 Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/E-View-360-Reviews-E689362.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-06-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Generall supportive”

</title><pros>Pros – As long as the client is happy my boss is happy - pretty simple.  I have always been treated fairly and rewarded for good work.  Most of  the folks there are pretty friendly and  have always been helpful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I am remote from HQ and don't always a good read on what is going on within the company - This is mainly due to my assignment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-11</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No communication”

</title><pros>Pros – Good opportunity for new skills and knowledge.  Very little over-the-shoulder management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lied about starting salery.  Vastly underpaid for the work I do.  I work remotely and have absolutly no communication with the office and have no idea what is going on there.  No effort is made to communicate with off-site.  Very tight on the purse strings.  No chance for any advancement.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“EView has a nice atmosphere, but as a business is not concerned with employees”

</title><pros>Pros – Great physical environment, relaxed, good peers</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lied about starting salery, very tight on the purse strings</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>