<name>Mama Mimi's Take 'N Bake Pizza Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Mama-Mimi-s-Take-N-Bake-Pizza-Reviews-E700173.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-07-15</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Family biz that needs some work”

</title><pros>Pros – - Some wonderful co-workers, and the family in charge seem like great people- No corporate BS- Real connection to the community- Food/ingredient quality fantastic, and you get a free pizza with every shift!</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Instead of other operating costs, employee hours are where costs are cut, and raises are a thing of the past unless you luck out and get a management position.- Your schedule will be highly variable and there could be weeks you work 50 hours, followed by weeks you work 15.- Lower-level employees are more often than not where blame for poor sales goes, with no regard for management or external factors.- If you can work at multiple stores, you could end up being tossed around quite a bit, and it gets exhausting.- Applicants are not always the best choices, and favoritism is practiced for friends of the family.- Passive-aggressive management techniques like cutting hours are employed when issues arise, or even if an employee is considered fired.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Things have changed a lot in the past year. I think your own policy of "back to the basics" would do this company a WORLD of good, at the level of managers and owners. Your employees bust their butts for you and many still love the company, but they aren't getting what they deserve for it. The frequent small raises that Jodi would give for good service and increased responsibilities (becoming a shift leader, keyholder, opener/closer) would do a WORLD of good to make your workers feel appreciated and motivated to stick around and CONTINUE busting their butts. Mama Mimi's has the potential to continue to be a bright, beautiful part of the community, but if employees continue to be the area where money and concern is slashed, I don't see the company or its vision sustaining itself. Even something as simple as closing one slow day out of the week could give you the money you need to dedicate to what really matters: your customers and your employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>