<name>F-Secure Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/F-Secure-Reviews-E7178.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2008-06-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Fellow (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Place to Work!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Company to work for</pros>
<cons>Cons – none that are major issues</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An Ok environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Perks are ok and colleagues</pros>
<cons>Cons – Senior Management long decision time</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Quality Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A good company to work with”

</title><pros>Pros – - good working environment- helpful colleagues- attract to advance technology</pros>
<cons>Cons – - decision making is slow</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – reduce some management layer to increase decision making time</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-30</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Development Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Devlopment Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – An international working environment, with interesting technology. Also a good work / life balance. Rather good benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – F-Secure is still rather much a anti-virus company focused on the PC / Desktop. The desktop market is declining, so new products need to be launch successfully (which is happening at the moment).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep finding new interesting business. Keep the startup mentality.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company”

</title><pros>Pros – Knowledgeable, friendly, helpful people. World-leading technology, interesting projects. Comfortable work place.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management could be more motivating and supporting. Decision making sometimes too slow.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-12</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Expert (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good working environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Everyone is friendly and employees help each other.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some of departments are exhausting.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Follow up exhausted people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-28</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Quality Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“This company truly cares for it's employees.”

</title><pros>Pros – Smart and generally affable coworkers. Interesting projects to work on. Mostly solid management. Decent benefits and good working hours. Amazing dedication to the wellbeing of their employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Decision making can be slow and heavy. Featuritis is sometimes apparent. Bad decisions made by other people in the past can sometimes haunt you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-13</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Product Management (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Working for a growing European and global safety company”

</title><pros>Pros – Still human size, quick to change, working close to the real it development, lots of talented people.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not so much if you are committed and volunteer.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Localization Coordinator (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good company”

</title><pros>Pros – nice working environment, good care of employees</pros>
<cons>Cons – Cannot think of any, all is good</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Fellowship”

</title><pros>Pros – Easygoing, youthful athmosphere. Strong fellowship.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Senior management positions dealt out to the "insiders".</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-11-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Channel Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good opportunities”

</title><pros>Pros – Target driven environment without the extra pressure of American managers</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not enough independence of local offices on some matters from Head Office</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More cross-functional/cross countries teams to direct new projects</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-09-28</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Quality Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Professionalism and Freedom to solve problems”

</title><pros>Pros – Developers and Testers here are motivated and professional. Many are passionate about their jobs and about improving themselves. There is great freedom to improve processes and products on your own. Innovation is appreciated and rewarded. The people are really what makes this a fantastic place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The virus protection industry as a whole is having some problems. Some of the old guard is set in their ways and have difficulty accepting change.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – motivate managers to spend more time interacting with their direct reports. One-to-Ones should be at least a monthly thing.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stable company but there's not enough investment in exciting new technology”

</title><pros>Pros – Good people, easy to communicate with management and product managers etc.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Innovation and product dev is lacking in some areas, need to do more to grow footprint.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Increase investment in innovation</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-11</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Scrum Master (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place but bureaucratic at times”

</title><pros>Pros – Can voice opinionsFun workmatesGood working conditions</pros>
<cons>Cons – Direction of company is not so clear at timesdecision making is slownot very good pay</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – delegate responsibility</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-24</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Software Engineer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Professional Environment”

</title><pros>Pros – F-Secure has very skilled and experienced world-class people. It is a great place to grow and the salaries compare well within the Helsinki area for similar jobs. There are also many different units starting from research like malware protection and analysis jobs ranging up to more common backend and client side development.</pros>
<cons>Cons – F-Secure is very stable and a bit stagnant company. The revenue and head count is growing constantly but slowly. For people looking for fast growth and ever-changing challenges the company environment might be too boring.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-12-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“not so busy and not so motivative”

</title><pros>Pros – not so busy and good at work life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – not so motivative to work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more focus on products/services</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>