<name>N-Tech Technologies Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/N-Tech-Technologies-Reviews-E733162.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Developer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Worst company i saw ever”

</title><pros>Pros – During my work period i didn't find any good reason to work at this company except you are helpless and not have any other option.</pros>
<cons>Cons – I am past employee of this company and want to share some facts.No systematic work. Projects are taken without feasibility study or discussion.Deadlines decided by a non technical person who is not even aware with fundamentals of project.Extremely unrealistic deadlines.Extreme insecurity of job as company fired around 35 people in just 1 year due to one reason or another. A team of 3 python developers fired without notice and strong reason.Company does not care for employees.No saturday off. You have to work till 9 PM to 10 PM. No leaves. Not even a single public holiday. Only fake promises to set those holidays to somewhere else.Nothing like management hierarchy.No scope for learning new things. For team of python programmers in company no senior person is there. You are at your own risk. You can be fired just for slight lake of performance. A senior iphone developer was fired only because he picked a phone call and started conversation when he was with ceo.Rigid management. No room for suggestions from employees to improve the system.Freshers are recruited at a very low compensation as a trainee but no training is given and no guidance is provided. Freshers have to bear a lot of work burden.No scope for onsite assignments in future.Lot of company politics. You have to work hard just to survive in company even if you are good at your work.No Work/Life balance. If you are hired at this company, it behaves like it owns you.My advice is to choose this company to work if you don't have any other option.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – make employees feel secure. don't fire them like you did. don't behave like you own them. if they will be dissatisfied you will lose your projects and in turn image and reputation of company. make some realistic deadline for projects.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>