<name>David J. Joseph Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/David-J-Joseph-Reviews-E7366.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-12-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great people to work with”

</title><pros>Pros – Great people to work with and flexibility with projects, get to work with a number of technologies and management values input/opinion. Great company values.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation could have been a bit better, but is adequate..</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-07</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good post college company to start with.”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent salary post college to start with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upward mobility is severely limited due to minimal managerial opportunities.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-09</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“DJJ”

</title><pros>Pros – Great selection process for people.  Workplace was fantastic and depending upon business unit, totally competent staff.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management skills training needed as there were some issues.  HR and Management need to work more in hand with employees if issues arise.  Trading and Operations were always at odds to work together and be profitable.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Spend some time looking into the process of evaluation of employees if managers see need for improvement or changes to current process.  Reviews and discussions must be made to fix issues before they escalate.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-17</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good Company”

</title><pros>Pros – Good company, good group of people</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes too conservative, opportunities for growth can be limited</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take some chances</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-13</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Salary”

</title><pros>Pros – The company is very well organized.</pros>
<cons>Cons – You have no control over where you are located.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>BUYER (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“poor senior leadership- yard level managers strong”

</title><pros>Pros – good insurance,salary,communicatios,ability to service customers is outstanding strongest in florida</pros>
<cons>Cons – disrespectful upper management, uneasiness of status in the company felt by all</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be willing to look at yourselves and stand up to the ones who are nasty to underlings no matter how much experience they have- treating your employees well is better in the long run</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>