<name>Swarovski Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Swarovski-Reviews-E8853.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-10-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Love the product. Not the management.”

</title><pros>Pros – This is a great place to shop for jewelry and gifts. The product is very good and the competition is minimal making sales very easy.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The management is so weird here. They really are more concerned about who you know, and what brand shoes are on your feet than whether you can do your job well. Many of their limited opportunities for career advancement are filled based on favoritism, not skill and reputation.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop the favoritism! On all levels! The bonus structure is pathetic and the employee perks, like the discount is laughable when compared to other similar brands.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-11</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Store Manager”

</title><pros>Pros – Opportunities to create an unparalleled consumer experience for a remarkable family owned company</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of succession planning and long term career growth opportunities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bad communication between corporate and the stores and unrealistic goals!”

</title><pros>Pros – The pay and benefits were very good.  The products are gorgeous!</pros>
<cons>Cons – I was actually paid well for my position and at first was very enthusiastic about Swarovski.  After doing very well for several years and making g large increases in sales, the company continued to set extremely high and impossible goals to reach.  Even when it was obvious the goals were way too high and the store was making last years numbers, they continued to set these pie in the sky goals and putting so much pressure on you and at the same time, never listening or asking you what inventory the store needed.  There was no control or input over inventory at the store level. Now they are replacing experienced managers with younger ones, so that they can pay less money.  In the end their business will suffer!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Make the sales plan realistic!  Ask your managers for feedback about products needs.  Hire people who are experienced  and actually know how to relate to others!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exploitation”

</title><pros>Pros – - Sometimes there are good coworkers- Enjoy admiring the shinny products</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Long hours working alone- Not able to clock out for lunch because you need to work by yourself- Being blamed for not being able to prevent thieves when you're the only person working in the store</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - Abide by the law and don't exploit workers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Crystal Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Beautiful enviornment”

</title><pros>Pros – Getting paid every single week!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unrealistic sales goals, short staffing results in being left on the sales floor for hours.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – ...</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Used to be a great company to work for”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice, luxury environment and the products are of great quality.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They expect too much of their managers and staff.  They have unrealistic sales expectations and have too many things going on at a time.  They also do not pay well at any level yet expect their part-timers and full-timers to do many things that are above their pay grade.  There is so much pressure to do everything but the resources and assistance isn't there to help you.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't have so many programs, projects, etc. going on at one time.  It takes us away from selling but we're still required to meet unrealistically high sales plans.  Also, pay your part-timers, full-timers, and managers more.  You are asking them to do so much and "take ownership" but with everything you're asking them to do, they simply don't get paid enough.  I lose so many GOOD associates because I can't match the pay of other companies or I can't give them a full--time position because my store is too low volume to have a full-timer in it.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pretty straightforward job with obtainable goals.”

</title><pros>Pros – Nice staff, helpful training materials</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slow industry, more female oriented</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-24</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Beautiful products, not so beautiful work environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Employee discount from 35- 50 %Lovely crystal designs</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unrealistic sales goalsManagers under extreme pressure to meet goalsLong hours on your feet, no chairs to sitNo commissions</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Senior management/ Corporate needs to take into account the location of the store & put less pressure on store mangers. No incentive to meet goals with zero commissions and unrealistic sales goals.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Sales Associate - Providence RI”

</title><pros>Pros – Was fun in the beginning</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low paysmall group of sales people you work withCranky -entitled customerCrappy product that breaks easilyNo work life balance</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees we know what the customers want</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-28</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Functions as Wholesale Company and not a Retail Company”

</title><pros>Pros – long history, family-owned, devoted customer following, allows for independent atmosphere at times, strong product quality, diverse range of learning opportunities and responsibilities</pros>
<cons>Cons – very limited upward mobility, company sets unattainable goals while poorly stocking their stores, very poor work/life balance for full-time staff, declining taste in product design, poor assortment of available products in individual stores with limited access for stores to receive these products for their customers, prefers company's benefit rather than satisfying customers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Install experienced business people in upper management and corporate level experience with proven track records of how to run successfully functioning retail companies; do more market research to set more attainable goals based on individual markets, product availabilities, and previous years' business; utilize more marketing opportunities such as advertising and product placements to meet company's retail goals</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's alright”

</title><pros>Pros – Great product, gaining valuable management skills even as a part timer because you work alone, employee discount, the included warranty on the product, decent hourly wage and part timers get vacation hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – Operations are not efficient at all, low tech company, laughably high sales goals, upper management plays favorites, low foot traffic, no advancement opportunity at store level, staffing is always an issue in the stores because the application process is extensive and difficultThis is the strangest retailer I've ever worked for. Other retailers I've worked for, it's all about accommodate the customer. At Swarovski, you can get in trouble for accommodating the customer! if it involves bending the policies.  The sales goals were ridiculous in order to make bonus. Honestly I feel like it's because they don't want to pay us a bonus.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't get mad at us for creating happy customers if it involves bending the rules. Invest in some technology, especially for inventory/shipment purposes</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-22</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great store manager, terrible upper management”

</title><pros>Pros – Beautiful products and workplace, good bonus incentives</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unresponsive upper management, pushy sales environment.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Be there for your stores, give more support and clarify issues.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“anyone could do better”

</title><pros>Pros – Some of the best reasons to work at Swarovski is because the schedules are flexible . You might get commissions/bonus .</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management sucks "very shady and unpleasant".</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Work on making management as efficient as the service offed to customers.lets make the team management as elite as the store is.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits, flexible, good training, excellent product, devoted customers.</pros>
<cons>Cons – A little boring sometimes when we didn't have customers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management at main office could communicate more.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-12-20</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Over all a good place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – - down time- still runned by the Swarovski family- some great people- great pay for a part time retail job</pros>
<cons>Cons – - management won't always teach you how to do things (like stuff on register or how to remover fixtures) then get mad at you.- some employees will steal your sales even though we're paid a flat hourly rate- it can be hard to get bouns, even if your like $2,000 over your daily sales goal, if you dont make you dpt goal forget about bouns.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – rethink a new plan for bouns for the employees</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-13</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Aweful”

</title><pros>Pros – If you love crystals you get 30% off the original price.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Long introduction period and manager was too unsociable to new workers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Allow for more improvement in management.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-10-14</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Development Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“this company sucks - bigtime”

</title><pros>Pros – the products are nice, but that's pretty much it. Also, it's nice to be working at a company with a brand name that people recognize. It gives you more credibility.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the management sucks, the work environment is not good, communication and potential for growth is lacking, overall bad experienceWork life balance is out of whack.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – you are barely doing your job and should simply be replaced by someone how has actual leadership skills</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good part time job”

</title><pros>Pros – -great working atmosphere-it's easy to work extra if one wants to-great bonus scheme</pros>
<cons>Cons – -it would be nice to have a bit more of structured training-sometimes overtime requirements</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide more training, listen to shop floor managers they know what they need</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Keyholder/Brand Ambassador (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not pleasant experience”

</title><pros>Pros – ProductsNice atmosphereGreat discountsLaidback uniform to wear</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor customer serviceManagers who lack everythingNo proper trainingImpossible Sales targetHigh Pressure</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire proper managers. Proper retail training is a must, Communication is the key !!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Graphics Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“My presence in this organization has been sweet if i could say but off lately i feel that i have been left out.”

</title><pros>Pros – In my profile i am not bothered at all by any intrusions during my work. Work timings are perfect. The work personal life balance is outstanding within my team.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of growth in teh company is very annoying and enough is not done to retain a good employee. There are communication gaps in between managements in between which people like me get stuck with unseen future and growth</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – To retain good employees they should motivate with better compensations every year instead of giving silly excuses over market inflation and other fallacies.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Brand Ambassador (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Positive and professional environment to work in”

</title><pros>Pros – Well training and learning experiences about the company and its products.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Hours are often changed and depending on the days, there are not enough customer flow in the store.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“over rated just like their product”

</title><pros>Pros – Lovely customers ,always v friendly and easy to serve and have a light banter with and the Fantastic staff discount</pros>
<cons>Cons – I had worked for smaller as well as larger companies than Swarovski and I had high hopes and expectations off Swarovski when I first joined .I am annoyed with myself for staying with them for 2 whole years.You will get a few employees who are long term but while I was  there I found that most would leave.No career opportunities,management especially higher are not v friendly,unsupportive,lacks people skills and doesn't bother with a lot of the staff ,you definitely get a sense of Us and Them...pay was low compare to my old job(commission based).Training..what training?</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get off your high horse and come back down to earth .Get decent EXPERIENCED management in and start showing some appreciation to those in the front line.Try and retain your sale staff so that your customers can trust that they're being served by knowledgable staff and not someone who hasn't been there 6 months yet and is giving out the wrong advice.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great insight in the jewelry industry, nice workplace”

</title><pros>Pros – - interesting tasks that are handed over to interns- already have responsibility in the tasks-nice colleagues, they treat you at the same level, are not patronizing- good benefits (discounts)-good transport link (buses from train station to the offices)</pros>
<cons>Cons – - unstable industry, too much competition from Asia- HQ is in a rather rural area- very competitory application process and not many prospects for people with just undergraduate studies (bachelor) for full- time work</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-05-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Marketing Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Inexperienced, local Management”

</title><pros>Pros – Colleagues, work life balance and outdoors</pros>
<cons>Cons – Intransparent career paths, culture of promotions within internal networks. Lack of understanding of customers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Christmas Sales Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Really Good”

</title><pros>Pros – Very friendly staff, good pay and bonuses</pros>
<cons>Cons – some interview questions I didn't expect</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Brand Ambassador (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great ambiance-easy sales-training okay -Management alright”

</title><pros>Pros – Easy sales commission of the store achievable - international brand- nice collection</pros>
<cons>Cons – Money is not the best even if I work hard- poor opportunity to move up</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop trying to cut wages especially when the store made their monthly target most of time</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-03</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great products, great heritage, lacking leadership and management”

</title><pros>Pros – good spirit, great culture if you are a people and networking person, can progress if you are performing, global reach and growing</pros>
<cons>Cons – messages you receive might be conflicting, values are great but not lived, lipservices only, unrealistic workload</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – look outside HQ, invest in leadership and people manager and not only promote functional experts, stick to the values and live them - throughout the organization</advice-to-management>
<recommended> – I'm not optimistic about the outlook for this company</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-04</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Software Developer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Swarovski is good organization to discover, learn and work more and more into Software Technologies.”

</title><pros>Pros – I have freedom to work on different technologies...New discovered things are accepted and implemented...</pros>
<cons>Cons – Decision making are very slow and management is least bothered about employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Take decision which are good to organization and also employees.Identify real productive employee and give them opportunity to do more and encourage them other than just showoff.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Brand Ambassdor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great introduction to Jewellery Sales”

</title><pros>Pros – The environment, the people you work with are quite like minded and switched on. Also not to mention the amazing Fashion jewellery.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The fact they do not provide you with a watch, and restrict you to not being able to wear your own watch. The fact the company enforces certain break times and no time penalties fro working outside of normal trading hours during extended 24hr trade.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-10-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Human Resources (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A great, international experience within a growing and promising company”

</title><pros>Pros – working in an international teamfulfilling interesting & challenging tasks day by dayhigh commitment of employees with a good culture and atmospherefun because of young colleagues</pros>
<cons>Cons – too high workload with a too less salarystructure is of historical growth, processes are not defined (to have a good existing network is a key)location in the middle of nowhere in most of the countries, where Swarovski is based</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – first get to know the basegood initiatives from corporate, bad implementation processes</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Easy money, bad management”

</title><pros>Pros – You don't really need to know much to work as an associate.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unless you constantly inquire the managers about your missing pay, they will not do anything about it. Where I worked, managers gave more opportunities to people who they knew personally or had ties to personally.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please take the time to understand what "conflict of interests" actually means.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-08</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Swarovski - Thumbs up!”

</title><pros>Pros – Love the people - all staff are lovely. And the products of course. It is so much fun seeing all the new pieces . Also we get great discounts!</pros>
<cons>Cons – From the amount that is expected of you..working for one of the top brands in the world- the pay rate is not fair in my opinion</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good coworkers under unreasonable headoffice”

</title><pros>Pros – coworkers and manager were nice and good, general working experince was good.</pros>
<cons>Cons – commission system was very unreasonable, the company does not reward hard working people.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – try to advance your current employee to management position is better then always put an outsider as manager. no one would like to work hard if they can't make the job as their career. Also, the commission system should change, people should get something for every item they sale!!!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“hard working company”

</title><pros>Pros – I don't think there are good pros, the benefits are okay, I had to use a lot of my medical care.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It is a place where you have to work very hard to get a decent salary, they suck your energy out of you, you have to work 6 days a week, doing extra hours of work, which you are not paid for, they are not flexible at all, I study in a very nice college, but they don't care about it and make me miss a lot of classes. It is a company that does not care about their employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Happier people produce more.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-07</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Designer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“he didn't encourage us, non-coperative,”

</title><pros>Pros – i like to work in products which they are produced.</pros>
<cons>Cons – non punctual salaries are happened</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – make labours happily, then the company and management will also happy</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-03-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“good company”

</title><pros>Pros – jewelry benefits, good training and holiday</pros>
<cons>Cons – no real career advancement opportunities</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – n/a</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-01-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Lots of great reasons to work here”

</title><pros>Pros – -work for a leading fashion accessories retailer-very competitive salary-great benefits (time off and health and wellness)-co-workers are supportive-advancement is possible with growing company-fantastic sales meetings and recognition awards</pros>
<cons>Cons – -upper management sometimes creates unrealistic sales goals causing stress-company not as operationally focused as other retailers-foot traffic in stores can be very light-work life balance is a challenge-upper management plays favorites-stores in remote parts of the country face challenges that stores in the major cities dont have (like brand awareness and product levels)-store managers only have part-time staff supporting them</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The stores are not one size fits all.  Opening stores at rapid speed without doing any advertising is challenging.  Keep the focus on the client experience, not how much payroll to save.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent”

</title><pros>Pros – Good pay, comfortable environment, never a dull moment.  Good discount on the crystal pieces and jewelry.  Opportunities for advancement exist.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Demanding customers and even more demanding managers--if you want people to treat this as their career, hire career-minded people, not part-timers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't take it so seriously when dealing with the non-full time staff; it's a part time job, not a career, for some of us.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-09-21</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good salary, fun environment.”

</title><pros>Pros – - Good salary- Friendly Environment- Good employee training- Fun environment- Reasonable benefits / discounts- Relatively easy to move up in the company- Family owned company</pros>
<cons>Cons – - sometimes boring- have to deal with demanding / sometimes annoying customers- management beginning to raise prices / take away certain benefits</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give more to the sales associates, more internship opportunities, and stop raising prices and taking items away from certain stores.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-08-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its a wonderful company and brand to be a part of.”

</title><pros>Pros – It is a strong international briand. Swarovski as a company in not affraid to make changes, they are a forrunner in fashion</pros>
<cons>Cons – The upper upper management, regionals are not trustworthy.  It is hard to love a company ad not trust upper management,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Give positive feedback.Ensure that you are telling the truth.  You have people who will put up with this behaviour, just to be apart of the company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Life and work balance is out of wack BIG TIME!!!!!!!!”

</title><pros>Pros – Family owned, great benefits, great salary, great product.</pros>
<cons>Cons – For managers the company doesn't care how many hours you work or even the number of days in a row, just as long as you make your DM's numbers so they can get their bonus. Their is no consistency with the structure of upper management to the stores, just do to their way, don't ever complain or else you'll be replaced. The stress level is out of hand and Hr or anyone in upper management is never willing to listen to your concerns without a threat of being fired.You'd think if this company is family owned that there would be a sense of loyalty to listening to their employees, but there isn't. It's sad because without great managers the stores would go to hell.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your store managers they are on the front line and work everyday 9 to 10 hours. Store mangers do have constructive criticism and it would be wonderful if someone would listen. Maybe someone in upper management should go on the show, Undercover Boss.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-01-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Representative (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Was very happy in the beginning but Now I realised how swarovski are not supportive of their staff.”

</title><pros>Pros – Discount is good and the product i loved.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management style, back stabbing etc</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get new area managers!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Assistant Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not Bad, Not Great Either”

</title><pros>Pros – -Decent Salary-Store Maintenance is easy-Most customers are nice; its a bit more upscale clientele-Potential for bonuses, though they can be quite difficult to obtain .</pros>
<cons>Cons – -They rarely promote from within-Some managers are only concerned with their numbers so your sales may be stolen, though this all depends on the manager-Unfortunately they have saturated the market in some areas with too many stores</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Start promoting from within.  Its very disheartening for employees to watch outside applicants constantly getting interviews for management positions.  Most assistants are never even given an opportunity to interview and on rare occasions when they do, its more done to keep them quiet.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall not too bad but definitely could improve”

</title><pros>Pros – -Really nice and unique products to sell-Pretty decent communication through emails of store policies-Semi-creative work fitting customer's needs, (picking out jewelry for them and matching items with clothing etc.)</pros>
<cons>Cons – -There are almost no promotions for customers, so it's harder to sell products-Corporate pushes numbers and goals ad nauseum, so much it makes working there annoying at times, also push you to sell memberships alot!-Employees write in store handbooks about selling technique and "what would you do situations" really wastes so much time when one could be on the floor selling or doing something productive-Did I mention corporate pushes numbers and memberships alot?-Maybe its my location, but theres a ton of theft by walk-ins, an earring rack is left in the open of the store which brings alot of theft, and its hard to prevent when working by yourself and showing another customer something, ultimately you get blamed</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Don't focus soo much on goals, good selling is important, but its not worth stressing your staff out, when ultimately it is the customer who decides to buy!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Store Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Slave work”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits ! 3 weeks off a year to start. Discount was wonderful too. Well known brand so easier to sell, has a cult following.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Um can we say you will be running a multi- million dollar store alone most of the time. over time will be expected. payroll is always an issue. upper management like to sit on their asses and watch you work over the cameras and critique you if you aren't able to help everyone.  impossible goals so you will hardly ever make a bonus.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – can you stop giving orders and actually work in your own stores? the ass kissing towards upper management here is keeping the company from hitting its full potential. managers here don't help, they just try to scare you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-06</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Representative (Summer) (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“working at  swarovski was a pain”

</title><pros>Pros – interior of store is nice, makes it comfortable to work in</pros>
<cons>Cons – management is incompetent and not very friendly towards staff</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – cut your emplyees some slack, they're people too</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-12</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“All that glitters, is it crystal?”

</title><pros>Pros – Great brand, family owned company and culture despite size, high fashion influences, diverse product range and applications of cut crystal</pros>
<cons>Cons – Gossip, dead wood that wont move on (long standing slackers or protected species)</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More international structure, assistance and sharing of expertise, improve cross functional comms</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>SAP Trainee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Nice company - but not the perfect job”

</title><pros>Pros – One aspect which speaks for the company is that Swarovski is an international firm and you will get the opportunity to travel regularely.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management does not really communicate with the workers, the working climate could be better, jobs are not really hard to do and people seem not to be perfectly motivated.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management should talk to their employees from time to time, to get knowledge about problems and the mood of the employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>