<name>E-LOAN Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/E-LOAN-Reviews-E9194.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2012-09-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Financial Analyst (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Consumer focused company with high values.”

</title><pros>Pros – Focused on allowing clients to make best choices with clear information and a work environment that allows for personal growth and self-driven opportunities.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Real Estate lending and Capital Markets ties.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Try the idea again.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Loan Agent (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“nice working environment”

</title><pros>Pros – good people, nice working environment, good compensation plan, good salary, good benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – ownership changed, benefits changed, poor management</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – hire more experienced managers</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-14</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E-Loan was great, until the founders left”

</title><pros>Pros – friendly people, interesting projects, fair pay</pros>
<cons>Cons – newer exec staff didn't line up well "with the people"</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Care more about the people</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-04-07</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“E-Loan is a wonderful place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – E-Loan is a wonderful place to work and provides work/life balance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – downsizing due to the Mortgage meltdown</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hang in there</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-08-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work, but limited salary and compensation”

</title><pros>Pros – Casual and collaborative working environment. In general, colleagues are very supportive and great to work with, but that experience may vary depending on the department you work for. If you are self-motivated, it is a good place to learn about internet and the banking industry. It is also pretty easy to maintain a work life balance.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation package and growth opportunity within the company can use improvement. E-LOAN went through a significant down sizing in late 2007, so there has been a significant reduction business support roles. Prior to that, the company also has relatively high turn over rate. The management doen't invest as much as they should in the skills and knowledge of employees. I believe opportunities will be quite limited going forward.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Senior management should be more open and direct with communication, especially during difficult times in the industry.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Use Eloan as a training ground and then take that experience elsewhere”

</title><pros>Pros – Probably the only reason to work for E-Loan is to obtain the experience and knowledge in the Mortgage and refinance world.  Some of their systems are robust and they address issues quickly.  Their offices are very nice being modern and clean.  They do provide ample free parking and they are located across from a major shopping mall and located right of of the freeway.  There is a busline and a Bart station nearby for those who use mass transit.     There does seem to be cohesioni between the information systems folks and project managers as they all work together to accomplish their goals.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Not very flexible in letting you work from home, benefits.  The HR department was pretty useless when it came to obtaining additional information about programs.  Some of their systems are robust and they address issues quickly, but the varying arrays of different systems that are not integrated cause inefficiencies.  There is no on-site gym or shower facility for those who ride bikes.  They do not offer any benefit for carpoolers, mass transit users, etc.   The location can be somewhat out of the way, especially if you do not live in the Pleasanton/San Ramon area.   The company did have a rash of lawsuits for employee discrimination and those were settled for an undisclosed amount.  The company did not admit any fault.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Listen to your employees.  They have valuable information that can assist the customer.   Senior Management does somewhat seem to be out of touch.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-06</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Retail Deposits Representative”

</title><pros>Pros – - dress code- management- salary- work life balance</pros>
<cons>Cons – - sitting for long hours</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – - none. The managers were all very fair and professional.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-01</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Loan Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“great job”

</title><pros>Pros – base plus comission, laid back environment, casual work atmosphere, good compensation for selling and monthly bonuses as well. overall good experience.</pros>
<cons>Cons – phone based selling, basiclly a call center, no direct customer interaction and the office was very small. fjdj the fhdldd</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – fdh fehe theo h fh the the the the the the the hte hte hth the the thet hte hte</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>