<name>Sanford C. Bernstein Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Sanford-C-Bernstein-Reviews-E9411.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-09-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Research Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company to kick off your career”

</title><pros>Pros – Highly reputable and knowledgeable bosses; industry reputation; real research; very good exit choice</pros>
<cons>Cons – hours depends on boss; limited upside for someone already has 5+ years experience.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend – I'm optimistic about the outlook for this company</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-01</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I love working inside the Bernstein culture, one that is full of energy.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great colleagues, good options for career path, great management team. Good architecture for associate growth and advancement opportunities. Managers are focused on making sure their associates are happy.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Could be paid more for the work I do, but still satisfied. Sometimes clients call and are upset but they aren't terrible to deal with.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Leadership is great and very accessible. While there is a hierarchical structure, even MDs are easy to speak witha nd readibly available.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-18</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Private Client Associate (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – People are amazingly helpful and very willing to train you. There is a great sense of community there and you can make genuine friends within the workplace.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Limited paths of growth, and if you are not interested in following those specific paths this may not be the place for you. Not much interaction between teams professionally.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep it up!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-10-26</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wonderful Learning & Growth Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Wonderful employee collaboration and professionalism. All people were a joy to work with and the atmosphere was fast-paced and interesting. I truly enjoyed working with a company that took great pride in its product (equity research) and was very serious about continuing its highly regarded reputation.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Slight feeling of hierarchy, but I think that is necessary in a business setting. Sales associates travel quite a bit.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The leadership are a joy to work with because they place great importance upon the idea of "mutual respect." I wanted to work better/ harder for my supervisors not only because I respected them, but also because they showed me respect as well.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-09-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Private Client Associate (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to learn.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place learn. Exposure into high net worth asset management. Bernstein's private client business is top notch. They have some of the most advanced research tools and capabilities in the country. As a private client associate you have the opportunity to use these research tools and the opportunity work directly with clients. The "Financial Advisor" does most of the selling and decision making, but you're part of it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Feels like you have to relocate for advancement. Most of the regional offices are small and you may have to wait a long time for promotional opportunities unless you move.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – More robust professional development. Being a private client associate is not a career path.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2008-06-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>V. P. (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“hidden gem in wall street”

</title><pros>Pros – 1. good team with little politics2. bonus</pros>
<cons>Cons – very segmented.  little communication between groups.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – encourage more transparency between business units</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not the highest caliber shop to be at unless you are a research analyst”

</title><pros>Pros – best research on the street</pros>
<cons>Cons – trading platform is third tier.  not a great caliber of equity professionals.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Sinking ship.  Don't be the last on the boat.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-07</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Assistant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Enjoyed it”

</title><pros>Pros – You have a ton of access</pros>
<cons>Cons – People take themselves a bit too seriously</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep it up</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-02-08</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Vice President (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great reputation in the industry; tough place for (most) sales people.”

</title><pros>Pros – Very well regarded firm in its industry.  Clients are treated very well and the platform for most private clients is among the best in the industry.  Most of the management is smart albeit somewhat cold towards rank and file employees.  The reputation in the industry, while damaged recently, is still very high.  It is reasonably difficult to get hired so there are many "A" players at the firm.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Compensation is below other firms and there is a Pareto distribution amongst the sales force (in terms of how much money).  The median compensation is far below the average.  The focus on getting new business conflicts with the need to service clients.  Compensation really doesn't reflect ability to service existing clients, only ability to get new business to the firm.  Not much interest in using technology to improve the business.  Many of the longest tenured senior managers do not appear willing to embrace change and evolve the firm forward.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Bring in new blood to improve business processes.  Consider upgrading the economics team and create a 'macro' risks team on the buy-side.  Shift advisor compensation to reward servicing of client relationships.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

</reviews>