<name>Suddenlink Communications Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/Suddenlink-Communications-Reviews-E9566.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2013-08-26</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great Company to work for!”

</title><pros>Pros – In this town, this day and age, there is nowhere better to work! Great benefits, and free cable phone and internet are a perk for sure.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very low pay considering what my counterparts are making</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Equalize pay for the same positions no matter the location...We all do the same job with the same responsibilities, we should be making the same money.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-11-04</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative II Tech Support (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A very high stress position with little to no room for error.”

</title><pros>Pros – Pay rate is halfway decent, but not worth the troubles.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Unachievable sales quota goals, worked in tech support not the sales department</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-10-20</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Direct Sales (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“(Promises Broken)Worst employer I have worked for. Found a new job”

</title><pros>Pros – Free Water, free air, decent insurance and air conditioning. That's about it.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Worst pay and hours I have had in 20 years. 6 day 55 hour work week. Some people are belittled by management regularly, thankful it wasn't me. Unrealistic sales goals. Management expects you to sale 10 or more RGU's a day or expect to be reprimanded, even though management has never sold services in there life. Expect Micro managing all the time with criticism. Company phones are GPS tracked and you will receive emails accusing you of turning off the GPS, even though you didn't.  Daily conference calls up to 2 hours before your work day starts. On the calls you will be asked to recite verbally company propaganda. If you do it wrong or with out enough excitement you will be criticized in front of 30 people.If you have a family, they are 2nd to the company in managements eyes. They will tell you that "if you loved your family, you would work more to make them more money" or when denied time off to be with your children there answer is, "we have a business to run here".My department of 20 has seen over 50 people come and go in 6 months. All coming in with high expectations, only to be crushed within weeks. Whole department is looking for jobs. Revolving door, no reason to get to know there names.I am a happy optimistic person (by the way no laughing or fun at work, NO-NO)and this company just gave me the worst summer of my life. The above only but scratches the surface of  there atrocities. Please avoid the trap. You will be promised great pay 80,000 + you will earn under 30,000, did I mention 6 day 55 hour work weeks. Every job I have had I stayed for more then 8 years before leaving for another job. I stayed to long with Suddenlink. Guess I believed it would get better but it didn't. Wished I had something nice to say but I don't.  Hope this helps you! :).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please go out and by your self, do the job your employees do for one week. You will learn a lot and may feel embarrassed by some of your earlier statements to employees but more important you will earn respect of your employees and will be able to share stories that are real, not made up. Hence the embarrassment.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-09-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Care Supervisor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Exercises in futility”

</title><pros>Pros – Good benefits. Discounted service for employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Questionable decision-making at the call center level. Human Resources untrustworthy. Failure to look beyond the immediate future before making changes that impact the majority of employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire 3rd party to conduct interviews with former employees and hold focus groups with current employees. Any information gained in-house will be tainted once it is filtered upward.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-08-19</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Horrible experience”

</title><pros>Pros – get free tv and chances to win things</pros>
<cons>Cons – horrible training, unprepared to help any customers. pretty much are just thrown out onto your own to try and help customers with equipment you have no idea about</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – improve training program and provide better experience to new hires</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-07-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Broad Band Tech IV (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great benefits and overall good place to work.”

</title><pros>Pros – Great benefits and people who actually seem to care about employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Some times long hours and what seems to be low wages.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-18</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Account Services Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great company to work for.”

</title><pros>Pros – Get to talk to people all day, nice people to work with, full time hours, good pay, occasional overtime</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sitting down all day, difficult customers, goals are sometimes hard to reach, talking all day can sometimes ruin your voice</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Direct Sales and Marketing Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Easy as counting to 1,356,254,7456”

</title><pros>Pros – Great local managment, cool benefits!</pros>
<cons>Cons – Always a new challenge to overcome, unrealistic expectations, upper management is out of the loop, policies and procedures change by the minute. Salary is a joke plus commision, 6 day work week, outrageous manadotory work hours. In the past few months I have done more work and put in more hours for far less pay. I dont even know if corporate is aware of the circus going on in my department recently. Half of my department is looking for other jobs but is too afraid to tell management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Quit changing things until they have been tested and are ready to be done. Change is good, but change for the sake of change isn't. Commision is based on an unrealistic sales pyramid. If you don't hit a specific number you do not get paid your commision.  My average pay My average pay has been cut in half with new restructuring.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative II (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It started of great but quickly headed downhill”

</title><pros>Pros – Excellent benefits. Free cable and Internet</pros>
<cons>Cons – (Call Center / Tech Support Dept.) After new management stepped in in 2011 they shifted from customer service to how much more can we squeeze out of our customers for a profit. They replaced knowledgeable supervisors with babysitters to make sure we were making sales ( i.e. the billing and tech departments). As the good supervisors left one by one, so did the veteran agents. Which lead to more calls from even more upset customers because all the rookies on the floor were not up to the challenge. I was there 5 years. The first 3 years would get 5 starts ~ year 4 was a 3, and I finally had to leave after the new people were getting better score cards than me when the only thing they did was sell stuff - not fix anything.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – You people forgot what customer service was all about. Taking care of there needs .. not trying to sell them services they don't want.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-06-10</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Poor Management”

</title><pros>Pros – Laid Back environment, free internet services</pros>
<cons>Cons – poor poor management, terrible training</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Field Systems Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Excellent place to start a career.”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent pay and benefitsFriendly employees and plenty of room to advance if you are willing to relocate.Management listens to concerns and is willing to assist.Provided with tools, uniforms, vehicle, and free service.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No domestic partnership benefits even though they promote diversity.Management pay is lower than equivalent positions in other telecommunications industries.Work order technology causes employees to rush to their next job.Technologies are delivered before they are tested, which hurts customer's perception of company.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Put your money where your mouth is when you speak of diversity. Promote it within by supporting different employee groups.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-03-19</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Tech Support (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Could be better”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Coworkers, free cable and inet service</pros>
<cons>Cons – Low Pay, in Q too much</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-04-03</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Toxic Working Environment”

</title><pros>Pros – Free cable/internet if you live in one of their markets.</pros>
<cons>Cons – It's a very "Title-Driven" culture.  Employees are not treated equally - the bigger/better your title, the higher your value to the company.  If you are unfortunate enough to rank lower than a Director level, and you forget your "place" in the organization, upper management will very quickly remind you.There's an extremely high level of mistrust among everyone.  It truly is an "every man for himself" environment.Pay is lower than average.There's no since of "fun" or "family" throughout the organization.  The corporate mentality is very old-fashioned, and even chauvinistic at times.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Value and recognize your employees and invest in their career development.  Most of the attention is focused entirely on sales staff and management...all of the others (support/admin staff, etc.) are forgotten or ignored.  And update your culture - take a cue from other cutting edge organizations like Zappos.com, Google, etc. who have happy employees and put into practice a 21st Century approach.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-02-13</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Suddenlink Your Connected”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent pay, great benefits, good people to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Pay could be better but who doesnt think that they should be paid more!!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-29</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales Agent (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Stressful, frustrating &, at times, exasperating!”

</title><pros>Pros – Benefits are decent- health, dental, 401k, free cable are a plus. Pay is decent for Tyler area...</pros>
<cons>Cons – When more big companies come to Tyler, there will be more of a need for competitive commissions, but in the past 2 years, Suddenlink has used all the creativity it can muster as a company to figure out how to pressure agents to sell sell sell and pay them as little as they can possibly get away with for their trouble. What was once a thriving,  pleasantly competitive & lucrative sales environment has been reduced to a floor of agents buckling under the pressure to force every product down a customer's throat, regardless of the reason for their call- and pay them peanuts for all the stress & effort. It's sad to see.Nepotism, favoritism & greed are the norm here. If you have "it", sups love you, promotions come quickly & easily & you pretty much do what you want. If you don't have "it", you'll be threatened with termination for the same things others are freely getting away with... it's all a matter of who likes you.Management jobs go to those who are well liked, not those with the best skills to lead. If the supervisor likes you, you'll be ok. If they don't, forget getting anything but the bare minimum from them. The direction a Suddenlink employee's career takes can rest largely on the supervisor they end up with, so the odds are definitely NOT good at all.Sales goals and expectations are inflated for the current economy and are a result of corporate greed. Businesses expect to make a profit, but this goes well beyond that. The majority of expectations are not feasible based on the given circumstances and trying isn't enough.... agents have been forced to call cusotmers back if they couldn't close the sale, etc.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get back to being a company that is customer focused and treats employees like assets, not like slaves to the company's bottom line, charged with obtaining sales at any cost. Empower your employees instead of making them feel they are in a vacuum where effort doesn't matter and nothing is ever enough.I envision a workplace where employees are smiling because they feel they are part of something awesome. (See 100 Best Places To Work: Google)  Happy employees make happy customers and happy customers buy! Remember that mentality? Get back to it!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2013-01-17</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Bbt2 (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“still going off the deep end”

</title><pros>Pros – free cable and internet and a pay check and a work truck to drive home that's about it</pros>
<cons>Cons – where to start. supervisors in my system are all more concerned about them selves looking good than anything else even if it means throwing a good tech under the bus. I am a service tech. they recently said we have to score a certain score on all categories across the board on our score cards and some of it I understand but the sales is the one that I don't agree with. I did not sign up to be a sales man I signed up to be a service tech if I wanted to be a sales man I would have signed up to be one. if we don't make that score they want we get punished but my job is to fix and install services and make sure my customers are happy suddenlink has sales people on staff to sale services. management is far out of touch with the people under them. they do not care about us at all. we get worked to death and every week at our meeting they announce a new policy that makes our job harder. we have 45 minutes to complete each job but we have to fix the problem and check behind all of the wall plates go up to the top of the pole check the connector there check all of the phone wiring if the problem is the drop that takes like 45 minutes its self to replace so basically keeping your points per hour good on your score card is very difficult. there is ALOT OF FAVORITEISM in the bryan college station system. supervisors perform very harsh quality control checks on techs that they don't like. but take it easy on there buddy's.  they lie to us and then punish people for reporting it to hr if they find out who it was or who they assume it was which violates the open door policy so now techs are afraid to say anything to anyone because a target WILL be painted on there back I have seen this too many times. management punishes us for not following safety procedures but I have seen first hand them not following the same safety procedures that they punish us for. one supervisor in particular put me in a unsafe position. he put my ladder on a pole I told him I was not comfortable climbing because I could not put my ladder on it in a safe position  according to how we were taught in the training course. There are ALOT of techs here that are looking for other jobs and the things that I have mentioned are just a few things that are going on here.  and I thank hr needs to meet with the techs one on one every once in a while to discuss how things are going that way hr can hold people accountable for there actions or try to make changes that would benefit everyone. HAPPY TECHS = GOOD WORK AND ATTITUDE  GOOD WORK AND ATTITUDE = HAPPY CUSTOMERS</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – practice what you preach, treat all techs fairly, try to make this a good place to work as we are as important as the customers, stop lying to us all the time, be fair, give us time to clean our trucks we need it very bad, hole your selves accountable for things instead of pushing it on us, treat us like the good people we are, lead by example, take care of your techs and they will take care of you.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-12-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>IP Engineer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Suddenlink : Poor training, management”

</title><pros>Pros – Free cable and internet.. Insurance was good for family prices. Discounts on other memberships and things as well.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Contractors do the home installs a lot of the time. I already had internet with this company for years and years, but when the courtesy service was turned on it took three separate trips (on different days) for them to resolve the install. Apparently making sure you didn't break someone's internet connection after installing cable tv is not a standard practice.Had a technician lie to me. Told me they stopped by at 6:30 pm , knocked but no one was home. I had been there since 6:00 pm and no one showed up at all or called me until I called them two days later, no robo or real person follow up.They hire from within a lot because they expect you to know the industry. Good luck  if you weren't already answering phones or installing cable modems for them.Long hours. I mean 60-70 hours a week. Salary.This job taught me to not trust your co-workers.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Train your employees. I had more training in safety practices than on my core duties..Don't hire under-educated people just because it's cheaper.Stop berating employees past and present.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-08-19</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It's not Suddenlink, it's Spinlink”

</title><pros>Pros – It was a paycheck.There is a minimum word criteria here but honestly, the regular check coming in is the only pro that comes to mind.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The management at this company is all about spin and how to make themselves look good to executive management, even at the expense of the employees and contractors under them.  Project managers are not allowed to manage projects, they only fill out endless paperwork and baby the project team to suit their every whim.  You don't need project managers in the industry sense for that kind of work.  You need data entry workers and file clerks that agree with you no matter what the situation or circumstance.The good ole boy network seems to be the standard method for hiring and advancement. This is the bias, favoritism, and nepotism referenced in another review.  Morale is ruined for anyone not in the club.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The culture and values that you plaster everywhere are not what this company is about in the slightest.  For starters, your VPs are arrogant and belittling, like a clique of middle school children.  They set the worst example possible.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative-technical Support (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Shameful Human resources Practices”

</title><pros>Pros – Laid back atmosphere, excellent pay and benefits, good people to work with</pros>
<cons>Cons – high rollover rate with employees, will fire you for anything, do not follow thier own procedures for termination, no program to help employees learn thier job better</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Training should be more incompassing, and supervisors should be more open with team members as far as performance and score cards, supervisors should be held more accountable for the failures of their teams.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-05</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Support (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not a bad experience...”

</title><pros>Pros – opportunities for commission, they do little things for employees that boost morale, decent benefits.</pros>
<cons>Cons – tech support and billing reps are required to offer, offer, offer, and sale, sale, sale ... which gets kind of annoying. I took the tech support position thinking I would be assisting and learning technical support skills, wrong, I'm a salesman and billing rep who helps fix internet, cable, and phone issues.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Technical Support should be allowed to sell products and not be forced to sell products. You won't keep good IT or Tech Support people for very long because they want to assist with technical issues not be forced to sell.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-06-06</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Sales (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Biased, Favoritism, Nepotism, Lies, Yuck!”

</title><pros>Pros – Free cable and internet were pluses when you have time to use them. Outside sales gives you some flexibility.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Local sales office run like it is owned by one person who basically controls all the decent leads and then also slants reviews of you up the management chain however the likes. Little opportunity to actually make any kind of decent money. Management always riding you for more or belittling your honest efforts as unsatisfactory. Micro management.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get your heads out of your ***es</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-11-11</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Small market company with small market salaries”

</title><pros>Pros – Free cable and internet to all employees.  Company is small enough where you can pretty much get to know management.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Company uses their small market to give out less than average salaries.  Management also does not like to give out good reviews of their management in order to not give out raises.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – At least look at what the market rate is for management positions when determining salaries.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-23</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Care Supervisor (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Suddenlink has given me the confidence to reach for goals and be independent.”

</title><pros>Pros – Suddenlink in my opinion has awesome benefits and gives me a feeling of family in our local systems. They are very supportive of family situations and offers great services (I never hesitate to tell a customer how much I like the service I receive).</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sometimes I feel that Suddenlink is trying to offer the best services out there to our customers but the manpower they expect us to achieve our goals is very limited. This does cause stress for all of our employees from management down to the front line employees that face the customers every day.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – I think it would go a long way to have senior managment above the district level come to the local systems and meet (round table style) with the local employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-09</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Call Center - Technical Support (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Standard Call Center job, with a small town feel.”

</title><pros>Pros – -Free Cable and internet-Supervisors are all very cool, they will do everything to try and get you paid better, get good days off, win incentives, etc.- Rather flexible with sick time/vacation time.- Pay is adequate compared to other jobs in greenville- Hours are all rather steady (call center is open 8am-10pm, no night shifts)</pros>
<cons>Cons – - Sales is pushed on everyone - if you do not sell, you will not be recognized - ever. No matter what position you are in.- Upper managements seems to work against supervisors in making this a nice place to work.  Upper management will require OT, and push new protocols that are more about making reps take on more responsability so that other departments have less to do.  Supervisor's know how stressful the CSR's job already is and they have a hard time enforcing alot of the new protocols as CSR's have so much on their plate to begin with.- The marketing team is supposed to take care of sales incentives for the call center and they fail so hard at it.  The old marketing person got promoted and the new person has no idea what he is doing.  CSR's constantly have to check their sales, check his math, email him about discrepencies, and basicly do his job for him.  If you think you should have won a prize (prizes could be as big as trips to vegas, flat screen tv's, ipads, etc) you really needed to put up a stink to get it.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-15</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Bbt2 (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I have enjoyed working @ suddenlink.”

</title><pros>Pros – I feel like i have job security ,a great opportunity for advancement ,as well as given the proper training and information to do my job .</pros>
<cons>Cons – My shift does not allow me much family time during the week. Could use more tools to do our jobs correctly !</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Need to find a way to hold employees accountable for their time , I personally know of employees riding out jobs at end of shift so they can go home on time !</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-09</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Broadband II (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Initially ok but seeing how the management had their favorites, I was very dissatisfied”

</title><pros>Pros – Is a steady pay check, but please be careful as to what situations you might  be in, Management is biased towards certain employees. In essence, 2 employees can be involved in same scenario at work but if management doesn't like you for what ever reason, you're out the door</pros>
<cons>Cons – Free services. Employees obtain certain priorit =y to various benefits in company. Enjoyed interacting with public i.e. customers. Kudos!</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Disband current management in Grenville,NC. Is very dysfunctional. Some management are good mentors and will help their employees, the rest  are just in their own little world</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-25</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Support - Tier I (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent Place to work..as long as you don't mind the available shifts.”

</title><pros>Pros – I loved working at Suddenlink. The training was great. The pay was awesome, and the commissions were nice. The supervisor(s) were quick to praise good work, and work with you to improve areas that needed improvement. The atmosphere was pretty laid back and enjoyable for a call center.</pros>
<cons>Cons – As with any call center there was the occasional angry customer. Once the employee count dropped too low the management had to make changes in schedules. Even those with seniority ended up having to choose between terrible schedules. That is actually the only reason I am no longer working for Suddenlink. The schedules I was presented to choose from would not have allowed ANY time with my family because of the distance I had to drive each way.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Come up with some way to ensure a work-life balance for newcomers and those who have seniority. Basically Suddenlink is a great place to work, but there needs to be more flexibility with scheduling. It would be also be great to open a 3rd shift in the call center.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-18</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“CSR I”

</title><pros>Pros – Free cable and internet at home.Commissions on salesFlexible Work hours</pros>
<cons>Cons – Covering for sales and billing calls during hours when those offices are open.Pressure to sell on every callCall score sheet grades on sale multiple timesCan get noisy when marketing is trying to drum up sales with promotions using bull horn and over excited people.Useless loud meetings that disturb the call center.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep the loud people out of the call center where tech support has to handle calls.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-10</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Direct manager can make or break your expierence at Suddenlink”

</title><pros>Pros – Strong company performance leads to good job stabilityGreat benefits and competitive payHard working employeesSenior management is visible</pros>
<cons>Cons – Competitive work environment, little encouragement for job diversification or advancementVery political environment. Important to make friends with upper managementCorporate headquarters far from operations</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Emphasize more focus on employee development and carrer path opportunities. Also allow for feedback to be received upwards as well as downwards</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-01-21</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Field Supervisor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Good place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Cutting Edge technology, great customer focuse</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bottom Line company, keep focus on getting the job done</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Keep your resume handy, make sure you meet your numbers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-11-26</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Support (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Tech Support - now just neutered to sales and account services!”

</title><pros>Pros – Competitive pay for entry level ITGreat benefits for entry levelRoom for advancement within the companyFree cable and internet?</pros>
<cons>Cons – Management is often conceitedSome questionable practices I didnt always agree withIf you get stuck with a supervisor that doesnt know what's going on have funTech support agents are "universal agents" that also have to do sales and account service calls.  Sales quotas and scripts</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stick to your company culture - it encourages wow in the workplace but in the call center i was in this definitely wasnt the case.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-07-01</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Bbt2 (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“tech treatment has gone down hill over tha past year”

</title><pros>Pros – free cable and internet company truck to drive home and the other service techs are a pretty good bunch of guys</pros>
<cons>Cons – we are worked like dogs in the field, management acts like they are there to help us but no action is ever taken when it needs to be taken, we have way too much to worry about in the field and things just keep getting added some of it can be done in an office so we can focus more on making our customers happy, not enough time alotted to complete tasks, put stuff on our score card that shouldent be there which makes it harder to get annual raises, we are way over booked so we have to rush so we are not out til 10 or 11 pm we cant meet time frames due to over booking and in the end its the customer that looses and we have to get chewed out by upset customers because we are late to the appoitment because we had 4 10 to 12 appoitments it seems almost every week there are changes to how things are done and new things for the field techs to worry about (the job keeps getting harder than it has to be) management is more concerned with how good the numbers are than there techs because if the numbers are good they look good, lots of favoritism,  our repeat numbers go up due to equipment failure when we just install the equipment its not our fault its defective, sales is on our score card and shouldent be our job is install and service we dont always have time to go sale services especially when we are so over booked, dispatch wait times are way too long making it take longer to get things done the pay should be more to match the amount of work we do and the long hours we work,</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – treat the field techs like people, try to make us happier about working here, listen to us, if all techs are complaining about the same thing then there is probabally a problem and something should be done about it</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-05-13</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Maintenance Technician (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very stressful, underpaid and VERY often taken advantage of.”

</title><pros>Pros – Decent benefits, room to grow and outside work. Offices are local. Company truck to drive home.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Technicians are thrown around and taken advantage of every day, as a technician we install security, cable, and phone. As well as perform maintenance on the services and the maintenance techs in smaller systems such as mine are worked to death and treated very poorly, including low wages considering the amount of work and quality of our work. Suddenlink managers are deeply out of touch with all employees and employees are thrown around and no one in management seems to care. Dispatchers are also severely overworked and treated unfairly. The training for field work is a joke, all management lies to not only the lower employees but also upper management so they can look good and keep their jobs. The majority of employees are very unhappy and upset with the company, although the company says we are not. Field equipment ranging from digital boxes to hardline, then on to hand tools are very very cheap and unreliable.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Learn how to be leaders, treat all your workers especially dispatchers and field techs ( your company's lifeline ), get out in the field and learn something and see how things are really ran instead of hiding behind your desk bossing everyone around. Raise everyone's pay especially dispatch and field techs to a fair rate considering the amount of work we put out. Your BBT level scale is SEVERELY flawed and everyone knows, be smart and fix it. Open your eyes before this company gets any worse, unhappy employees = unhappy customers. Stop lying to employees and treating us like we are expendable. A better way to express ourselves to upper management, any complaint should go unpunished and have no reprocutions. And remember, your techs are the lifeline of the company and all employees are as important as the customer.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-04-02</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>3</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Interesting Experience”

</title><pros>Pros – Overall a good experience for motivated individuals to gain valuable work experience. Well intentioned attempts at training and developing employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Extremely nepostistic environment where qualifications, results and experience are regularly overlooked in hiring. An extremely frustrating work environment for competent employees.</cons>
<advice-to-management></advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-27</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>2</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“work here only if its your last option”

</title><pros>Pros – Small town companyGrowing companycompany occasionally feeds employees to boost morale.the pay for hourly employees is ok based on companies of similar size.</pros>
<cons>Cons – salary poor compared to similar companiesmanagement style very poor</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat employees fair and as an asset to company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2012-02-12</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Not so great”

</title><pros>Pros – The usual free cable, 401K, health, vision, dental, etc. which are all good.The pay rate is about mid-industry average for cable.  Field people get a take home vehicle and for people who want to learn at their own pace they offer good online training.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper management are clueless when it comes to leading people.  They initiate changes in the operation that require overtime or a schedule change with almost no advance notice. As an employee I can understand the need to make changes, but upper management should at least have the foresight to see more than 5 days ahead. They push a panic button on an update or change in work load and managers and supervisors have to start throwing people at the problem. Seems like the upper team lacks vision. Other companies try to look far enough ahead so employees can adjust family schedules.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Provide ALL leaders from director on down with real leadership training. Communication from outside the system is almost always top down and often mixed with arrogance. System level people know what is needed and it would be wise to build a relationship to provide that feedback.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-07-22</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Collections (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“very great atmosphere”

</title><pros>Pros – Great company and awesome people</pros>
<cons>Cons – The sick time and vacation tme is a downside</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Very great leadership at suddenlink communications. Very up to date with technology, Leaders are very helpful at what the do</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-06-04</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I am very happy with the Suddenlink experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – Management is on top of changing enviroment of the businessSafety is a top priority and on going safety programs are in place and promotedFamily first enviromentTraining for all employees on the latest upgradesRealize that the employees are their greatest asset and treat them as suchSCTE certified techs with over 90 days of employee 100%Very proactive in the customer service area, it's their top priority</pros>
<cons>Cons – Salaries are somewhat low but the benefits package makes up for it</cons>
<advice-to-management>Yes, I would recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-03-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service/Technical Support/Billing (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“A very stressful place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – good benefits, good pay and commisions</pros>
<cons>Cons – stressful environment, not family/child friendly</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – more communication on a personal level</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-14</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>In Bound Tech Support (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Overall, not bad.”

</title><pros>Pros – the medical benefits, etc.. are really good for todays work market, and the mgmt does a good job shwing the employees that they do care, and appreciate us.</pros>
<cons>Cons – the pay is a little weak, the no-fault attendance policy - while being a call center staple - is a seriously flawed attendance system for ANY company who claims to care about their employees, and the families of those employees.  Communication to the standard employees leaves soemthing to be desired.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – the chain of communication leading downward is flawed, and leaves a lot to be desired.better, more thorough training on new product releases, AND more information on the network as a whole.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-09</date>
<rating>5.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>BBT I (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“I have worked for Suddenlink for almost 5 years and really enjoy my job and customers.”

</title><pros>Pros – insurancehourly paydirect deposit of paycheckcoworkerscompany is there in an emergencycompany vecihle, gas card and work phoneholidays off with pay</pros>
<cons>Cons – oncall weekslong hourswaiting to get trained for a new positionmonthly salesgetting called out all hours of the nightworking in all weather</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The advice I would offer management is don't change a thing.  I work in an office with great co-workers and a great supervisor.  They are always there to help, answer questions or bring equipment if needed.  We always are there to help each other.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-02-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>BBT4 (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Very overworked, very underpaid, and highly unappreciated.”

</title><pros>Pros – They provide us with a company vehicle. Free cable and Pay Per View is half price.My home phone is only $25.00. We get paid vacations if you schedule them when they want you to and paid holidays.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The company thinks more about "the company" than the employees who maintain it and keep it running. Numbers mean more to them than people do. We get paid vacations but can only take them when it is convient for the company to let you off. If you schedule 1 or more vacation days thru the week and work any overtime, your overtime hours are paid in straight time. There is too much avoidable stress put on technicians and too many hours to work per day. We are not told how many sick days we have acrued unless we ask the office manager. They spend way too much in advertising such as, commercials and marketing and not enough pay to its employees! That is why they can't keep technicians in my area.</cons>
<advice-to-management>No, I would not recommend this company to a friend</advice-to-management>
</review>

</reviews>