<name>ACS (Actividades de construccion y Servicios) Reviews </name>
<url>http://www.glassdoor.com/Reviews/ACS-Actividades-de-construccion-y-Servicios-Reviews-E9755.htm
</url>
<reviews>
<review>
<date>2010-11-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place if you are friends with upper management!”

</title><pros>Pros – Good pay if you are fortune to have a long tenure with ACS.  You do learn a lot as most departments are understaffed which affords you the ability to wear different hats.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Upper  management is not concerned with customer service but with the bottom line.  It is all about who you know and not what you know. Lay offs are foreseeable even when profits are up.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Time to review the senior management and their leadership abilities. An open door policy does not exist, literally, doors are closed 75% of the time.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-02</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>1</upvote>
<employee-type>Customer Service Representative (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Decent place if you are entering or re-entering the workforce.”

</title><pros>Pros – Managers are flexible and try to help employees with work/life balance.  You get to meet a diversity of people, some good and some bad and I am talking about the employees working there.  Most first line supers were helpful and available if you had questions.  The training was extremely fine-tuned and complete so you were comfortable with the various programs you were using when you got to your workstation.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Apparently the managers or whoever is hiring still does not check into the background of employees well enough.  There seemed to be a noticeable lack of professionalism in a number of the employees working there in the way that they dressed and conducted themselves.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Get even more stringent with the hiring and background checking of employees.  Try to hire the best quality employees possible.  Really listen when interviews are being conducted to determine better the maturity and professionalism level of the person.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-05</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Technical Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ACS”

</title><pros>Pros – Great Domain Knowledge Experience, Work  closely with Business Analysts. Learn about the full suite of IBM products and Commercial Off the Shelf software</pros>
<cons>Cons – Late hours, not very flexible work hours. Some bad managers who do not respect your time-off. Huge egos for some managers</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Welcome more feedback from employees. Respect employees vacation time. Provide benefits for extra work hours and late nights. Employee appraisal should be fair</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Slow place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Flexible and can work remote</pros>
<cons>Cons – The working process is horrible</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do not rely on offshore</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-21</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ACS”

</title><pros>Pros – Some of the poeple who work there are great, others are not.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The job salaries are below standard.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Hire people who know what they are doing</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-30</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“No loyalty to employee, Remote Management without personal interaction. Employees are treated  as expendable resources.”

</title><pros>Pros – If you don't care about your career and just want to make a few bucks, ACS is the place to work.</pros>
<cons>Cons – No pad on the back for doing a good job, and thus no incentive for being loyal to the company and to your job responsbility.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management should develop a closer relationship to the employee.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-23</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Aid Officer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Processing”

</title><pros>Pros – Make own hours, do not have to talk to customers. You also get to sit and listen to music all day long and people here are pretty conservative and just sit at the computer all day long.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Sit at a computer terminal for 8 hours. No human contact which can be good depending on the way you love your life.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Do not micro manage and be more open to vacation plans. Also please consider that we are human beings and not processing machines. Also you could pay us more just the bare fact that you pay us 11.54 an hour is not good.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-08-23</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Elgibility Specialist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Felt like a slave”

</title><pros>Pros – The hourly pay at ACS is very high for the area and type of work (customer service) . The other women I worked with were for the most part friendly and not back stabbers.  I enjoyed the their comaradie, and helpfulness to share information.</pros>
<cons>Cons – My main complaint is the way employees were treated.  I was forced into a new area with little to no training. I felt so imcompetent and had to call over help for every call, putting client on hold for long periods of time. While was expected to keep time of calls down.  No one asked me if I WOULD take the position, I was FORCED to, after learning all I could to do the job I was hired for for 3 months.  I did not feel appreciated for the effort put in.  My first evaluation of my performance was  "failure", which really crushed me, after trying so hard to do a good job.  I was basically marked down for 1 little thing I didn't say.  They expect you to go by a script to answer questions when half the questions aren't IN the script! And the search capibilities of the script is non-existant. You are timed at breaks strickly and pay cut if you go over break or lunch time. This felt like inhuman treatment. Sometimes ya gotta take a potty break and want to get a cup of joe and decompress on your break but the timing is so strict-  I have worked for small companies before this and was treated like a person, not a thing.  Their benefits are non-exhistant and not even offered until after 90 days.  I didn't need their health insurance thank goodness but feel sorry for all those who do.  Only the pay is good and its not worth it when you feel like this about your job.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Treat people like people, not machines.  ASK if they are willing to take a new position.  TRAIN them for the new position if they take it.  Worry about the customer/client more and less about TIME used to help the person.  Again Treat people like PEOPLE.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-06-24</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Trainer (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“n/a”

</title><pros>Pros – Great place for college graduates to begin employment, potential for career building skills and a good work ethic.  The company itself does offer some opportunity for advancement but limited and you can be capped with options if not a part of clicks certain circles of networking.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Promotions are not fairly approved or allocated.  Good people can get stuck and overlooked when performing greatly and poor performers are promoted for failure.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It would be most beneficial to review the promotion trends of employees and have workshops and training classes in place to educate the managment personnel.  Many of the actions are unjust and bias in terms of why people are promoted versus one that are not.  Maybe a charted career path to show how one can successfully complete one thing in route to promotional opportunities.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-20</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“OK place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Lots of diverse opportunities within the company.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor salary and benefis compared to the rest of the industry.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Pay more attention to employee concerns.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-22</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Development Senior Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Comfortable but not satisfying”

</title><pros>Pros – Some very nice coworkers who are hard workersFlexible projects and continual challengesUnderstanding of work hours and schedulesNot a lot of extra hours required</pros>
<cons>Cons – No road map for career advancementNo consistent recognition of key playersFinancial package is poorSenior management willing to sacrifice at the lower level in order to meet bottom-line goals</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The engineers and developers doing the actual work  are the real important resources of the company. Support their growth professionally and financially and you would see a greater return in product quality and speed of delivery.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-16</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Instructional Designer (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Shame on you ACS for offshoring our jobs to India!”

</title><pros>Pros – Great payFlexibilityAbility to work from home (and avoid all the drama, politics and lack of productivity associated with working in a corporate office)</pros>
<cons>Cons – Lack of job securityWorking from home makes you less visible (and perceived as less valuable)Ambiguity</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Shame on you for offshoring jobs oversees, especially during these tough economic times when so many US citizens are out of work. There are plenty of qualified, well-educated, hard-working people here in the US who NEED jobs. Hopefully, you'll wake up when you start losing clients because of the reduced quality of work and inconveniences of working with people oversees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-04</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Great place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – Very fast paced environment, team environment</pros>
<cons>Cons – Layoffs, Not enough time to make necessary changes at the site in which I was employed</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – none</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-18</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Senior Consultant (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Senior Consultant at ACS”

</title><pros>Pros – Good pay, good benefits, and they paid travel expenses.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Very transactional atmosphere - with people as transactions; work, make money for the company, get to keep some of the money, repeat.  Very little human sensitivity.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – People are more than just financial transactions.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-08</date>
<rating>2.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Wouldn't Recommend”

</title><pros>Pros – Good entry level job to gain experience.Good advancement opportunity.If you are up for a challenge, this is the place for you.Good peer group- hard working</pros>
<cons>Cons – Length of hours required at management level.Unrealistic client expectations.Poorly  maintained  facilityExpectations from low paid staff are unrealistic.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – i would look at the way that the upper management treats their staff. Much like expendable commodities instead of like people.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2011-10-03</date>
<rating>4.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Project Manager (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It is the best place to start a career. You must be capable of working with very little help from your superiors.”

</title><pros>Pros – - You will build a good resume. Specially if you go abroad.- No boundaries. All the information is at your reach if you are willing to get responsibility.- Friendly relations between the employees.</pros>
<cons>Cons – - No coaching, training, feedback of any type.- If you are working abroad, be sure that you are going to be alone (don´t expect any help from your superiors).</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – The empowerment the manager do is great. But some feedback will be good. Communicate what are the expectations you have for your employees.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>Yes</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-28</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Business Services Specialist (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Acs review”

</title><pros>Pros – It was great experience for my resume and future jobs. I learned a lot and interacted with some great people because of my position and that network has been very useful.</pros>
<cons>Cons – The pay was really low relative to other similar positions.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Worklife in some smaller offices and beaches should be checked regularly.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-11-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Consultant (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Pros and Cons”

</title><pros>Pros – A good name, great acquisition of xerox company, a big company</pros>
<cons>Cons – limited benefits, no valuable training, limited career growth</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – add more benefits like retirement plan so that people would not look for new company.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-12</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Development Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Its Ok”

</title><pros>Pros – Good Work EnvironmentGood salary structure(less deduction)Flexible work timingWork from homeNo firingprovide good salary, if you join with good salary</pros>
<cons>Cons – No hike after joiningNo HR supportNo promotionHR Policy is not familiarIf you send mail to HR, they wont respond</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Management should work, as they are telling anything going to introduce.They should be true with their word. they dont work as they are telling.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-15</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Systems Development Senior Specialist (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Place to get experience and move on”

</title><pros>Pros – Work and  Family balance, Good benifits ,people are  very friendly  longer your there the benifits are better</pros>
<cons>Cons – Promotions and recognitions are rare, non existant. Favors are the way to go. no need to show performance</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Recognise talent and honor them</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-09-01</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“working for acs”

</title><pros>Pros – the remote site is rewarding in terms of small company feel and atmosphere. Peers are great to work with too.</pros>
<cons>Cons – When ACS headquarters gets involved, it's usually bad. They don't really know what we do locally, they have proved themselves untrustworthy in the past.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – It would be nice if management was more involved proactively, not just when things go bad or they want to cut back headcount.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-10-01</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Bad Managers No Training”

</title><pros>Pros – The pay is fair. Co-workers are okay to work with.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Bad management and no training provided. No HR on site.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop doing what everybody else does and start caring about your people. Inspire others to work harder. Get training on-board.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-26</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Supervisor (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Okay Place To Work”

</title><pros>Pros – Relaxed attire.Good work/life balance. Manager was always understanding of unplanned family issues that needed to be attended to.Opportunities for advancement were available but minimal.</pros>
<cons>Cons – Poor benefits that cost a lot out of pocket.Understaffing many departments in order to keep costs down yet workload continued to increase with no additional head count.On-site HR not very knowledgable.  Always directed to call corporate HR.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Please provide the departments with the staffing they need in order to get the job done and satisfy the customer.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-07-23</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“ACS PMO - Healthcare”

</title><pros>Pros – ASC provided a great deal of challenges, however the people that I worked with were some of the best I have ever worked with</pros>
<cons>Cons – Need to provide more time to market, schedules were unrealistic and need to communicate accurate information to the customers, even if it is bad news.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Spend time talking to the workers, not just managers.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-27</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“average place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – good work life balance, not bad salary, average holiday, good variety of work, can get involved with numerous customers and projects</pros>
<cons>Cons – ask to work weekends adnd out of hours with very little notice, very poor redundancy package when it happened, and didnt care about employees, didnt try to find other work or training courses</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – listen to the employees more, about ways to streamline perfromance and make working easier, and ways to improve current processes</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-05-14</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Contractor Through ACS (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Ok place to work”

</title><pros>Pros – They were proactive in finding me a position.  The recruiters were friendly and were constantly asking me about positions, trying to get me placed.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They don't fight or work for what you want from a client.  I think they just want to get you placed so they start making money.  Once hired, I heard from the recruiter once...in a year.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Aren't the contractors ACS's source of income?  Show them some respect!</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-03-30</date>
<rating>3.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Financial Analyst-Intern (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“An unmemorable experience.”

</title><pros>Pros – -People take time to get to know one another; great networking opportunities during work hours.-Various online materials available to learn about the company and various subjects matters that affect the company.-Flexible work hours.-Employees are not expected to work long hours.</pros>
<cons>Cons – -A very stagnant environment.-Opportunities for advancement are few and far between.-The overall environment is not a happy, productive one.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – -Focus on creating a positive, dynamic work environment.-Encourage employees to think outside the box to improve performance.-Spend more time developing talent at the lower levels.</advice-to-management>
<recommended></recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-04-15</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“What have they done?”

</title><pros>Pros – There were some good people here.</pros>
<cons>Cons – They got rid of most of them and the others jumped or are jumping.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Stop trying to bully your employees and treat them like adult human beings.</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2010-02-02</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type>Anonymous Employee (Former Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“Management is a BEAST!”

</title><pros>Pros – - alright pay- decent coworkers- flexible work hours- sick time- flexible with emergency issues- raises</pros>
<cons>Cons – - HORRIBLE upper management- your direct management is so frustrated because of their bosses that they just stop caring and you suddenly become a number crunching idiot without an insightful opinion.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – stop being power hungry B's and actually listen to your employee's ladies. without them your evil little empire will FALL!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

<review>
<date>2009-05-12</date>
<rating>1.0</rating>
<upvote>0</upvote>
<employee-type> Human Resources Agent  (Current Employee)</employee-type>
<title>

“It would be more satisfying to work in a bar.”

</title><pros>Pros – You'll always have a job to fall back on if you're in Barcelona</pros>
<cons>Cons – Extremely underpaid jobs, discrimination (Polish workers earn less than German workers, although based in the same office), ridiculous rules, extremely poor morale, total disrespect for the employee.</cons>
<advice-to-management>Advice to Senior Management – Sort your act out!</advice-to-management>
<recommended>No</recommended>
</review>

</reviews>